[
    {
        "title": "Mondiale di Softball 2024 in Friuli Venezia Giulia: diramato il calendario",
        "date_raw": "29 novembre 2023, 11:40",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/pressrelease/sport/2023/11/29/mondiale-di-softball-2024-in-friuli-venezia-giulia-diramato-il-calendario_a79f0713-28c5-4d13-8bfb-40ac83ade438.html",
        "subtitle": "Le otto migliori squadre al mondo impegnate a Castions di Strada dal 15 al 20 luglio. Italia nel girone di Stati Uniti, Canada e Cina,",
        "content": "Per la prima volta nella storia le medaglie iridate del softball femminile verranno assegnate in Italia. Il diamante di Le otto squadre qualificate sono state divise in due gironi da quattro. Nel L'Italia esordirà Terminati i gironi, le squadre verranno divise in altri due raggruppamenti con gli incontri che si terranno  I biglietti in vendita dal 14 dicembre attraverso i canali Vivaticket. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.452244,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "World of Softball 2024 in Friuli Venezia Giulia: calendar",
        "en_content": "For the first time in history, the iridate medals of women's softball will be awarded in Italy. The diamond of The eight qualified teams were divided into two four rounds. In Italy the group will debut, the teams will be divided into two other groupings with the meetings that will be held the tickets for sale from December 14 through the channels Vivaticket.",
        "en_subtitle": "The eight best teams in the world engaged in Castions di Strada from July 15 to 20. Italy in United States, Canada and China,",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "World of Softball 2024",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Friuli",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezia Giulia",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Castions di Strada",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "July 15 to 20",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "December 14",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Baseball e Softball ai Giochi di Los Angeles 2028",
        "date_raw": "16 ottobre 2023, 14:58",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/pressrelease/sport/2023/10/16/baseball-e-softball-ai-giochi-di-los-angeles-2028_ac685f56-3625-424c-8a94-ccba5171f2dd.html",
        "subtitle": "Il CIO a Mumbai ha confermato nel programma tutte le discipline richieste dal Comitato Organizzatore americano. Le dichiarazioni del Presidente della World Baseball Softball Confederation Riccardo Fraccari e del Presidente della Federazione Italiana Baseball Softball Andrea Marcon",
        "content": "La 141a Sessione del Comitato Internazionale Olimpico ha ratificato lunedì 16 ottobre l’ingresso di tutti e cinque gli sport proposti dal Comitato Organizzatore nel programma di Los Angeles 2028 già approvati dall’Esecutivo. Insieme a cricket, flag football, lacrosse e squash, ritornano quindi nel contesto sportivo più prestigioso al mondo anche baseball e softball. In un immediato messaggio a tutte le Federazioni affiliate, il Presidente della World Baseball Softball Confederation Il baseball torna nel programma ufficiale dei Giochi per la settima volta, con l’Italia presente in 4 (1992, 1996, 2000, 2004), il softball per la sesta, con le Azzurre qualificate in 3 occasioni (2000, 2004, 2020). “Desidero innanzitutto ringraziare e congratularmi con Riccardo Fraccari e la WBSC per questo risultato, per nulla scontato e dietro al quale si cela un lavoro enorme – ha dichiarato il Presidente della Federazione Italiana Baseball Softball ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.4808574,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Baseball and Softball at the Los Angeles Games 2028",
        "en_content": "The 141th Session of the International Olympic Committee ratified on Monday, October 16 the entry of all five sports proposed by the Organizing Committee in the program of Los Angeles 2028 already approved by the Executive. Along with cricket, flag football, lacrosse and squash, they return to the world's most prestigious sports environment also baseball and softball. In an immediate message to all affiliates, the President of the World Baseball Softball Confederation Baseball returns to the official Games program for the seventh time, with Italy in 4 (1992, 1996, 2000, 2004), the softball for the sixth, with the Blues qualified on 3 occasions (2000, 2004, 2020). “I would first like to thank and congratulate Riccardo Fraccari and WBSC for this result, for nothing discounted and behind which there is a huge job – said the President of the Italian Federation Baseball Softball",
        "en_subtitle": "The CIO in Mumbai has confirmed in the program all the disciplines required by the American Organizing Committee. Statements by the President of the World Baseball Softball Confederation Riccardo Fraccari and the President of the Italian Federation Baseball Softball Andrea Marcon",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Baseball and Softball",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Los Angeles Games",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2028",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mumbai",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the American Organizing Committee",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the World Baseball Softball Confederation Riccardo Fraccari",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Federation Baseball Softball",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrea Marcon",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the International Olympic Committee",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday, October 16",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "five",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Organizing Committee",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Los Angeles",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2028",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Executive",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the World Baseball Softball Confederation Baseball",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Games",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 511,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "seventh",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4 (1992, 1996",
                "start_char": 556,
                "end_char": 569,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2000",
                "start_char": 571,
                "end_char": 575,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2004",
                "start_char": 577,
                "end_char": 581,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "sixth",
                "start_char": 605,
                "end_char": 610,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 640,
                "end_char": 641,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2000, 2004,",
                "start_char": 653,
                "end_char": 664,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2020",
                "start_char": 665,
                "end_char": 669,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 681,
                "end_char": 686,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Riccardo Fraccari",
                "start_char": 718,
                "end_char": 735,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "WBSC",
                "start_char": 740,
                "end_char": 744,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Federation Baseball Softball",
                "start_char": 846,
                "end_char": 886,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "La Rai blinda De Martino con un contratto pluriennale",
        "date_raw": "",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/economia/economia.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/cultura/tv/2024/05/23/la-rai-blinda-de-martino-con-un-contratto-pluriennale_e2389f69-b8d4-4c4a-af25-64539ac955ff.html",
        "subtitle": "\"Sarà impegnato nelle fasce pregiate di Rai 1 e Rai 2\"",
        "content": "Messo in cascina il futuro di Sanremo, con la doppietta 2025 e 2026 affidata a Carlo Conti in veste di direttore artistico e conduttore, la Rai punta su Stefano De Martino, blindandolo con \"un accordo pluriennale\", annuncia Viale Mazzini. Il contratto - a quanto si apprende - ha la durata di quattro anni e vedrà il golden boy della tv italiana \"impegnato per la Direzione Intrattenimento Prime Time nelle fasce pregiate di Rai1 e Rai2\". In ballo c'è innanzi tutto la successione ad Affari Tuoi, il game show dell'access prime time della rete ammiraglia che Amadeus ha rinnovato e rilanciato in vetta all'Auditel: il contratto con Endemol-Banijay per il format dei pacchi è in scadenza, ma non è un mistero che - nelle intenzioni di Viale Mazzini - in pole position ci sia proprio De Martino. Secondo Dagospia, il contratto - oltre a prevedere un mega compenso - spazierebbe tra access e prime time e comprenderebbe anche l'opzione Sanremo post Conti. Dell'accordo farebbero parte anche alcune serate speciali e non è escluso che De Martino possa apparire all'Ariston già nel 2025, magari come co-conduttore di una delle serate. Intanto l'artista incassa i complimenti dell'amministratore delegato Roberto Sergio e del direttore generale Giampaolo Rossi \"per gli ottimi risultati raggiunti in questa stagione\": su Rai2 Stasera tutto è possibile - il comedy show in cui De Martino ha preso il posto di Amadeus dalla quinta edizione - chiude proprio questa sera la stagione più vista di sempre. Nato a Torre Annunziata il 3 ottobre 1989, Stefano De Martino comincia a 10 anni a muovere i primi passi nel mondo della danza, contagiato dalla passione trasmessa dal padre. Nel 2007 vince una borsa di studio al Broadway Dance Center di New York, avvicinandosi alla danza moderna e contemporanea. Nel 2009 la svolta con il debutto ad Amici dove vince un contratto con la Complexions Contemporary Ballet, partecipando a un tour che tocca Nuova Zelanda, Australia e Hawaii. Nel 2010 ritorna al programma di Maria De Filippi come ballerino. Da qui comincia la sua attività di coreografo. Nel 2015 è ancora nella squadra di Amici come supporter e nello stesso anno conduce l'appuntamento in day time della trasmissione. Nella stagione 2016-2017 è uno dei mentori di Selfie - Le cose cambiano su Canale 5, nel 2018 è l'inviato dell'Isola dei Famosi. Nel 2019 debutta in Rai con Made in Sud e conduce con Belen Rodriguez - con cui avrà un lungo e altalenante legame, da cui è nato il figlio Santiago - la Notte della Taranta. L'anno dopo è alla guida della finale di Castrocaro e sostituisce Amadeus al timone di Stasera tutto è possibile. Nel 2021 torna da Amici come giudice, confermato anche per l'edizione successiva. Tra il 2021 e il 2023 apre il suo Bar Stella su Rai2, rete per cui farà anche da voce narrante per l'ottava edizione del Collegio e per lo speciale Da Natale a Santo Stefano, in onda lo scorso 26 dicembre Riproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.500594,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "La Rai armora De Martino with a multi-year contract",
        "en_content": "Putting down the future of Sanremo, with the doublet 2025 and 2026 entrusted to Carlo Conti as artistic director and conductor, the Rai points on Stefano De Martino, arming him with \"a multi-year agreement\", announces Viale Mazzini. The contract - to what is learned - has the duration of four years and will see the golden boy of the Italian TV \" engaged for the Entertainment Direction Prime Time in the precious bands of Rai1 and Rai2\". First of all, there is the succession to Business Tuoi, the first-time access game show of the flagship network that Amadeus has renewed and relaunched at the Auditel: the contract with Endemol-Banijay for the format of the packages is expiring, but it is not a mystery that - in the intentions of Viale Mazzini - in pole position there is De Martino. According to Dagospia, the contract - in addition to predicting a mega compensation - would range between access and first time and would also include the option Sanremo post Accounts. Some special evenings would also be part of the agreement and it is not excluded that De Martino may appear at the Ariston in 2025, perhaps as a co-host of one of the evenings. Meanwhile, the artist took the compliments of CEO Roberto Sergio and general manager Giampaolo Rossi \"for the excellent results achieved this season\": on Rai2 Tonight everything is possible - the comedy show in which De Martino took the place of Amadeus from the fifth edition - it closes just this evening the most seen season ever. Born in Torre Annunziata on 3 October 1989, Stefano De Martino began 10 years to move the first steps in the world of dance, influenced by his father's passion. In 2007 he won a scholarship at the Broadway Dance Center in New York, approaching modern and contemporary dance. In 2009, he made his debut at Amici where he won a contract with Complexions Contemporary Ballet, taking part in a tour that touches New Zealand, Australia and Hawaii. In 2010 she returned to Maria De Filippi's program as a dancer. From here begins his choreographer activity. In 2015 he is still on the Amici team as a supporter and in the same year he conducts the day-time appointment of the broadcast. In the 2016-2017 season is one of the mentors of Selfie - Things change on Channel 5, in 2018 is the envoy of the Famous Island. In 2019 she debuted in Rai with Made in South and leads with Belen Rodriguez - with which she will have a long and swinging bond, from which her son Santiago - the Night of the Taranta. The next year he is leading the Castrocaro final and replaces Amadeus at tonight's helm everything is possible. In 2021 he returned from Amici as a judge, also confirmed for the next edition. Between 2021 and 2023 he opens his Bar Stella on Rai2, a network for which he will also be a storyteller for the eighth edition of the College and for the special Da Natale a Santo Stefano, aired on 26 December Reproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA",
        "en_subtitle": "\"He will be engaged in the bands of Rai 1 and Rai 2\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "La Rai armora De Martino",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "multi-year",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sanremo",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2026",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Conti",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stefano De Martino",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "multi-year",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Viale Mazzini",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "four years",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "First",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Business Tuoi",
                "start_char": 481,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 500,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Amadeus",
                "start_char": 557,
                "end_char": 564,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Endemol-Banijay",
                "start_char": 626,
                "end_char": 641,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Viale Mazzini",
                "start_char": 738,
                "end_char": 751,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "De Martino",
                "start_char": 780,
                "end_char": 790,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dagospia",
                "start_char": 805,
                "end_char": 813,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 909,
                "end_char": 914,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanremo",
                "start_char": 954,
                "end_char": 961,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "De Martino",
                "start_char": 1063,
                "end_char": 1073,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariston",
                "start_char": 1092,
                "end_char": 1099,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 1103,
                "end_char": 1107,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 1133,
                "end_char": 1136,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Sergio",
                "start_char": 1204,
                "end_char": 1218,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giampaolo Rossi",
                "start_char": 1239,
                "end_char": 1254,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "this season",
                "start_char": 1291,
                "end_char": 1302,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "De Martino",
                "start_char": 1371,
                "end_char": 1381,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amadeus",
                "start_char": 1400,
                "end_char": 1407,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifth",
                "start_char": 1417,
                "end_char": 1422,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "this evening",
                "start_char": 1448,
                "end_char": 1460,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Torre Annunziata",
                "start_char": 1496,
                "end_char": 1512,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 October 1989",
                "start_char": 1516,
                "end_char": 1530,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stefano De Martino",
                "start_char": 1532,
                "end_char": 1550,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years",
                "start_char": 1557,
                "end_char": 1565,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1578,
                "end_char": 1583,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2007",
                "start_char": 1652,
                "end_char": 1656,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Broadway Dance Center",
                "start_char": 1681,
                "end_char": 1706,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 1710,
                "end_char": 1718,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2009",
                "start_char": 1766,
                "end_char": 1770,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amici",
                "start_char": 1793,
                "end_char": 1798,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Complexions Contemporary Ballet",
                "start_char": 1828,
                "end_char": 1859,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "New Zealand",
                "start_char": 1896,
                "end_char": 1907,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 1909,
                "end_char": 1918,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hawaii",
                "start_char": 1923,
                "end_char": 1929,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2010",
                "start_char": 1934,
                "end_char": 1938,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria De Filippi's",
                "start_char": 1955,
                "end_char": 1973,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2015",
                "start_char": 2043,
                "end_char": 2047,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amici",
                "start_char": 2067,
                "end_char": 2072,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the same year",
                "start_char": 2100,
                "end_char": 2113,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "day",
                "start_char": 2130,
                "end_char": 2133,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2016-2017 season",
                "start_char": 2176,
                "end_char": 2192,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 2196,
                "end_char": 2199,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Selfie - Things",
                "start_char": 2218,
                "end_char": 2233,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Channel 5",
                "start_char": 2244,
                "end_char": 2253,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2018",
                "start_char": 2258,
                "end_char": 2262,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Famous Island",
                "start_char": 2279,
                "end_char": 2296,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "2019",
                "start_char": 2301,
                "end_char": 2305,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 2321,
                "end_char": 2324,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 2338,
                "end_char": 2343,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belen Rodriguez",
                "start_char": 2359,
                "end_char": 2374,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santiago - the Night",
                "start_char": 2447,
                "end_char": 2467,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The next year",
                "start_char": 2484,
                "end_char": 2497,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Castrocaro",
                "start_char": 2516,
                "end_char": 2526,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Amadeus",
                "start_char": 2546,
                "end_char": 2553,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 2557,
                "end_char": 2564,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 2599,
                "end_char": 2603,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amici",
                "start_char": 2621,
                "end_char": 2626,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Between 2021 and 2023",
                "start_char": 2676,
                "end_char": 2697,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bar Stella",
                "start_char": 2711,
                "end_char": 2721,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "eighth",
                "start_char": 2789,
                "end_char": 2795,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Da Natale",
                "start_char": 2839,
                "end_char": 2848,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "26",
                "start_char": 2875,
                "end_char": 2877,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA",
                "start_char": 2921,
                "end_char": 2925,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "L'Italia conquista il primo titolo europeo di Baseball Giocato da Ciechi",
        "date_raw": "08 ottobre 2023, 16:04",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/pressrelease/sport/2023/10/08/litalia-conquista-il-primo-titolo-europeo-di-baseball-giocato-da-ciechi_6ba6e8b2-7f14-4920-9ad6-82d90a22f781.html",
        "subtitle": "Il primo Europeo di Baseball Giocato da Ciechi WBSCE ha premiato l’esperienza e la tecnica degli azzurri, autori di un percorso netto nella due giorni bolognese che ha anche testimoniato la crescita delle altre selezioni partecipanti.",
        "content": "Il primo La manifestazione, assegnata dalla World Baseball Softball Confederation Europe alla FIBS e organizzata dalla Associazione Italiana Baseball per Ciechi con la collaborazione di tutto il Gruppo Fortitudo baseball/softball, ha visto in campo  La giornata decisiva si è aperta con la  Di ben altro tenore l’altra  La partita per il Il secondo turno degli isolani è stato altrettanto produttivo, con i 5 punti segnati prima del secondo out in virtù di battute precise che la difesa transalpina non è riuscita a controllare. La Gran Bretagna conquista quindi il podio con un rotondo 9-0, senza concede nulal ai francesi nemmeno nel terzo attacco.  L’ I due inning congiunti di attacco olandese, chiamati in gergo BXC primo e secondo ‘morso’, volano via in un attimo, con L’Italia inizia con due valide di Il manager Fabio Azzaro opera qualche cambio per il secondo turno e questa volta la difesa olandese, concentrata e precisa, con l’esterno destro Restituito il favore, la Nazionale Italiana inizia il terzo attacco con Ambra Trefolello, che batte bene a destra, ma è eliminata da una lunga assistenza dell’esterno sinistro olandese.  Anche a livello individuale, l’Italia ha svettato con 3 dei 4 premi, con Miglior difensore il britannico   Game 11: Francia vs Italia Game 12: Paesi Bassi vs Gran Bretagna Game 13 Bronzo: Francia vs Gran Bretagna Game 14 Oro/Argento: Paesi Bassi vs Italia  L’Italia era emersa come la squadra da battere già dalla prima giornata, chiusa con un percorso netto di 4 vittorie, tutte larghe nel punteggio e la sola Olanda capace di realizzare 1 punto contro la difesa azzurra. A tallonarla la Gran Bretagna, molto compatta in campo, con un record di 3-1, seguita dai Paesi Bassi a 2-2. Per Francia e Germania, entrambe a 3 sconfitte e 1 pareggio, il calcolo del Team Quality Balance aveva poi decretato il quarto posto per i francesi.   Game 1: Francia vs Germania    Tutte le partite, trasmesse in live streaming, sono disponibili sul      ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.5340874,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Italy wins the first European Baseball title played by Ciechi",
        "en_content": "The first event, assigned by the World Baseball Softball Confederation Europe to FIBS and organized by the Italian Association Baseball for Ciechi with the collaboration of the entire Fortitudo baseball/softball Group, saw in the field The decisive day opened with the Di ben altri teno l'altra The game for the second round of the islanders was equally productive, with the 5 points scored before the second out in virtue of precise jokes that the transalpine defense. Britain then conquered the podium with a round 9-0, without giving back to the French even in the third attack. The I two joint innings of Dutch attack, called in BXC jargon first and second ‘morso’, fly away in a moment, with Italy begins with two valid of The manager Fabio Azzaro operates some change for the second turn and this time the Dutch defense, concentrated and precise, with the right outside Returned the favor, the Italian National begins the third attack with Ambra Trefolello, which beats well on the right Also on an individual level, Italy has scored with 3 of the 4 awards, with Best Defender the British Game 11: France vs Italy Game 12: Netherlands vs Great Britain Game 13 Bronze: France vs Britain Game 14 Gold/Silver: Netherlands vs Italy Italy had emerged as the team to beat already from the first day, closed with a net course of 4 wins, all wide in the score and the only Holland able to achieve 1 point against the blue defense. To heel it Britain, very compact in the field, with a record of 3-1, followed by the Netherlands to 2-2. For France and Germany, both at 3 defeats and 1 draw, the calculation of Team Quality Balance had then declined fourth place for the French. Game 1: France vs Germany All games, broadcast live streams, are available on",
        "en_subtitle": "The first European Baseball Played by Ciechi WBSCE has rewarded the experience and technique of the blue, authors of a net course in the two days of Bologna that has also witnessed the growth of the other selections.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European Baseball",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ciechi",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ciechi WBSCE",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the two days",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bologna",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the World Baseball Softball Confederation Europe",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "FIBS",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Association Baseball for Ciechi",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fortitudo baseball/softball Group",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Di ben altri",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "l'altra",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Britain",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "9",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 518,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 549,
                "end_char": 555,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 568,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 588,
                "end_char": 591,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dutch",
                "start_char": 609,
                "end_char": 614,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 644,
                "end_char": 649,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 654,
                "end_char": 660,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 697,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 715,
                "end_char": 718,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fabio Azzaro",
                "start_char": 740,
                "end_char": 752,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 782,
                "end_char": 788,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dutch",
                "start_char": 812,
                "end_char": 817,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian National",
                "start_char": 896,
                "end_char": 916,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 928,
                "end_char": 933,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ambra Trefolello",
                "start_char": 946,
                "end_char": 962,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1023,
                "end_char": 1028,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 1045,
                "end_char": 1046,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 1054,
                "end_char": 1055,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Best Defender",
                "start_char": 1069,
                "end_char": 1082,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1110,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1114,
                "end_char": 1119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 1129,
                "end_char": 1140,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Great Britain Game",
                "start_char": 1144,
                "end_char": 1162,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "13",
                "start_char": 1163,
                "end_char": 1165,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 1174,
                "end_char": 1180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Britain",
                "start_char": 1184,
                "end_char": 1191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 1213,
                "end_char": 1224,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1228,
                "end_char": 1233,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1234,
                "end_char": 1239,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the first day",
                "start_char": 1285,
                "end_char": 1298,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 1328,
                "end_char": 1329,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Holland",
                "start_char": 1371,
                "end_char": 1378,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1",
                "start_char": 1395,
                "end_char": 1396,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Britain",
                "start_char": 1440,
                "end_char": 1447,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 1493,
                "end_char": 1494,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 1514,
                "end_char": 1525,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 1529,
                "end_char": 1530,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 1538,
                "end_char": 1544,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 1549,
                "end_char": 1556,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 1566,
                "end_char": 1567,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "1",
                "start_char": 1580,
                "end_char": 1581,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Team Quality Balance",
                "start_char": 1607,
                "end_char": 1627,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "fourth",
                "start_char": 1646,
                "end_char": 1652,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 1667,
                "end_char": 1673,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "1",
                "start_char": 1680,
                "end_char": 1681,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 1683,
                "end_char": 1689,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 1693,
                "end_char": 1700,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Giorgio Minisini nello stand della polizia",
        "date_raw": "11 maggio 2024, 18:50",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/videogallery/sport/2024/05/11/giorgio-minisini-nello-stand-della-polizia_c7a0a6f8-4190-402c-97da-17fd094fb7b5.html",
        "subtitle": "Il campione di nuoto artistico al Salone del Libro di Torino",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.5984864,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Giorgio Minisini at the police stand",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "The champion of artistic swimming at the Turin Book Show",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgio Minisini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Turin Book Show",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Djokovic, selfie e autografi con il casco",
        "date_raw": "11 maggio 2024, 19:11",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/videogallery/sport/2024/05/11/djokovic-selfie-e-autografi-con-il-casco_79e3f91a-4713-4826-9335-9edc7360ea2d.html",
        "subtitle": "Il tennista serbo ironizza dopo l'incidente della borraccia",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.6062326,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Djokovic, selfies and autographs with helmet",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "Serbian tennis player irons after the incident of the bottle",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Djokovic",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Serbian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Monika Niederstatter: \"I giovani hanno perso la leggerezza\"",
        "date_raw": "16 maggio 2024, 12:35",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/videogallery/sport/2024/05/16/monika-niederstatter-i-giovani-hanno-perso-la-leggerezza_6e83aec2-20c2-417f-a495-03335c6235d6.html",
        "subtitle": "Psicologa ed ex olimpionica, \"molta pressione sui ragazzi\"",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.6246088,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Monika Niederstatter: \"Young people have lost their lightness\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "Psychologist and former Olympic, \"many pressure on boys\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Monika Niederstatter",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Olympic",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Motta: \"Il Giro potrebbe essere chiuso, ma ci sono ancora tanti ostacoli\"",
        "date_raw": "16 maggio 2024, 14:04",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/videogallery/sport/2024/05/16/motta-il-giro-potrebbe-essere-chiuso-ma-ci-sono-ancora-tanti-ostacoli_f83e88d6-dfca-42bb-844d-7347c90c12d4.html",
        "subtitle": "L'ex ciclista: \"Pogacar e' il piu' forte, spiace che non ha avversari\"",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.6739821,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Motta: \"The Giro could be closed, but there are still so many obstacles\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "The former cyclist: \"Pogacar is the strongest, sorry he has no opponents\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Motta",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pogacar",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "First highlight of UEFA EURO 2024 - Hamburg presents...",
        "date_raw": "04 dicembre 2023, 14:30",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/pressrelease/sport/2023/12/04/first-highlight-of-uefa-euro-2024-hamburg-presents...-_ba9187da-fbd5-4af7-a720-89bc7a081bf9.html",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "   25 Containers, plus twelve reach stackers (container stackers), each weighing 70 tons, and 70 port employees and one spectacular result. A structure 12 metres high, built from containers, turns the Final Draw of UEFA EURO 2024 into an impressive experience for the whole of Europe. Using containers designed in the flags of the participating nations, the group draw was simultaneously recreated in a spectacular fashion. This led to the creation of the six eye-catching container towers, that will remain at the O’Swaldkai terminal in Hamburg until 10 December 2023.  The container installation has the backing of Hamburg Marketing GmbH with executive support from UNIKAI Lagerei- und Speditionsgesellschaft mbH and LOTUS Containers GmbH.  Contact: Host City Hamburg Media Team – Hamburg Marketing GmbH Mr. Konstantin Muffert Phone: +49 40 41 11 10 - 628 Mobil: +49 162 73 83 911 E-Mail: konstantin.muffert@marketing.hamburg.de  ",
        "ranked": 9,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.6816456,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "First highlight of UEFA EURO 2024 - Hamburg presents.. .",
        "en_content": "25 Containers, plus twelve reach stackers (container stackers), each weighing 70 tons, and 70 port employees and one spectacular result. A structure 12 metres high, built from containers, turns the Final Draw of UEFA EURO 2024 into an impressive experience for the whole of Europe. Using containers designed in the flags of the participating nations, the group draw was proclaimed in a spectacular fashion. This led to the creation of the six eye-catching container towers, that will remain at the O’Swaldkai terminal in Hamburg until 10 December 2023. The container installation has the backing of Hamburg Marketing GmbH with executive support from UNIKAI Lagerei- und Speditionsgesellschaft mbH and LOTUS Containers GmbH.",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "First",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "UEFA EURO",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamburg",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "25",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "twelve",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "70 tons",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "70",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "12 metres",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "six",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 442,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamburg",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 December 2023",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 551,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamburg Marketing GmbH",
                "start_char": 599,
                "end_char": 621,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "UNIKAI Lagerei- und Speditionsgesellschaft",
                "start_char": 650,
                "end_char": 692,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "LOTUS Containers",
                "start_char": 701,
                "end_char": 717,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Coppa del Mondo di Softball: dal 14 dicembre la Promo Natale per gli abbonamenti",
        "date_raw": "14 dicembre 2023, 10:30",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/pressrelease/sport/2023/12/14/coppa-del-mondo-di-softball-dal-14-dicembre-la-promo-natale-per-gli_af8b80c7-7b68-432b-a3c7-dc814f62e5a1.html",
        "subtitle": "Si apre su Vivaticket a tutti gli appassionati la vendita degli abbonamenti per la Fase Finale della Coppa del Mondo di luglio.",
        "content": "Si apre il 14 dicembre alle 10:00 sulla piattaforma Si comincia con un’offerta speciale, la   Dopo la fase a gironi del 2023, le otto squadre qualificate sono state divise in due gironi. Il Gruppo A comprende gli Il Gruppo B comprende il Si giocheranno quattro partite ogni giorno, con l'Australia che affronterà il Giappone nella partita inaugurale il 15 luglio alle 11:00 e l’Italia che esordirà alle 20:30 la Cina dopo la cerimonia d’apertura. Le prime due squadre di ogni gruppo avanzeranno al Super Round, mentre le ultime due squadre di ogni gruppo si sfideranno nel girone di piazzamento per determinare le posizioni dal quinto all’ottavo posto. La finale della Coppa del mondo di softball femminile e la partita per la medaglia di bronzo si svolgeranno il 20 luglio.  Il programma completo:  Nella foto di Ezio Ratti/FIBS l'esterno Laura Vigna  ",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.6882193,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "World Cup of Softball: from 14 December Promo Natale for subscriptions",
        "en_content": "Opens December 14 at 10:00 on the platform It begins with a special offer, the After the group stage of 2023, the eight qualified teams were divided into two groups. The Group A includes the Group B will play four games each day, with Australia facing Japan in the inaugural match on July 15 at 11:00 and Italy that will debut at 20:30 China after the opening ceremony. The first two teams of each group will advance to the Super Round, while the last two teams of each group will compete in the field to determine positions from fifth to eighth. The final of the World Cup of Women's Softball and the match for the bronze medal will take place on July 20. The complete program: In the photo of Ezio Ratti/FIBS the outside Laura Vigna",
        "en_subtitle": "It opens on Vivaticket to all fans the sale of subscriptions for the Final Phase of the World Cup in July.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "World Cup of Softball",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "14 December",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the World Cup",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "July",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "December 14",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "10:00",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Group A",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Group",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "July 15",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "11:00",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Super Round",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifth to eighth",
                "start_char": 530,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the World Cup of Women's Softball",
                "start_char": 560,
                "end_char": 593,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "July 20",
                "start_char": 648,
                "end_char": 655,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ezio Ratti",
                "start_char": 695,
                "end_char": 705,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "FIBS",
                "start_char": 706,
                "end_char": 710,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Laura Vigna",
                "start_char": 723,
                "end_char": 734,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Malago': \"Authority presuppone un soggetto terzo e indipendente\"",
        "date_raw": "11 maggio 2024, 16:19",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/videogallery/sport/2024/05/11/malago-authority-presuppone-un-soggetto-terzo-e-indipendente_9f6f1c4a-28fe-491e-82cb-4d6e84f62f19.html",
        "subtitle": "Il presidente del Coni: \"Scontro e' stato evitato\"",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.7361808,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Malago: \"Authority presupposes a third and independent subject\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "The President of the Council: \"Clash was avoided\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Malago",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Clash",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Torneo delle Regioni Baseball/Softball: ecco le sedi e il logo dell’edizioni Piemonte 2024",
        "date_raw": "29 dicembre 2023, 18:47",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/pressrelease/sport/2023/12/29/torneo-delle-regioni-baseballsoftball-ecco-le-sedi-e-il-logo-delledizioni-piemonte-2024_c4ce6a75-831f-4706-87d0-e26414641e95.html",
        "subtitle": "Sette le location, per nove campi complessivi, a Torino le finali.",
        "content": "La XXI edizione del Torneo delle Regioni si svolgerà in Piemonte dal 6 al 9 giugno 2024.  Ciascun Comitato Regionale FIBS seleziona le Squadre Regionali delle categorie Little League (U-12), Junior League (U-14), Senior League (U-16) di baseball e Little League, Junior League di softball. La squadra regionale vincitrice di ciascuna categoria rappresenta poi l’Italia alla manifestazione internazionale Little League Europe-Africa Regional Tournament e la formazione campione d’Europa acquisisce il diritto a partecipare alle Little League World Series negli Stati Uniti in rappresentanza del Vecchio Continente. Il Piemonte torna quindi nuovamente protagonista, dopo aver ospitato l’edizione del 2015, che aveva viste coinvolte 38 squadre (sono previste una cinquantina questa volta) provenienti da 13 Regioni d’Italia, e l’European Baseball Championship nel 2021. Il Consigliere Federale di riferimento per la regione, Il Presidente del Comitato Regionale Piemonte, La XXI edizione si svolgerà con il patrocinio di: Regione Piemonte, Comune di Torino, Comune di Avigliana, Comune di Castellamonte, Comune di Fossano, Comune di La Loggia, Comune di Pinerolo e Comune di Settimo Torinese. L’assessore allo Sport della Regione Piemonte, Lanciato il logo del TDR 2024, firmato da  ",
        "ranked": 12,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.7488692,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Tournament of the Regions Baseball/Softball: here are the offices and logo of the Piedmont editions 2024",
        "en_content": "The XXI edition of the Tournament of the Regions will take place in Piedmont from 6 to 9 June 2024. Each FIBS Regional Committee selects the Regional Teams of the categories Little League (U-12), Junior League (U-14), Senior League (U-16) baseball and Little League, Junior League softball. The winning regional team of each category then represents Italy at the international Little League Europe-Africa Regional Tournament and the European champion training acquires the right to participate in the Little League World Series in the United States representing the Old Continent. Piedmont is back again the protagonist, after hosting the 2015 edition, which had seen 38 teams involved (one fifty this time) coming from 13 regions of Italy, and the European Baseball Championship in 2021. The Federal Councillor for the Region, The President of the Regional Committee of Piedmont, The XXI edition will take place with the patronage of: Regione Piemonte, Comune di Torino, Comune di Avigliana, Comune di Castellamonte, Comune di Fossano, Comune di La Loggia, Comune di Pinerolo and Comune di Settimo Torinese. The Councillor for Sport of the Piedmont Region, Launched the logo of the TDR 2024, signed by",
        "en_subtitle": "Seven locations, for nine total fields, in Turin the finals.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Regions Baseball/Softball",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Piedmont",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Seven",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "nine",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turin",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Piedmont",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 to 9 June 2024",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "FIBS Regional Committee",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Regional Teams",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Junior League",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Senior League",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Little League",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Junior League",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the international Little League Europe-Africa Regional Tournament",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 433,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Little League World Series",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piedmont",
                "start_char": 581,
                "end_char": 589,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2015",
                "start_char": 639,
                "end_char": 643,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "38",
                "start_char": 668,
                "end_char": 670,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "13",
                "start_char": 720,
                "end_char": 722,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 734,
                "end_char": 739,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Baseball Championship",
                "start_char": 745,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 783,
                "end_char": 787,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Regional Committee of Piedmont",
                "start_char": 845,
                "end_char": 879,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Regione Piemonte",
                "start_char": 936,
                "end_char": 952,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Comune",
                "start_char": 954,
                "end_char": 960,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "di Torino",
                "start_char": 961,
                "end_char": 970,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Comune",
                "start_char": 972,
                "end_char": 978,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Avigliana",
                "start_char": 982,
                "end_char": 991,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Comune di Castellamonte",
                "start_char": 993,
                "end_char": 1016,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Comune",
                "start_char": 1018,
                "end_char": 1024,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "di Fossano",
                "start_char": 1025,
                "end_char": 1035,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Comune",
                "start_char": 1037,
                "end_char": 1043,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Loggia",
                "start_char": 1047,
                "end_char": 1056,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Comune",
                "start_char": 1058,
                "end_char": 1064,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pinerolo",
                "start_char": 1068,
                "end_char": 1076,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Comune",
                "start_char": 1081,
                "end_char": 1087,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Torinese",
                "start_char": 1099,
                "end_char": 1107,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Piedmont Region",
                "start_char": 1137,
                "end_char": 1156,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Giro d'Italia, pieno inverno sullo Stelvio: la Cima Coppi mancata",
        "date_raw": "21 maggio 2024, 14:37",
        "date": "2024-05-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/sport.shtml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/videogallery/sport/2024/05/21/giro-ditalia-pieno-inverno-sullo-stelvio-la-cima-coppi-mancata_f26e93cb-8a54-42ce-b451-1e34d34e9fc7.html",
        "subtitle": "Per rischio valanghe modificato il percorso della 16esima tappa",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 13,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716537843.757255,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-24 10:04:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-24T10.04.03",
        "en_title": "Giro d'Italia, full winter on Stelvio: La Cima Coppi missed",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "For avalanche risk modified the path of the 16th stage",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giro d'Italia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "winter",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stelvio",
