[
    {
        "title": "Halle Berry al Congresso Usa, basta vergognarsi della menopausa",
        "date_raw": "",
        "date": "2024-05-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/canale_lifestyle/notizie/people/2024/05/03/halle-berry-al-congresso-usa-basta-vergognarsi-della-menopausa_a6212017-a406-41ea-91bc-fff33f798552.html",
        "subtitle": "L'attrice si batte per chiedere fondi per la salute femminile",
        "content": "\"Sono in menopausa\". Dall'alto di un podio a Capitol Hill, la sede del Congresso Usa, Halle Berry va sul personale per sostenere una legge che stanzierebbe 275 milioni di dollari per la ricerca e l'educazione alla menopausa. Riproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714802932.1241403,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-04 08:08:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-04T08.08.52",
        "en_title": "Halle Berry at the U.S. Congress, just be ashamed of menopause",
        "en_content": "\"I'm in menopause.\" From the top of a podium in Capitol Hill, the US Congress headquarters, Halle Berry goes on staff to support a law that would stagnate $275 million for menopause research and education. Reproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA",
        "en_subtitle": "The actress fights to ask for funds for female health",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Halle Berry",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the U.S. Congress",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Capitol Hill",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Halle Berry",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "$275 million",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Senna",
        "date_raw": "01 maggio 2024, 18:44",
        "date": "2024-05-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/videogallery/short_video/2024/05/01/senna_ef30aaf2-25b1-421f-8d49-600fe76d2691.html",
        "subtitle": "30 ANNI FA IN PISTA MORIVA AYRTON SENNA",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714802932.2487009,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-04 08:08:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-04T08.08.52",
        "en_title": "Seine",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "30 YEARS AYRTON SENNA",
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "30 YEARS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "A Miami Verstappen in pole per la Sprint davanti a Leclerc",
        "date_raw": "",
        "date": "2024-05-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/f1/2024/05/03/f1-miami-a-verstappen-la-pole-per-la-sprint-2o-leclerc_5261ab89-fc4e-4b8c-9828-8c9044a43065.html",
        "subtitle": "Terzo tempo per Perez poi Ricciardo e l'altro ferrarista Sainz",
        "content": "Max Verstappen ha ottenuto la pole della gara Sprint sul circuito di Miami. Il pilota della RedBull con il tempo di 1'27\"641 ha preceduto la Ferrari di Charles Leclerc e il compagno di squadra Sergio Perez. Quarto empo per Daniel Ricciardo e quinto per la Ferrari di Carlos Sainz. La gara Sprint è in programma sabato 4 maggio alle ore 18. Riproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714802932.2705224,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-04 08:08:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-04T08.08.52",
        "en_title": "In Miami Verstappen in pole for the Sprint in front of Leclerc",
        "en_content": "Max Verstappen got the Sprint race pole on the Miami circuit. The RedBull driver with the time of 1'27\"641 preceded Charles Leclerc's Ferrari and teammate Sergio Perez. Fourth empo for Daniel Ricciardo and fifth for Ferrari by Carlos Sainz. The Sprint race is scheduled on Saturday 4 May at 6 pm. Reproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA",
        "en_subtitle": "Third time for Perez then Ricciardo and the other Ferrari player Sainz",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Miami Verstappen",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sprint",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Leclerc",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Third",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Perez",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ricciardo",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ferrari",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sainz",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Max Verstappen",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sprint",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Miami",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "RedBull",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1'27\"641",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Charles Leclerc's",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ferrari",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Perez",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fourth",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Daniel Ricciardo",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifth",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ferrari",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlos Sainz",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sprint",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday 4 May",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 pm",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Parte il Giro d'Italia 2024, tutti contro Pogacar",
        "date_raw": "",
        "date": "2024-05-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/2024/05/03/parte-il-giro-ditalia-2024-tutti-contro-pogacar_46f20992-e836-4346-9bee-d74012c74468.html",
        "subtitle": "La tappa d'esordio da Venaria a Torino, con le prime salite",
        "content": "Le colline di Torino, Superga e la Maddalena, promettono un avvio del Giro d'Italia tutt'altro che scontato, nella tappa che parte domani poco prima delle 14 dalla Reggia di Venaria. Non una cronometro, quindi, ma 140 chilometri con una salita di terza categoria e una di seconda. alla vigilia del primo arrivo da brividi, ai 1.142 metri di Oropa (Biella). Praticamente all'unanimità c'è un predestinato a vestire la maglia rosa il 26 maggio a Roma: lo sloveno Tadej Pogacar, che la corsa rosa non l'ha mai fatta e vorrebbe prendersela subito, per farne poi un'accoppiata con il Tour che invece ha già conquistato due volte. \"Sulla carta partiamo tutti battuti, ma tre settimane di corsa sono piene di variabili e incognite: non dobbiamo lasciarci sfuggire le occasioni di mettere Pogacar in difficoltà\", è l'incoraggiamento di Damiano Caruso, l'ultimo italiano a salire sul podio, secondo nel 2021 al Giro vinto dal colombiano Bernal.  A far saltare il pronostico, pur sapendo che sarà dura, ci proverà anche il 38enne britannico Geraint Thomas, secondo l'anno scorso alle spalle dello sloveno Roglic; tenteranno l'impresa 'impossibile' ancheil francese Romain Bardet, l'australiano Ben O'Connor. Gli italiani in gara sono poco più di 40, tra loro anche Domenico Pozzovivo, al suo diciottesimo (e ultimo) Giro. A 41 anni è la chioccia per i giovani della Bardiani, l'unica squadra tutta italiana, che punta su Giulio Pellizzari e Alessandro Tonelli. \"Tre settimane di corsa sono lunghe, ma sono tranquillo - si schermisce Pellizzari - alla classifica generale ci penserò tra un paio di anni, voglio vivere il Giro tappa per tappa, cercando di combinare qualcosa di buono\". Riproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714802932.3014238,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-04 08:08:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-04T08.08.52",
        "en_title": "Starting the Giro d'Italia 2024, all against Pogacar",
        "en_content": "The hills of Turin, Superga and La Maddalena, promise a start of the Giro d'Italia anything but obvious, in the stage that starts tomorrow just before 14 from the Reggia di Venaria. Not a chronometer, therefore, but 140 kilometers with a third category climb and one second. on the eve of the first arrival from thrills, at 1,142 meters of Oropa (Biella). Practically unanimously there is a predestined to dress the pink jersey on May 26 in Rome: the Slovenian Tadej Pogacar, who the pink race never made it and would like to take it immediately, to make it a pair with the Tour that instead has already conquered twice. \"On the card we start all beaten, but three weeks of race are full of variables and unknown: we must not miss the opportunity to put Pogacar in difficulty\", is the encouragement of Damiano Caruso, the last Italian to climb on the podium, second in 2021 at the Giro won by Colombian Bernal. To blow up the prediction, while knowing that it will be hard, the 38-year-old British Geraint Thomas, according to last year behind the Slovenian Roglic; will try the 'impossible' enterprise also the French Romain Bardet, the Australian Ben O'Connor. The Italians in the race are little more than 40, among them also Domenico Pozzovivo, to his eighteenth (and last) Giro. At the age of 41 he is the bare for the young people of Bardiani, the only Italian team, which focuses on Giulio Pellizzari and Alessandro Tonelli. \"Three weeks of racing are long, but I'm quiet - you screen Pellizzari - to the general ranking I will think of in a couple of years, I want to live the Giro stage by stage, trying to combine something good\". Reproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA",
        "en_subtitle": "The debut stage from Venaria to Turin, with the first climbs",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Giro d'Italia 2024",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pogacar",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venaria",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turin",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Turin",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Superga",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "La Maddalena",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Giro d'Italia",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "14",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reggia",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venaria",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "140 kilometers",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "one second",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the eve of the",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1,142 meters",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Oropa",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 26",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Slovenian Tadej Pogacar",
                "start_char": 447,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tour",
                "start_char": 574,
                "end_char": 578,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three weeks",
                "start_char": 659,
                "end_char": 670,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pogacar",
                "start_char": 754,
                "end_char": 761,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Damiano Caruso",
                "start_char": 802,
                "end_char": 816,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 827,
                "end_char": 834,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 859,
                "end_char": 865,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 869,
                "end_char": 873,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giro",
                "start_char": 881,
                "end_char": 885,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombian Bernal",
                "start_char": 893,
                "end_char": 909,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "38-year-old",
                "start_char": 978,
                "end_char": 989,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 990,
                "end_char": 997,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Geraint Thomas",
                "start_char": 998,
                "end_char": 1012,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "last year",
                "start_char": 1027,
                "end_char": 1036,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Slovenian",
                "start_char": 1044,
                "end_char": 1057,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roglic",
                "start_char": 1058,
                "end_char": 1064,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 1112,
                "end_char": 1118,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Romain Bardet",
                "start_char": 1119,
                "end_char": 1132,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australian",
                "start_char": 1138,
                "end_char": 1148,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ben O'Connor",
                "start_char": 1149,
                "end_char": 1161,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 1167,
                "end_char": 1175,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 40",
                "start_char": 1199,
                "end_char": 1211,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Domenico Pozzovivo",
                "start_char": 1229,
                "end_char": 1247,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giro",
                "start_char": 1278,
                "end_char": 1282,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the age of 41",
                "start_char": 1287,
                "end_char": 1300,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bardiani",
                "start_char": 1340,
                "end_char": 1348,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 1359,
                "end_char": 1366,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giulio Pellizzari",
                "start_char": 1390,
                "end_char": 1407,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alessandro Tonelli",
                "start_char": 1412,
                "end_char": 1430,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Three weeks",
                "start_char": 1433,
                "end_char": 1444,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "a couple of years",
                "start_char": 1547,
                "end_char": 1564,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giro",
                "start_char": 1585,
                "end_char": 1589,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Serie A: volate Champions e salvezza, il clou è Roma-Juventus",
        "date_raw": "",
        "date": "2024-05-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/2024/05/03/serie-a-volate-champions-e-salvezza-il-clou-e-roma-juventus_b1efd0b5-f6c1-4794-a8fd-373f99975325.html",
        "subtitle": "Milan qualificazione a un passo, Empoli-Frosinone sfida delicata",
        "content": "Al Anche la Assegnato lo scudetto all' L' Il campo principale resta però l'Olimpico, trincea della Roma che continua a battere record di pubblico. Ma l'innalzamento dell'asticella delle difficoltà fa faticare la pattuglia di De Rossi che, dopo la lunga e felice rincorsa, mostra un po' d'affanno, come testimoniano i due ko in casa, con Bologna e Leverkusen. Arriva una Juve che ha non pochi problemi, con Allegri che sembra destinato al congedo e una formazione alterna, che però è più fresca della Roma e si prepara psicologicamente a tentare di alzare, sempre all'Olimpico, il trofeo della Coppa Italia nella complicata finale con l'Atalanta. Allegri presenterà Chiesa e Vlahovic supportati da Rabiot. De Rossi deve ricostruire il morale della squadra dopo il ko col magnifico Leverkusen di Xabi Alonso. L'errore di Karsdorp (come quello di Sanches col Napoli) chiama in causa le carenze di organico più che le scelte del tecnico. Sarà difficile anche ragionare sulla distribuzione delle energie visto che in una settimana, dopo la Juve, ci sarà il ritorno quasi proibitivo col Leverkusen e poi la trasferta con l'Atalanta, sorta di spareggio Champions. Gasperini, in attesa di giocarsi la finale di Europa League col Marsiglia dopo il pari dell'andata, ha un giorno in più per far riposare i suoi giocatori che potrà ruotare visto che giocherà contro una Salernitana già in B. Alle spalle avanza la Lazio di Tudor, che è tornata a sperare nella Champions con la creatività di Luis Alberto, il rilancio di Kamada e Castellanos, i gol del recuperato Zaccagni. Spartiacque sarà la sfida contro un Monza che, raggiunta la salvezza, sembra avere perso smalto. Obiettivi diversi per le due milanesi: l'Inter pensa al mercato e darà spazio alla sua ricca panchina in casa di un Sassuolo all'ultima spiaggia che, se non vincerà abbrevierà il percorso verso la serie B. Il Milan vive una fase di frustrazione e di incertezza, con tanti giocatori in partenza, ma può ottenere domenica la sicurezza della Champions: dovrà fare i conti però con un Genoa sempre competitivo, con un Gudmundsson implacabile, che sembra destinato a proseguire la sua carriera proprio al Meazza, sponda Inter. Le altre quattro partite riguardano la lotta per non retrocedere. Ad essere messa peggio, al momento, è l' Riproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714802932.3137891,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-04 08:08:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-04T08.08.52",
        "en_title": "Serie A: Champions and salvation flies, the clou is Roma-Juventus",
        "en_content": "The Assigned also the shield to the L'Il campo principale remains the Olympic, trench of Rome that continues to beat record of audience. But the raising of the asticella of difficulties is hard to find the De Rossi patrol, which, after the long and happy race, shows a bit of afar, as the two kos in the house testify, with Bologna and Leverkusen. Here comes a Juve that has not a few problems, with Allegri that seems destined to leave and alternating training, but it is cooler than Rome and prepares psychologically to try to raise, always at the Olimpico, the trophy of the Italian Cup in the complicated final with the Atalanta. Allegri will present Church and Vlahovic supported by Rabiot. De Rossi must rebuild the team's morale after the ko with the magnificent Leverkusen of Xabi Alonso. Karsdorp's error (such as Sanches's and Naples) calls into question the shortages of staff rather than the choices of the technician. It will also be difficult to think about the distribution of energies as in a week, after Juve, there will be the almost prohibitive return with Leverkusen and then the transfer with the Atalanta, a sort of Champions shoot. Gasperini, waiting to play the Europa League final with Marseille after the match of the way, has one more day to get his players to rest as he will play against a Salernitana already in B. Behind it is the Lazio of Tudor, which returned to hope in the Champions with the creativity of Luis Alberto, the revival of Kamada and Castellanos, the goals of the recovered Zaccagni. Disappearance will be the challenge against a Monza that, achieved salvation, seems to have lost enamel. Different objectives for the two Milanese: Inter thinks about the market and will give space to its rich bench in the house of a Sassuolo at the last beach that, if not won will subscribe the path towards the series B. Milan lives a phase of frustration and uncertainty, with many players leaving, but can get on Sunday the safety of the Champions: he will have to deal with a Genoa always competitive, with an implacable Gudmundsson, which seems destined to continue his career at Meazza, shore Inter. The other four games concern the fight not to reverse. To be put worse, at the moment, is the reserved Play © Copyright ANSA",
        "en_subtitle": "Milan one step qualification, Empoli-Frosinone delicate challenge",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Roma-Juventus",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Empoli-Frosinone",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Assigned",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Olympic",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bologna",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Juve",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Allegri",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 407,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 485,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Olimpico",
                "start_char": 550,
                "end_char": 558,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Cup",
                "start_char": 574,
                "end_char": 589,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Atalanta",
                "start_char": 624,
                "end_char": 632,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Church",
                "start_char": 655,
                "end_char": 661,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vlahovic",
                "start_char": 666,
                "end_char": 674,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rabiot",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 694,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "De Rossi",
                "start_char": 696,
                "end_char": 704,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leverkusen",
                "start_char": 770,
                "end_char": 780,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xabi Alonso",
                "start_char": 784,
                "end_char": 795,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karsdorp",
                "start_char": 797,
                "end_char": 805,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanches",
                "start_char": 823,
                "end_char": 830,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 837,
                "end_char": 843,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "a week",
                "start_char": 1007,
                "end_char": 1013,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Juve",
                "start_char": 1021,
                "end_char": 1025,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leverkusen",
                "start_char": 1076,
                "end_char": 1086,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atalanta",
                "start_char": 1118,
                "end_char": 1126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Champions",
                "start_char": 1138,
                "end_char": 1147,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gasperini",
                "start_char": 1155,
                "end_char": 1164,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europa",
                "start_char": 1186,
                "end_char": 1192,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marseille",
                "start_char": 1211,
                "end_char": 1220,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 1253,
                "end_char": 1256,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salernitana",
                "start_char": 1319,
                "end_char": 1330,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "B.",
                "start_char": 1342,
                "end_char": 1344,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lazio",
                "start_char": 1362,
                "end_char": 1367,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tudor",
                "start_char": 1371,
                "end_char": 1376,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luis Alberto",
                "start_char": 1441,
                "end_char": 1453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kamada",
                "start_char": 1470,
                "end_char": 1476,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Castellanos",
                "start_char": 1481,
                "end_char": 1492,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zaccagni",
                "start_char": 1521,
                "end_char": 1529,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monza",
                "start_char": 1577,
                "end_char": 1582,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1665,
                "end_char": 1668,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milanese",
                "start_char": 1669,
                "end_char": 1677,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sassuolo",
                "start_char": 1765,
                "end_char": 1773,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "B. Milan",
                "start_char": 1852,
                "end_char": 1860,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 1949,
                "end_char": 1955,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 2013,
                "end_char": 2018,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gudmundsson",
                "start_char": 2058,
                "end_char": 2069,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meazza",
                "start_char": 2118,
                "end_char": 2124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Inter",
                "start_char": 2132,
                "end_char": 2137,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 2149,
                "end_char": 2153,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Serie A: Monza-Lazio, probabili formazioni LIVE",
        "date_raw": "",
        "date": "2024-05-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/sport/calcio/2024/05/03/serie-a-monza-lazio-probabili-formazioni-live_8d749ce5-19d5-49d5-8f9c-ed21e2721c92.html",
        "subtitle": "Esame Monza per Tudor: 'Serve obiettività sui traguardi'",
        "content": "\"Quella dell'andata è stata totalmente un'altra partita: ora c'è un nuovo allenatore con altri principi di gioco. Adesso c'è un bravo allenatore che fa dell'intensità e dei duelli dei punti di forza: forse è un calcio più cinico e concreto rispetto alla passata stagione. Sarà una partita complicata, ma noi non ci siamo mai snaturati\". Alla vigilia della partita di sabato alle 18 contro la Lazio, l'allenatore del Monza, Raffaele Palladino, entra nel dettaglio sul piano tattico: \"Sarri faceva un gioco con principi diversi, Tudor l'ho studiato e lo conosco bene anche come persona, ho condiviso con lui lo spogliatoio quando io ero un bambino, ai tempi di mister Lippi\". \"Lo affronto domani e mi fa piacere, è un allenatore che ha fatto bene sia a Marsiglia che a Verona e ha preso in corsa una squadra con altri principi dandogli la sua identità\", ha aggiunto Palladino. L'obiettivo è fare il massimo, ma Igor Tudor non vuole tabelle di marcia per la Champions, perché \"ci sono anche le altre squadre. Possiamo guardare solo alle nostre prestazioni\", sottolinea il tecnico prima della gara con il Monza. E proprio sulla corsa Champions si concentra il croato aprendo il dibattito su Atalanta-Fiorentina, rinviata e senza una data fissata per il recupero. \"E' una cosa non giusta, non sarebbe regolare giocare a fine campionato. Capisco che ci sono i calendari, ma bisogna migliorare nell'organizzazione delle partite\", le sue parole al riguardo. Intanto, però, c'è da pensare al Monza, così come all'ambiente che circonda la squadra sul quale Tudor, dopo 45 giorni di Lazio, comincia ad avere le idee piuttosto chiare. \"Ho parlato con un tifoso che voleva lo scudetto. Ho capito che c'è grande passione, ma vedo poca obiettività nei giudizi. Ci sono 20 squadre, bisogna capire qual è la qualità della rosa, che incide per il 70/80%. L'obiettivo deve essere fare meglio della posizione in cui dovremmo essere. L'anno scorso questa Lazio non era da secondo posto l'anno scorso eppure ci è arrivata. Il troppo amore, però, può indurre a sopravvalutare certe situazioni\", chiarisce Tudor. Che, per la gara col Monza, avrà a disposizione tutti tranne Gila, con la grande incognita rappresentata da Provedel, ristabilito dall'infortunio alla caviglia ma \"che ha svolto solo qualche allenamento con noi\", al quale molto probabilmente verrà preferito Mandas, e il solito dubbio in attacco dove potrebbe rivedersi Immobile da titolare. Chi ci sarà sicuramente è Zaccagni, un calciatore che \"dobbiamo essere bravi a capire come utilizzarlo. Bello averlo in rosa e cerchiamo di sfruttarlo al massimo\", aggiunge Tudor, pronto a studiare soluzioni per un finale di campionato che, seppur senza tabelle, potrebbe permettere alla Lazio di conquistare una qualificazione alla Champions del prossimo anno che, prima dell'arrivo del croato, non poteva neanche essere immaginata. Monza (4-2-3-1): 16 Di Gregorio; 19 Birindelli, 3 Marì, 4 Izzo, 77 Kyriakopoulos; 38 Bondo, 8 Akpa Akpro; 20 Zerbin, 28 Colpani, 21 Carboni V.; 11 Djuric. (22 Sorrentino, 66 Gori, 2 Donati, 5 Caldirola, 9 Colombo, 10 Caprari, 13 Pereira, 27 Maldini, 33 D'Ambrosio, 47 Mota Carvalho, 61 Ferraris). All.: Palladino. Squalificati: Gagliardini, Gomez. Diffidati: Djuric, Izzo. Indisponibili: Carboni A., Bettella, Machin, Ciurria, Popovic, Vignato. Lazio (3-4-2-1): 35 Mandas; 4 Patric, 13 Romagnoli, 23 Hysaj; 77 Marusic, 8 Guendouzi, 6 Kamada, 20 Zaccagni; 7 Felipe Anderson, 10 Luis Alberto; 17 Immobile. (94 Provedel, 33 Sepe, 3 Pellegrini, 15 Casale, 29 Lazzari, 65 Rovella, 32 Cataldi, 5 Vecino, 28 A.Anderson, 9 Pedro, 18 Isaksen, 19 Castellanos, 70 Saná Fernandes). All.: Tudor. Squalificati: nessuno. Diffidati: Pedro. Indisponibili: Gila. Arbitro: Pairetto di Pinerolo. Riproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714802932.3418,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AnsaHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-05-04 08:08:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-04T08.08.52",
        "en_title": "Serie A: Monza-Lazio, probable LIVE formations",
        "en_content": "\"The one on the way was totally another game: now there is a new coach with other game principles. Now there is a good coach who makes strength and duels of strengths: Perhaps it is a more cynical and concrete kick compared to the past season. It's gonna be a complicated game, but we've never broken.\" On the eve of the Saturday match at 18 against Lazio, the coach of Monza, Raffaele Palladino, enters the detail on the tactical plane: \"Sarri made a game with different principles, Tudor studied it and I know it well as as a person, I shared with him the locker room when I was a child, at the time of Mister Lippi.\" \"I face him tomorrow and I am pleased, he is a coach who has done well both in Marseille and Verona and took a team with other principles giving him his identity,\" added Palladino. The goal is to do the most, but Igor Tudor does not want marching tables for the Champions, because \"there are also the other teams. We can only look at our performance,\" says the technician before the race with Monza. And precisely on the Champions race the Croatian focuses opening the debate on Atalanta-Fiorentina, postponed and without a fixed date for recovery. \"It's not fair, it wouldn't be regular at the end of the championship. I understand that there are calendars, but you have to improve in the organization of matches,\" his words about it. Meanwhile, however, we have to think about Monza, as well as the environment surrounding the team on which Tudor, after 45 days of Lazio, begins to have quite clear ideas. \"I talked to a fan who wanted the shield. I realized that there is great passion, but I see little objectivity in judgments. There are 20 teams, you have to understand the quality of the rose, which affects 70/80%. The goal must be to do better than where we should be. Last year this Lazio was not second place last year but it arrived. Too much love, however, can induce to overestimate certain situations,\" explains Tudor. That, for the race with Monza, will have at disposal all except Gila, with the great incognita represented by Provedel, reestablished from the injury to the ankle but \"which has only carried out some training with us\", to which most likely will be preferred Mandas, and the usual doubt in attack where he could see himself Immobile from owner. Who will surely be there is Zaccagni, a footballer who \"we must be good at understanding how to use it. Nice to have it in pink and try to exploit it to the maximum,\" adds Tudor, ready to study solutions for a final championship that, although without tables, could allow Lazio to conquer a qualification to the Champions next year that, before the arrival of Croatian, could not even be imagined. Monza (4-2-3-1): 16 Of Gregory; 19 Birindelli, 3 Marì, 4 Izzo, 77 Kyriakopoulos; 38 Bondo, 8 Akpa Akpro; 20 Zerbin, 28 Colpani, 21 Carboni V.; 11 Djuric. (22 Sorrentino, 66 Gori, 2 Donati, 5 Caldirola, 9 Colombo, 10 Caprari, 13 Pereira, 27 Maldini, 33 D'Ambrosio, 47 Mota Carvalho, 61 Ferraris). All. Disqualified: Gagliardini, Gomez. Diffidati: Djuric, Izzo. Unavailable: Carboni A., Bettella, Machin, Ciurria, Popovic, Vignato. Lazio (3-4-2-1): 35 Mandas; 4 Patric, 13 Romagnoli, 23 Hysaj; 77 Marusic, 8 Guendouzi, 6 Kamada, 20 Zaccagni; 7 Felipe Anderson, 10 Luis Alberto; 17 Immobile. (94 Provedel, 33 Sepe, 3 Pellegrini, 15 Casale, 29 Lazzari, 65 Rovella, 32 Cataldi, 5 Vecino, 28 A.Anderson, 9 Pedro, 18 Isaksen, 19 Castellanos, 70 Saná Fernandes). All.: Tudor. Disqualified: no one. Diffidati: Pedro. Unavailable: Gila. Referee: Pairetto di Pinerolo. Reproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA",
        "en_subtitle": "Monza for Tudor: 'Serve goals on goals'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Monza-Lazio",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Monza",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tudor",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the past season",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the eve of the",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lazio",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monza",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raffaele Palladino",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sarri",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tudor",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lippi",
                "start_char": 612,
                "end_char": 617,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marseille",
                "start_char": 699,
                "end_char": 708,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Verona",
                "start_char": 713,
                "end_char": 719,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palladino",
                "start_char": 790,
                "end_char": 799,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Igor Tudor",
                "start_char": 833,
                "end_char": 843,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monza",
                "start_char": 1013,
                "end_char": 1018,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Croatian",
                "start_char": 1060,
                "end_char": 1068,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atalanta-Fiorentina",
                "start_char": 1099,
                "end_char": 1118,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monza",
                "start_char": 1399,
                "end_char": 1404,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tudor",
                "start_char": 1463,
                "end_char": 1468,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "45 days",
                "start_char": 1476,
                "end_char": 1483,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lazio",
                "start_char": 1487,
                "end_char": 1492,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 1663,
                "end_char": 1665,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "70/80%",
                "start_char": 1735,
                "end_char": 1741,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Last year",
                "start_char": 1798,
                "end_char": 1807,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lazio",
                "start_char": 1813,
                "end_char": 1818,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 1827,
                "end_char": 1833,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last year",
                "start_char": 1840,
                "end_char": 1849,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tudor",
                "start_char": 1947,
                "end_char": 1952,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monza",
                "start_char": 1978,
                "end_char": 1983,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gila",
                "start_char": 2018,
                "end_char": 2022,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Provedel",
                "start_char": 2064,
                "end_char": 2072,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zaccagni",
                "start_char": 2326,
                "end_char": 2334,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tudor",
                "start_char": 2470,
                "end_char": 2475,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lazio",
                "start_char": 2570,
                "end_char": 2575,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "next year",
                "start_char": 2620,
                "end_char": 2629,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Croatian",
                "start_char": 2658,
                "end_char": 2666,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monza",
                "start_char": 2696,
                "end_char": 2701,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 2703,
                "end_char": 2704,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "19",
                "start_char": 2728,
                "end_char": 2730,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Birindelli",
                "start_char": 2731,
                "end_char": 2741,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 2743,
                "end_char": 2744,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 2751,
                "end_char": 2752,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "77 Kyriakopoulos",
                "start_char": 2759,
                "end_char": 2775,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "38",
                "start_char": 2777,
                "end_char": 2779,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 2787,
                "end_char": 2788,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 2801,
                "end_char": 2803,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zerbin",
                "start_char": 2804,
                "end_char": 2810,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "28",
                "start_char": 2812,
                "end_char": 2814,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "21",
                "start_char": 2824,
                "end_char": 2826,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carboni V.",
                "start_char": 2827,
                "end_char": 2837,
