[
    {
        "title": "  Calano gli incassi dalle multe, ma Roma resta al top  ",
        "date_raw": " 02 giugno 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/economia/news/2024-06-02/comuni-codacons-classifica-citta-incassano-multe-codice-strada-26607191/",
        "subtitle": "  Fanalino di coda Napoli, che riesce a incassare poco più di 8 euro pro capite dalle infrazioni stradali, ma è a Firenze che si registrano i maggiori introiti, con quasi 19 milioni di euro all'anno  ",
        "content": " AGI - Nel 2023 i\n Ancora una volta - sottolinea il Codacons - l\n Considerato il numero di abitanti in ciascun Comune, Potenza e Firenze vantano il più alto valore pro capite delle multe, con un importo pari a oltre 123 euro a residente, 111 euro Bologna, 107 euro Milano.\n Nove città su 20 registrano, invece, un decremento dei proventi, col \n \"A fronte di tali numeri imponenti - dichiara il presidente Codacons, Carlo Rienzi - non possiamo non chiederci che fine abbia fatto l'Osservatorio sulle multe stradali introdotto dal decreto legge Pa bis del 2023 e che sarebbe dovuto entrare in funzione entro 90 giorni dalla conversione in legge del decreto (pubblicata in GU il 16 agosto 2023) con il compito di realizzare una relazione annuale 'contenente in particolare i dati relativi agli incidenti stradali e alla regolarità e trasparenza nell'utilizzo dei proventi delle sanzioni amministrative pecuniarie e nell'uso dei dispositivi elettronici di controllo della velocità, nonché di verificare 'le segnalazioni delle associazioni dei consumatori operanti nel settore e richiedere dati e informazioni alle competenti amministrazioni'. \n Nonostante la crociata avviata dal ministro Salvini contro autovelox e limiti di velocità - conclude - di tale Osservatorio, che fa capo proprio al Mit, non si è saputo più nulla\".  \n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.5934143,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "The fines fall, but Rome remains at the top",
        "en_content": "AGI - In 2023\nAgain - underlines the Codacons - l\nConsidered the number of inhabitants in each municipality, Potenza and Florence have the highest per capita value of the fines, with an amount equal to more than 123 euro per resident, 111 euro Bologna, 107 euro Milan.\nNine out of 20 cities, however, record a decrease in income, with\n\"In the face of these imposing numbers - says President Codacons, Carlo Rienzi - we can not ask ourselves what happened the Observatory on road fines introduced by the decree Pa bis of 2023 and that it would have to enter into operation within 90 days from the conversion into law of the decree (published in OJ on 16 August 2023) with the task of carrying out an annual report 'containing in particular data on road accidents and regularity and transparency'\nDespite the crusade initiated by the minister Salvini against speed cameras and speed limits - he concludes - of this Observatory, which is headed precisely to the Mit, nothing has been known\".\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Fanalino di tail Naples, which manages to cash a little more than 8 euros per capita from the traffic infractions, but it is in Florence that the largest revenues are recorded, with almost 19 million euros per year",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florence",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "almost 19 million euros",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Codacons",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Potenza",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florence",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 123 euro",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "111 euro",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bologna",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "107 euro",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 262,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nine",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Codacons",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Rienzi",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 413,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Observatory",
                "start_char": 459,
                "end_char": 470,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 524,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "90 days",
                "start_char": 579,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "OJ",
                "start_char": 644,
                "end_char": 646,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "16 August 2023",
                "start_char": 650,
                "end_char": 664,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "annual",
                "start_char": 699,
                "end_char": 705,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 841,
                "end_char": 848,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mit",
                "start_char": 959,
                "end_char": 962,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Negoziati in corso per la riapertura di Rafah. Non si arrestano i raid su Gaza  ",
        "date_raw": " 02 giugno 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/estero/news/2024-06-02/negoziati-tregua-gaza-raid-israele-26614218/",
        "subtitle": "  Nonostante gli appelli internazionali perché Israele e Hamas discutano la proposta di una tregua annunciata due giorni fa dal presidente americano Joe Biden, continuano gli attacchi di Israele sulla Striscia   ",
        "content": " AGI - Nonostante gli appelli internazionali perché Israele e Hamas discutano la proposta di una tregua annunciata due giorni fa dal presidente americano Joe Biden, continuano gli attacchi di Israele sulla Striscia di Gaza e in particolare a Rafah. Mentre la guerra sta per compiere 8 mesi, nonostante le proteste della comunità internazionale, l'esercito israeliano continua l'offensiva sulla città del sud confinante con l'Egitto. Da quello che è ormai divenuto l'epicentro della guerra, circa un milione di palestinesi sono fuggiti di fronte all'avanzata, sotto copertura aerea delle forze israeliane. \"A causa delle operazioni israeliane, migliaia di famiglie sono state costrette a fuggire. I 36 rifugi a Rafah dell'\n Nel nord della Striscia, tre palestinesi, tra cui un bambino, sono stati uccisi in un bombardamento che ha distrutto la loro casa nel quartiere Al-Darraj della città di Gaza, secondo una fonte ospedaliera. Al centro, anche i settori di Deir al-Balah, Bureij e Nousseirat sono stati presi di mira dagli attacchi israeliani. L'esercito ha confermato gli attacchi, parlando di operazioni \"mirate\" a Rafah e nel centro di Gaza.  Nelle ultime 24 ore, secondo IDF, sono stati presi di mira \"30 obiettivi terroristici, tra cui depositi di armi e cellule armate\". Sul fronte diplomatico, i Paesi mediatori Qatar, Stati Uniti ed Egitto hanno chiesto congiuntamente a \"Hamas e Israele di finalizzare l'accordo di cessate il fuoco basato sui principi stabiliti dal\n Il leader dell'opposizione Yair Lapid e il presidente Isaac Herzog appoggiano invece l'accordo se prevede la liberazione degli ostaggi e tutela gli obiettivi di sicurezza dello Stato. Hamas ha considerato in modo positivo la proposta di Biden, ma ha ribadito la richiesta di un cessate il fuoco permanente e di un ritiro totale di Israele da Gaza. Oggi al Cairo si svolge un incontro fra Egitto, Stati Uniti e Israele per discutere del valico di Rafah, cruciale per l'ingresso degli aiuti umanitari a Gaza e chiuso da quando le forze israeliane hanno preso il controllo della parte palestinese a maggio. Secondo le autorità israeliane, 764 camion egiziani che trasportavano aiuti sono entrati a Gaza questa settimana \n",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.5998335,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Negotiations in progress for the reopening of Rafah. The raids on Gaza",
        "en_content": "AGI - Despite international appeals because Israel and Hamas discuss the proposal of a truce announced two days ago by American President Joe Biden, Israel's attacks on the Gaza Strip and in particular to Rafah continue. While the war is about to take 8 months, despite the protests of the international community, the Israeli army continues the offensive on the southern city bordering Egypt. From what has now become the epicenter of the war, about a million Palestinians have fled in front of the advance, under aerial cover of the Israeli forces. \"Due to Israeli operations, thousands of families were forced to flee. The 36 refuges in Rafah\nIn the north of the Strip, three Palestinians, including a child, were killed in a bombing that destroyed their home in the Al-Darraj district of the city of Gaza, according to a hospital source. In the middle, the Deir al-Balah, Bureij and Nousseirat sectors were also targeted by Israeli attacks. The army confirmed the attacks, talking about \"mirate\" operations to Rafah and the center of Gaza. In the last 24 hours, according to IDF, 30 terrorist targets have been targeted, including weapons deposits and armed cells. On the diplomatic front, the Qatari, United States and Egypt mediators asked jointly to \"Hamas and Israel to finalize the ceasefire agreement based on the principles established by the\nThe opposition leader Yair Lapid and President Isaac Herzog support the agreement if it plans to release the hostages and protect the security objectives of the state. Hamas considered Biden's proposal positively, but reiterated the request for a ceasefire and a total withdrawal of Israel from Gaza. Today in Cairo there is a meeting between Egypt, the United States and Israel to discuss the Rafah Passage, crucial for the entry of humanitarian aid to Gaza and closed since the Israeli forces took control of the Palestinian side in May. According to the Israeli authorities, 764 Egyptian trucks carrying aid entered Gaza this week\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Despite international appeals because Israel and Hamas discuss the proposal of a truce announced two days ago by American President Joe Biden, Israel's attacks on the Strip continue",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two days ago",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 172,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two days ago",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 months",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about a million",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 460,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 542,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 566,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 579,
                "end_char": 588,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "36",
                "start_char": 626,
                "end_char": 628,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 640,
                "end_char": 645,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 666,
                "end_char": 671,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 673,
                "end_char": 678,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 679,
                "end_char": 691,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 804,
                "end_char": 808,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "al-Balah",
                "start_char": 866,
                "end_char": 874,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bureij",
                "start_char": 876,
                "end_char": 882,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nousseirat",
                "start_char": 887,
                "end_char": 897,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 928,
                "end_char": 935,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 1014,
                "end_char": 1019,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1038,
                "end_char": 1042,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last 24 hours",
                "start_char": 1047,
                "end_char": 1064,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "IDF",
                "start_char": 1079,
                "end_char": 1082,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "30",
                "start_char": 1084,
                "end_char": 1086,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Qatari",
                "start_char": 1198,
                "end_char": 1204,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 1206,
                "end_char": 1219,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 1224,
                "end_char": 1229,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1258,
                "end_char": 1263,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1268,
                "end_char": 1274,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yair Lapid",
                "start_char": 1376,
                "end_char": 1386,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isaac Herzog",
                "start_char": 1401,
                "end_char": 1413,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1522,
                "end_char": 1527,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 1539,
                "end_char": 1544,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1637,
                "end_char": 1643,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1649,
                "end_char": 1653,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 1655,
                "end_char": 1660,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cairo",
                "start_char": 1664,
                "end_char": 1669,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 1697,
                "end_char": 1702,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 1704,
                "end_char": 1721,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1726,
                "end_char": 1732,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Rafah Passage",
                "start_char": 1744,
                "end_char": 1761,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1808,
                "end_char": 1812,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1834,
                "end_char": 1841,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 1869,
                "end_char": 1880,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "May",
                "start_char": 1889,
                "end_char": 1892,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1911,
                "end_char": 1918,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "764",
                "start_char": 1932,
                "end_char": 1935,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egyptian",
                "start_char": 1936,
                "end_char": 1944,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1973,
                "end_char": 1977,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this week",
                "start_char": 1978,
                "end_char": 1987,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Calcio, nasce Kings League Italia, Totti esordisce al 'mondiale'  ",
        "date_raw": " 27 maggio 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/news/2024-05-27/calcio-kings-league-italia-totti-mondiale-26545094/",
        "subtitle": "  Il nuovo campionato di calcio a 7 mette insieme giocatori in attività, vecchie glorie e perfetti sconosciuti  ",
        "content": " AGI - \n Poche ore prima era arrivato l\n Tra i giocatori in attività che partecipano alla Kings Cip ci sono il '\n Nel febbraio 2024 è stata la volta della Americas Kings League Santander, che ha visto esportare il modello dall'altra parte dell'oceano, dimostrando così le potenzialità globali del progetto. Iniziativa poi consolidata con l'attuale Kings World Cup in Messico e l'inaugurazione di questa nuova lega. Questo è solo uno dei primi passi che porteranno nel prossimo futuro all'espansione in molti altri Paesi. La Kings League, organizzata da Kosmos e guidata da Gerard Pique', ha recentemente annunciato la chiusura di un round di finanziamento da 60 milioni di euro per accelerare l'espansione del fenomeno Kings a livello globale.  \n",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.6096494,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Football, born Kings League Italy, Totti debuts at the 'world'",
        "en_content": "AGI -\nA few hours before it arrived\nAmong the players participating in the Kings Cip there are the '\nIn February 2024 it was the turn of the Americas Kings League Santander, who saw the model export across the ocean, thus demonstrating the overall potential of the project. Then consolidated initiative with the current Kings World Cup in Mexico and the inauguration of this new league. This is just one of the first steps that will lead to expansion in many other countries in the near future. The Kings League, organized by Kosmos and led by Gerard Pique, recently announced the closure of a €60 million loan round to accelerate the expansion of the Kings phenomenon globally.\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The new football championship at 7 puts together players in activities, old glories and perfect strangers",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kings League",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Totti",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "A few hours",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Kings",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "February 2024",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "World Cup",
                "start_char": 326,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Kings League",
                "start_char": 495,
                "end_char": 511,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kosmos",
                "start_char": 526,
                "end_char": 532,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gerard Pique",
                "start_char": 544,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "€60 million",
                "start_char": 594,
                "end_char": 605,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kings",
                "start_char": 652,
                "end_char": 657,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Fiorentina beffata al 116', la Conference League all'Olympiacos  ",
        "date_raw": " 29 maggio 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/news/2024-05-29/fiorentina-beffata-olympiacos-conference-league-supplementari-26574911/",
        "subtitle": "  A distanza di quasi un anno dalla sconfitta di Praga con il West Ham, i viola cadono ancora in finale  ",
        "content": " AGI - A distanza di quasi un anno dalla beffa di Praga con il West Ham, la \n Il primo vero squillo del match è dei biancorossi che al 4' si rendono subito pericolosi con Podence, bravo ad accentrarsi sul destro ed esplodere una conclusione dal limite che impegna Terracciano nella deviazione in corner. I viola rispondono immediatamente, prima con un tiro impreciso di Belotti, poi con una \n Poco più tardi tornano a farsi vedere anche i greci di nuovo con Podence, stavolta con un colpo di testa da corner bloccato attentamente dal portiere toscano. Nella ripresa è ancora \n L'Olympiakos fa invece più fatica a fraseggiare in fase offensiva, così prova a sfruttare le situazioni da palla inattiva: proprio da una di queste, all'80', i biancorossi vanno a un passo dal vantaggio con un colpo di testa di Iborra che sfiora il palo su cross di Horta. Nel finale dei 90' regolamentari succede poco altro, così si \n Nel \n",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.6181085,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Fiorentina beffed at 116', the Conference League at Olympiacos",
        "en_content": "AGI - Nearly a year from the Prague beff with West Ham, the\nThe first real call of the match is the Biancorossi who at 4' immediately get dangerous with Podence, good at accenting on the right and explode a conclusion from the limit that commits Terracciano in the deviation in corner. The violets respond immediately, first with an imprecise shot of Belotti, then with a\nA little later, the Greeks come back to be seen again with Podence, this time with a headshot blocked by the Tuscan goalkeeper. In the shooting is still\nOlympiakos is more difficult to phrasing in the offensive phase, so try to exploit inactive ball situations: Right from one of these, to the 80', the white-reds go one step from the advantage with a head shot of Iborra that touches the pole on Horta's cross. In the final of the 90' regulation, little more happens, so you\nIn\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Nearly a year after the defeat of Prague with the West Ham, the violas still fall in the final",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Fiorentina beffed",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "116'",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Conference League",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nearly a year",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prague",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Ham",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Prague",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "beff",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "West Ham",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biancorossi",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Terracciano",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Belotti",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greeks",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuscan",
                "start_char": 481,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Olympiakos",
                "start_char": 525,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 689,
                "end_char": 692,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iborra",
                "start_char": 737,
                "end_char": 743,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Horta",
                "start_char": 769,
                "end_char": 774,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "90",
                "start_char": 804,
                "end_char": 806,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Olimpiadi: possibile doppia assegnazione Giochi 2030 e 2034  ",
        "date_raw": " 30 maggio 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/news/2024-05-30/olimpiadi-doppia-assegnazione-giochi-invernali-26579382/",
        "subtitle": "  Le Alpi francesi nel 2030 e Salt Lake City nel 2034 hanno presentato il loro dossier con le offerte alle federazioni olimpiche invernali  ",
        "content": " AGI - I Giochi olimpici invernali dopo l'edizione di Milano Cortina 2026 potrebbero essere assegnati alle \n Non è escluso che, com'era accaduto per Parigi 2024 e Los Angeles 2028, si possa avere una doppia assegnazione anche per i Giochi invernali. Nello Utah l'eredità dell'edizione del 2002 è ancora molto forte anche perché i luoghi di gara sono raggiungibili entro un'ora dal Villaggio olimpico. L'intenzione degli States è quella di organizzare l'evento nel 2034 per non essere troppo a ridotto dell'edizione di LA2028. \n",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.714565,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Olympic Games: possible double assignment Games 2030 and 2034",
        "en_content": "AGI - The Winter Olympic Games after the Milan edition Cortina 2026 could be assigned to\nIt is not excluded that, as it had happened for Paris 2024 and Los Angeles 2028, you can have a double assignment also for the Winter Games. In the Utah the legacy of the 2002 edition is still very strong because the places of competition are within an hour from the Olympic Village. The intention of the States is to organize the event in 2034 not to be too small of the LA2028 edition.\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The French Alps in 2030 and Salt Lake City in 2034 presented their dossier with offers to winter Olympic federations",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Olympic Games",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2034",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alps",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "2030",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salt Lake City",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2034",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "winter",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Olympic",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Winter Olympic Games",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cortina 2026",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Los Angeles",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2028",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Winter Games",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 228,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Utah",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2002",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "an hour",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Olympic Village",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2034",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 433,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Volley: quinta vittoria Italia in Nations League, Egonu mette a segno 20 punti  ",
        "date_raw": " 30 maggio 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/news/2024-05-30/volley-femminile-risultato-italia-repubblica-domenicana-26576888/",
        "subtitle": "  Le azzurre hanno sconfitto la Repubblica Domenicana per 3 a 0. L'Italia è al quinto posto ed è la prima Nazione di quelle non qualificate ai Giochi con 70,90 punti di vantaggio sull'Olanda  ",
        "content": " AGI - Quinta vittoria consecutiva nella Volleyball Nations League 2024, seconda nel torneo di Macao e ulteriore passo verso la qualificazione per le Olimpiadi di Parigi. L'Italia della pallavolo femminile ha sconfitto la Repubblica Domenicana per 3 a 0 (set: 25-12, 25-19, 25-21). Le ragazze del commissario tecnico Julio Velasco hanno messo nel carniere 6,68 punti validi per il ranking mondiale. Grande prestazione di Paola Egonu che al termine della partita ha messo a referto ben 20 punti, Miriam Sylla 9 e Anna Danesi 7. \n \n",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.728146,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Volley: fifth victory in Italy in Nations League, Egonu scores 20 points",
        "en_content": "AGI - Fifth consecutive victory in the Volleyball Nations League 2024, second in the Macau tournament and further step towards qualifying for the Paris Olympics. Italy of the female volleyball defeated the Dominican Republic for 3 to 0 (set: 25-12, 25-19, 25-21). The girls of the technical commissioner Julio Velasco put in the carniere 6,68 points valid for the world ranking. Great performance by Paola Egonu who at the end of the match reported 20 points, Miriam Sylla 9 and Anna Danesi 7.\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The blues defeated the Dominican Republic for 3 to 0. Italy is in fifth place and is the first Nation of those not qualified in the Games with 70,90 points of advantage on Holland",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Volley",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "fifth",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nations League",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Egonu",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Dominican Republic",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifth",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Holland",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "AGI - Fifth",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Volleyball Nations League",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Macau",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Paris Olympics",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Dominican Republic",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "25-12",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "25",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "25",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Julio Velasco",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paola Egonu",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 451,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Miriam Sylla 9",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anna Danesi",
                "start_char": 479,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Chi è Anna Kalinskaja, la nuova fidanzata di Sinner  ",
        "date_raw": " 28 maggio 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/news/2024-05-27/sinner-fidanzata-anna-kalinskaja-ex-braccini-26547265/",
        "subtitle": "  Il campione altoatesino ha ufficializzato la loro relazione. La tennista russa ha preso il posto dell'influencer Maria Braccini nel cuore del numero uno al mondo  ",
        "content": " AGI - \"La verità è che non gli piaci abbastanza\". Forse Maria Braccini, l'influencer fidanzata con Jannik Sinner per oltre quattro anni che ha appena dovuto cedere il posto alla tennista russa Anna Kalinskaja, numero 25 del ranking, con tanto di ufficializzazione odierna del quasi numero uno del mondo (\"si', io e Anna stiamo insieme\") avrebbe dovuto vedere la commedia romantica del 2009 con Scarlett Johansonn, Jennifer Aniston e Ben Affleck per capire che per lei non c'era un gran futuro. Nel suo caso: se lui non la voleva sugli spalti, se l'aveva obbligata a un patto di riservatezza vietando di postare sue foto, da solo o tanto meno in coppia, se le ha concesso un'unica uscita pubblica (allo stadio per il suo Milan) la verità è che Braccini non gli piaceva abbastanza, come nel film che demolisce tutti i contorcimenti mentali delle donne in cerca di spiegazioni logiche per i comportamenti (eloquenti) dei partner riluttanti. \n La povera Maria, sul suo Instagram da 354 mila follower è mestamente ferma alle immagini di marzo che la ritraggono a Miami, a passeggio mentre il fidanzato giocava. Niente stadio, niente spalti, niente immagini tennistiche ma un laconico \"Welcome to Miami\". Braccini, che pure si era trasferita a Monte-Carlo con Sinner, interpretava un po' il ruolo dell'amante, costretta a nascondersi, mentre la vera moglie del campione era la racchetta. \n Ci starebbe pure, per un tennista prossimo a diventare numero uno. Peccato pero' che le prospettive siamo cambiate quando nella vita di Sinner ha fatto irruzione la russa Kalinskaja, 25 anni, tre più del campione, ex di un altro tennista l'australiano Nick Kyrgios, a sua volta ex di Ajla Tomljanovic (ex di Matteo Berrettini). Mentre la povera Maria si era dovuta accontentare di passetti da tartaruga, per Anna è andato tutto molto in fretta: prima apparizione a Torino, quando Sinner si stava curando l'anca al J medical, seguita da una cenetta immortalata dai fotografi a Parigi alla Langosteria dello Cheval Blanc, vista sulla Tour Eiffel. \n Ma soprattutto, prima dell'ufficializzazione il colpo letale al cuore di Maria è arrivato oggi, quando la tennista russa è apparsa sulle tribune del Suzanne Lenglen, dove l'influencer non si era mai potuta neanche accostare. Anna non era nel box ufficiale di Sinner ma era comunque in una postazione d'onore, dietro il capitano di Davis Filippo Volandri e Paolo Lorenzi, intenta a seguire il match d'esordio di Sinner contro Eubanks nonostante la sua partita contro la francese Clare Burel fosse programmata nel pomeriggio. \n Piglio e sguardo ricordavano quelli di Mirka Vavrinec, la moglie manager di Federer, l'ex tennista che ritirata per una serie di infortuni due anni dopo aver conosciuto Roger, ha fatto la sua fortuna. Chissà.. Intanto è nata una nuova coppia: i \"Kalinskinner\" emuleranno i Tsitsidosa? (Tsitsipas e Badosa, separati a Roma, sono tornati insieme). Vedremo.  \n",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.7448165,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Who is Anna Kalinskaja, the new girlfriend of Sinner",
        "en_content": "AGI - \"The truth is he doesn't like you enough.\" Perhaps Maria Braccini, the fluencer engaged with Jannik Sinner for over four years who just had to give way to Russian tennis player Anna Kalinskaja, number 25 of the ranking, with today's almost number one officialization of the world (\"yes, Anna and I are together\") should have seen the romantic comedy of 2009 with Scarlett Johansonn, Jennifer Aniston and Ben Affleck to understand that for the future there was no great. In his case: if he did not want it on the shoulders, if he had complied with a confidentiality pact by prohibiting posting his photos, alone or so less in pairs, if he granted her a single public exit (at the stadium for his Milan) the truth is that Braccini did not like enough, as in the film that demolishes all the mental accounts of women in search of logical explanations for the behaviors (eloquents).\nThe poor Maria, on her Instagram from 354 thousand followers is meticulously firm to the March pictures depicting her in Miami, walking while her boyfriend played. No stadium, no spalti, no tennis images but a laconic \"Welcome to Miami\". Braccini, who had also moved to Monte-Carlo with Sinner, played a little the role of the lover, forced to hide, while the real wife of the champion was the racket.\nHe'd be there for a tennis player next to be number one. It is a pity that the prospects changed when the Russian Kalinskaja broke into Sinner's life, 25 years, three more than the champion, former of another tennis player, Australian Nick Kyrgios, in turn former of Ajla Tomljanovic (former of Matteo Berrettini). While the poor Maria had to settle for turtle passes, for Anna everything went very quickly: First appearance in Turin, when Sinner was taking care of his hip at J medical, followed by a dinner immortalized by photographers in Paris at the Langosteria del Cheval Blanc, seen on the Eiffel Tower.\nBut above all, before the formalization the lethal blow to the heart of Mary arrived today, when the Russian tennis player appeared on the tribune of Suzanne Lenglen, where the influencer had never even been able to approach. Anna was not in Sinner's official box, but was still in an honorary position, behind Davis captain Filippo Volandri and Paolo Lorenzi, intent on following Sinner's debut match against Eubanks despite his match against French Clare Burel was scheduled in the afternoon.\nPiglio and look remembered those of Mirka Vavrinec, Federer's wife manager, the former tennis player who retired for a series of injuries two years after he met Roger, made his fortune. Who knows? In the meantime a new couple was born: will the \"Kalinskinner\" emulate the Tsitsidosa? (Tsitsipas and Badosa, separated in Rome, are back together). We'll see.\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The South Tyrolean champion officialized their relationship. Russian tennis player took the place of the influencer Maria Braccini in the heart of number one in the world",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Anna Kalinskaja",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinner",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "South Tyrolean",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria Braccini",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Maria Braccini",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jannik Sinner",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "four years",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anna Kalinskaja",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "number 25",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "almost number one",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anna",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2009",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Scarlett Johansonn",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 387,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jennifer Aniston",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ben Affleck",
                "start_char": 410,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 701,
                "end_char": 706,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "eloquents",
                "start_char": 873,
                "end_char": 882,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria",
                "start_char": 894,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Instagram",
                "start_char": 908,
                "end_char": 917,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "354 thousand",
                "start_char": 923,
                "end_char": 935,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 974,
                "end_char": 979,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Miami",
                "start_char": 1006,
                "end_char": 1011,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "spalti",
                "start_char": 1064,
                "end_char": 1070,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Miami",
                "start_char": 1115,
                "end_char": 1120,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monte-Carlo",
                "start_char": 1155,
                "end_char": 1166,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinner",
                "start_char": 1172,
                "end_char": 1178,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "number one",
                "start_char": 1332,
                "end_char": 1342,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1393,
                "end_char": 1400,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kalinskaja",
                "start_char": 1401,
                "end_char": 1411,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinner",
                "start_char": 1423,
                "end_char": 1429,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "25 years",
                "start_char": 1438,
                "end_char": 1446,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 1448,
                "end_char": 1453,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australian",
                "start_char": 1511,
                "end_char": 1521,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nick Kyrgios",
                "start_char": 1522,
                "end_char": 1534,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ajla Tomljanovic",
                "start_char": 1554,
                "end_char": 1570,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Matteo Berrettini",
                "start_char": 1582,
                "end_char": 1599,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria",
                "start_char": 1617,
                "end_char": 1622,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anna",
                "start_char": 1660,
                "end_char": 1664,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "First",
                "start_char": 1695,
                "end_char": 1700,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Turin",
                "start_char": 1715,
                "end_char": 1720,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinner",
                "start_char": 1727,
                "end_char": 1733,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "J medical",
                "start_char": 1764,
                "end_char": 1773,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 1829,
                "end_char": 1834,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Langosteria del Cheval Blanc",
                "start_char": 1838,
                "end_char": 1870,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Eiffel Tower",
                "start_char": 1880,
                "end_char": 1896,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mary",
                "start_char": 1970,
                "end_char": 1974,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 1983,
                "end_char": 1988,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1999,
                "end_char": 2006,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Suzanne Lenglen",
                "start_char": 2048,
                "end_char": 2063,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anna",
                "start_char": 2124,
                "end_char": 2128,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinner",
                "start_char": 2140,
                "end_char": 2146,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Davis",
                "start_char": 2209,
                "end_char": 2214,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Filippo Volandri",
                "start_char": 2223,
                "end_char": 2239,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paolo Lorenzi",
                "start_char": 2244,
                "end_char": 2257,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinner",
                "start_char": 2279,
                "end_char": 2285,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eubanks",
                "start_char": 2308,
                "end_char": 2315,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 2342,
                "end_char": 2348,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Clare Burel",
                "start_char": 2349,
                "end_char": 2360,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "afternoon",
                "start_char": 2382,
                "end_char": 2391,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mirka Vavrinec",
                "start_char": 2429,
                "end_char": 2443,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Federer",
                "start_char": 2445,
                "end_char": 2452,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two years",
                "start_char": 2531,
                "end_char": 2540,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roger",
                "start_char": 2554,
                "end_char": 2559,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kalinskinner",
                "start_char": 2639,
                "end_char": 2651,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tsitsidosa",
                "start_char": 2665,
                "end_char": 2675,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tsitsipas",
                "start_char": 2678,
                "end_char": 2687,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Badosa",
                "start_char": 2692,
                "end_char": 2698,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 2713,
                "end_char": 2717,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Roland Garros, buona la prima per Arnaldi, Musetti, Fognini e Paolini. Nadal saluta Parigi  ",
        "date_raw": " 27 maggio 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/news/2024-05-27/tennis-roland-garros-nadal-saluta-pubblico-parigi-26549286/",
        "subtitle": "  \"Non sono sicuro al 100% che questa sia stata la mia ultima partita qui, ma se lo dovesse essere devo ringraziarvi\", ha detto il 37enne spagnolo sconfitto in 3 set da Zverev, fresco vincitore degli Internazionali di Roma  ",
        "content": " AGI - Non c'è soltanto Jannik Sinner a tenere alta la bandiera dei tennisti italiani al Roland Garros. Anche \n Va avanti anche \n Per quanto riguarda le atlete azzurre, buona la prima per \n La giornata sportiva di Parigi, comunque, è segnata dall'addio di \n",
        "ranked": 9,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.75297,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Roland Garros, good first for Arnaldi, Musetti, Fognini and Paolini. Nadal salutes Paris",
        "en_content": "AGI - There is not only Jannik Sinner to hold high the flag of Italian tennis players at Roland Garros. Also\nGo ahead.\nAs for the blue athletes, good the first for\nThe Paris sports day, however, is marked by the farewell\n",
        "en_subtitle": "\"I'm not 100% sure that this was my last game here, but if it were to be thanked,\" said the 37-year-old Spanish defeated in 3 sets by Zverev, fresh winner of the Rome Internationals.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Roland Garros",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Arnaldi",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Musetti",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fognini",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paolini",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nadal",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "100%",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "37-year-old",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 125,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zverev",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Rome Internationals",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Jannik Sinner",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roland Garros",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Paris sports day",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "  Cristiano Ronaldo bomber d'Arabia. CR7 è il primo capocannoniere di 4 Paesi  ",
        "date_raw": " 28 maggio 2024 ",
        "date": "2024-06-02",
        "url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/",
        "news_url": "https://www.agi.it/sport/news/2024-05-28/cristiano-ronaldo-bomber-d-arabia-cr7-capocannoniere-26555720/",
        "subtitle": "  È il primo calciatore ad aver conquistato questo titolo in quattro campionati diversi: Premier League, Liga e Serie A e Arabia Saudita  ",
        "content": " AGI - Cristiano Ronaldo ha vinto la classifica cannonieri in Arabia Saudita con le 35 reti segnate nella stagione 2023/2024, diventando il primo calciatore ad aver conquistato questo titolo in quattro campionati diversi (gli altri erano stati Premier League, Liga e Serie A). Tra l'altro il 39enne attaccante portoghese ha battuto il record di marcature nella Saudi Pro League che apparteneva al bomber marocchino Abderrazak Hamdallah con i 34 gol realizzati nel 2018/2019.  \n",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717344192.7592347,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "AgiHomePage",
        "local_time": "2024-06-02 18:03:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-02T18.03.12",
        "en_title": "Cristiano Ronaldo bomber of Arabia. CR7 is the first head of 4 countries",
        "en_content": "AGI - Cristiano Ronaldo won the guns in Saudi Arabia with 35 goals scored in the 2023/2024 season, becoming the first player to win this title in four different championships (the others had been Premier League, Liga and Serie A). Among other things, the 39-year-old Portuguese attacker beat the score record in the Saudi Pro League that belonged to the Moroccan bomber Abderrazak Hamdallah with the 34 goals made in 2018/2019.\n",
        "en_subtitle": "He is the first player to have won this title in four different championships: Premier League, Liga and Serie A and Saudi Arabia",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arabia",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "CR7",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Premier League",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Liga",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Serie A",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "35",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2023/2024 season",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Premier League",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Liga",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Serie",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "39-year-old",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Portuguese",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Saudi Pro League",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moroccan",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abderrazak Hamdallah",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "34",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
