[
    {
        "title": "Una persona è morta su un aereo diretto da Londra a Singapore colpito da una forte turbolenza in volo",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "https://www.ilpost.it/mondo/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ilpost.it/2024/05/21/singapore-londra-volo-turbolenze-morto/",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "Martedì una persona  e diverse altre sono state ferite su un aereo della compagnia Singapore Airlines che durante il volo è stato colpito da una forte turbolenza e ha perso molto rapidamente quota. L’aereo, un aereo Boeing 777, era partito da Londra ed era diretto a Singapore: a bordo c’erano 211 persone e 18 membri dell’equipaggio. Non è chiaro cosa sia successo esattamente, e ora verranno svolti accertamenti: le turbolenze sono un evento piuttosto comune, ma incidenti di questo tipo sono rari. Dopo l’incidente il volo è stato deviato a Bangkok, in Thailandia, dove ai passeggeri è stata fornita assistenza medica.",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289208.1102202,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ilPost",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "A person died on a direct plane from London to Singapore hit by a strong turbulence in flight",
        "en_content": "On Tuesday a person and several others were wounded on a plane of the Singapore Airlines company that during the flight was hit by a strong turbulence and lost very quickly quota. The plane, a Boeing 777 aircraft, had departed from London and was headed to Singapore: on board were 211 people and 18 crew members. It is not clear what exactly happened, and now there will be investigations: turbulence is a rather common event, but such accidents are rare. After the accident the flight was deviated in Bangkok, Thailand, where the passengers were provided with medical assistance.",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore Airlines",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boeing",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "777",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "211",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bangkok",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thailand",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "L’uomo accusato di aver sparato al primo ministro slovacco Robert Fico potrebbe non aver agito da solo, dice il ministro dell’Interno ",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.ilpost.it/mondo/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ilpost.it/2024/05/20/uomo-accusato-attentato-robert-fico/",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "Domenica il ministro dell’Interno slovacco Matus Sutaj Estok  che l’uomo accusato per , compiuto mercoledì scorso, potrebbe non aver agito da solo, contrariamente a quanto ritenuto finora. Fico è stato colpito con diversi colpi di arma da fuoco dopo un evento politico ad Handlová, 180 chilometri a nord-est della capitale Bratislava: è ricoverato in condizioni gravi, ma non è in pericolo di vita. Dopo l’attentato le autorità avevano detto che l’attacco sembrava avere motivazioni politiche, ma che il principale sospettato, secondo i media locali un’ex guardia di sicurezza di 71 anni, non sembrava avere legami con organizzazioni politiche di qualche tipo.Domenica Estok ha detto che le prime indagini sembrano suggerire il contrario. In particolare il fatto che due ore dopo l’attentato sono state cancellate le comunicazioni dell’uomo effettuate via internet, sia su Facebook che altrove: secondo quanto riferito da Estok, a cancellare la cronologia non sarebbe stato né il sospettato stesso né sua moglie. Le indagini comunque sono ancora in corso, e puntano ad accertare proprio l’eventuale esistenza di legami tra l’uomo e altre persone relativamente all’attentato.Secondo le informazioni attualmente disponibili, l’uomo che ha sparato era molto contrario alla politica del governo filorusso di Fico sulla guerra in Ucraina e si era radicalizzato soprattutto dopo la vittoria di  alle elezioni presidenziali del mese scorso. Come Fico, anche Pellegrini ha posizioni filorusse: benché il suo ruolo di presidente sia cerimoniale, la sua elezione ha un valore simbolico perché comporta, di fatto, un ulteriore spostamento della Slovacchia su posizioni sempre più ostili nei confronti dell’Unione Europea e vicine alla Russia.",
        "ranked": 13,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289208.3828483,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ilPost",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "The man accused of shooting the Slovak Prime Minister Robert Fico may not have acted alone, says Interior Minister",
        "en_content": "On Sunday, the Slovenian Interior Minister Matus Sutaj Estok, who the man accused for last Wednesday, may not have acted alone, contrary to what he considered so far. Fico was hit with several gunshots after a political event in Handlová, 180 kilometers north-east of the capital Bratislava: He is admitted in severe conditions, but he is not in danger of life. After the attack, the authorities had said that the attack seemed to have political reasons, but that the main suspect, according to local media, a former security guard of 71 years, did not seem to have links with political organizations of some kind. Sunday Estok said that the first investigations seem to suggest otherwise. In particular, the fact that two hours after the attack were cancelled the communications of the man made via the internet, both on Facebook and elsewhere: According to Estok, erasing history would not have been either the suspect himself or his wife. However, the investigations are still underway, and they aim to ensure the existence of links between man and other persons regarding the attack. According to the information currently available, the man who shot was very opposed to the politics of the Fico Philo government on the war in Ukraine and had radicalized especially after the victory in the presidential elections last month. Like Fico, Pellegrini also has protruded positions: Although its role as president is ceremonial, its election has a symbolic value because it implies, in fact, a further shift of Slovakia on increasingly hostile positions towards the European Union and close to Russia.",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Slovak",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Robert Fico",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovenian",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Matus Sutaj Estok",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "last Wednesday",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Handlová",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "180 kilometers",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bratislava",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "71 years",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday Estok",
                "start_char": 615,
                "end_char": 627,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 642,
                "end_char": 647,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two hours",
                "start_char": 719,
                "end_char": 728,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Facebook",
                "start_char": 822,
                "end_char": 830,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Estok",
                "start_char": 859,
                "end_char": 864,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico Philo",
                "start_char": 1195,
                "end_char": 1205,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 1231,
                "end_char": 1238,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last month",
                "start_char": 1318,
                "end_char": 1328,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 1335,
                "end_char": 1339,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pellegrini",
                "start_char": 1341,
                "end_char": 1351,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovakia",
                "start_char": 1510,
                "end_char": 1518,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 1561,
                "end_char": 1579,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1593,
                "end_char": 1599,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Le più grosse divisioni nel governo israeliano dall’inizio della guerra",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.ilpost.it/mondo/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ilpost.it/2024/05/20/gantz-gallant-critiche-netanyahu/",
        "subtitle": "I due più importanti membri del gabinetto di guerra hanno criticato il primo ministro Benjamin Netanyahu per la sua mancanza di strategia: uno di loro, Benny Gantz, gli ha dato anche un ultimatum",
        "content": "Negli ultimi giorni in Israele i due più importanti esponenti del governo di unità nazionale di Benjamin Netanyahu – il membro del gabinetto di guerra e capo dell’opposizione Benny Gantz e il ministro della Difesa Yoav Gallant – hanno criticato duramente il primo ministro sul modo in cui sta conducendo la guerra nella Striscia di Gaza, accusandolo nemmeno tanto velatamente di mettere i propri interessi politici personali davanti all’interesse nazionale di Israele.Le divisioni all’interno del governo di Netanyahu , ma quelle di questi giorni sono le più profonde dall’inizio della guerra, e potrebbero portare alla fine del governo di unità nazionale e allo scioglimento del gabinetto di guerra, l’organo che finora ha preso le decisioni strategiche sulle operazioni contro Hamas. Non è chiaro però fino a che punto potrebbero mettere in difficoltà politica Netanyahu, che continua ad avere una maggioranza di estrema destra che lo sostiene nel parlamento israeliano.La più notevole delle critiche viene da Benny Gantz, ex capo di stato maggiore e leader dell’opposizione, che era  subito dopo : sabato, con un messaggio televisivo, Gantz ha accusato Netanyahu di bloccare tutti i tentativi di sviluppare un piano per il futuro politico della Striscia di Gaza, e gli ha dato un ultimatum: se entro l’8 giugno il primo ministro non avrà presentato un piano per il futuro della Striscia, Gantz uscirà dal governo di unità nazionale. «Se scegli di seguire la strada dei fanatici e gettare tutta la nazione nell’abisso, saremo costretti a lasciare il governo», ha detto.Prima di Gantz il ministro della Difesa Yoav Gallant, anche lui ex capo di stato maggiore ma membro dello stesso partito di Netanyahu, il Likud, aveva fatto accuse molto simili contro Netanyahu, sostenendo che il primo ministro non ha un piano per il futuro della Striscia di Gaza e per la gestione di quello che succederà dopo la guerra, e che questo sta portando Israele «su una strada pericolosa».Gallant ha fatto capire che Netanyahu sta volontariamente bloccando ogni piano post bellico («da ottobre ho sollevato più volte la questione nel gabinetto di guerra, e non ho ricevuto risposta») e ha chiesto a Netanyahu di impegnarsi affinché Israele non occupi la Striscia di Gaza anche dopo la guerra: «Chiedo al primo ministro Benjamin Netanyahu di prendere una decisione e dichiarare che Israele non stabilirà un controllo civile sulla Striscia di Gaza e che Israele non stabilirà un controllo militare sulla Striscia di Gaza».Queste critiche di Gantz e Gallant erano a loro volta state anticipate da alcune dichiarazioni anonime di importanti ufficiali dell’esercito israeliano, che nei giorni precedenti avevano  grosse perplessità su Netanyahu, che secondo i militari sta proseguendo la guerra senza una vera strategia e sta «sperperando» i risultati ottenuti finora.In pochi giorni dunque i comandi dell’esercito (in forma anonima) e i due più importanti esponenti del governo di Netanyahu (entrambi ex generali, ed entrambi membri del consiglio di guerra) hanno criticato duramente il primo ministro, e in particolare hanno criticato l’assenza di una strategia da parte sua su cosa fare una volta che la guerra a Gaza sarà finita.Benjamin Netanyahu, Yoav Gallant e Benny Gantz durante una conferenza stampa il 28 ottobre 2023 (Abir Sultan/Pool Photo via AP, File)Questa è da mesi la principale ragione di scontro tra Netanyahu e i suoi avversari, interni ed esterni. Secondo Gantz e Gallant, non avere un piano su cosa succederà dopo la guerra è rischioso e potenzialmente dannoso, perché potrebbe significare un inutile prolungamento del conflitto e perché concentrarsi esclusivamente sulle operazioni militari senza nessuna soluzione politica provocherà ulteriore instabilità in futuro. Netanyahu sostiene invece che è inutile preoccuparsi di cosa succederà alla Striscia finché Hamas continuerà a esistere, e che bisogna concentrarsi esclusivamente sulla distruzione del gruppo e sulla «vittoria totale».Secondo molti analisti, la posizione di Netanyahu ha ragioni politiche, e non strategiche. Il primo ministro in questo momento si trova tra due posizioni opposte. Da un lato quella dei partiti di estremisti di destra e fondamentalisti religiosi che sostengono il suo governo, e da cui Netanyahu dipende per la sua sopravvivenza politica: i leader di questi partiti sostengono da tempo che Israele dovrebbe  e consentire la costruzione di nuove colonie ebraiche.Dall’altro lato ci sono i membri del governo di unità nazionale come Gantz e gli alleati internazionali, come gli Stati Uniti, che ritengono un impegno prolungato a Gaza estremamente pericoloso per Israele, e chiedono una soluzione politica che consenta ai palestinesi di governare nel loro territorio. Negli scorsi giorni il consigliere per la Sicurezza nazionale degli Stati Uniti Jake Sullivan (che di fatto è uno dei principali consiglieri per le questioni internazionali del presidente Joe Biden) ha visitato Israele e incontrato Netanyahu, e ha  proprio di «collegare le operazioni militari [di Israele] a una strategia politica».Se questa strategia non c’è (o è ), è perché – secondo i suoi critici – l’interesse principale di Netanyahu è di garantire la propria sopravvivenza politica, e quindi di non inimicarsi gli estremisti che lo sostengono al governo, e al tempo stesso garantirsi gli aiuti e il sostegno dell’opposizione e degli alleati internazionali.Secondo i sondaggi, dopo il 7 ottobre Netanyahu è diventato molto impopolare tra gli israeliani, e in caso di elezioni sarebbe duramente sconfitto proprio da Benny Gantz. Dovrebbe inoltre affrontare numerosi processi per corruzione e altri reati, tutti intentati prima della guerra. I processi erano stati sospesi dopo l’attacco del 7 ottobre: sono ripresi nei mesi successivi ma stanno comunque .A ogni modo, Netanyahu continua a trovarsi in una posizione di forza, e l’ultimatum di Gantz . Gantz ha detto nel suo messaggio che è arrivato «il momento della verità», ma anche se lui abbandonasse il governo di unità nazionale, Netanyahu manterrebbe la maggioranza in parlamento grazie ai suoi alleati di estrema destra, e potrebbe continuare a governare, sebbene con una maggioranza ristretta di 64 deputati su 120.",
        "ranked": 16,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289208.3869321,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ilPost",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "The largest divisions in the Israeli government since the war began",
        "en_content": "In recent days in Israel, the two most important members of Benjamin Netanyahu’s national unity government – the member of the war cabinet and head of opposition Benny Gantz and Defense Minister Yoav Gallant – have harshly criticized the Prime Minister about how he is leading the war in the Gaza Strip, accusing him even so veiledly to put his personal interests in front of Israel’s national interest. The divisions within the Netanyahu government, but those of these days are the deepest since the beginning of the war, and could lead to the end of the government of national unity and to the dissolution of the cabinet of war, the organ that so far has made strategic decisions on operations against Hamas. However, it is not clear how far Netanyahu could be put into political trouble, which continues to have a far-right majority supporting it in the Israeli parliament. The most notable of the criticism comes from Benny Gantz, former head of state and opposition leader, who was immediately after: Saturday, with a television message, Gantz accused Netanyahu of blocking all attempts to develop a plan for the political future of the Gaza Strip, and gave him a ultimatum: if by June 8 the Prime Minister will not present a plan for the future of the Strip, Gantz will exit from the national government. “If you choose to follow the path of fanatics and throw the whole nation into the abyss, we will be forced to leave the government,” he said. Before Gantz, Defense Minister Yoav Gallant, former head of state but a member of the same party of Netanyahu, Likud, had made very similar accusations against Netanyahu, claiming that the prime minister has no plan for the future of the Gaza Strip and for the management of what will happen after the war, and that this is bringing Israel \"on a dangerous road\". Gallant has made it clear that Netanyahu is voluntarily blocking every post-war plan («since October I have raised the matter several times in the war cabinet, and I have not received an answer) and asked Netanyahu to commit Israel not to occupy the Gaza Strip even after the war: \"I ask Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to make a decision and declare that Israel will not establish civil control over the Gaza Strip and that Israel will not establish military control over the Gaza Strip.\" These criticisms of Gantz and Gallant were in turn anticipated by some anonymous statements of important Israeli army officers, who in previous days had great perplexity on Netanyahu, who according to the military is continuing the war without a real strategy and is “dispersing” the results achieved so far. In a few days, then, the army commands (in anonymous form) and the two most important members of the Netanyahu government (both former generals, and both members of the war council) have severely criticized the Prime Minister, and in particular criticized the absence of a strategy on his part on what to do once the war in Gaza is over. Benjamin Netanyahu, Yoav Gallant and Benny Gantz during a press conference on October 28, 2023 (Abir Sultan/Pool Photo via AP, File)This is for months the main reason for the confrontation between Netanyahu and its internal and external opponents. According to Gantz and Gallant, not having a plan on what will happen after the war is risky and potentially harmful, because it could mean a useless extension of the conflict and why focus exclusively on military operations without any political solution will cause further instability in the future. Netanyahu argues instead that it is useless to worry about what will happen to the Strip until Hamas will continue to exist, and that it is necessary to focus exclusively on the destruction of the group and on the \"total history\". According to many analysts, Netanyahu's position has political, non-strategic reasons. The Prime Minister is now among two opposite positions. On the one hand, the parties of right-wing extremists and religious fundamentalists who support his government, and from which Netanyahu depends on his political survival: the leaders of these parties long argued that Israel should and allow the construction of new Jewish colonies. On the other hand there are members of the government of national unity such as Gantz and international allies, such as the United States, who believe a prolonged commitment to Gaza extremely dangerous to Israel, and ask for a political solution that allows the Palestinians to rule in their territory. In recent days, U.S. National Security Counselor Jake Sullivan (who is actually one of President Joe Biden's leading international affairs advisors) visited Israel and met Netanyahu, and has \"connected Israeli military operations to a political strategy\". If this strategy is not (or is ), it is because – according to its critics – Netanyahu’s main interest is to guarantee its political survival, and therefore not to inspire the extremists who support it to the government, and at the same time to guarantee the aid and support of the opposition and international allies. According to the polls, after October 7 Netanyahu became very unpopular among the Israelis, and in case of elections it would be severely defeated by Benny Gantz. It should also face numerous processes for corruption and other crimes, all intent before the war. The trials were suspended after the October 7 attack: They are resumed in the following months, but they are still . Anyway, Netanyahu continues to be in a strong position, and Gantz's ultimatum . Gantz said in his message that he arrived \"the moment of truth\", but even if he abandoned the government of national unity, Netanyahu would maintain the majority in parliament thanks to his far-right allies, and could continue to rule, although with a narrow majority of 120.",
        "en_subtitle": "The two most important members of the war cabinet criticized Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu for his lack of strategy: One of them, Benny Gantz, also gave him an ultimatum",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benny Gantz",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "recent days",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benny Gantz",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yoav Gallant",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "these days",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 704,
                "end_char": 709,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 744,
                "end_char": 753,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 857,
                "end_char": 864,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benny Gantz",
                "start_char": 922,
                "end_char": 933,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 1006,
                "end_char": 1014,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 1043,
                "end_char": 1048,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 1057,
                "end_char": 1066,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 1138,
                "end_char": 1152,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "June 8",
                "start_char": 1186,
                "end_char": 1192,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 1258,
                "end_char": 1263,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 1265,
                "end_char": 1270,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 1460,
                "end_char": 1465,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 1467,
                "end_char": 1474,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yoav Gallant",
                "start_char": 1484,
                "end_char": 1496,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 1553,
                "end_char": 1562,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Likud",
                "start_char": 1564,
                "end_char": 1569,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 1613,
                "end_char": 1622,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 1687,
                "end_char": 1701,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1786,
                "end_char": 1792,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 1816,
                "end_char": 1823,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 1847,
                "end_char": 1856,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "October",
                "start_char": 1909,
                "end_char": 1916,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 2021,
                "end_char": 2030,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2041,
                "end_char": 2047,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 2062,
                "end_char": 2076,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 2119,
                "end_char": 2137,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2174,
                "end_char": 2180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 2219,
                "end_char": 2233,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2243,
                "end_char": 2249,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 2291,
                "end_char": 2305,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 2328,
                "end_char": 2333,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 2338,
                "end_char": 2345,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 2413,
                "end_char": 2420,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "previous days",
                "start_char": 2443,
                "end_char": 2456,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 2481,
                "end_char": 2490,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days",
                "start_char": 2620,
                "end_char": 2630,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 2684,
                "end_char": 2687,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 2718,
                "end_char": 2727,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the war council",
                "start_char": 2782,
                "end_char": 2797,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 2941,
                "end_char": 2945,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 2955,
                "end_char": 2973,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yoav Gallant",
                "start_char": 2975,
                "end_char": 2987,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benny Gantz",
                "start_char": 2992,
                "end_char": 3003,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 28, 2023",
                "start_char": 3033,
                "end_char": 3049,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abir Sultan/Pool Photo",
                "start_char": 3051,
                "end_char": 3073,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 3078,
                "end_char": 3080,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "months",
                "start_char": 3099,
                "end_char": 3105,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 3152,
                "end_char": 3161,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 3216,
                "end_char": 3221,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 3226,
                "end_char": 3233,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 3505,
                "end_char": 3514,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 3588,
                "end_char": 3593,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 3600,
                "end_char": 3605,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 3764,
                "end_char": 3773,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 3855,
                "end_char": 3858,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 4006,
                "end_char": 4015,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 4097,
                "end_char": 4103,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 4145,
                "end_char": 4151,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 4242,
                "end_char": 4247,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 4282,
                "end_char": 4299,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 4339,
                "end_char": 4343,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 4367,
                "end_char": 4373,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 4424,
                "end_char": 4436,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent days",
                "start_char": 4468,
                "end_char": 4479,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S. National Security",
                "start_char": 4481,
                "end_char": 4503,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jake Sullivan",
                "start_char": 4514,
                "end_char": 4527,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 4562,
                "end_char": 4571,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 4622,
                "end_char": 4628,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 4637,
                "end_char": 4646,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 4667,
                "end_char": 4674,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 4798,
                "end_char": 4807,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 7",
                "start_char": 5070,
                "end_char": 5079,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 5080,
                "end_char": 5089,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israelis",
                "start_char": 5122,
                "end_char": 5130,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benny Gantz",
                "start_char": 5190,
                "end_char": 5201,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 7",
                "start_char": 5338,
                "end_char": 5347,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the following months",
                "start_char": 5376,
                "end_char": 5396,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 5427,
                "end_char": 5436,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 5479,
                "end_char": 5484,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gantz",
                "start_char": 5499,
                "end_char": 5504,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 5623,
                "end_char": 5632,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "120",
                "start_char": 5770,
                "end_char": 5773,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il “portale” video fra New York e Dublino è stato riattivato, dopo essere stato spento perché usato in modo inappropriato",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.ilpost.it/mondo/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ilpost.it/2024/05/20/portale-dublino-new-york-riattivato/",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "Il “portale” video che collega Dublino, capitale dell’Irlanda, con New York, negli Stati Uniti, è stato riaperto, con qualche precauzione, dopo essere  perché usato . Il portale è una specie di oblò con uno schermo di 2,4 metri di diametro, con una telecamera che trasmette le immagini 24 ore su 24 da un punto all’altro: nel periodo in cui era stato attivo (meno di una settimana), alcune persone lo avevano usato tra le altre cose per mostrare foto delle  in fiamme e, nel caso di una donna poi portata via dalla polizia, strofinando il proprio corpo sul portale.Ora il “portale” sarà attivo solo per dieci ore al giorno, dalle 11 alle 21 a Dublino, corrispondenti alle 6 e alle 16 a New York. Inoltre ora il portale rileverà se qualcuno si avvicina troppo all’installazione artistica, salendo sulla pedana su cui è montata o avvicinando un telefono. In situazioni del genere il video sarà sfocato per le persone in entrambe le città.Nel periodo in cui il portale era stato attivo c’erano stati casi in cui le immagini inappropriate erano state mostrate anche senza avvicinarsi molto al portale, cosa che le nuove misure dovrebbero impedire. Erano circolati per esempio i video di un uomo che da Dublino aveva mostrato , e di una donna newyorkese che aveva mostrato le proprie tette, entrambi a qualche metro di distanza: non è chiaro come le autorità intendano evitare casi simili. La riduzione dell’orario di attività dovrebbe comunque diminuire la presenza di persone ubriache dopo aver passato la serata in uno dei molti pub che ci sono nel quartiere del centro di Dublino dove si trova l’installazione.Il portale video fra Dublino e New York rimarrà  e nei prossimi mesi dovrebbe trasmettere anche eventi culturali e connettersi ad altre installazioni simili nel resto del mondo: per ora ce n’è un altro che collega la capitale lituana Vilnius con Lublino, in Polonia.",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289208.4604,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ilPost",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "The “portal” video between New York and Dublin was reactivated, after being turned off because used inappropriately",
        "en_content": "The “portal” video that connects Dublin, capital of Ireland, with New York, in the United States, was reopened, with some precaution, after being used. The portal is a kind of porthole with a screen of 2.4 meters in diameter, with a camera that transmits images 24 hours a day from one point to another: in the period in which it had been active (less than a week), some people had used it among other things to show photos of the burning and, in the case of a woman then taken away from the police, rubbing her body on the portal. Now the “door” will be active only for ten hours a day, from 11 to 21 in Dublin, corresponding to 6 and 16 in New York. Also now the portal will detect if someone approaches too much artistic installation, climbing on the platform on which it is mounted or approaching a phone. In such situations the video will be blurred for people in both cities. In the period when the portal had been active there were cases where inappropriate images had been shown even without much approach to the portal, which the new measures should prevent. For example, the videos of a man from Dublin had shown , and a New York woman who had shown her tits, both a few meters away: It is not clear how authorities intend to avoid such cases. The reduction of activity time should however decrease the presence of drunk people after spending the evening in one of the many pubs that are in the district of the center of Dublin where the installation is located. The video portal between Dublin and New York will remain and in the coming months should also broadcast cultural events and connect to other similar installations in the rest of the world: for now there is another linking the Lithuanian capital Vilnius with Lublin, Poland.",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2.4 meters",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 hours",
                "start_char": 262,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "less than a week",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "ten hours",
                "start_char": 571,
                "end_char": 580,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "11",
                "start_char": 593,
                "end_char": 595,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 605,
                "end_char": 611,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "6",
                "start_char": 630,
                "end_char": 631,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "16",
                "start_char": 636,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 642,
                "end_char": 650,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 1106,
                "end_char": 1112,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 1131,
                "end_char": 1139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few meters",
                "start_char": 1175,
                "end_char": 1187,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 1368,
                "end_char": 1371,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 1431,
                "end_char": 1437,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 1498,
                "end_char": 1504,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 1509,
                "end_char": 1517,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming months",
                "start_char": 1537,
                "end_char": 1554,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuanian",
                "start_char": 1699,
                "end_char": 1709,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vilnius",
                "start_char": 1718,
                "end_char": 1725,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lublin",
                "start_char": 1731,
                "end_char": 1737,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 1739,
                "end_char": 1745,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "In Cina due persone sono state uccise e 10 ferite in un attacco con coltello in una scuola elementare",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.ilpost.it/mondo/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ilpost.it/2024/05/20/cina-attacco-coltello-scuola-elementare/",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "Diverse persone  lunedì in una scuola elementare in Cina, nella città di Guixi (circa 600 chilometri a sud di Shanghai): due persone sono state uccise e 10 ferite. La polizia ha fermato una donna di 45 anni, sospettata di aver compiuto l’attacco con un coltello da cucina. Le motivazioni dell’attacco e l’età delle persone colpite non sono ancora state rese note.",
        "ranked": 12,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289208.464656,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ilPost",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "In China two people were killed and 10 wounds in a knife attack in an elementary school",
        "en_content": "Several people Monday in a primary school in China, in the city of Guixi (about 600 kilometers south of Shanghai): two people were killed and 10 wounds. The police stopped a 45-year-old woman, suspected of attacking a kitchen knife. The reasons for the attack and age of the affected persons have not yet been made known.",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guixi",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 600 kilometers",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shanghai",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "45-year-old",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il presidente dell’Iran Ebrahim Raisi è morto",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.ilpost.it/mondo/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ilpost.it/2024/05/20/ebrahim-raisi-elicottero-caduto/",
        "subtitle": "L'elicottero su cui viaggiava era caduto domenica in una zona montuosa nel nord-ovest del paese: a bordo c'era anche il ministro degli Esteri, Hossein Amir-Abdollahian",
        "content": "Il presidente dell’Iran, , è morto in un incidente in  avvenuto domenica vicino alla città di Jolfa, nella provincia iraniana dell’Azerbaigian Orientale, nel nord-ovest del paese, in una zona montuosa e boschiva difficile da raggiungere. I rottami dell’elicottero su cui viaggiava sono stati  dopo molte ore di ricerche. Oltre a Raisi, sull’elicottero c’erano anche il ministro degli Esteri iraniano, Hossein Amir-Abdollahian, il governatore della provincia iraniana dell’Azerbaigian Orientale, Malek Rahmati, e l’ayatollah Mohammad Ali Ale-Hashem, rappresentante della Guida suprema iraniana in Azerbaigian Orientale (la Guida suprema è Ali Khamenei, la massima autorità politica e religiosa dell’Iran).Ebrahim Raisi aveva 63 anni ed era presidente dell’Iran dal 2021. Era espressione della componente ultraconservatrice della politica iraniana ed era considerato molto vicino a Khamenei, di cui era anche accreditato come potenziale successore. Contro il regime, tra il 2022 e il 2023, in Iran erano andate avanti per mesi estesissime proteste che nel giro di poco tempo si erano trasformate in una rivolta, la più estesa manifestazione di dissenso dalla rivoluzione del 1979, che trasformò l’Iran in una Repubblica Islamica. Il regime aveva represso le proteste con violenza,  a morte diverse persone, con .In molte parti dell’Iran l’incidente in cui è morto Raisi è stato  già prima della notizia della sua morte. Sui social network sono circolate anche  di fuochi d’artificio e festeggiamenti per le strade di varie città: molti li hanno attribuiti all’incidente in cui è morto Raisi, ma in Iran in questi giorni  per l’anniversario della nascita dell’imam Ali ibn Musa al-Reza, una specie di santo nella religione sciita. I media di stato iraniani hanno  anche immagini di persone riunite nelle strade che pregavano per Raisi.La notizia della morte di Raisi è stata commentata con  da vari leader di paesi arabi vicini all’Iran, come l’Iraq e il Qatar, e dalle milizie che il regime sostiene da tempo, come Hamas e gli , in Yemen: insieme a  , in Libano, gli Houthi e Hamas fanno parte di quello che i generali iraniani definiscono un , cioè un complesso di alleanze in vari paesi attive nel contrasto dell’influenza di paesi come gli Stati Uniti e Israele. Raisi era diretto verso la città di Tabriz, vicino a dove l’elicottero è precipitato, di ritorno dall’Azerbaigian, un paese con cui l’Iran confina a nord-ovest, dove era andato per inaugurare una diga col presidente azero Ilham Aliyev. Nel pomeriggio di domenica i media iraniani avevano parlato di «un brusco atterraggio» dell’elicottero vicino a Jolfa. Dell’elicottero di Raisi non si era saputo più nulla e per molte ore erano proseguite le ricerche, rese molto difficoltose dalla fitta nebbia presente in quella zona, montuosa e particolarmente remota. Alle ricerche  decine di squadre di soccorso inviate sia dal governo iraniano che dall’estero.Soccorritori tra i relitti dell’elicottero a bordo del quale c’era il presidente dell’Iran Ebrahim Raisi (Azin Haghighi, Moj News Agency via AP/LaPresse)Ora che è morto, Raisi  dal vicepresidente del paese, Mohammad Mokhber, come previsto dalla Costituzione iraniana. Mokhber è considerato altrettanto vicino alla Guida suprema, Ali Khamenei, che ha confermato la sua nomina. Il ministro degli Esteri iraniano Hossein Amir-Abdollahian è stato temporaneamente sostituito dal suo vice, Ali Bagheri Kani. Dopodiché andranno organizzate nuove elezioni entro un periodo massimo di 50 giorni: significa che le elezioni presidenziali che avrebbero dovuto svolgersi nel 2025 potrebbero tenersi già quest’estate. Nel frattempo Khamenei  cinque giorni di lutto nazionale per la morte di Raisi.",
        "ranked": 19,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289208.49868,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ilPost",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "Iran President Ebrahim Raisi died",
        "en_content": "The president of Iran, died in an accident on Sunday near the town of Jolfa, in the Iranian province of East Azerbaijan, in the northwest of the country, in a mountainous and woody area difficult to reach. The scraps of the helicopter on which he traveled were after many hours of research. In addition to Raisi, on the helicopter were also the Iranian Foreign Minister, Hossein Amir-Abdollahian, the Governor of the Iranian province of East Azerbaijan, Malek Rahmati, and Ayatollah Mohammad Ali Ale-Hashem, representative of the Iranian Supreme Guide in East Azerbaijan (the Supreme Guide is Ali religious and political authority). Ebrahim Raisi was 63 years old and was president of Iran since 2021. It was an expression of the ultraconservative component of Iranian politics and was considered very close to Khamenei, of which it was also credited as a potential successor. Against the regime, between 2022 and 2023, Iran had gone on for months extensive protests that in a short time had turned into a revolt, the largest manifestation of dissent from the 1979 revolution, which turned Iran into an Islamic Republic. The regime had repressed the protests with violence, to death several people, with .In many parts of Iran the accident in which Raisi died was already before the news of his death. On social networks there are also fireworks and celebrations on the streets of various cities: Many attributed them to the incident in which Raisi died, but in Iran these days for the anniversary of the birth of the imam Ali ibn Musa al-Reza, a kind of saint in the Shiite religion. The Iranian state media also have images of people gathered in the streets praying for Raisi. The news of Raisi's death has been commented by various leaders of Arab countries close to Iran, such as Iraq and Qatar, and by the militias that the regime has long supported, such as Hamas and , in Yemen: together with the Houthi and Hamas in Lebanon are part of what the Iranian generals call a complex of alliances in various countries active in contrasting the influence of countries such as the United States and Israel. Raisi was headed towards the city of Tabriz, near where the helicopter crashed, returning from Azerbaijan, a country with which Iran borders to the northwest, where he had gone to inaugurate a dam with Azerbaijani President Ilham Aliyev. On Sunday afternoon, the Iranian media spoke of “a rough landing” of the helicopter near Jolfa. Raisi's helicopter had no knowledge of anything and for many hours the research had continued, made very difficult by the thick fog present in that area, mountainous and particularly remote. Tens of rescue teams sent by both the Iranian government and abroad. Reliefs among the wrecks of the helicopter on board which was the president of Iran Ebrahim Raisi (Azin Haghighi, Moj News Agency via AP/LaPresse)Now that he died, Raisi from the vice president of the country, Mohammad Mokhber, as provided by the Iranian Constitution. Mokhber is considered as close to the Supreme Guide, Ali Khamenei, who confirmed his appointment. Iranian Foreign Minister Hossein Amir-Abdollahian was temporarily replaced by his deputy, Ali Bagheri Kani. Afterwards new elections will be organized within a maximum period of 50 days: means that the presidential elections that should take place in 2025 could be held this summer. In the meantime Khamenei five days of national mourning for the death of Raisi.",
        "en_subtitle": "The helicopter on which he traveled had fallen on Sunday in a mountainous area in the north-west of the country: on board was also the Foreign Minister, Hossein Amir-Abdollahian",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir-Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jolfa",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "many hours",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir-Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Malek Rahmati",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ayatollah Mohammad Ali Ale-Hashem",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Iranian Supreme Guide",
                "start_char": 526,
                "end_char": 551,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "East Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 570,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ali",
                "start_char": 593,
                "end_char": 596,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 633,
                "end_char": 646,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "63 years old",
                "start_char": 651,
                "end_char": 663,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 685,
                "end_char": 689,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 696,
                "end_char": 700,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 761,
                "end_char": 768,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 811,
                "end_char": 819,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "between 2022 and 2023",
                "start_char": 897,
                "end_char": 918,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 920,
                "end_char": 924,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "months",
                "start_char": 941,
                "end_char": 947,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1979",
                "start_char": 1060,
                "end_char": 1064,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1090,
                "end_char": 1094,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "an Islamic Republic",
                "start_char": 1100,
                "end_char": 1119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1222,
                "end_char": 1226,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 1249,
                "end_char": 1254,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 1443,
                "end_char": 1448,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1462,
                "end_char": 1466,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "these days",
                "start_char": 1467,
                "end_char": 1477,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ali ibn Musa al-Reza",
                "start_char": 1523,
                "end_char": 1543,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shiite",
                "start_char": 1568,
                "end_char": 1574,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 1589,
                "end_char": 1596,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 1672,
                "end_char": 1677,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 1691,
                "end_char": 1696,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 1746,
                "end_char": 1750,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1770,
                "end_char": 1774,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 1784,
                "end_char": 1788,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Qatar",
                "start_char": 1793,
                "end_char": 1798,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1864,
                "end_char": 1869,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 1879,
                "end_char": 1884,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 1904,
                "end_char": 1910,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1915,
                "end_char": 1920,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 1924,
                "end_char": 1931,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 1953,
                "end_char": 1960,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 2076,
                "end_char": 2093,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2098,
                "end_char": 2104,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 2106,
                "end_char": 2111,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 2143,
                "end_char": 2149,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 2201,
                "end_char": 2211,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 2234,
                "end_char": 2238,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Azerbaijani",
                "start_char": 2308,
                "end_char": 2319,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilham Aliyev",
                "start_char": 2330,
                "end_char": 2342,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 2347,
                "end_char": 2353,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "afternoon",
                "start_char": 2354,
                "end_char": 2363,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 2369,
                "end_char": 2376,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jolfa",
                "start_char": 2433,
                "end_char": 2438,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 2440,
                "end_char": 2445,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "many hours",
                "start_char": 2496,
                "end_char": 2506,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tens",
                "start_char": 2631,
                "end_char": 2635,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 2669,
                "end_char": 2676,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 2779,
                "end_char": 2783,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 2784,
                "end_char": 2797,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Azin Haghighi",
                "start_char": 2799,
                "end_char": 2812,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moj News Agency",
                "start_char": 2814,
                "end_char": 2829,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AP/LaPresse)Now",
                "start_char": 2834,
                "end_char": 2849,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 2864,
                "end_char": 2869,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohammad Mokhber",
                "start_char": 2910,
                "end_char": 2926,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Iranian Constitution",
                "start_char": 2943,
                "end_char": 2967,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mokhber",
                "start_char": 2969,
                "end_char": 2976,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Guide",
                "start_char": 3003,
                "end_char": 3020,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ali Khamenei",
                "start_char": 3022,
                "end_char": 3034,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 3067,
                "end_char": 3074,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir-Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 3092,
                "end_char": 3116,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ali Bagheri Kani",
                "start_char": 3157,
                "end_char": 3173,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "50 days",
                "start_char": 3245,
                "end_char": 3252,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 3318,
                "end_char": 3322,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "this summer",
                "start_char": 3337,
                "end_char": 3348,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 3366,
                "end_char": 3374,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "five days",
                "start_char": 3375,
                "end_char": 3384,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 3423,
                "end_char": 3428,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Le truppe statunitensi lasceranno il Niger a metà settembre",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.ilpost.it/mondo/",
        "news_url": "https://www.ilpost.it/2024/05/20/stati-uniti-niger-esercito/",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "In una dichiarazione congiunta pubblicata domenica gli Stati Uniti e il Niger  che le truppe statunitensi lasceranno definitivamente il paese entro il 15 settembre. Gli Stati Uniti hanno in Niger più di mille soldati e una base militare considerata fondamentale per il controllo dell’area del Sahel (la zona che si trova nella parte sud del deserto del Sahara) e il contrasto delle attività dei gruppi islamisti e jihadisti attivi nella regione. Si trovavano in Niger per questo motivo dal 2013.A marzo la giunta militare che governa il Niger dal colpo di stato del luglio del 2023  la fine «con effetto immediato» degli accordi che permettevano agli Stati Uniti di impiegare personale militare e civile nel paese. Gli Stati Uniti  di opporsi a questa decisione, senza successo. Fino all’anno scorso l’esercito statunitense aveva collaborato sul campo con l’esercito francese, che però  a settembre del 2023, dopo che la giunta aveva cancellato gli accordi di collaborazione con la Francia.È un ulteriore allontanamento dall’influenza occidentale da parte del governo militare del Niger, che si sta spostando sempre più verso la Russia, a cui si è rivolto per un sostegno economico e militare: ad aprile  in Niger dei militari russi per addestrare le truppe locali. Il paese ha anche da poco  un accordo di cooperazione militare con altri due paesi dell’area, il Mali e il Burkina Faso, dove a partire del 2021 c’erano stati .",
        "ranked": 18,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289208.574745,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ilPost",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "US troops will leave the Niger in mid-September",
        "en_content": "In a joint statement published on Sunday, the United States and the Niger that US troops will leave the country permanently by September 15. The United States has in Niger more than a thousand soldiers and a military base considered fundamental to control the Sahel area (the area that is located in the south of the Sahara desert) and the contrast of the activities of Islamist and jihadist groups active in the region. They were in Niger for this reason since 2013. In March, the military junta governing the Niger from the July 2023 coup d'état, the \"immediate effect\" of the agreements which allowed the United States to employ military and civil personnel in the country. The United States to oppose this decision, without success. Until last year the U.S. Army had collaborated on the field with the French army, but in September 2023, after the junta had cancelled the cooperation agreements with France. It is a further distancing from Western influence by the Niger military government, which is moving more and more towards Russia, to which it turned for economic and military support: in April in Niger of the Russian military to train the local troops. The country also recently has a military cooperation agreement with two other countries in the area, Mali and Burkina Faso, where from 2021 there had been .",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Niger",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "mid-September",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Niger",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "September 15",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Niger",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than a thousand",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sahel",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sahara",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "LOC",
