[
    {
        "title": "Trump:\"Ha ragione.Europei parassiti\"157  ISRAELE, LIBERATO REGISTA HAMDAN BALLAL Premio Oscar di \"No Other Land\"",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Israele, liberato regista Hamdan Ballal Rilasciato Hamdan Ballal, il regista di \"No other land\", premiato agli Oscar. Arrestato ieri dall'esercito isrealiano dopo che ha subito un pestaggio dai coloni a Susiya, in Cisgiordania.  Il coautore del documentario,Abraham,ha scritto ieri dell'arresto su X,spiegando che Ballal dopo le botte, ha chiamato l'ambulanza, da cui i soldati lo  hanno prelevato e portato via.L'avvocato di Ballal ha riferito che il regista \"è stato ammanettato, bendato e picchiato tutta la notte in una base dell' esercito israeliano\" e poi liberato. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742940007.2833943,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "Trump:\"He's right. European Parasites\"157 ISRAELE, FREE REGIST HAMDAN BALLAL Oscar Award of \"No Other Land\"",
        "en_content": "Israel, freed director Hamdan Ballal Released Hamdan Ballal, director of \"No other land\", awarded to the Oscars. He was arrested yesterday by the Islamic army after he suffered a plague from the settlers in Susiya, West Bank. The co-author of the documentary, Abraham, wrote yesterday of the arrest on X, explaining that Ballal after the barrels, called the ambulance, from which the soldiers took him and took him away. Ballal's lawyer reported that the director \"was handcuffed, blindfolded and beaten all night in a base of the Israeli army\" and then released.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European Parasites\"157",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ISRAELE",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamdan Ballal",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamdan Ballal",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Oscars",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamic",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Susiya",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West Bank",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abraham",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ballal",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ballal",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "all night",
                "start_char": 504,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ACCONTI CON ALIQUOTE IRPEF PER IL 2025  Mef: intervento sarà in tempo utile",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Governo: sì acconti aliquote Irpef 2025 Il governo interviene per consentire l' applicazione aliquote '25 per la determinazione dell'acconto Irpef.Lo si legge in nota del Mef a seguito dei dubbi di alcuni Caf e dalla Cgil.   \"Al fine di salvaguardare tutti i contribuenti interessati, il governo interverrà anche in via normativa per  consentire l'applicazione delle nuove aliquote del 2025 per la determinazione dell'acconto. L'intervento sarà  realizzato in tempo utile per evitare ai contribuenti aggravi in termini di dichiarazione e di versamento\".  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.3007028,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "ACCONTS WITH IRPEF ALIQUOTE FOR 2025 Mef: intervention will be in good time",
        "en_content": "Government: yes aliquotes Irpef 2025 The government intervenes to allow the aliquote application '25 for the determination of the Irpef. It is read in the Mef note following the doubts of some Caf and Cgil. \"In order to safeguard all the taxpayers concerned, the government will also intervene by law to allow the application of the new rates of 2025 for the determination of the deposit. The intervention will be carried out in good time to avoid aggressive taxpayers in terms of declaration and payment\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ACCONTS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mef",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Irpef 2025",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "'25",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Irpef",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mef",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Caf and Cgil",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CASO CHAT,VANCE:\"ODIO SALVARE L'EUROPA\" Messaggi inviati per sbaglio a reporter Trump:\"Ha ragione.Europei parassiti\"150  STRAGE ERBA, CASSAZIONE: NO A REVISIONE Rigettato ricorso di Olindo e Rosa",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742940007.3104722,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "CASO CHAT,VANCE: \"I'd like to save the EURO\" Messages sent by mistake to reporter Trump:\"You're right. European parasites\"150 STRAGE ERBA, CASSATION: NO TO REVISIONS Rejected recourse of Olindo and Rosa",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CASO CHAT",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "VANCE",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Olindo",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rosa",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Totti conferma il viaggio a Mosca",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=201",
        "content": "     ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742940007.3196182,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "Totti confirms his trip to Moscow",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Totti",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mosca:sì tregua dopo revoca sanzioni153  KIEV, MISSILE LONG NEPTUNE SULLA CRIMEA Ha già colpito sul territorio russo",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Kiev:uso missile Long Neptune in Crimea Il nuovo missile a lungo raggio \"LongNeptune\" di fabbricazione ucraina e con una gittata di 1.000 chilometri è stato usato anche in Crimea.   Lo ha rivelato il ministro ucraino delle Industrie strategiche Smetanin, dopo che la settimana scorsa il 'super missile' aveva già colpito una raffineria di petrolio in territorio russo. \"La prima volta che lo abbiamo utilizzato è quando abbiamo attaccato un obiettivo militare nella penisola  occupata di Crimea\", ha affermato in un'intervista a un giornale norvegese. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742940007.3703716,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "Moscow: yes truce after revocation sanctions153 KIEV, MISSILE LONG NEPTUNE ON CRIMEA He has already hit on Russian territory",
        "en_content": "Kiev: Long Neptune missile use in Crimea The new long-range missile \"LongNeptune\" of Ukrainian manufacture and with a 1,000-kilometre trip was also used in Crimea. It was revealed by the Ukrainian Minister of Strategic Industries Smetanin, after last week the 'super missile' had already hit an oil refinery in Russian territory. \"The first time we used it is when we attacked a military target in the Crimean occupied peninsula,\" he said in an interview with a Norwegian newspaper.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "sanctions153 KIEV",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "LongNeptune",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "1,000-kilometre",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "last week",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimean",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 409,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norwegian",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Chat Vance: \"Odio salvare l'Europa\"",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Chat Vance:odio salvare ancora l'Europa \"Non sopporto salvare di nuovo l'Europa\", \"Condivido pienamente il tuo odio per il parassita europeo,è patetico\".E' lo scambio di messaggi tra il vicepresidente Usa JD Vance e il Segretario alla Difesa Hegseth, riportati dal caporedattore dell'Atlantic, Goldberg, che ha fatto sapere di essersi ritrovato per errore in una chat, altamente classificata, tra il capo del Pentagono Vance e funzionari di primo piano. Immediata la reazione di GB: \"Lavorato a stretto contatto Usa per sicurezza\". \"Contributo\" Londra a raid anti-Houthi.",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742940007.379238,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "Chat Vance: \"To save Europe\"",
        "en_content": "Chat Vance: hate to save Europe again \"I can't stand saving Europe again\", \"I fully share your hatred for the European parasite, it's pathetic.\" It is the exchange of messages between US Vice President JD Vance and Secretary of Defense Hegseth, reported by the editor of the Atlantic, Goldberg, who made it known that he found himself mistakenly in a highly classified chat between the head of the Pentagon Vance and prominent officials. Immediate GB reaction: \"Use for safety.\" \"Contribution\" London to anti-Houthi raid.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vance",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vance",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "JD Vance",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hegseth",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atlantic",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Goldberg",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Pentagon Vance",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "GB",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 450,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 494,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Houthi",
                "start_char": 504,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CASA BIANCA:\"NESSUN SEGRETO SULLA CHAT\" Caso scambio messaggi da Pentagono",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Casa Bianca:\"Nessun segreto sulla chat\" Nessuna informazione militare classificata è stata condivisa. Lo ha affermato la portavoce della Casa Bianca,Leavitt, a proposito della chat del Pentagono sui piani anti-Houthi condivisa per errore con il direttore di The Atlantic. \"Nessun piano di guerra è stato discusso\" e \"nessun materiale classificato è stato mandato nello scambio messaggi\". Il presidente Trump difende il suo consigliere per la Sicurezza:\"Waltz ha imparato la lezione ed è un brav'uomo\". Non c'è stato \"alcun impatto\" sull'operazione militare.La Casa Bianca:fuga di notizie è atto \"politico\" per distrarre",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742940007.3924394,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ Message exchange case from Pentagon",
        "en_content": "White House: \"No secret on the chat\" No classified military information was shared. The White House spokesman, Leavitt, said about the Pentagon chat on anti-Houthi plans shared by mistake with the director of The Atlantic. \"No war plan has been discussed\" and \"no classified material has been sent into the message exchange.\" President Trump defends his security advisor: \"Waltz learned the lesson and is a good man.\" There wasn't any impact on the military operation. The White House: news escape is act \"political\" to distract",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Leavitt",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Houthi",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atlantic",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Waltz",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The White House",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 484,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "INTESA USA-KIEV SU NAVI SICURE MAR NERO \"Condordati stessi punti di Mosca\"",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742940007.4115715,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "INTESA USA-KIEV ON NAVI SAURE MAR NERO \"Condordati si punti di Mosca\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "INTESA USA-KIEV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NAVI SAURE MAR",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "INTESA USA-KIEV SU NAVI SICURE MAR NERO \"Condordati stessi punti di Mosca\"",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Usa:accordo navigazione sicura Mar Nero Gli esperti dei gruppi di lavoro UsaRussia hanno concordato a Riad sugli stessi punti condivisi da Washington e Kiev. Emerge da nota della Casa Bianca. Si annuncia un accordo per il cessate fuoco \"per garantire la sicurezza della navigazione, eliminare l'uso della forza e impedire l'uso di navi commerciali a scopi militari nel Mar Nero\".Concordi anche a \"sviluppare misure\" per vietare i bombardamenti delle infrastrutture energetiche. Usa \"restano impegnati\" su scambio dei prigionieri e ritorno bimbi ucraini.\"Imperativo\" Trump:basta morti.",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742940007.4329076,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "INTESA USA-KIEV ON NAVI SAURE MAR NERO \"Condordati si punti di Mosca\"",
        "en_content": "Use: Black Sea Safe Navigation Agreement Experts from US Russian working groups agreed to Riad on the same points shared by Washington and Kiev. It emerges from the White House. An agreement is announced for the ceasefire \"to ensure the safety of navigation, eliminate the use of force and prevent the use of commercial ships for military purposes in the Black Sea\". I also agreed to \"develop measures\" to ban the bombing of energy infrastructure. Use \"rest committed\" on exchange of prisoners and return Ukrainian children. \"Imperative\" Trump: dead enough.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "INTESA USA-KIEV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NAVI SAURE MAR",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Black Sea Safe Navigation Agreement Experts",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riad",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Black Sea",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "E a editori: libro presidio libertà",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Mattarella: \"Libri presidio di libertà\" Le case editrici, grandi o piccole, sono \"presidio di libertà e di promozione di cultura, di promozione dei diritti, indispensabile condizione per qualunque Paese\". Così il Presidente Mattarella ricevendo al Quirinale una delegazione dell'Associazione italiana editori,  guidata dal presidente Cipolletta. \"Questo presidio di libertà e di diritti che attraverso i libri si esplica e si realizza è un elemento indipensabile per la nostra democrazia\". \"Numeri eloquenti\", commenta i dati: in Italia oltre 5mila editori.    ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.4494288,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "And to publishers: book presidio libertà",
        "en_content": "Mattarella: \"Libri presidio di libertà\" The publishing houses, large or small, are \"freedom and promotion of culture, rights promotion, indispensable condition for any country\". Thus President Mattarella receives a delegation from the Italian Association of Publishers, led by President Cipolletta. \"This garrison of freedom and rights that through books is explanatory and is realized is an indispensable element for our democracy.\" \"Numeri eloquenti\", comments the data: in Italy more than 5 thousand publishers.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "presidio libertà",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libri presidio di libertà",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Association of Publishers",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cipolletta",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Numeri",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISTANBUL,SABATO MANIFESTA L'OPPOSIZIONE Per sostenere Ekrem Imamoglu",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=159",
        "content": " Istanbul,sabato manifesta l'opposizione Il leader del Partito popolare repubblicano (Chp), la principale forza dell'opposizione turca, ha indetto una grande manifestazione sabato a Istanbul a sostegno del sindaco detenuto della città, Ekrem Imamoglu.   \"Sarete sabato alla grande manifestazione per sostenere Ekrem Imamoglu, per opporvi alla (sua) detenzione e dire che vogliamo elezioni anticipate?\" ha chiesto il leader del Chp,Ozgur Ozel alla folla riunita per la settima sera consecutiva davanti al municipio di  Istanbul.     ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742940007.4684002,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ To support Ekrem Imamoglu",
        "en_content": "Istanbul,Saturday manifests opposition The leader of the Republican People's Party (Chp), the main force of the Turkish opposition, called a big demonstration Saturday in Istanbul in support of the city's detainee mayor, Ekrem Imamoglu. \"You will be Saturday at the great event to support Ekrem Imamoglu, to oppose (his) detention and say that we want early elections?\" asked the leader of the Chp, Ozgur Ozel to the crowd gathered for the seventh consecutive evening in front of the Istanbul City Hall.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ekrem Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Republican People's Party",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ekrem Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ekrem Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chp",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the seventh consecutive",
                "start_char": 436,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Istanbul City Hall",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 502,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DA MINISTERO STRETTA PER MEDICI RADIATI Iter più snello, sanzioni esecutive",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Da Ministero stretta per medici radiati Procedure più snelle e immediata esecutività delle sanzioni comminate dagli ordini professionali. E' quanto prevede lo schema di riforma della Commissione Centrale per gli esercenti le professioni sanitarie (CEEPS), incaricata di giudicare i ricorsi contro i provvedimenti disciplinari degli Ordini, quelli su iscrizione e cancellazione dagli Albi nonché i ricorsi elettorali.  Lo annuncia il ministero della Salute, che ha predisposto lo schema di riforma con obiettivo di\"rendere più spedita la trattazione e decisione del giudizio\". ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.4716084,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "MINISTERS FOR MEDICINAL PRODUCTS RADIATI Iter more slender, executive sanctions",
        "en_content": "By strict Ministry for Radiated Doctors Procedures more slender and immediate execution of sanctions committed by professional orders. This is the plan of reform of the Central Commission for health professionals (EECPS) who are responsible for judging actions against the disciplinary measures of the Orders, those on registration and deletion from the Albis and electoral actions. It announces the Ministry of Health, which has prepared the scheme of reform with aim to \"make more sent the treatment and decision of judgment\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ministry for Radiated Doctors Procedures",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Central Commission",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EECPS",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Albis",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Health",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky: \"Verso giusta direzione\"",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Zelensky:accordo nella giusta direzione L'accordo per fermare gli attacchi militari nel Mar Nero e sulle infrastrutture energetiche, mediato dagli Usa, è un passo nella giusta direzione. Così il presidente ucraino Zelensky. \"E' troppo presto per dire che funzionerà, ma questi sono stati gli incontri giusti, le decisioni giuste, i passi giusti\", ha detto dopo i colloqui a  Riad. \"Faremo la nostra parte per attuare gli accordi\", assicura. Ma no alla revoca delle sanzioni alla Russia. La tregua nel Mar Nero sarà monitorata da \"terze parti\" come la Turchia. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742940007.4911704,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "Zelensky: \"Verso right direction\"",
        "en_content": "Zelensky: agreement in the right direction The agreement to stop military attacks in the Black Sea and energy infrastructure, mediated by the US, is a step in the right direction. So Ukrainian President Zelensky. \"It's too early to say it will work, but these were the right meetings, the right decisions, the right steps,\" he said after the talks at Riad. \"We will do our part to implement the agreements,\" he says. But not to revoke sanctions to Russia. The truce in the Black Sea will be monitored by \"third parties\" like Turkey.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Verso",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Black Sea",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riad",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Black Sea",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 482,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 525,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SANTANCHE'CAMBIA AVV,ISTANZA PER RINVIO Forse posticipata udienza di domani",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Truffa Inps,Santanché cambia il legale La ministra del Turismo Santanchè cambia il legale e,per i termini a difesa, potrebbe saltare l'udienza di domani davanti al gup per l'accusa di truffa aggravata all'Inps, in relazione alla cassa integrazione nel periodo Covid per alcuni dipendenti di Visibilia.  Il nuovo difensore domani non appena prenderà la parola chiederà un rinvio legato ai cosiddetti \"termini a difesa\" per consentire al nuovo legale di studiare le carte e gli atti processuali. L'udienza avrebbe dovuto portare al  proscioglimento al rinvio a giudizio della ministra.    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.4985323,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "Perhaps postponed hearing tomorrow",
        "en_content": "Truffa Inps,Santanché changes the legal The Santanch Tourism Minister changes the legal and, for defense terms, could skip the hearing tomorrow in front of the gup for the charge of fraud aggravated to the Inps, in relation to the fund integration in the Covid period for some Visibilia employees. The new defender tomorrow as soon as he takes the word he will ask for a referral tied to the so-called \"defense rules\" to allow the new lawyer to study the cards and the procedural acts. The hearing should have led to the motion for a referral to the judgment of the Minister.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Truffa Inps",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santanché",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Santanch",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Inps",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Covid",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Visibilia",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Toyota,stop impianto batterie litio",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Toyota, stop produzione batterie litio La Toyota rinvierà la costruzione di una fabbrica di batterie agli ioni di litio nella prefettura di Fukuoka a  causa della scarsa domanda di veicoli elettrici a livello globale.  Lo anticipa la stampa nipponica che cita una fonte dell'azienda a conoscenza del dossier, spiegando che Koji Sato, presidente della casa automobilistica, avrebbe deciso lo stop a causa della domanda di veicoli elettrici inferiore alle aspettative,ma anche perché si è registrata un'impennata dei costi dei materiali e della manodopera.  ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.5084722,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "Toyota,stop lithium battery system",
        "en_content": "Toyota, stop production lithium batteries Toyota will renew the construction of a lithium-ion battery factory in the Fukuoka prefecture due to the low demand of electric vehicles globally. It anticipates the Japanese press that cites a source of the company to knowledge of the dossier, explaining that Koji Sato, president of the car, would have decided the stop because of the demand of electric vehicles less than the expectations, but also because there has been an impennata of the costs of materials and labor.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Toyota",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Toyota",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Toyota",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fukuoka",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japanese",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Koji Sato",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FRANCESCHINI:A FIGLI SOLO COGNOME MADRE \"Risarcimento ingiustizia secolare\"",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Franceschini:a figli solo cognome madre \"Ai figli solo il cognome della madre\". E' la proposta che l'ex ministro e sen. Pd Franceschini presenterà al Senato. All'Assemblea Pd, dice: \"Anziché creare infiniti problemi con la gestione dei doppi cognomi o con la scelta tra quello del padre o della madre, dopo secoli in cui i figli hanno preso quello dei padri stabiliamo che prenderanno quello della madre. E' semplice ed è anche un risarcimento per un'ingiustiza secolare che ha avuto non solo valore simbolico, ma è stata una delle fonti delle disuguaglianze di genere\", spiega al Pd. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.5116427,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ _",
        "en_content": "Franceschini: to children only mother surname \"To children only the surname of the mother\". It is the proposal that the former Minister and Mr Pd Franceschini will present to the Senate. To the Pd Assembly, he says: \"In order to create infinite problems with the management of the double surnames or with the choice between that of the father or mother, after centuries in which the children took that of the fathers we establish that they will take that of the mother. It is simple and it is also a compensation for a secular unjustice that has not only had symbolic value, but it was one of the sources of gender inequalities,\" he explains.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Franceschini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mr Pd Franceschini",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Pd Assembly",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "centuries",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FdI: \"Se andrà a giudizio lascerà\"",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " FdI: se Santanché a giudizio lascerebbe FdI ha ribadito che se la ministra Santanchè dovesse essere rinviata a giudizio per la cassa Covid,si dimetterebbe. Il capogruppo di FdI alla Camera,Bignami,ha spiegato:\"Non se è confermata l' udienza domani,ma cambia poco.Noi riteniamo-come ha detto il ministro stesso quando è venuta in Aula-che nel momento in cui dovesse esserci un rinvio si arriverebbe a una presa d'atto della necessità di lasciare l'incarico.Non perché stia governando male il turismo,ma per garantirle la possibilità di difensi\".Donzelli:ha detto se a giudizio lascia.Cambio legale è vicenda personale.",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.5520983,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "FdI: \"If he goes to trial, he'll leave.\"",
        "en_content": "FdI: if Santanché in judgement would leave FdI reiterated that if the Santanchè ministra should be postponed to trial for the Covid case, he would resign. The FdI group leader at the Chamber,Bignami, explained: \"Not if the hearing is confirmed tomorrow, but it changes little. We believe — as the minister himself said when he came to the Chamber — that at the time when a referral was to be referred, it would be necessary to leave the office. Not because it is misleading tourism, but to ensure it is possible to defend itself.\" Donzelli: he said if he leaves. Legal change is personal.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Santanché",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Santanchè",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Covid",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bignami",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "COLLE: \"GRAVE SOVRAFFOLLAMENTO CARCERI\" Così per 208° Polizia penitenziaria",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Colle: \"Grave sovraffollamento carceri\" Per la Polizia penitenziaria, \"quotidianamente\", \"difficili situazioni di tensione e sofferenza, a causa del grave fenomeno di sovraffollamento in atto\" nelle carceri.    Così il Presidente Mattarella, che sottolinea il \"determinante contributo\"degli agenti\"all'attuazione del principio costituzionale della funzione rieducativa della pena per il possibile reinserimento dei detenuti, nonostante le critiche condizioni del sistema carcerario\". Il messaggio in occasione del 208° anniversario del Corpo.   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.5580654,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "COLLE: \"GRAVE SOVRAFFOLLATION CARCERI\" So for 208° Penitentiary Police",
        "en_content": "Colle: \"Grave overcrowding prisons\" For the penitentiary police, \"quotidianly\", \"difficult situations of tension and suffering, because of the serious phenomenon of overcrowding in the prisons. Thus President Mattarella, who emphasizes the \"determinant contribution\" of the agents\" to the implementation of the constitutional principle of the educational function of the penalty for the possible reintegration of the prisoners, despite the critical conditions of the prison system\". The message on the occasion of the 208° anniversary of the Body.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "COLLE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "208",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "208",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AUTO, DIMEZZATE IN EUROPA VENDITE TESLA Ibride +18,7%,superano auto benzina",
        "date_raw": "March 25, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Auto, dimezzate in Ue vendite di Tesla Le vendite europee di auto elettriche Tesla sono calate del 49% in gennaio e febbraio rispetto allo stesso periodo dell'anno precedente. Sono i dati dell' Associazione dei costruttori europei di automobili (Acea). Pesano i modelli obsoleti ma -si ipotizzaanche la vicinanza del proprietario Musk a Trump. Il calo in controtendenza rispetto alla crescita registrata nel mercato elettrico. I modelli ibridi (motore elettrico e batteria non collegata) segnano +18,7%, arrivando al 35,2% delle vendite nei primi 2 mesi 2025. Le auto a  batteria segnano +28,4% (15,2% mercato)",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742940007.5655973,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-25 23:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-25T22.00.07",
        "en_title": "AUTO, DIMEZZATE IN EUROPE SALE TESLA Hybride +18.7%,superior auto petrol",
        "en_content": "Auto, halved in Ue sales of Tesla European sales of Tesla electric cars fell by 49% in January and February compared to the same period of the previous year. These are the data of the Association of European Car Builders (Acea). They weigh the obsolete models but - it is also hypothesized the proximity of the owner Musk to Trump. The decline in counter-tendency compared to the growth recorded in the electric market. Hybrid models (electric motor and unconnected battery) mark +18.7%, reaching 35.2% of sales in the first 2 months 2025. Battery cars score +28.4% (15.2% market)",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ue",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tesla European",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tesla",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "49%",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "January",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "February",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the previous year",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Association of European Car Builders",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Acea",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "mark +18.7%",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "35.2%",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 502,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the first 2 months 2025",
                "start_char": 515,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "15.2%",
                "start_char": 567,
                "end_char": 572,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
