[
    {
        "title": "TRUMP CONDANNATO NEL PROCESSO PORNOSTAR Per i 34 capi di accusa contestati",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Trump condannato nel caso pornostar  Donald Trump è stato ritenuto colpevole per tutti i 34 capi di accusa sul caso Stormy Daniels.     Lo storico verdetto, raggiunto all'unanimità dalla giuria dopo due giorni di Camera di Consiglio,fa di Trump il primo ex presidente condannato in un processo penale e anche il primo candidato presidente a correre come pregiudicato (status che non preclude l'elezione). Udienza l'11 luglio per stabilire la condanna, variabile da un massimo di 4 anni alla messa in probva, fino a una multa. \"Una vergogna, continuerò a lottare\",ha detto Trump.Ricorso gia pronto",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717156807.7673514,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ For the 34 defendants",
        "en_content": "Trump convicted in the pornstar Donald Trump case was found guilty for all 34 charges on Stormy Daniels case. The historic verdict, unanimously reached by the jury after two days of the Council Chamber, makes Trump the first former president convicted in a criminal trial and also the first candidate president to run as a felony (status that does not preclude election). Audience on 11 July to establish the sentence, varying from a maximum of 4 years to the probva, up to a fine. \"A shame, I will continue to fight,\" Trump said.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "34",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "34",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stormy Daniels",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two days",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council Chamber",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "11 July",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "4 years",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 524,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Summit Difesa con Usa a Singapore",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Usa-Cina, ministri Difesa a Singapore Faccia a faccia a Singapore tra i ministri della Difesa di Usa e Cina, Austin e Jun, il primo tra i responsabili delle due potenze dal 2022. Un portavoce di Pechino definisce l'incontro \"pratico e costruttivo\".    Jun ha criticato le azioni Usa su Taiwan in violazione del \"principio dell'Unica Cina\",mentre Austin ha chiesto a Pechino di non usare la transizione politica di Taiwan \"come pretesto per misure coercitive\". Jun ha assicurato che la Cina non ha dato armi \"a nessuna delle parti in conflitto in Ucraina\". ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717156807.7777047,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "US Defense Summit in Singapore",
        "en_content": "USA-China, Defence Ministers in Singapore Face to face in Singapore between U.S. Defence Ministers and China, Austin and Jun, the first among the leaders of the two powers since 2022. A Beijing spokesman defines the \"practical and constructive\" meeting. Jun criticized the US actions on Taiwan in violation of the \"Unica China principle\", while Austin asked Beijing not to use Taiwan's political transition \"as a pretext for coercive measures\". Jun assured that China did not give weapons \"to any party in conflict in Ukraine\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US Defense Summit",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defence Ministers",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Austin",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jun",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2022",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jun",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unica China",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Austin",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jun",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISRAELE CONFERMA: OPERIAMO CENTRO RAFAH \"Attività mirate, su intelligence\"",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " M.O, Idf conferma operazione a Rafah L'Idf ha confermato per la prima volta di operare nel centro di Rafah,sud della Striscia di Gaza,in un'offensiva  contro Hamas \"precisa\" e \"basata sull' intelligence\",     L'esercito isreliano riferisce che sono stati localizzati lanciarazzi, tunnel e depositi di armi di Hamas e che un combattente è stato ucciso da un drone. Altre armi ed equipaggiamenti sarebbero stati localizzati nella parte orientale di Rafah, nel Corridoio Filadelfia che corre lungo il confine con l'Egitto. ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717156807.7832325,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "M.O, Idf confirms operation to Rafah The Idf confirmed for the first time to operate in the center of Rafah,south of the Gaza Strip, in an offensive against Hamas \"precise\" and \"based on intelligence\", The Isrelian army reports that they were located rocket launchers, tunnels and weapons deposits of Hamas and that a fighter was killed by a drone. Other weapons and equipment would be located in the eastern part of Rafah, in the Philadelphia Corridor running along the border with Egypt.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "M.O",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Philadelphia Corridor",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "YEMEN,RAID USA-GB CONTRO RIBELLI HOUTHI Colpite Sanaa e,sulla costa,Hodeida",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Yemen,raid Usa-Gb su città degli Houthi Attacchi aerei angloamericani su diversi obiettivi nello Yemen, contro i ribelli Houthi. Colpite la capitale Sana e la città portuale di Hodeida. Prese di mira anche le infrastrutture di telecomunicazioni a Taiz. La tv Al-Masirah, legata agli Houthi, riferisce di 14 morti e trenta feriti.   Gli Houthi -si legge in una nota della Difesa britannicacontinuano ad attaccare le navi internazionali in Mar Rosso e Golfo di Aden, da qui l'operazione per \"minare le loro capacità militari\". Il raid di notte,per ridurre rischi per i civili, aggiunge la nota da Londra. ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717156807.798144,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Yemen, U.S.-Gbraid on Houthi City Anglo-American Air Attacks on several targets in Yemen, against the Houthi rebels. Hit the Sana capital and the port city of Hodeida. Telecommunications infrastructure in Taiz is also targeted. Al-Masirah, linked to the Houthi, reports 14 dead and thirty wounded. The Houthi - read in a note of the British Defense continue to attack international ships in the Red Sea and Gulf of Aden, hence the operation to \"mine their military capabilities\". The night raid, to reduce risks to civilians, adds the note from London.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.-Gbraid",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi City Anglo-American Air Attacks",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sana",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hodeida",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiz",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Masirah",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "14",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "thirty",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the British Defense",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gulf",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "night",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 545,
                "end_char": 551,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nato a Kiev: sia uso responsabile",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Nato:uso\"responsabile\"armi contro Mosca \"E' la Russia che ha dato il via all' escalation, prima invadendo un altro Paese e ora aprendo il nuovo fronte a Kharkiv\": così il segretario Nato Stoltenberg all'informale Esteri a Praga. Parlando dell'uso delle armi fornite a Kiev dai Paesi alleati, ha aggiunto: \"Speriamo tutti\" che un uso contro  obiettivi militari in territorio russo avvenga \"in linea col diritto internazionale e in modo responsabile\". \"Ogni volta che abbiamo dato mezzi all'Ucraina, Putin ci ha minacciato; è stato così per artiglieria,tank missili,F-16\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717156807.9091,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "Born in Kiev: both responsible use",
        "en_content": "NATO: use \"responsible\" weapons against Moscow \"It's Russia that started escalation, first invading another country and now opening the new front to Kharkiv\": so the secretary NATO Stoltenberg to the foreign information in Prague. Speaking of the use of weapons supplied in Kiev by allied countries, he added: \"We all hope that a use against military targets in Russian territory will take place \"in line with international law and in a responsible manner\". \"Every time we've given means to Ukraine, Putin has threatened us; it was like that for artillery,tank missiles,F-16\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prague",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 278,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 500,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "F-16",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 574,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "G7 PUGLIA, TORNANO CONTROLLI FRONTIERE  Viminale: \"E' prassi consolidata\"",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " G7 Puglia, sospeso Accordo Schengen  Il Viminale annuncia che in occasione del prossimo G7, a metà giugno in Puglia, \"le frontiere nazionali terrestri, marittime e aeree, come da prassi consolidata in occasione di eventi analoghi, saranno temporaneamente soggette a controlli\".     L'appuntamento per i leader dei Paesi G7 è a Borgo Egnazia dal 13 al 15 giugno. La sospensione degli accordi di libertà di movimento in Area Schengen parte il 5 giugno e si conclude il 18. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1717156807.91199,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "G7 PUGLIA, TORNANO CONTROLS FRONTIERE Viminale: \"It's consolidated practice\"",
        "en_content": "G7 Puglia, suspended Schengen Agreement The Viminale announces that on the occasion of the next G7, in mid-June in Puglia, \"the national terrestrial, marine and aerial borders, as from consolidated practice on the occasion of similar events, will be temporarily subject to controls\". The appointment for the leaders of the G7 Countries is in Borgo Egnazia from 13 to 15 June. The suspension of freedom of movement agreements in the Schengen Area starts on 5 June and ends on 18.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "G7 Puglia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schengen Agreement",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the next G7",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "mid-June",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Puglia",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the G7 Countries",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Borgo",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "13 to 15 June",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Schengen Area",
                "start_char": 428,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 June",
                "start_char": 456,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "USO ARMI, KIEV INCASSA ANCHE OK BERLINO Nato: \"Ma impiego sia responsabile\"",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1717156807.914981,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ \"But employment is responsible\"",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "CROSETTO:NO A NOSTRE ARMI CONTRO RUSSIA Aiutiamo alleati ma non siamo in guerra \"Lo diremo a Nato in modo franco\"",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Crosetto:nostre armi non puntino Russia \"Aiutiamo Kiev, ma le nostre armi non possono servire per attaccare\". Lo afferma il ministro della Difesa Crosetto in un'intervista a Il Domani.  i, \"Noi forniamo aiuti, anche militari, a una nazione aggredita, per difendersi e riconquistare la sua sovranità violata. Lo diremo ai nostri alleati in modo  franco, leale, sereno, senza alzare i toni. E' tutto nell'art.11 della Costituzione. Dobbiamo aiutare l'alleato aggredito, ma non essensdo in guerra non possiamo lasciargli usare gli aiuti per colpire nel territorio del nemico\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1717156807.916789,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "We help allies but we are not at war \"We will tell NATO in a frank way\"",
        "en_content": "Crosetto: Our weapons do not point Russia \"We aid Kiev, but our weapons cannot serve to attack\". The Minister of Defense Crosetto said this in an interview with Il Domani. i, \"We provide aid, including military, to an assaulted nation, to defend itself and regain its violated sovereignty. We will tell our allies frankly, loyal, serene, without raising the tones. That's all in Art.11 of the Constitution. We need to help the attacked ally, but I do not disagree in war, we cannot let him use the aid to hit the enemy's territory.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Il Domani",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI:UE,SERVE MAGGIORANZA COMPATIBILE \"Con la sinistra non posso stare\"",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Meloni:Ue,serve maggioranza compatibile \"Con la sinistra non ci posso stare né in Italia, né in Europa, né da nessuna parte\". Così a Skuola.net la premier Meloni risponde sui possibili scenari dopo il voto europeo dell'8 e 9 giugno. \"Sono due modelli alternativi l'uno  all'altro\". L'alleanza con il partito Popolare europeo è invece percorribile. \"Con il centrodestra, come accade in Italia, si trovano delle sinergie.Penso che anche in Europa vada costruita una maggioranza compatibile. Con le maggioranze arcobaleno, non riesci a fare  niente\", ha detto Meloni.   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1717156807.9471533,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.07",
        "en_title": "MELONI:EU, I can't stand with the left",
        "en_content": "Meloni:Ue,serve a compatible majority \"With the left I cannot stand neither in Italy, nor in Europe, nor anywhere\". So in Skuola.net, Premier Meloni responds to the possible scenarios after the European vote of 8 and 9 June. \"They are two alternative models to each other.\" The alliance with the European People's Party is also viable. \"With the centre, as it happens in Italy, there are synergies. I think that a compatible majority is also built in Europe. With rainbow majority, you can't do anything,\" Meloni said.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 and 9 June",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European People's Party",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 457,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 512,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1717156808.2644157,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MARINA BERLUSCONI CAVALIERE DEL LAVORO  Come lo fu il padre Silvio nel 1977   Tra insigniti anche Caselli e Boni",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=135",
        "content": " Marina Berlusconi Cavaliere del Lavoro Il Presidente Mattarella ha firmato un decreto con cui,su proposta del ministro delle Imprese e del made in Italy, Urso, sono stati nominati 25 nuovi Cavalieri del Lavoro.    Tra i neo nominati c'è Marina Berlusconi,la primogenita del fondatore di Forza Italia scomparso un anno fa, anche lui insignito della stessa onorificenza nel 1977.      Tra gli altri, anche la produttrice discografica Caterina Caselli e la stilista Chiara Boni.     ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1717156808.2671933,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "MARINA BERTS How was his father Silvio in 1977 Among awarded also Caselli and Boni",
        "en_content": "Marina Berlusconi Cavaliere del Lavoro The President Mattarella has signed a decree with which, on proposal of the Minister of Enterprises and made in Italy, Urso, 25 new Knights of Labor were appointed. Among the newly appointed there is Marina Berlusconi, the firstborn of the founder of Forza Italia who died a year ago, also awarded the same honor in 1977. Among others, also the record producer Caterina Caselli and designer Chiara Boni.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Silvio",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1977",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caselli",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Boni",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Marina Berlusconi Cavaliere del Lavoro",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Minister of Enterprises",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Urso",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "25",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Knights of Labor",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marina Berlusconi",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a year ago",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1977",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caterina Caselli",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chiara Boni",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "G7 PUGLIA,TORNA CONTROLL0 FRONTIERE",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1717156808.2690146,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "G7 PUGLIA, CONTROLL0 FRONTIERE",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CONTROLL0",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "OMICIDIO SAMAN, MADRE PRESA IN PAKISTAN Era l'unica latitante, da maggio'21",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1717156808.2702215,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "_ She was the only latizer, from May 21",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "May 21",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Crosetto:no nostre armi contro Mosca120  BANKITALIA:\"PNRR CRUCIALE PER CRESCITA\" Panetta: ma dev'esserci piano credibile \"Su lavoro pesa calo demografico\"",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1717156808.272085,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "Crosetto:no our weapons against Mosca120 BANKITALIA: \"CRUCIALE PNRR PER CRESCITA\" Panetta: but there must be credible plan \"On work we weigh demographic decline\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CRUCIALE",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Panetta",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ESTATE 2024, ATTESE 216MLN DI PRESENZE  Più stranieri, gli italiani stabili",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Estate, attese 216 milioni di presenze Dopo l'inizio dell'anno con il segno positivo, continua a crescere il turismo. Tra giugno e agosto, si prevedono 216 mln di presenze nelle strutture ricettive: +1,5% rispetto al 2023. Nei primi 5 mesi dell'anno le presenze sono aumentate del +3,8%.Emerge dall'indagine del Centro studi turistici di Firenze per Assoturismo Confesercenti.  Trainano la crescita della domanda i turisti stranieri: 105 mln, in aumento del 2,5%. La domanda italiana dovrebbe restare pressoché stabile a 110,9 mln, in lieve aumento dello 0,5%.   ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1717156808.557441,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "ESTATES 2024, ATTESE 216MLN PRESENCE More foreigners, stable Italians",
        "en_content": "Summer, expected 216 million visitors After the beginning of the year with the positive sign, continues to grow tourism. Between June and August, there are 216 mln of attendance in the accommodation facilities: +1.5% compared to 2023. In the first 5 months of the year attendance increased by +3.8%. It emerges from the survey of the Centro Studi turistico di Firenze for Assoturismo Confesercenti. Train demand growth foreign tourists: 105 mln, up 2.5%. The Italian demand should remain almost stable at 110.9 mln, slightly increasing by 0.5%.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "ATTESE 216MLN PRESENCE More",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Summer",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "216 million",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the beginning of the year",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Between June and August",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "216 mln",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "+1.5%",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the first 5 months of the year",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "+3.8%",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Assoturismo Confesercenti",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "105 mln",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2.5%",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 459,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "110.9 mln",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "0.5%",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CINA GRANDE ASSENTE SUMMIT PACE UCRAINA Tra motivi, mancato invito a Mosca",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Cina non sarà a conferenza pace Ucraina Il 15 e 16 giugno prossimi Pechino non parteciperà alla conferenza di pace  sull'Ucraina prevista in Svizzera. Lo riferiscono più fonti.Tra le motivazioni, la Russia non invitata al summit. Comunicando la decisione, Pechino l'ha motivata con l'assenza di \"partecipazione paritaria di tutte le parti e di una discussione equa di tutte le proposte disponibili\". Inutile quindi il  pressing diplomatico europeo sulla Cina Intanto, a Singapore primo incontro in 18 mesi,tra Cina e Usa su temi militari",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717156808.5632932,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "_ For reasons, missed invitation to Moscow",
        "en_content": "China will not be at conference peace Ukraine On 15 and 16 June, Beijing will not participate in the peace conference on Ukraine in Switzerland. More sources report it. Among the reasons, Russia is not invited to the summit. Communicating the decision, Beijing motivated it with the absence of \"the equal participation of all parties and a fair discussion of all available proposals\". Needless therefore European diplomatic pressing on China Meanwhile, in Singapore first meeting in 18 months, between China and USA on military themes",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "15 and 16 June",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 436,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 456,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "18 months",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 492,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"Su lavoro pesa calo demografico\"",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Lavoro, Panetta: favorire smart working L'occupazione potrebbe aumentare con\"una diversa organizzazione del lavoro tra quello in presenza e quello a distanza\".Così Panetta nelle considerazioni finali. Decisi aumenti dei tassi di occupazione\"potrebbero arrivare a controbilanciare gli effetti del calo demografico e mantenere invariato il numero degli occupati\".Un aiuto potrebbe arrivare dal flusso di immigrati regolari da gestire con più integrazione. \"Modeste\" le previsioni di crescita  nell'Eurozona, soggette peraltro \"a rischi al ribasso\".    ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1717156808.6023064,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "\"On work we weigh demographic decline\"",
        "en_content": "Work, Panetta: favor smart working Employment could increase with \"a different organization of work between the one in the presence and the one at a distance\". So Panetta in the final considerations. These increases in employment rates would be able to counterbalance the effects of population decline and maintain the number of employees unchanged.\" A help could come from the flow of regular immigrants to manage with more integration. \"Modeste\" growth forecasts in the Eurozone, however, subject to \"low risks\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Panetta",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Modeste",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eurozone",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BANKITALIA:\"PNRR CRUCIALE PER CRESCITA\" Panetta: serve un piano credibile",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Pnrr, Panetta: cruciale per la crescita \"La piena attuazione degli investimenti e delle riforme previste dal Pnrr-oltre innalzare il prodotto di oltre 2 punti percentuali nel breve termineavrebbe effetti duraturi sulla crescita dovuti a incrementi di produttività stimabili tra 3 e 6 punti in un decennio\". Così il governatore di Bankitalia, Panetta, nella sua prima Relazione annuale. Serve \"un piano credibile volto a stimolare crescita e produttività, volto a realizzare un graduale e costante miglioramento dei conti pubblici\".Bisogna mettere il rapporto debito/Pil \"su una traiettoria stabilmente discendente\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1717156808.6077757,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "BANKITALIA: \"PNRR CRUCIALE FOR CRESCITA\" Panetta: it serves a credible plan",
        "en_content": "Pnrr, Panetta: crucial for growth \"The full implementation of investments and reforms provided by the Pnrr-beyond raising the product of more than 2 percentage points in the short term would have lasting effects on growth due to estimated productivity gains between 3 and 6 points in a decade\". Thus the governor of Bankitalia, Panetta, in his first Annual Report. It serves \"a credible plan aimed at stimulating growth and productivity, aimed at achieving a gradual and constant improvement of public accounts\". The debt/Pil ratio must be put on a stablely descending trajectory.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CRUCIALE",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Panetta",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Panetta",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 2",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "between 3 and 6",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "a decade",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bankitalia",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Panetta",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Annual Report",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "USO ARMI, KIEV INCASSA ANCHE OK BERLINO Per impiegarle in territorio russo",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Germania, ok a Kiev uso armi in Russia Si allarga il fronte dei Paesi favorevoli all'uso delle armi Nato per colpire obiettivi in Russia. Anche Berlino dà il via libera agli ucraini per usare le armi ricevute, anche tedesche, contro obiettivi nel territorio russo.  In una nota il portavoce del cancelliere Scholz, Hebestreit, dichiara che la Germania autorizza gli ucraini a difendersi\"nel rispetto del diritto internazionale\" contro gli attacchi che arrivano da immediatamente oltre confine. E questo anche con le armi consegnate, \"comprese quelle fornite da noi\", spiega la nota.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1717156808.6138294,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "_ To use them in Russian territory",
        "en_content": "Germany, ok in Kiev use weapons in Russia It widens the front of NATO countries to target target targets in Russia. Berlin also gives way to Ukrainians to use weapons received, even German, against targets in the Russian territory. In a note the spokesman of Chancellor Scholz, Hebestreit, declares that Germany authorizes Ukrainians to defend themselves \"in accordance with international law\" against attacks that arrive immediately beyond the border. And this also with the weapons delivered, \"including those provided by us\", explains the note.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Berlin",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainians",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "German",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Scholz",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hebestreit",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainians",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISTAT: CRESCITA ACQUISITA PIL A +0,6%  Spingono famiglie e investimenti a",
        "date_raw": "May 31, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Istat: crescita acquisita Pil a +0,6% Nel primo trimestre il Pil,corretto pe gli effetti di calendario e destagiona lizzato, segna +0,3% sul trimestre pre cedente e +0,7% sullo stesso periodo 2023. Così l'Istat, che ha rivisto al rialzo (+0,6% da +0,5% a aprile)la cre scita acquisita per il 2024. Nel Def i governo previsto +1% di crescita annua Crescita spinta da consumi di famiglie e Isp(Istituzioni sociali private)e da gli investimenti,con contributo rispet tivo di +0,2% e +0,1%. Nullo l'apporto di spesa delle Amministrazioni pubbliche.       ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1717156808.6436656,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T14.00.08",
        "en_title": "ISTAT: CRESCITA ACQUISITA PIL A +0.6% Push families and investments to",
        "en_content": "Istat: GDP growth at +0.6% In the first trimester the GDP,correct for the effects of calendar and destagiona lized, marks +0.3% on the pre yielding quarter and +0.7% on the same period 2023. So the Istat, which reviewed the rise (+0.6% from +0.5% to April) the ski growth acquired for 2024. In the Def the planned government +1% of annual growth Growth boosted by consumption of households and private social institutions) and investments, with a return contribution of +0.2% and +0.1%. No public administration expenditure.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISTAT",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ACQUISITA PIL",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "destagiona lized",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.3%",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the pre yielding quarter",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.7%",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the same period 2023",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.5%",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 246,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "April",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "annual",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.2",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
