[
    {
        "title": "RAI, DAVIDE DI PIETRO RIELETTO NEL CDA  Come rappresentante dei dipendenti",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=127",
        "content": " Rai,Davide Di Pietro confermato nel Cda Davide Di Pietro è stato confermato  consigliere nel Cda della Rai in rappresentanza dei dipendenti. Su 6462 votanti ne ha ottenuti 2690. Alessandra Clementini 1950 voti, Pietro Muratori 1865. Gli aventi diritto al voto erano 11.131.      A Di Pietro le congratulazioni dell'Ad Rai Roberto Sergio: \"Ho avuto modo di apprezzare le sue doti ed il suo impegno, in questo semestre, in sostituzione del compianto Riccardo Laganà,  prematuramente scomparso. Buon lavoro, sempre a favore dei dipendenti tutti e dell'Azienda Rai\".    ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716285606.3662207,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "RAI, PIETRO DAVIDE IN THE CDA As employee representative",
        "en_content": "Rai,Davide Di Pietro confirmed in the Cda Davide Di Pietro was confirmed advisor in the Board of Rai representing the employees. On 6462 votes he obtained 2690. Alessandra Clementini 1950 votes, Pietro Muratori 1865. The voting rights were 11.131. To Di Pietro the congratulations of Ad Rai Roberto Sergio: \"I had the opportunity to appreciate his skills and his commitment, in this semester, replacing the late Riccardo Laganà, prematurely disappeared. Good job, always in favor of the employees all and the company Rai\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CDA",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Davide Di Pietro",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cda Davide Di Pietro",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Board of Rai",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "6462",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2690",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alessandra Clementini",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1950",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pietro Muratori",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1865",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "11.131",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 246,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Di Pietro",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ad Rai Roberto Sergio",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "this semester",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riccardo Laganà",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Le presidenziali il 28 giugno",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Iran, verso presidenziali il 28 giugno Le elezioni per eleggere il nuovo presidente dopo la morte di Ebraim Raisi sono programmate per il 28 giugno. Lo ha reso noto un funzionario della commissione elettorale, come riporta la Tass. Il termine è entro 50 giorni.  L'agenzia Isna conferma che il primo vicepresidente iraniano Mohammad  Mokhber, come prevede la Costituzione del Paese, assume le funzioni del presidente Ebrahim Raisi.   Un consiglio speciale composto da tre persone deve organizzare le nuove elezioni.      ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716285606.5663874,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "Presidential on 28 June",
        "en_content": "Iran, to presidential on June 28 The elections to elect the new president after the death of Ebraim Raisi are scheduled for June 28. It was announced by an official of the electoral commission, as the Tass reports. The deadline is within 50 days. The agency Isna confirms that the first Iranian Vice-President Mohammad Mokhber, as the Constitution of the Country provides, assumes the functions of President Ebrahim Raisi. A special council composed of three people must organize the new elections.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "28 June",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "June 28",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebraim Raisi",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "June 28",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the electoral commission",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "50 days",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isna",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohammad Mokhber",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Constitution of the Country",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CAPO STATO IN IRLANDA, INCONTRA HIGGINS Europa e M.O. tra i temi trattati",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Mattarella e Higgins parlano di Ue e MO Il presidente della Repubblica Sergio Mattarella ha incontrato il suo omologo irlandese Michael D.Higgins durante la sua visita di cortesia in Irlanda. I due capi di Stato hanno parlato in maniera informale dei principali dossier del momento come l'Ucraina, l'Unione Europea, la tragedia di Gaza e le connesse proteste studentesche e l'Iran dopo la morte del presidente Raisi.  Mattarella ha detto a Higgins che l'Ucraina spinge a \"rafforzare il nostro impegno per un ruolo sempre più incisivo dell'Unione Europea,attore di pace\".",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716285606.5825431,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "CHAPTER STATE IN IRELAND, MEETING HIGGINS Europe and M.O. among the topics covered",
        "en_content": "Mattarella and Higgins talk about Ue and MO The President of the Republic Sergio Mattarella met his Irish counterpart Michael D.Higgins during his courtesy visit to Ireland. The two heads of state spoke informally about the main dossiers of the moment such as Ukraine, the European Union, the Gaza tragedy and the associated student protests and Iran after the death of President Raisi. Mattarella told Higgins that Ukraine urges \"to strengthen our commitment to an increasingly incisive role of the European Union, actor of peace\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IRELAND",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "M.O.",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Higgins",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ue",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "MO",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Mattarella",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Irish",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michael D.Higgins",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 172,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Higgins",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 496,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Netanyahu:l'ordine è contro Israele",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Corte dell'Aja chiede arresto Netanyahu La Corte Penale Internazionale dell'Aja ha richiesto un mandato di arresto per il premier israeliano Netanyahu e il ministro della Difesa Gallant per presunti crimini di guerra. Richiesta di arresto anche per tre leader di Hamas, Sinwar, Mohammed Deif e Ismail Haniyeh. \"Il diritto internazionale si applica a tutti. Nessuno può agire impunemente\", ha detto il procuratore capo Khan. Il ministro israeliano Katz:\"Un attacco frontale alle vittime del 7 ottobre\". Per Hamas: \"Decisione della Corte equipara vittima al carnefice\".  ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716285606.6205676,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "Netanyahu: the order is against Israel",
        "en_content": "The International Criminal Court of Aja called for an arrest warrant for Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu and Defense Minister Gallant for alleged war crimes. Request for arrest also for three leaders of Hamas, Sinwar, Mohammed Deif and Ismail Haniyeh. \"International law applies to all. No one can act uncleanly,\" said Chief Prosecutor Khan. Israeli Minister Katz: \"A frontal attack on the victims of October 7\". For Hamas: \"Decision of the Court equates victim to the executioner.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aja",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinwar",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohammed Deif",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ismail Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khan",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 7",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Court",
                "start_char": 442,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MATTARELLA: CORDOGLIO PER MORTE RAISI  Meloni:\"Spero in futura ledership\"",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Mattarella: cordoglio per morte Raisi \"Esprimo il mio cordoglio per la morte del Presidente Ebrahim Raisi, del ministro degli Esteri Hossein Amir Abdollahian e di tutte le vittime della sciagura aerea che si è consumata nella giornata di ieri\", scrive Mattarella. La premier Meloni esprime \"solidarietà al governo e al popolo iraniano. Spero futura leadership s'impegni per stabilizzazione della regione\".   Il ministro degli Esteri Tajani:\"Ci auguriamo che la nuova dirigenza iraniana lavori per il dialogo\".   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716285606.713894,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Mattarella: \"I express my sympathy for the death of President Ebrahim Raisi, Foreign Minister Hossein Amir Abdollahian and all the victims of the air disaster that was consumed yesterday,\" writes Mattarella. Prime Minister Meloni expresses \"solidarity to the government and the Iranian people. I hope future leadership is committed to stabilizing the region.\" Foreign Minister Tajani: \"We hope that the new Iranian leadership will work for dialogue.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716285606.7854507,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RAISI,TAJANI:SERVE STABILITA'AREA,PACE  Auspicabili obiettivi per successore   Così ministro Esteri al Corsera",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Raisi,Tajani:serve stabilità area,pace Ci auguriamo che \"chi prenderà provvisoriamente il posto del presidente e chi poi vincerà alle prossime elezioni si impegni per la stabilità dell'area e per la pace\".Così il ministro degli Esteri Tajani al Corsera commentando la morte del presidente iraniano Raisi. Sulle polemiche per le condoglianze  fatte dal governo per Raisi, Tajani dice:\"Le condoglianze sono dovute alle modalità drammatiche dell'incidente,sono morte persone che avevano ruoli di governo.Il cordoglio è indipendente da giudizi politici sull'operato di Raisi\"",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716285606.8067272,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "RAISI,TAJANI:REA STABILITY,PACE Achievable goals for success So Foreign Minister at the Corsera",
        "en_content": "Raisi,Tajani:serve stability area,peace We hope that \"who will provisionally take the seat of the president and who will then win the next elections will commit themselves to the stability of the area and for peace\". So the Foreign Minister Tajani at the Corsera commented on the death of Iranian President Raisi. On the controversy over the condolences made by the government for Raisi, Tajani says: \"Condolences are due to the dramatic modes of the incident, people who had roles of government died. The Cordoglio is independent of political judgments on the work of Raisi\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "RAISI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "REA",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Corsera",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Corsera",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 307,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 381,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 394,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cordoglio",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 569,
                "end_char": 574,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "COSTRUZIONI, A MARZO PRODUZIONE -1,9%  Ma cresce la media del trimestre",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=135",
        "content": " Costruzioni,a marzo produzione -1,9% A marzo 2024 si stima che l'indice destagionalizzato della produzione nelle costruzioni diminuisca dell'1,9% rispetto a febbraio.    Nella media del primo trimestre del  del 2024, la produzione nelle costruzioni, al netto della stagionalità, aumenta in termini congiunturali dell' 1,5% nel confronto con il trimestre  precedente. Così l'Istat.   ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716285606.8200274,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "CONSTRUCTIONS, A MARCH PRODUCTION -1,9% But the average of the quarter",
        "en_content": "Construction in March production -1.9% In March 2024 it is estimated that the seasonal index of production in buildings decreased by 1.9% compared to February. On the average of the first quarter of 2024, production in buildings, net of seasonality, increases in conjunctural terms of 1.5% in comparison with the previous quarter. So Istat.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CONSTRUCTIONS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the quarter",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 2024",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "seasonal",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.9%",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "February",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the first quarter of 2024",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.5%",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the previous quarter",
                "start_char": 309,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Biden: Israele, nessun genocidio",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Netanyahu:l'ordine Cpi è contro Israele \"L'ordine assurdo e falso del pubblico ministero dell'Aja non è diretto solo contro premier e ministro della Difesa, ma contro l'intero Stato d'Israele\". E' la reazione di Netanyahu alla Corte. \"Respingo con disgusto il paragone del procuratore dell'Aja tra l'Israele democratico e gli assassini di massa di Hamas. -ha aggiuntoquesto è il nuovo antisemitismo,si è spostato dai campus all'Aja\".      Per il ministro della Difesa Gallant,la Corte,di cui \"Israele non riconosce l' autorità\",fa un \"parallelo disgustoso\" tra Israele e Hamas.    ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716285606.944403,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.06",
        "en_title": "Biden: Israel, no genocide",
        "en_content": "Netanyahu: order Cpi is against Israel \"The absurd and false order of the Aja prosecutor is not directed only against Prime Minister and Defense Minister, but against the entire State of Israel\". It's Netanyahu's reaction to the court. \"I repudiate with disgust the comparison of the Aja prosecutor between democratic Israel and the mass murderers of Hamas. - added this is the new anti-Semitism, moved from campuses to the Aja.\" For the Minister of Defense Gallant, the Court, of which \"Israel does not recognize the authority\", makes a \" disgusting paralytic\" between Israel and Hamas.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aja",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aja",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aja",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Court",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 488,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 576,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 581,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FINE MANDATO ZELENSKY,MOSCA: USURPATORE Cremlino:avanti operazione speciale",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Biden: Cpi vergognosa su leader Israele \"La richiesta del procuratore della  Corte penale internazionale di mandati di arresto contro i leader israeliani è vergognosa\".Così il presidente Usa Biden in una nota.    \"Non esiste alcuna equivalenza,nessuna, tra Israele e Hamas. Saremo sempre al fianco di Israele contro le minacce alla sua sicurezza\", assicura Biden.Il presidente esclude anche che l'offensiva di Israele a Gaza sia un\"genocidio\". Il segretario di Stato Blinken: \"Rifiutiamo l'equiparazione di Israele con Hamas\". E avverte: così a rischio le trattative per un cessate il fuoco. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716285607.0103374,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.07",
        "en_title": "ZELENSKY MANDATO FINE,MOSCA: USURPATORE Kremlin: advance special operation",
        "en_content": "Biden: Shame on leader Israel \"The request of the attorney of the international criminal court of arrest warrants against Israeli leaders is shameful.\" So US President Biden in a note. \"There is no equivalence between Israel and Hamas. We will always be alongside Israel against threats to its security,\" Biden says. The President also excludes that Israel's offensive in Gaza is a \"genocide\". Secretary of State Blinken: \"Let us reject Israel's equalization with Hamas.\" And warns: so at risk negotiations for a ceasefire.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MOSCA",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "USURPATORE Kremlin",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the international criminal court",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 420,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Droni russi su Kharkiv, danni",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Fine mandato Zelensky,Mosca: usurpatore Un \"usurpatore\" e un \"obiettivo militare legittimo\" per la Russia. Così l'ex presidente russo Medvedev ha definito Zelensky,che oggi conclude il suo mandato da presidente ucraino senza che si siano potute tenere le elezioni per una sua riconferma o per la scelta di un successore a causa della legge marziale Il Cremlino si è mostrato indifferente al problema istituzionale della fine del mandato di Zelensky,e sulle possibili conseguenze sull'andamento del  conflitto,il portavoce Peskov ha risposto: \"L'operazione speciale continua\". ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716285607.0165064,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.07",
        "en_title": "Russian drones on Kharkiv, damage",
        "en_content": "End mandate Zelensky,Moscow: usurper A \"usurper\" and a \"legitimate military target\" for Russia. So former Russian President Medvedev defined Zelensky, which today concludes his mandate as Ukrainian president without being able to hold elections for a reconfirm or for the choice of a successor due to martial law The Kremlin was indifferent to the institutional problem of the end of Zelensky's mandate, and the possible consequences of the conflict, the spokesman Peskov replied: \"Special operation continues.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Medvedev",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peskov",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAN, 5 GIORNI DI LUTTO PER MORTE RAISI Schianto velivolo, aperta inchiesta   I funerali il 23 maggio a Mashhad",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Raisi,corteo funebre a Tabriz e Teheran La cerimonia funebre per il presidente iraniano Raisi morto domenica in un incidente in elicottero,insieme al ministro degli Esteri Amir-Abdollahian,è iniziata con un corteo a Tabriz,capitale dell'Azerbaigian orientale.La salma poi sarà trasferita nella città santa di Qom e da lì nella capitale dove stasera l'Ayatollah Khamenei guiderà le preghiere in una cerimonia di addio.  Domani le processioni nella capitale e giovedì la salma di Raisi sarà trasferita a Mashhad,sua città natale per la sepoltura.In tutto 5 i giorni di lutto proclamati in Iran.    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716285607.0198185,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.07",
        "en_title": "IRAN, 5 LIGHT DAYS FOR MORTE RAISI Schianto aircraft, open investigation funeral on 23 May at Mashhad",
        "en_content": "Raisi, a funeral race in Tabriz and Tehran The funeral ceremony for Iranian President Raisi died on Sunday in a helicopter crash, along with Foreign Minister Amir-Abdollahian, began with a procession in Tabriz, capital of East Azerbaijan. The psalm will then be transferred to the holy city of Qom and from there to the capital where tonight the Ayatollah Khamenei will guide prayers in a farewell ceremony. Tomorrow the processions in the capital and Thursday the Psalm of Raisi will be transferred to Mashhad, his birthplace for the burial. In all 5 days of mourning proclaimed in Iran.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 LIGHT DAYS",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "23 May",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mashhad",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amir-Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Qom",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ayatollah Khamenei",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 460,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mashhad",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "all 5 days",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 587,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PNRR,FITTO:IN LINEA CON ROADMAP EUROPEA A Palazzo Chigi la Cabina di regia",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Pnrr,Fitto:in linea con roadmap europea \"La Cabina di regia di oggi conferma l'allineamento dell'Italia con la  roadmap europea del Pnrr\". Così il ministro per gli Affari europei, Sud, Politiche di coesione e Pnrr Fitto, al termine della riunione a Palazzo Chigi. \"Con l'avvio della rendicontazione degli obiettivi della sesta rata, il governo prosegue incessantemente nell' attuazione del Piano nazionale di ripresa e resilienza\", si legge in una nota.La riunione ha riguardato anche la copertura finanziaria di tutti gli interventi dei Piani Urbani Integrati. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716285607.0264657,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.07",
        "en_title": "PNRR,FITTO:IN LINE WITH EUROPEAN ROADMAP At Palazzo Chigi the Cabin of direction",
        "en_content": "Pnrr,Fitto: in line with European roadmap \"The Cabin of direction of today confirms the alignment of Italy with the European roadmap of the Pnrr\". So the Minister for European Affairs, South, Cohesion Policies and Pnrr Fitto, at the end of the meeting at Palazzo Chigi. \"With the start of the reporting of the objectives of the sixth installment, the government continues incessantly in the implementation of the National Resumption and Resilience Plan,\" reads in a note. The meeting also covered the financial cover of all the interventions of the Integrated Urban Plans.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "European Affairs",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pnrr Fitto",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "sixth",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Resumption and Resilience Plan",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Integrated Urban Plans",
                "start_char": 545,
                "end_char": 571,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "OGGI SCIOPERO TAXI DALLE 8 ALLE 22    \"No alla deregolamentazione\"",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Sciopero dei taxi,no deregolamentazione Sciopero nazionale dei taxi,oggi dalle 8 alle 22, con una manifestazione a  Roma, dalle 11 alle 17, a piazza San Silvestro.     \"E' fondamentale la partecipazione di tutta la categoria a difesa del proprio lavoro, per contrastare l'uso illegittimo delle autorizzazioni da noleggio e salvaguardare la propria autonomia e indipendenza dalla schiavitù degli algoritmi e delle multinazionale\", spiega un comunicato delle sigle sindacali. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716285607.0292122,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.07",
        "en_title": "OGGI SCIOPERO TAXI FROM 8 TO 22 \"No to deregulation\"",
        "en_content": "Taxi strike, no deregulation National strike of taxis, today from 8 to 22, with an event in Rome, from 11 to 17, in Piazza San Silvestro. \"It is essential to participate in the entire category to defend its work, to counter the illegitimate use of rental authorizations and to safeguard its autonomy and independence from the slavery of algorithms and multinationals,\" explains a communiqué of trade union law.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "OGGI SCIOPERO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "11 to 17",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza San Silvestro",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISTAT:MENO GIOVANI,MA RIPRESA POSSIBILE Il 69,4% desidera avere figli",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Istat:meno giovani,ma ripresa possibile Al 1°gennaio 2024 i residenti in Italia tra gli 11-19 anni sono 5 milioni 140 mila. Un numero destinato a diminuire nelle proiezioni demografiche.Tuttavia, dalle intenzioni degli intervistati una ripresa demografica sembra possibile nel Rapporto Istat \"Bambini e ragazzi\". Il 69,4% dei giovanissimi desidera avere figli, solo l'8,8% è per il figlio unico,il 18,2% pensa a tre o più figli. Il 34% dei ragazzi immagina un futuro all'estero.L'85% dei giovanissimi ha un profilo social.I ragazzi stranieri nati in Italia sono il 59,5%.   ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716285607.142743,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ 69.4% wishes to have children",
        "en_content": "Istat:less young people, but possible recovery At 1 January 2024 residents in Italy between 11-19 years are 5 million 140 thousand. A number intended to decrease in demographic projections. However, from the intentions of the respondents a demographic recovery seems possible in the Istat Report \"Children and boys\". 69.4% of young people want to have children, only 8.8% is for their only child, 18.2% thinks of three or more children. 34% of the boys imagine a future abroad. 85% of young people have a social profile.The foreign children born in Italy are 59.5%.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "69.4%",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1 January 2024",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "11-19 years",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 million 140 thousand",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Istat Report \"Children",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "69.4%",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "only 8.8%",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "18.2%",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "34%",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "85%",
                "start_char": 478,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 549,
                "end_char": 554,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "59.5%",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 564,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BOLOGNA-JUVE SHOW, CLAMOROSO 3-3",
        "date_raw": "May 21, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=201",
        "content": "     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716285607.1446462,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 12:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T12.00.07",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
