[
    {
        "title": "SALE LA FIDUCIA DEI CONSUMATORI     Istat: scende quella delle imprese",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Sale fiducia consumatori,ma non imprese Il clima di fiducia dei consumatori è salito a febbraio passando da 98,2 a 98,8, mentre l'indicatore composito del clima di fiducia delle imprese è sceso da 95,7 a 94,8.     E' quanto stima l'Istat, spiegando che tra i consumatori si evidenzia un miglioramento delle opinioni sulla situazione personale, corrente e futura. Ma peggiorano le valutazioni sulla situazione economica generale. Per quanto riguarda le imprese, l'Istat segnala un peggioramento in tutti i comparti indagati ad eccezione della manifattura. ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740693603.978372,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.03",
        "en_title": "SALE LA FIDUCIA DI CONSUMATORI Istat: down that of the enterprises",
        "en_content": "Consumer confidence rooms,but not enterprises The consumer confidence climate rose in February from 98.2 to 98.8, while the composite indicator of the confidence climate of enterprises fell from 95.7 to 94.8. This is what Istat estimates, explaining that among consumers there is an improvement of opinions on the personal, current and future situation. But the assessments of the general economic situation worsen. With regard to enterprises, Istat reports a worsening in all sectors investigated except manufacturing.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "February",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "98.2 to 98.8",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "95.7",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "94.8",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 444,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "3 mld di aiuti.Bonus sociale a 8mln",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Bollette:platea bonus sociale più ampia Alzare la soglia Isee del bonus sociale dagli attuali 9.530 euro a 25mila euro. E' questa, l'ipotesi di soluzione raggiunta al vertice di Palazzo Chigi in attesa del Decreto Bollette atteso in Consiglio dei Ministri.    Dovrebbe essere previsto un meccanismo a scaglioni in base al quale le fasce Isee più basse ricevano un aiuto più consistente: chi ha fino a 9.530 euro di Isee dovrebbe ricevere il bonus attuale e il nuovo, mentre da 9.530 a 25 mila solo il nuovo contributo.Il provvedimento prevederebbe 3 mld di aiuti. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.0028691,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "3 mld of aid. Social bonus at 8mln",
        "en_content": "Bullets: wider social bonus Raise the Isee threshold of the social bonus from current 9.530 euros to 25 thousand euros. This is the hypothesis of solution reached at the summit of Palazzo Chigi waiting for the Decree Bollette expected in the Council of Ministers. A scallops mechanism should be envisaged according to which the lower Isee bands receive a more substantial help: who has up to 9.530 euros of Isee should receive the current bonus and the new, while from 9.530 to 25 thousand only the new contribution. The measure would include 3 mld of aid.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "3 mld",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Isee",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "9.530 euros to 25 thousand euros",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Bollette",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council of Ministers",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Isee",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "9.530 euros",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isee",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "9.530",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "25 thousand",
                "start_char": 478,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 mld",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"INCINTA? PUO' DIMETTERSI\". E' BUFERA  Lascia consigliera FdI a Treviglio",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=127",
        "content": " Incinta?Può dimettersi.Ma lascia la FdI Silvia Colombo, consigliera comunale e capogruppo di FdI a Treviglio (Bergamo) ha annunciato le sue dimissioni. \"Torno a lavorare e a fare la mamma\".  La decisione dopo la polemica per le sue affermazioni a proposito di lavoro da remoto e gravidanza. Colombo era intervenuta sulla richiesta di una consigliera Pd di sedute in streaming per facilitare neo-genitori o chi ha gravidanze a rischio, affermando che se si è incinta ci si può dimettere. Colombo ha lamentato anche \"troppa leggerezza\" del suo partito nell'affrontare la vicenda.",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.0286174,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "\"INCINTA? _ It's BUFERA",
        "en_content": "Pregnant? You can resign. But he leaves the FdI Silvia Colombo, municipal councilman and FdI group leader in Treviglio (Bergamo) announced his resignation. \"I come back to work and be a mom.\" The decision after the controversy for his claims about remote work and pregnancy. Colombo had intervened on the request of a Pd board of streaming sessions to facilitate neo-parents or those with risky pregnancy, stating that if you are pregnant you can resign. Colombo also complained about his party's \"too much lightness\" in dealing with the affair.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "BUFERA",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Treviglio",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bergamo",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombo",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombo",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"DAZI PREOCCUPANO, UE ABBIA CORAGGIO\"  Orsini:agire subito,con una visione",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Orsini: dazi preoccupano, Ue agisca ora \"E' saltato un paradigma:serve coraggio e agire subito con una visione di lungo termine.L'Europa deve mettere al centro la competitività del sistema industriale e quindi la crescita sociale\".  Il presidente di Confindustria, Orsini, ribadisce la necessità di agire, dopo l'annuncio dei dazi sulle merci Ue da parte dell'amministrazione Trump.  \"La preoccupazione è innegabile.  Abbiamo solo una possibilità: cambiare subito con misure straordinarie per un momento straordinario\".   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.036417,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "Orsini: act immediately, with a vision",
        "en_content": "Orsini: duties worry, EU acts now \"A paradigm has jumped: it serves courage and act immediately with a long-term vision. Europe must focus on the competitiveness of the industrial system and therefore social growth.\" The president of Confindustria, Orsini, reiterates the need to act, after the announcement of the duties on goods EU by the Trump administration. \"The concern is undeniable. We have only one possibility: change immediately with extraordinary measures for an extraordinary moment.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Orsini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Orsini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Confindustria",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orsini",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FONTANA: DATI SU SANITA' INACCETTABILI  Governatore:Lombardia è la migliore",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Fontana: dati su Sanità inaccettabili Il presidente della Lombardia, Fontana, giudica \"inaccettabile\" la classifica del ministero della Salute sulla qualità di cura delle Regioni. \"I parametri indicati non hanno niente a che vedere con il funzionamento della Sanità\".  Nei dati diffusi ieri, la Lombardia è al settimo posto. \"L'importante è che il Niguarda sia il migliore ospedale d'Italia e tra i primi 10 altri 5 sono lombardi.La Lombardia è la migliore,per questo dà fastidio. Da Roma continui attacchi ingiustificati\",dice Fontana. Replica il ministero: \"Dal governatore linguaggio inopportuno\".a   ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.0431333,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "FONTANA: DATA SU SANITA' INACCETTABILI Governor:Lombardy is the best",
        "en_content": "Fontana: data on unacceptable health The president of Lombardy, Fontana, judges \"unacceptable\" the ranking of the Ministry of Health on the quality of care of the Regions. \"The parameters indicated have nothing to do with the functioning of Health.\" In the data reported yesterday, Lombardy is in seventh place. \"The important thing is that Niguarda is the best hospital in Italy and among the top 10 other 5 are Lombards. Lombardy is the best, for this it bothers. From Rome continue unjustified attacks\", says Fontana. Replica the ministry: \"From the governor inappropriate language.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FONTANA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "SU SANITA'",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "INACCETTABILI",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombardy",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Fontana",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombardy",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fontana",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Health",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Health",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombardy",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "seventh",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Niguarda",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 other 5",
                "start_char": 398,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombards",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombardy",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 475,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fontana",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 519,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PAPA,CONDIZIONI ANCORA IN MIGLIORAMENTO \"Stabilità per sciogliere prognosi\"",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740693604.0588257,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI VEDE KAPLAN SU INVESTIMENTI META \"Temi legati a tecnologia e IA\"",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Meloni vede Kaplan su investimenti Meta La premier Meloni ha incontrato a  Palazzo Chigi Joel Kaplan, capo degli Affari globali di Meta. Lo riferisce una nota.      Il colloquio s'inserisce \"in un ciclo d'incontri mirati a discutere i temi legati alla transizione tecnologica e allo sviluppo dell'intelligenza artificiale\", spiega la nota.    \"Tra i punti all'ordine del giorno, la possibilità di valorizzare le attività già esistenti sul territorio italiano e valutare nuovi investimenti\".  ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.0691862,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "MELONI VEDE KAPLAN ON METAL INVESTMENTS \"Technology and IA themes\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni sees Kaplan on investments Meta Premier Meloni met at Palazzo Chigi Joel Kaplan, Head of Global Affairs of Meta. It's a note. The interview is \"in a series of meetings aimed at discussing issues related to the technological transition and the development of artificial intelligence\", explains the note. \"Among the points on the agenda, the possibility of enhancing the existing activities on the Italian territory and evaluating new investments\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kaplan",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meta",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi Joel Kaplan",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Global Affairs of Meta",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCHLEIN: MELONI AVALLA DISGREGAZIONE UE \"E scappa su Paragon,Cutro,Almasri\"",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Schlein: Meloni avalla disgregazione Ue \"Gaza appartiene ai palestinesi e i miliardi di Musk e Trump non possono comprarla\". Così la segretaria Pd Schlein, alla direzione del partito, che bolla come \"ignobile\" il video di Trump. In Ucraina \"umiliati gli aggrediti,riabilitati gli aggressori.Per niente condivisibili le parole di Trump\".Sostegno a Kiev,ma serve \"maggiore sforzo diplomatico europeo\".Anche ieri il presidente Usa ha attaccato l'Ue.Meloni \"è vassalla di un progetto di disgregazione europea\". Inoltre, \"scappa su Paragon, Cutro,Almasri.Cosa nasconde?\". Auguri e applauso della direzione per il Papa. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.094987,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "SCHLEIN: MELONI AVALLATION EU DISGREGATION \"And escapes on Paragon,Cutro,Almasri\"",
        "en_content": "Schlein: \"Gaza belongs to the Palestinians and the billions of Musk and Trump cannot buy it.\" So the secretary Pd Schlein, at the party's direction, who bubbles as \"ignoble\" Trump's video. In Ukraine \"humiliated the attacked, rehabilitated the aggressors. Trump's words cannot be shared at all.\" Supporting Kiev, but it serves \"more European diplomatic effort\". Even yesterday US President attacked the EU.Meloni \"is a vassal of a European disintegration project\". Also, \"scappa su Paragon, Cutro,Almasri. What's he hiding?\" Wishes and applause of the direction for the Pope.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Paragon,Cutro",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd Schlein",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 333,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 439,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "scappa su Paragon",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cutro",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL BOLLETTE,AIUTO A FAMIGLIE E IMPRESE  Concluso il vertice di maggioranza",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Governo:in dl bollette aiuto a famiglie \"Verrà adottato un pacchetto di misure che va incontro alle esigenze delle famiglie e delle imprese italiane,garantendo un sostegno concreto in un momento di difficoltà economica legato all' aumento dei costi energetici\" e \"il Governo continuerà a lavorare parallelamente per ulteriori iniziative di medio e lungo periodo che possano rafforzare il sistema nel suo complesso\".  E' quanto si apprende al termine del vertice a Palazzo Chigi sul decreto  contro il caro-bollette che sarà varato domani dal Consiglio dei ministri.  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.0995204,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "DL BOLLETTE, FAMILY AID AND IMPRESE The majority summit concluded",
        "en_content": "Government: in the bills help to families \"A package of measures will be adopted that meets the needs of Italian families and enterprises, guaranteeing concrete support at a time of economic difficulty linked to the increase of energy costs\" and \"the government will continue to work parallelly for further medium and long-term initiatives that can strengthen the system as a whole\". It is what is learned at the end of the summit at Palazzo Chigi on the decree against the caro-bollette that will be launched tomorrow by the Council of Ministers.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IMPRESE",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 510,
                "end_char": 518,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council of Ministers",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Coccarda Tricolore e Carta in mano",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Sciopero toghe, Anm: \"Alta l'adesione\" \"Ci stanno arrivando dati su un'alta partecipazione allo sciopero, di assemblee molto partecipate\". Così il segretario Anm Maruotti, nell'assemblea al cinema Adriano a Roma nel giorno dello sciopero delle toghe contro la riforma sulla separazione delle carriere.  A Milano, si parla del 90% di adesione, a Palermo del 70%, a Genova del 95%. A Roma, flash mob sulla scalinata della Cassazione, con magistrati con le toghe, coccarda Tricolore e una copia  della Costituzione in mano.  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.1047719,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "Coccarda Tricolore e Carta in mano",
        "en_content": "Toghe strike, Anm: \"High membership\" \"We are getting data on a high participation in the strike, of very participated assemblies\". Thus the secretary Anm Maruotti, in the assembly at the cinema Adriano in Rome on the day of the strike of toghe against the reform on the separation of careers. In Milan, we talk about 90% of the membership, in Palermo of 70%, in Genoa of 95%. In Rome, flash mob on the steps of the Cassation, with magistrates with toghe, Tricolore coccarda and a copy of the Constitution in hand.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Coccarda Tricolore e Carta",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "mano",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Toghe",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anm",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anm Maruotti",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Adriano",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 90%",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Palermo",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "70%",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "95%",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 379,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cassation",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GOVERNO:APERTI A DIALOGO CON MAGISTRATI Vertice a P.Chigi sulla Giustizia",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Governo:aperti a dialogo con magistrati La maggioranza conferma \"la propria disponibilità a un confronto costruttivo, con particolare attenzione al dialogo con l'Anm. La riforma della giustizia non è concepita contro i magistrati, ma nell'interesse dei cittadini\".E' quanto emerso dal vertice di governo, a Palazzo Chigi.      La premier Meloni incontrerà l'Anm il 5 marzo. In quella data avrà anche una riunione con l'Unione delle Camere penali. Il vertice a Palazzo Chigi è stato finalizzato alla preparazione  dei due incontri.    ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.110088,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "GOVERNMENT: OPENING DIALOGUE WITH MAGISTERed Summit in P.C. on Justice",
        "en_content": "Government:open to dialogue with magistrates The majority confirms \"its availability to a constructive comparison, with particular attention to the dialogue with the Am. The reform of justice is not conceived against the magistrates, but in the interests of citizens.\" This is what emerged from the government summit at Palazzo Chigi. Premier Meloni will meet the Am on March 5. On that date you will also have a meeting with the Union of Criminal Chambers. The summit at Palazzo Chigi was aimed at preparing the two meetings.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "P.C.",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Justice",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 5",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Union of Criminal Chambers",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Idf:restiamo in corridoio Filadelfia156  OCALAN A PKK:DEPORRE ARMI E SCIOGLIERSI Appello del leader curdo da carcere",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Ocalan a Pkk:deporre armi e sciogliersi Il fondatore del Partito dei lavoratori del Kurdistan (Pkk), Ocalan, chiede al gruppo di deporre le armi e sciogliersi. Lo storico appello è arrivato dalla prigione di Imrali, in Turchia, dove il leader curdo è rinchiuso dal 1999. \"Il Pkk ha esaurito il suo ciclo. Mi assumo la responsabilità dinanzi alla storia di questo appello. Ringrazio coloro che credono nei turchi e curdi che vivono fianco a fianco e quanti non  vedevano l'ora che arrivasse la pace\", scrive Ocalan, tentando di porre fine a un conflitto che dura da oltre 40 anni.",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740693604.1277537,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "Idf: Retreat in the corridor Philadelphia156 OCALAN To PKK: DEPORRE ARMI And SCIOGLIERSI Appeal of Kurdish leader from prison",
        "en_content": "Ocalan to Pkk:to lay weapons and dissolve The founder of the Kurdistan Workers' Party (Pkk), Ocalan, asks the group to lay down their weapons and dissolve. The historic appeal came from Imrali prison, Turkey, where Kurdish leader has been locked up since 1999. \"The Pkk has exhausted its cycle. I assume responsibility for the history of this appeal. I thank those who believe in the Turks and Kurds who live side by side and those who did not see the time for peace,\" writes Ocalan, trying to end a conflict that lasts for over 40 years.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "PKK",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SCIOGLIERSI",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kurdish",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Kurdistan Workers' Party (Pkk",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ocalan",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Imrali",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kurdish",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "1999",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turks",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kurds",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ocalan",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 482,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 40 years",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 537,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AL VIA I DAZI USA A MESSICO,CANADA,CINA Trump: dal 4 marzo, del 25% e 10%",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Trump:al via dazi a Messico,Canada,Cina Dal 4 marzo scatteranno i dazi del 25% contro Messico e Canada e del 10% contro la Cina. Lo ha annunciato il presidente Usa, Donald Trump.   \"Continuano ad arrivare nel nostro Paese fiumi di droghe dal Messico e dal Canada.Gran parte,sotto forma di Fentanil, sono fornite dalla Cina\", scrive Trump sul suo social. \"Oltre 100mila persone sono morte lo scorso anno per questi veleni. Imporremo dazi finché questo flagello non si fermerà\".  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740693604.1672904,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "AL VIA I DAZI USA A MESSICO,CANADA,CINA Trump: from March 4, 25% and 10%",
        "en_content": "Trump: Off duties in Mexico,Canada,China From March 4, they will split duties of 25% against Mexico and Canada and 10% against China. President Donald Trump announced that. \"They keep coming to our country rivers of drugs from Mexico and Canada. Much, in the form of Fentanil, are provided by China\", writes Trump on his social. \"Over 100 thousand people died last year for these poisons. We will impose duties until this scourge stops.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MESSICO",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "CANADA",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 4",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "10%",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 4",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10%",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fentanil",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Over 100 thousand",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "last year",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"DOMANI FIRMERO' ACCORDO SU TERRE RARE\" Casa Bianca, Trump incontra Starmer",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740693604.1798418,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "\"Women I'm going to make an AGREEMENT ON THREE RARE\" White House, Trump meets Starmer",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "THREE",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ANM: \"SCIOPERO A DIFESA COSTITUZIONE\"  Toghe contro separazione carriere",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Anm:\"E' sciopero a difesa Costituzione\" \"Non è uno sciopero contro qualcuno ma a difesa di una serie di principi della Costituzione in cui fermamente crediamo e che sono fondamentali per i cittadini\", ha detto Parodi, presidente dell' Anm,a Radio24 a proposito dello sciopero di oggi dei magistrati contro la separazione delle carriere.\"Ci aspettiamo numeri soddisfacenti di adesione\". \"E' tutto fuorché una difesa di casta. Noi non difendiamo nessun privilegio\", ha spiegato Parodi,sottolineando il\"rischio che il pm possa essere condizionato dai poteri forti e questo sarebbe l'aspetto più negativo per i cittadini\"",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740693604.1862102,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ Toghe against career separation",
        "en_content": "Anm: \"It's a defense strike Constitution\" \"It is not a strike against someone but in defense of a series of principles of the Constitution in which we firmly believe and which are fundamental to citizens,\" said Parodi, president of Anm,a Radio24 on today's strike of magistrates against the separation of careers. \"We expect satisfactory numbers of membership.\" \"It's all but a caste defense. We do not defend any privilege\", Parodi explained, underlining the \"risk that the pm can be conditioned by strong powers and this would be the most negative aspect for citizens\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Toghe",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parodi",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anm",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parodi",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "HAIFA,AUTO SU FOLLA.\"UCCISO TERRORISTA\" Dieci israeliani feriti, tre gravi",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Haifa,auto su folla:\"Ucciso terrorista\" Un'auto ha travolto alcune persone ad Haifa, nel Nord d'Israele, mentre erano alla fermata di un bus. Almeno 10 sono rimaste ferite, tre in modo grave. Lo ha reso noto la polizia, parlando di \"attacco terroristico\".   La polizia ha intercettato il veicolo e ha poi annunciato di aver \"ucciso il terrorista\". Si tratta di un arabo israeliano di 24 anni, originario dei pressi di Haifa.     ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740693604.2062783,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "Ten Israelis wounded, three serious",
        "en_content": "Haifa, car on crowd: \"Uccid terrorist\" A car overwhelmed some people in Haifa, Northern Israel, while they were at the bus stop. At least 10 were injured, three were severely injured. The police reported it, talking about \"terror attack\". The police intercepted the vehicle and announced that they \"killed the terrorist.\" It is a 24-year-old Israeli Arab, originally from Haifa.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ten",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israelis",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Haifa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haifa",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Northern Israel",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "At least 10",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "24-year-old",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haifa",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MOSCA:\"SU TERRE OCCUPATE NON TRATTIAMO\" \"Parti indivisibili della Russia\"",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Mosca:\"Su terre occupate non trattiamo\" I territori occupati in Ucraina sono una parte \"indivisibile\" della Russia e quindi non saranno soggetti a trattative. Lo ha precisato il portavoce del Cremlino, Peskov.     Commentando la decisione di Trump sui dazi all'Ue, Peskov ha detto: \"Non vorremmo vedere guerre commerciali nel  mondo perché in un modo o nell'altro questo avrà un impatto negativo su tutti\".E poi:Trump è disposto ad ascoltare gli altri, a differenza di Biden, ed è \"una caratteristica molto importante che distingue\" le due amministrazioni. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740693604.2122257,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Moscow: \"On occupied lands we do not treat\" The territories occupied in Ukraine are a \"indivisible\" part of Russia and therefore will not be subject to negotiations. The Kremlin spokesman, Peskov. Commenting on Trump's decision on EU duties, Peskov said: \"We do not want to see trade wars in the world because in one way or another this will have a negative impact on all\". And then:Trump is willing to listen to others, unlike Biden, and is \"a very important feature that distinguishes\" the two administrations.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Peskov",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Peskov",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 428,
                "end_char": 433,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"DOMANI FIRMERO' ACCORDO SU TERRE RARE\" Casa Bianca, Trump incontra Starmer",
        "date_raw": "February 27, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Trump incontra Starmer:un uomo speciale Ricevendo il premier britannico Starmer il presidente Usa Trump dice:\"E'un onore averlo qui. E' un uomo speciale\". In Ucraina è necessario un accordo per il cessate il fuoco,prima di parlare di forze di pace,dice Trump.\"Non credo che Putin violerà la sua parola\" su un accordo. Ribadisce il no all'adesione di Kiev alla Nato e assicura che domani firmerà l'intesa sulle terre rare con Zelensky,sostenendo che è una garanzia di sicurezza per Kiev.\"Dazi reciproci, non ci piace come ci tratta la Ue\". La Brexit fu una cosa positiva. Infine,Zelensky dittatore? \"L'ho detto io?\"  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740693604.2798638,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-27 23:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-27T22.00.04",
        "en_title": "\"Women I'm going to make an AGREEMENT ON THREE RARE\" White House, Trump meets Starmer",
        "en_content": "Trump meets Starmer: a special man Receiving the British Premier Starmer US President Trump says: \"It's an honor to have him here. He's a special man.\" In Ukraine it is necessary an agreement for the ceasefire, before speaking of peace forces, says Trump.\"I don't think Putin will violate his word\" on an agreement. He reiterates the no to the accession of Kiev to NATO and assures that tomorrow he will sign the agreement on rare lands with Zelensky, stating that it is a security guarantee for Kiev.\"Dazi reciproci, we do not like how it treats the EU\". Brexit was a good thing. Finally,Zelensky dictator? \"I said that?\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "THREE",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 361,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 442,
                "end_char": 450,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 496,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 551,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brexit",
                "start_char": 556,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 589,
                "end_char": 597,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    }
]
