[
    {
        "title": "AUTO ELETTRICHE NEL MIRINO ANTITRUST   Pratiche commerciali scorrette?",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Auto elettriche nel mirino Antitrust L'Antitrust ha avviato 4 istruttorie nei confronti di BYD Industria Italia, Stellantis Europe, Tesla Italy e  Volkswagen Group Italia per possibili pratiche commerciali scorrette.  Le istruttorie riguardano le informazioni fornite ai consumatori sulla autonomia di percorrenza chilometrica dei veicoli elettrici, sulla perdita di capacità della batteria e sulle informazioni relative alle limitazioni di operabilità della garanzia sulle  batterie.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.1474195,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "ELECTRICAL CAR IN MIRINO ANTITRUST Unfair commercial practices?",
        "en_content": "Electric cars in the Antitrust viewfinder L'Antitrust has started 4 investigations against BYD Industria Italia, Stellantis Europe, Tesla Italy and Volkswagen Group Italia for possible incorrect commercial practices. The investigations concern the information provided to consumers about the mileage of electric vehicles, the loss of battery capacity and the information regarding the operating restrictions of the warranty on batteries.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Antitrust",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "L'Antitrust",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "BYD Industria Italia",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Stellantis Europe",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tesla Italy",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volkswagen Group Italia",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Netanyahu: faremo i conti con Hamas",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Netanyahu: faremo i conti con Hamas  \"Fratelli e sorelle, cari cittadini di Israele, oggi siamo tutti uniti nel  dolore insopportabile. Abbassiamo la testa per la pesante perdita dei nostri 4 ostaggi\": così il premier Netanyahu. \"Tutti noi soffriamo con un dolore mescolato a rabbia -continuaSiamo  tutti furiosi con le bestie di Hamas.Le 4 bare dei nostri cari ci obbligano a giurare che ciò che è accaduto il 7/10 non accadrà mai più. Faremo i conti con gli assassini infami.Riporteremo a casa tutti i nostri, elimineremo Hamas e  insieme garantiremo il nostro futuro\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740132004.1728294,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "Netanyahu: we will deal with Hamas",
        "en_content": "Netanyahu: we will deal with Hamas \"Brothers and sisters, dear citizens of Israel, today we are all united in unbearable pain. We put our heads down for the heavy loss of our 4 hostages\": So Prime Minister Netanyahu. \"All of us suffer with a pain mixed with anger - we are all furious with the beasts of Hamas. The 4 coffins of our loved ones force us to swear that what happened on 7/10 will never happen again. We'll deal with the infamous killers. We will bring all ours home, eliminate Hamas and together we will guarantee our future.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "7/10",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 387,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 490,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TEL AVIV, BOMBE SU CINQUE BUS VUOTI   Nessun ferito.Blitz in Cisgiordania",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Tel Aviv, bombe su 5 bus:ne esplodono 3 Due autobus sono esplosi nella periferia di Tel Aviv, poco dopo ne è esploso un terzo. I mezzi erano vuoti e non ci sarebbero feriti. La polizia israeliana ha parlato di un possibile attacco terroristico coordinato. Altre bombe sono state trovate su altri due autobus a Holon, ma sono state disinnescate. Secondo il capo della Polizia erano simili a dispositivi che di solito vengono fabbricati in Cisgiordania. Si cercano i responsabili. Netanyahu ha  convocato un incontro per discutere  della situazione.Israele intensifica le operazioni militari in Cisgiordania. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740132004.1774619,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "TEL AVIV, BOMBE ON CINQUE BUS VUOTI No injuries.Blitz in West Bank",
        "en_content": "Tel Aviv, bombs on 5 buses:exploding 3 Two buses exploded in the outskirts of Tel Aviv, a third exploded shortly after. The means were empty and there wouldn't be hurt. The Israeli police spoke of a possible coordinated terrorist attack. Other bombs were found on two other buses in Holon, but were disconnected. According to the police chief they were similar to devices that are usually manufactured in the West Bank. They're looking for managers. Netanyahu convened a meeting to discuss the situation. Israel intensifies military operations in the West Bank.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "TEL AVIV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West Bank",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tel Aviv",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 Two",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tel Aviv",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Holon",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 405,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 511,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 560,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Cina: si apre finestra per la pace",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Cina: finestra per la pace in Ucraina Il ministro degli Esteri cinese Wang Yi ha detto che \"si sta aprendo una  finestra per la pace\" in Ucraina, dopo i colloqui tra Stati Uniti e Russia a Riad.       \"La Cina sostiene tutti gli sforzi profusi per la pace\", ha aggiunto Wang, auspicando un dialogo verso \"soluzioni sostenibili e durature che tengano conto delle reciproche preoccupazioni\".",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740132004.179347,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "China: opens window for peace",
        "en_content": "China: window for peace in Ukraine Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi said that \"it is opening a window for peace\" in Ukraine, after talks between the United States and Russia at Riad. \"China supports all efforts for peace,\" Wang added, calling for a dialogue on \"sustainable and lasting solutions that take into account mutual concerns.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wang Yi",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riad",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wang",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UE A TRUMP: \"KIEV DEMOCRAZIA, MOSCA NO\" \"Zelensky eletto con voto libero\"",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Ue: Zelensky eletto in votazioni libere \"Abbiamo una posizione chiara: il presidente ucraino è stato legittimamente eletto in elezioni libere, eque e democratiche\". E' la presa di posizione  della Ue dopo l'attacco di Trump a Zelensky, definito \"un dittatore mai eletto\".      \"L'Ucraina è una democrazia. La Russia di Putin non lo è\", così il portavoce della Commissione europea Keersmaecker, rispondendo alla stampa sul duro attacco del presidente degli Stati Uniti al leader dell'Ucraina.    ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740132004.1821606,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "EU at TRUMP: \"KIEV DEMOCRAZIA, MOSCA NO\" \"Zelensky elected with free vote\"",
        "en_content": "EU: Zelensky elected in free vote \"We have a clear position: the Ukrainian president was legitimately elected in free, fair and democratic elections.\" It's the position of the EU after Trump's attack on Zelensky, called \"a dictator never elected.\" \"Ukraine is a democracy. Putin's Russia is not,\" said the European Commission spokesman Keersmaecker, responding to the press on the hard attack of the President of the United States to the leader of Ukraine.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "TRUMP",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "KIEV",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "MOSCA",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 278,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Keersmaecker",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GB PROPONE INVIO TRUPPE EUROPEE A KIEV  Mosca:no a militari Nato in Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Gb proporrà a Usa invio soldati a Kiev Il premier britannico Starmer presenterà al presidente Usa Trump un piano che prevede l'invio di circa 30mila soldati europei in Ucraina per mantenere un  eventuale accordo di cessate il fuoco mediato dagli Usa.Lo riferisce il Telegraph, secondo cui Starmer presenterà il piano a Trump durante un incontro a Washington la prossima settimana. Starmer riferirà a Trump come queste truppe potrebbero far rispettare la tregua. Ma è già arrivato il no di Mosca con la \"preoccupazione\" del Cremlino per \"contingenti della Nato in Ucraina\".  ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740132004.1995351,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "GB PROPONE INVIDUAL TRUPPE At KIEV Moscow:no to military Born in Ukraine",
        "en_content": "Gb will propose to Usa sending soldiers to Kiev The British Premier Starmer will present to US President Trump a plan that previews the sending of about 30 thousand European soldiers in Ukraine to maintain a possible agreement of ceasefire mediated by the US. The Telegraph reports that Starmer will present Trump's plan during a meeting in Washington next week. Starmer will report to Trump how these troops could enforce the truce. But the no of Moscow has already arrived with the \"preoccupation\" of the Kremlin for \"contingents of NATO in Ukraine\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GB PROPONE INVIDUAL",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "KIEV Moscow",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 30 thousand",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegraph",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next week",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 361,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 386,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 539,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISRAELE: CORPO NON E' DI SHIRI BIBAS   Salma consegnata non è madre bimbi",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Israele: corpo non è di Shiri Bibas  Israele ha accusato il movimento  palestinese Hamas di aver ucciso i bambini Ariel e Kfir Bibas durante la loro prigionia a Gaza e di aver  consegnato il corpo di una persona sconosciuta invece di quello della madre Shiri, di origine argentina. Shiri e i suoi figli Ariel e Kfir, che avevano quattro anni e otto mesi quando furono rapiti il 7 ottobre 2023, erano diventati un simbolo degli ostaggi presi da Hamas. Il padre, anch'egli  rapito, è stato rilasciato il primo  febbraio.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740132004.2453232,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Israel: The body is not of Shiri Bibas Israel accused the Palestinian movement Hamas of killing the children Ariel and Kfir Bibas during their captivity in Gaza and having delivered the body of an unknown person instead of that of the mother Shiri, of Argentine origin. Shiri and his sons Ariel and Kfir, who were four years and eight months old when they were kidnapped on October 7, 2023, had become a symbol of the hostages taken by Hamas. The father, also kidnapped, was released on February 1st.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shiri Bibas",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir Bibas",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shiri",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shiri",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir",
                "start_char": 299,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "four years",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight months old",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 7, 2023",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 436,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "February 1st",
                "start_char": 487,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "USA: NO RISOLUZIONE ONU SOSTEGNO A KIEV Mosca non è \"aggressore\" in Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Usa: Russia non è \"aggressore\" Ucraina Gli Stati Uniti si oppongono alla  ipotesi di definire la Russia Paese  \"aggressore\" in una dichiarazione del G7 in occasione dell'anniversario dell' invasione dell'Ucraina da parte di Mosca. Lo scrive il Financial Times. Secondo Reuters, Washington si oppone anche a una risoluzione Onu di sostegno all'Ucraina e condanna per la Russia. Intanto il segretario al Tesoro statunitense Scott Bessent ha affermato che durante il negoziato potrebbe essere discusso un alleggerimento delle sanzioni per Mosca poiché potrebbe essere un modo per porre fine alla guerra. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740132004.2669132,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "USA: NO SUPPORT UN RESOLUTION TO KIEV Moscow is not \"aggressor\" in Ukraine",
        "en_content": "Use: Russia is not \"aggressor\" Ukraine The United States opposes the hypothesis of defining Russia Country \"aggressor\" in a declaration of the G7 on the anniversary of the invasion of Ukraine by Moscow. The Financial Times writes it. According to Reuters, Washington also opposes an UN resolution to support Ukraine and condemn Russia. Meanwhile, U.S. Secretary of the Treasury Scott Bessent said that during the negotiation, a relief of sanctions could be discussed for Moscow because it could be a way to end the war.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Financial Times",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Reuters",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Treasury",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Scott Bessent",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISRAELE: CORPO NON E' DI SHIRI BIBAS   Tel Aviv, bombe su cinque bus vuoti",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740132004.2690625,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "NOTTE TRASCORSA BENE PER PAPA FRANCESCO Condizioni in lieve miglioramento    Ravasi: se limiti,potrebbe lasciare",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740132004.2944462,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "NEWS TRASCORSA BEN FOR FRANCESCO PAPA Conditions in mild improvement Ravasi: if limits, could leave",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FRANCESCO PAPA Conditions",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ravasi",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CASO COSPITO, CONDANNA PER DELMASTRO   Meloni: Delmastro resta al suo posto   Anm: sconcerta l'attacco ai giudici",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740132004.3011618,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ Delmastro remains in his place Anm: the attack against the judges",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anm",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI A TRUDEAU: \"ITALIA PER LA PACE\"  \"Fermare il conflitto in Ucraina\"",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Meloni a Trudeau: \"Italia per la pace\" \"Il presidente del Consiglio ha ribadito che la priorità per l'Italia è la stessa del resto d'Europa, dell'Alleanza Atlantica e di Kiev: fare il possibile per fermare il conflitto e raggiungere la pace\". Questo afferma una nota di Palazzo Chigi dopo la telefonata fra la premier Giorgia Meloni e il primo ministro canadese e presidente di turno del G7 Justin Trudeau.  \"L'Italia, insieme agli Stati Uniti e ai suoi partner europei e occidentali, lavora per una pace duratura in Europa\" e per assicurare garanzie all'Ucraina. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.3067956,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Meloni in Trudeau: \"Italy for Peace\" \"The President of the Council reiterated that the priority for Italy is the same as the rest of Europe, the Atlantic Alliance and Kiev: do everything possible to stop the conflict and reach peace\". This says a note of Palazzo Chigi after the call between Premier Giorgia Meloni and Canadian Prime Minister and G7 President Justin Trudeau. \"Italy, together with the United States and its European and Western partners, works for lasting peace in Europe\" and to ensure guarantees to Ukraine.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trudeau",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy for Peace",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The President of",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Atlantic Alliance",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 314,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Justin Trudeau",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 398,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 482,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IL DECRETO MILLEPROROGHE E' LEGGE    Tra novità la rottamazione quater",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Sì Camera al Dl Milleproroghe, è legge La Camera ha approvato con 165 sì, 105 no, 3 astenuti il Decreto Milleproroghe Con il via libera dell'Aula di Montecitorio il Dl è legge. Ieri il sì alla fiducia posta dal governo nel testo  identico a quello licenziato dal Senato Tra le novità nel Decreto legge: riammissione, con condizioni, alla 'rottamazione quater' per i contribuenti che avevano aderito all'operazione,ma erano decaduti dal beneficio fiscale per mancato, insufficiente o tardivo versamento delle rate.     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.311658,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "The MILLEPROROGUED DECREATE Among novelties the quater scrap",
        "en_content": "Yes Chamber at the Dl Milleproroghe, is the law The Chamber has approved with 165 yes, 105 no, 3 abstained the Decreto Milleproroghe With the free way of the House of Montecitorio the Dl is law. Yesterday the yes to the trust placed by the government in the text identical to that dismissed by the Senate Among the novelties in the Decree Law: the 'quater hijacking' for the taxpayers who had joined the operation, but had fallen from the tax benefit for failure, insufficient or late payment of the installments.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Dl Milleproroghe",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "165",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "105",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Decreto Milleproroghe",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the House of Montecitorio the Dl",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yesterday",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Decree Law: the 'quater",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AUTO ELETTRICHE NEL MIRINO ANTITRUST   Pratiche commerciali scorrette?",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740132004.313633,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "ELECTRICAL CAR IN MIRINO ANTITRUST Unfair commercial practices?",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "Nordio: \"Disorientato e addolorato\"",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Condanna Delmastro,Nordio:disorientato \"Sono disorientato e addolorato per  una condanna che colpisce uno dei collaboratori più cari e capaci. Confido in una sua radicale riforma in sede  di impugnazione e rinnovo all'amico  Andrea Delmastro la più totale e incondizionata fiducia. Continueremo a lavorare insieme per le indispensabili a urgenti riforme della Giustizia\".  Lo dichiara in una nota il ministro  della Giustizia, Carlo Nordio.  ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.3365746,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "Nordio: \"Disoriented and grieving\"",
        "en_content": "Condanna Delmastro,Nordio:disoriented \"I am disoriented and grieved for a conviction that affects one of the most dear and capable collaborators. I trust in a radical reform in the grip and I renew to my friend Andrea Delmastro the most total and unconditional trust. We will continue to work together for the indispensable urgent reforms of Justice.\" In a note the Minister of Justice, Carlo Nordio.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Condanna Delmastro",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrea Delmastro",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Justice",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Nordio",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni:Delmastro resta al suo posto",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Meloni:\"Delmastro rimane al suo posto\" \"Sono sconcertata per la sentenza di condanna del sottosegretario Andrea  Delmastro, per il quale il pubblico  ministero aveva inizialmente richiesto l'archiviazione e successivamente l' assoluzione. Mi chiedo se il giudizio sia realmente basato sul merito della questione. Il sottosegretario   Delmastro rimane al suo posto\".  Così il presidente del Consiglio,Giorgia Meloni.     ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.3437762,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "Meloni: Delmastro stays in his place",
        "en_content": "Meloni: \"Delmastro remains in his place\" \"I am bewildered for the sentence of undersecretary Andrea Delmastro, for which the public ministry had initially requested the archiving and subsequently absolution. I wonder if the judgment is actually based on the merits of the matter. Undersecretary Delmastro remains in place.\" So the President of the Council, Mr Meloni.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrea Delmastro",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Schlein:da destra commenti eversivi",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Schlein: \"Da destra commenti eversivi\" La segretaria del Pd, Elly Schlein,  chiede le dimissioni di Delmastro. \"Giorgia Meloni adesso lo faccia  dimettere anziché continuare a mentire sui fondi alla sanità pubblica e a non far nulla sulle bollette più care  d'Europa\".     E sulle dichiarazioni di Giorgia Meloni e dello stesso Delmastro aggiunge: \"Ma questa destra che governa non si rende conto che in uno Stato di diritto  queste dichiarazioni sono tecnicamente eversive?\".     ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.3532314,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "Schlein:from the right eversive comments",
        "en_content": "Schlein: \"From the right eversive comments\" The PD secretary, Elly Schlein, calls for Delmastro's resignation. \"Giorgia Meloni now lets him resign instead of continuing to lie on funds to public health and not to do anything about the most expensive bills in Europe.\" And on the statements of Giorgia Meloni and Delmastro himself adds: \"But does this right-wing government not realize that in a rule of law these statements are technically ever-exive? \".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "PD",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elly Schlein",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CASO COSPITO, DELMASTRO CONDANNATO    8 mesi, rivelazione segreto d'ufficio  \"Non mi dimetto, sentenza politica\"",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Cospito, Delmastro condannato a 8 mesi Il Tribunale di Roma ha condannato a otto mesi di reclusione e all'interdizione di un anno dai pubblici uffici il sottosegretario alla Giustizia, Andrea Delmastro, per rivelazione di segreto d'ufficio in relazione alla vicenda  dell'anarchico Alfredo Cospito.  I giudici hanno riconosciuto a Delmastro le attenuanti generiche e la sospensione della pena. \"Spero ci sia un giudice a Berlino\", ha affermato Delmastro, \"non mi dimetto, è una sentenza politica, fondata sul nulla\". Il sottosegretario avrebbe rivelato le conversazioni di Cospito in carcere.  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.3566422,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "CASO COSPITO, DELMASTRO CONDANNATO 8 months, secret revelation of office \"I do not dismiss, political sentence\"",
        "en_content": "Conspito, Delmastro sentenced to 8 months The Tribunal of Rome has sentenced to eight months of imprisonment and to the interdiction of a year from public offices the undersecretary to Justice, Andrea Delmastro, for revelation of office secret in relation to the affair of anarchist Alfredo Cospito. The judges have recognized Delmastro the general attenuation and suspension of the sentence. \"I hope there's a judge in Berlin,\" said Delmastro, \"I don't reject it, it's a political judgment, based on nothing.\" The undersecretary would reveal Cospito's conversations in prison.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CASO COSPITO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "DELMASTRO CONDANNATO",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "8 months",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Conspito",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 months",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Tribunal of Rome",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "eight months",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "a year",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Justice",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrea Delmastro",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alfredo Cospito",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Berlin",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delmastro",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cospito",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCIOPERO DI 8 ORE DEI METALMECCANICI   Protesta per rinnovo del contratto",
        "date_raw": "February 21, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Sciopero di 8 ore dei metalmeccanici Oggi sciopero nazionale di 8 ore dei lavoratori metalmeccanici indetto da Fiom-Cgil, Fim-Cisl e Uilm-Uil per il rinnovo del contratto collettivo nazionale di lavoro.     Cortei e presidi si sono svolti ieri in varie parte d'Italia. A Genova si è svolto un corteo che ha percorso il centro cittadino fino alla sede della Confindustria contro la quale sono stati lanciati petardi e uova. Bandiere sindacali si sono viste davanti a stabilimenti industriali in tutta Italia. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740132004.361302,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-21 11:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-21T10.00.04",
        "en_title": "SCIOPERO DI 8 ORE OF METALMECCANICI",
        "en_content": "8-hour strike of metal mechanics Today a national strike of 8 hours of metalworking workers organized by Fiom-Cgil, Fim-Cisl and Uilm-Uil for the renewal of the national collective labor contract. Courts and Presidents took place yesterday in various parts of Italy. In Genoa there was a procession that ran the city center until the headquarters of the Confindustria against which were launched firecrackers and eggs. Trade union flags have been seen in front of industrial plants throughout Italy.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SCIOPERO DI 8 ORE OF",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "METALMECCANICI",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "8-hour",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 hours",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fiom-Cgil",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fim-Cisl",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Uilm-Uil",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Confindustria",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 493,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    }
]
