[
    {
        "title": "M.O.,\"ITALIA INVOCA DIRITTO UMANITARIO\" Riunito Consiglio supremo di Difesa",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " M.O. L'Italia invoca diritto umanitario Il Consiglio supremo di difesa ha condannato \"l'aggressione del movimento terroristico Hamas a Israele,che ha innescato pericolose spirali di violenza, rischiando di compromettere ogni tentativo di dialogo tra i Paesi della regione\" e sottolineato come la reazione di Israele aggravi l'impatto sui civili Così una nota del Quirinale al termine della riunione, rimarcando che l'Italia \"è impegnata a contribuire nel fornire aiuto alla popolazione coinvolta e invoca l'applicazione del diritto umanitario e delle Convenzioni di Ginevra\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716336004.7596629,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "M.O., \"ITALY INVOCA DIRITTO UMANITARI\" Reunited Supreme Defense Council",
        "en_content": "M.O. Italy calls for humanitarian law The Supreme Council of Defence condemned \"the aggression of the Hamas terrorist movement to Israel, which triggered dangerous spirals of violence, risking compromising every attempt to dialogue between the countries of the region\" and stressed how the reaction of Israel aggravated the impact on civilians So a note from the Quirinale at the end of the meeting, pointing out that Italy \"is committed to helping the people involved and calls for the application of humanitarian law and the Geneva Conventions\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "M.O.",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "M.O.",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Supreme Council of Defence",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Geneva Conventions",
                "start_char": 523,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GAZA,\"ITALIA INVOCA DIRITTO UMANITARIO\" Riunito Consiglio supremo di Difesa",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716336004.8085043,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "GAZA, \"ITALY INVOCA DIRITTO UMANITARI\" Reunited Supreme Defense Council",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GAZA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SINNER PARTE PER PARIGI,OK ULTIMI ESAMI Calcio. Ranieri lascia il Cagliari",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716336004.810072,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "SINNER PART FOR PARIGI,OK ULTIMI ESAMI Calcio. Ranieri leaves Cagliari",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "OK ULTIMI ESAMI Calcio",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ranieri",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cagliari",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TORNA REDDITOMETRO, SI APPLICA DAL 2016 Leo: più garanzie per contribuenti",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716336004.8959012,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "TORNA REDDITOMETRO, SI APPLICA DAL 2016 Leo: more guarantees for taxpayers",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Leo",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716336004.899083,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL SUPERBONUS, GOVERNO PONE LA FIDUCIA  Il voto si terrà domani pomeriggio",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Dl Superbonus, governo pone la fiducia Il governo ha posto la questione di  fiducia alla Camera sul decreto Superbonus, già approvato dal Senato e in scadenza il 28 maggio.   Lo ha annunciato in Aula il ministro per i Rapporti con il Parlamento, Ciriani. Il voto si terrà domani pomeriggio, dalle 17.45 come stabilito dalla capigruppo di Montecitorio. Il via libera definitivo atteso giovedì mattina. Protestano Pd e M5S per \"l'ennesima\" fiducia. E' stata posta per coprire \"le divisioni nella maggioranza\",sostengono",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.0120506,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ The vote will be held tomorrow afternoon",
        "en_content": "Dl Superbonus, government places confidence The government placed the question of trust in the House on the Superbonus decree, already approved by the Senate and expiring on May 28. It was announced in the Chamber by the Minister for Relations with Parliament, Ciriani. The vote will be held tomorrow afternoon, from 17.45 as established by the group leader of Montecitorio. The final freeway expected on Thursday morning. They test Pd and M5S for \"the eternal\" trust. It was placed to cover \"the divisions in the majority\", they support",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "afternoon",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "May 28",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ciriani",
                "start_char": 261,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "afternoon",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "17.45",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Montecitorio",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 405,
                "end_char": 413,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "morning",
                "start_char": 414,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd",
                "start_char": 433,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Crosetto ha un malore,va in ospedale122  CAMPI FLEGREI, ATTESO VERTICE A P.CHIGI Musumeci: con Meloni e i ministri",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Campi Flegrei,oggi vertice con Meloni La premier Meloni presiederà oggi a  Palazzo Chigi un vertice interministeriale sulla situazione ai Campo Flegrei dopo l'ultimo sciame sismico. Lo ha annunciato il ministro della Protezione Civile, Musumeci.    Sul tavolo \"eventuali ulteriori interventi da parte del governo, dopo quelli già promossi e in corso di attuazione con il decreto legge dell'ottobre scorso\", ha detto. \"Sono in costante contatto con il presidente del Consiglio Giorgia Meloni che segue sin da ieri la situazione\", ha dichiarato Musumeci. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.0220695,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "Crosetto has a malore,va in the hospital122 CAMPI FLEGREI, ATTESO VERTICA P.CHIGI Musumeci: with Meloni and the ministers",
        "en_content": "Campi Flegrei, today summit with Meloni Premier Meloni will today preside at Palazzo Chigi an interministerial summit on the situation at Campo Flegrei after the last seismic swarm. It was announced by the Minister of Civil Protection, Musumeci. On the table \"eventual further interventions by the government, after those already promoted and in progress of implementation with the decree law of last October\", he said. \"I am in constant contact with the President of the Council Giorgia Meloni who has been following the situation since yesterday,\" said Musumeci.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Crosetto",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "malore,va",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "FLEGREI",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ATTESO",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "VERTICA",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "P.CHIGI Musumeci",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Flegrei",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Campo Flegrei",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Minister of Civil Protection",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Musumeci",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last October",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Musumeci",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 563,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CAMPI FLEGREI, PREOCCUPA SCIAME SISMICO Atteso il vertice a Palazzo Chigi",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716336005.0927289,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "CAMPI FLEGREI, PREOCCUPA SCIAME SISMICO Expected the summit at Palazzo Chigi",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FLEGREI",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SISMICO",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCIOPERO DEI TAXI DALLE 8 ALLE 22    \"No alla deregolamentazione\"",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Sciopero dei taxi,no deregolamentazione Sciopero nazionale dei taxi,oggi dalle 8 alle 22, con una manifestazione a  Roma, dalle 11 alle 17, a piazza San Silvestro.     \"E' fondamentale la partecipazione di tutta la categoria a difesa del proprio lavoro, per contrastare l'uso illegittimo delle autorizzazioni da noleggio e salvaguardare la propria autonomia e indipendenza dalla schiavitù degli algoritmi e delle multinazionale\", spiega un comunicato delle sigle sindacali. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.1078675,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "SCIOPERO DI TAXI DALLE 8 ALLE 22 \"No to deregulation\"",
        "en_content": "Taxi strike, no deregulation National strike of taxis, today from 8 to 22, with an event in Rome, from 11 to 17, in Piazza San Silvestro. \"It is essential to participate in the entire category to defend its work, to counter the illegitimate use of rental authorizations and to safeguard its autonomy and independence from the slavery of algorithms and multinationals,\" explains a communiqué of trade union law.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SCIOPERO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "22",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "11 to 17",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza San Silvestro",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Leo: più tutele per i contribuenti",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Redditometro? \"Più tutele contribuenti\" Il viceministro dell'Economia Leo precisa che non si torna al vecchio redditometro.\"Il Centrodestra è sempre stato contrario al meccanismo introdotto nel 2015 dal governo Renzi.Il nuovo decreto mette finalmente dei limiti al potere discrezionale dell'Amministrazione finanziaria\".      Il redditometro era stato abolito nel 2018 dal governo Conte 1,stabilendo che si dovesse emanare un nuovo decreto con paletti precisi a garanzia del contribuente,spiega Leo. \"Il governo è finalmente intervenuto,introducendo solo più garanzie per i contribuemnti\".  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.1228333,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "Leo: more suits for taxpayers",
        "en_content": "Editor? \"More taxpayers\" The Deputy Minister of Economy Leo points out that you do not return to the old income meter. \"The Centre has always been against the mechanism introduced in 2015 by the Renzi government. The new decree finally sets limits to the discretionary power of the Financial Administration.\" The income meter had been abolished in 2018 by the Count 1, establishing that a new decree should be issued with precise stakes to guarantee the taxpayer, Explains Leo. \"The government has finally intervened, introducing only more guarantees for contributors.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Leo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Leo",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2015",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Renzi",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Financial Administration",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2018",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Count 1",
                "start_char": 356,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leo",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"ESERCITAZIONI ARMI NUCLEARI TATTICHE\"  Mosca:al via al confine con Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716336005.138853,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "Moscow: at the border with Ukraine",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TORNA REDDITOMETRO, SI APPLICA DAL 2016 Strumento analizza capacità spesa",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Torna Redditometro, si applica dal 2016 Un decreto del 7 maggio,firmato dal viceministro dell'Economia Leo e pubblicato in Gazzetta Ufficiale, reintroduce il redditometro. Il precedente era stato sospeso nel 2018.    E' lo strumento che consente al fisco di risalire al reddito dei contribuenti analizzando la capacità di spesa:dovrà essere compatibile con le proprie risorse finanziarie. Si applica sui redditi a partire dal 2016. Tra le spese analizzate,quelle per i consumi alimentari,abbigliamento, abitazione, consumi energetici, sanità, auto e istruzione. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.1680763,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "TORNA REDDITOMETRO, SI APPLICA DAL 2016 Instrument analyzes spending capacity",
        "en_content": "Back Editor, applies since 2016 A decree of 7 May, signed by the Deputy Minister of Economy Leo and published in the Official Journal, reintroduces the income meter. The previous was suspended in 2018. It is the tool that allows the tax to pay back to the income of the taxpayers by analyzing the spending capacity: it will have to be compatible with its financial resources. It applies to income from 2016. Among the expenses analysed, those for food consumption, clothing, housing, energy consumption, health, car and education.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2016",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "7 May",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Official Journal",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2018",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2016",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 406,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAN, 5 GIORNI DI LUTTO PER MORTE RAISI Avviate a Tabriz le cerimonie funebri  I funerali il 23 maggio a Mashhad",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Raisi,corteo funebre a Tabriz e Teheran La cerimonia funebre per il presidente iraniano Raisi morto domenica in un incidente in elicottero,insieme al ministro degli Esteri Amir-Abdollahian,è iniziata con un corteo a Tabriz,capitale dell'Azerbaigian orientale.La salma poi sarà trasferita nella città santa di Qom e da lì nella capitale dove stasera l'Ayatollah Khamenei guiderà le preghiere in una cerimonia di addio.  Domani le processioni nella capitale e giovedì la salma di Raisi sarà trasferita a Mashhad,sua città natale per la sepoltura.In tutto 5 i giorni di lutto proclamati in Iran.    ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716336005.193271,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "IRAN, 5 Days of LUTTO FOR MORTE RAISI Start in Tabriz funeral ceremonies The funeral ceremonies on 23 May at Mashhad",
        "en_content": "Raisi, a funeral race in Tabriz and Tehran The funeral ceremony for Iranian President Raisi died on Sunday in a helicopter crash, along with Foreign Minister Amir-Abdollahian, began with a procession in Tabriz, capital of East Azerbaijan. The psalm will then be transferred to the holy city of Qom and from there to the capital where tonight the Ayatollah Khamenei will guide prayers in a farewell ceremony. Tomorrow the processions in the capital and Thursday the Psalm of Raisi will be transferred to Mashhad, his birthplace for the burial. In all 5 days of mourning proclaimed in Iran.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 Days",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "LUTTO FOR MORTE",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "23 May",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mashhad",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amir-Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Qom",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ayatollah Khamenei",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 460,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mashhad",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "all 5 days",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 587,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"TURBOLENZE IN VOLO\":UN MORTO,30 FERITI Panico sull'aereo Singapore-Londra    Atterraggio d'emergenza a Bangkok",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " \"Forti turbolenze volo\":un morto,feriti Una persona è morta e una trentina sono rimaste ferite su un volo della Singapore Airlines,da Londra a Singapore, in seguito a forti turbolenze. L'aereo è stato fatto atterrare a Bangkok.  A bordo c'erano 211 passeggeri e 18  membri dell'equipaggio,soccorsi all'arrivo all'aeroporto. Ancora non è chiaro cosa sia esattamente successo. L'aereo viaggiava a oltre 11mila metri, poi in 3 minuti è sceso a 9mila 400 metri. E' rimasto a tale quota per 10 minuti,prima di scendere rapidamente e atterrare. La vittima sarebbe un 73enne con problemi cardiaci, riporta il Guardian. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716336005.2027876,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "\"TURBOLENZE IN VOLO\":A MORTO,30 FERITI Panico on the plane Singapore-London Emergency landing in Bangkok",
        "en_content": "\"Fort flight turbulence\": a dead person died and about thirty were injured on a Singapore Airlines flight, from London to Singapore, following strong turbulence. The plane was landed in Bangkok. There were 211 passengers on board and 18 crew members on arrival at the airport. It is still unclear what exactly happened. The plane traveled over 11 thousand meters, then in 3 minutes it fell to 9 thousand 400 meters. He remained at that altitude for 10 minutes, before he quickly descended and landed. The victim would be a 73-year-old with heart problems, the Guardian reports.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "TURBOLENZE",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "VOLO\":A",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "MORTO,30",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bangkok",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "about thirty",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore Airlines",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bangkok",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "211",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 11 thousand meters",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 minutes",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "9 thousand 400 meters",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 minutes",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "73-year-old",
                "start_char": 523,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guardian",
                "start_char": 560,
                "end_char": 568,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FINE MANDATO ZELENSKY,MOSCA: USURPATORE Cremlino:avanti operazione speciale",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Fine mandato Zelensky,Mosca: usurpatore Un \"usurpatore\" e un \"obiettivo militare legittimo\" per la Russia. Così l'ex presidente russo Medvedev ha definito Zelensky,che oggi conclude il suo mandato da presidente ucraino senza che si siano potute tenere le elezioni per una sua riconferma o per la scelta di un successore a causa della legge marziale Il Cremlino si è mostrato indifferente al problema istituzionale della fine del mandato di Zelensky,e sulle possibili conseguenze sull'andamento del  conflitto,il portavoce Peskov ha risposto: \"L'operazione speciale continua\". ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716336005.2077878,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "ZELENSKY MANDATO FINE,MOSCA: USURPATORE Kremlin: advance special operation",
        "en_content": "End mandate Zelensky,Moscow: usurper A \"usurper\" and a \"legitimate military target\" for Russia. So former Russian President Medvedev defined Zelensky, which today concludes his mandate as Ukrainian president without being able to hold elections for a reconfirm or for the choice of a successor due to martial law The Kremlin was indifferent to the institutional problem of the end of Zelensky's mandate, and the possible consequences of the conflict, the spokesman Peskov replied: \"Special operation continues.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MOSCA",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "USURPATORE Kremlin",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Medvedev",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peskov",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"ESERCITAZIONI ARMI NUCLEARI TATTICHE\"  Mosca:al via al confine con Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Mosca ostenta armi nucleari tattiche La Russia ha iniziato la prima fase  \"dell'esercitazione con addestramento pratico sulla preparazione e l'uso di armi nucleari non strategiche\". Lo ha riferito il ministero della Difesa.  Le esercitazioni si tengono nel di stretto militare meridionale, non lontano dal confine con l'Ucraina e ha lo scopo di mantenere pronto il personale e le attrezzature in caso di \"dichiazioni provocatorie e minacce di singoli funzionari occidentali contro la  Federazione Russa\", ha spiegato il Ministero della Difesa.   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716336005.2277133,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "Moscow: at the border with Ukraine",
        "en_content": "Moscow flaunted tactical nuclear weapons Russia began the first phase of \"exercition with practical training on the preparation and use of non-strategic nuclear weapons\". The Defense Ministry reported it. Exercises are held in the southern military strait, not far from the border with Ukraine and it is intended to keep staff and equipment ready in case of \"provoking statements and threats of individual Western officials against the Russian Federation\", explained the Ministry of Defense.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Defense Ministry",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 286,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 413,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Federation",
                "start_char": 432,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Defense",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RITORNO LEVA, BOTTA E RISPOSTA LEGA-FI  Salvini: proposta avrà effetti positivi No di Tajani:sarebbe troppo costoso",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Ritorno leva, botta e risposta Lega-FI \"Depositata alla Camera la proposta di legge della Lega per reintrodurre 6 mesi di servizio civile o militare, per i ragazzi tra i 18-26 anni,su base regionale e da svolgere esclusivamente in Italia\". Così il leader della Lega Salvini sui social. \"Ne sono convinto. E' una forma di educazione civica al servizio della comunità, di disciplina,attenzione al prossimo.Potrà avere effetti molto positivi\", aggiunge.   In disaccordo Tajani (FI). \"Non credo possa reintrodursi. Con il sistema che abbiamo sarebbe troppo costoso\".  ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.238738,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "LEVA, BOTTA and LEGA-FI Salvini Answer: proposal will have positive effects No of Tajani: it would be too expensive",
        "en_content": "Return lever, barrel and response Lega-FI \"Deposit to the House the law proposal of the League to reintroduce 6 months of civil or military service, for children between 18-26 years, on a regional basis and to be carried out exclusively in Italy\". So the leader of the Salvini League on social media. \"I'm convinced. It is a form of civic education at the service of the community, of discipline, attention to the neighbor. It may have very positive effects,\" he adds. In disagreement Tajani (FI). \"I don't think he can reintroduce himself. With the system we have would be too expensive.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "LEVA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "League",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "6 months",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "between 18-26 years",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Salvini League",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 485,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Rafah,Unrwa:stop distribuzione cibo",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Rafah,Unrwa:stop distribuzione alimenti L'agenzia Onu responsabile per i rifugiati palestinesi,Unrwa,ha annunciato che sospenderà le distribuzioni alimentari a Rafah,nel sul della Striscia. \"A seguito dell'operazione militare (israeliana) in corso nella parte orientale di Rafah,dal 7 maggio,il centro di distribuzione dell'Unrwa e il magazzino del Pam,programma alimentare mondiale, entrambi situati a Rafah,sono inaccessibili. -afferma l'agenziaLe distribuzioni di cibo sono attualmente sospese a causa della mancanza di rifornimenti e dell'insicurezza in città\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716336005.2678523,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "Rafah,Unrwa:stop food distribution",
        "en_content": "Rafah,Unrwa:stop food distribution The UN agency responsible for Palestinian refugees,Unrwa, announced that it will suspend food distributions in Rafah, on the Strip. \"As a result of the military operation (Israeli) in progress in the eastern part of Rafah, from May 7, the distribution center of the Unrwa and the warehouse of Pam, world food program, both located in Rafah, are inaccessible. -affirms the agency Food distributions are currently suspended due to lack of supplies and insecurity in the city.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unrwa",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unrwa",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unrwa",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 7",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unrwa",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Food",
                "start_char": 414,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AP DENUNCIA ISRAELE DI CENSURA SU GAZA  Proteste Usa, decisione revocata",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Ap denuncia Israele di censura su Gaza Le riprese in diretta televisiva dal sud di Israele dell'Associated Press sono state interrotte da funzionari  israeliani che hanno anche sequestrato le apparecchiature di ripresa.Lo ha denunciato la stessa agenzia di stampa Usa che ha chiesto alle autorità israeliane la restituzione delle attrezzature e il ripristino del feed live.  Anche l'Onu ha condannato l'episodio.Ma solo dopo che si è attivata la Casa  Bianca con la richiesta di riattivare diretta video dell'agenzia su Gaza,  Israele ha annunciato la revoca della sua decisione.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716336005.393102,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ CENSURA SU GAZA Proteste Usa, decision revoked",
        "en_content": "Ap denounces Israel of censorship on Gaza Television live footage from southern Israel of the Associated Press was interrupted by Israeli officials who also seized the shooting equipment. He denounced the same US press agency that asked Israeli authorities to return equipment and restore live feed. The UN also condemned the episode. But only after the White House was activated with the request to reactivate live video of the agency on Gaza, Israel announced the revocation of its decision.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SU GAZA",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Proteste Usa",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza Television",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Associated Press",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 451,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ZUPPI: PREOCCUPA STATO SALUTE ITALIA   Presidente Cei:\"Aumenta la povertà\"",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=135",
        "content": " Zuppi: preoccupa stato salute Italia \"Lo stato di salute del Paese desta  articolare preoccupazione. E' sempre più difficile uscire dall'abisso dell' indigenza.Si rafforzano le povertà croniche e quelle intermittenti,relative ai nuclei familiari che oscillano tra il'dentro' e il 'fuori' dalla condizione di bisogno\". Così il presidente Cei, card.Zuppi, all'Assemblea dei vescovi. \"Si rafforza il divario generazionale:i giovani sono sempre più esposti a difficoltà economiche\",aggiunge.Serve \"legalità certa che combatta gli abusi\" e urge\"rispondere a domanda mano d'opera\"",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.4261477,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "ZUPPI: PREOCCUPA STATO SALUT ITALIA President Cei: \"Increasing poverty\"",
        "en_content": "Zuppi: health care Italy \"The state of health of the country is causing concern. It's more and more difficult to get out of the abyss of indigence. Chronic and intermittent poverty are strengthened, related to family nuclei ranging between the back and the 'outside' from the need condition.\" Thus President Cei, Cardinal Zuppi, to the Assembly of Bishops. \"The generational gap is strengthened: young people are increasingly exposed to economic difficulties,\" added. It serves \"certain legality that fights abuse\" and urges \"to respond to labor demand\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ZUPPI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "SALUT",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cei",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zuppi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cei",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Assembly of Bishops",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AI,MELONI:SFIDA EPOCALE,GESTIRE IMPATTO Videomessaggio al Summit di Seoul",
        "date_raw": "May 22, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Ai,Meloni:sfida epocale,gestire impatto \"L'intelligenza artificiale è una sfida epocale per l'intera società. Siamo di fronte a una nuova frontiera del progresso, che per la prima volta nella storia rischia di mettere in discussione il principio stesso della centralità dell'uomo\". Così la premier Meloni in un videomessaggio al Summit di Seoul. \"Ora è l'intelletto che rischia di essere sostituito. Con un impatto, se non gestito,inevitabile anche sui lavoratori a più alta specializzazione\". E la classe media \"potrebbe sparire\",paventa Inciderà anche su \"scenari geopolitici\"",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716336005.70014,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-22 02:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-22T02.00.05",
        "en_title": "AI,MELONI:SFIDA EPOCALE,GESTIRE IMPATTO Video message at the Seoul Summit",
        "en_content": "Ai,Meloni: epochal challenge, managing impact \"Artificial intelligence is an epochal challenge for the entire society. We are facing a new frontier of progress, which for the first time in history is likely to question the very principle of the centrality of man.\" So premier Meloni in a video message at the Seoul Summit. \"Now is the intellect that is likely to be replaced. With an impact, if not managed,invitable also on the most highly specialized workers\". And the middle class \"may disappear,\" Paventa will also affect \" geopolitical scenes\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "AI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Seoul Summit",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Seoul Summit",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
