[
    {
        "title": "AUTOVELOX, DAL 2017 OMOLOGATI D'UFFICIO Lo prevede decreto ministero Trasporti  Verso stop a ricorsi automobilisti",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Autovelox, dal 2017 omologati d'ufficio Probabile stop ai ricorsi contro le  multe per gli autovelox. Dalla prossima estate tutti i dispositivi approvati dal giugno 2017 in poi saranno infatti da ritenersi automaticamente omologati. E' quanto prevede un decreto in arrivo dal ministero dei Trasporti. Inviato a Bruxelles, sarà operativo da luglio. Il Codacons tuttavia fa presente: la norma conferma che gli autovelox non conformi vanno spenti o si rischia una raffica di ricorsi da parte degli  automobilisti.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.3035853,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "AUTOVELOX, DAL 2017 OMOLOGATI D'UFFICIO It previews decree ministry Transports To stop resorts motorists",
        "en_content": "Autovelox, since 2017 approved of office Probabile stop to appeals against fines for speed cameras. From next summer all devices approved since June 2017 will be automatically approved. It's what a decree comes from the Ministry of Transport. Posted in Brussels, will be operational from July. The Codacons, however, points out: the standard confirms that non-compliant speed cameras must be turned off or a burst of appeals is likely by motorists.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2017",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "OMOLOGATI",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2017",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "next summer",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "June 2017",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Transport",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "July",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Codacons",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISTRUTTORIA ANTITRUST SU RFI E FS    \"Remano contro un nuovo operatore\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Antitrust, istruttoria su Rfi e FS L'Autorità Garante della Concorrenza e del Mercato ha avviato un'istruttoria nei confronti di Rete Ferroviaria Italiana S.p.A e della holding Ferrovie dello Stato Italiane S.p.A. in merito a un presunto abuso di posizione dominante in violazione dell'art.102 del Trattato sul funzionamento Ue (Tfue).  Secondo l'Autorità \"risulterebbe rallentato e in alcuni casi ostacolato l' accesso all'infrastruttura nazionale\" e \"l'ingresso nel mercato\" del nuovo operatore SNCF Voyages Italia. Fs: piena collaborazione, la nostra correttezza emergerà dalle ispezioni.   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.3300083,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "ANTITRUST INSTRUCTORS ON RFI AND FS \"Remant against a new operator\"",
        "en_content": "Antitrust, Rfi and FS instructor The Guarantor Authority of Competition and Market has initiated an investigation towards Rete Ferroviaria Italiana S.p.A and the holding company Ferrovie dello Stato Italiane S.p.A. regarding an alleged abuse of dominant position in violation of art.102 of the Treaty on European Functioning (Tfue). According to the Authority \"it would be slowed down and in some cases hindered access to the national infrastructure\" and \"the entry into the market\" of the new operator SNCF Voyages Italy. Fs: full collaboration, our correctness will emerge from the inspections.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "RFI",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "FS \"Remant",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rfi",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "FS",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Guarantor Authority of Competition and Market",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rete Ferroviaria Italiana S.p.",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Treaty",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "European Functioning",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Authority",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SNCF Voyages Italy",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCIOPERO TRASPORTO LOCALE, POCHI DISAGI Metropolitane aperte a Roma e Milano   Protesta indetta da sindacati base",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Sciopero trasporto locale, pochi disagi Disagi contenuti nel giorno dello  sciopero di 24 ore del trasporto  pubblico locale, proclamato dai  sindacati di base.    Metro aperte a Roma e Milano. Servizio regolare a Torino. Qualche disagio in più a Bologna.     La protesta è stata proclamata da Adl Cobas, Sgb, Cub Trasporti e Cobas  Lavoro Privato, che non hanno partecipato alla trattativa al ministero dei Trasporti sul rinnovo del contratto  nazionale, firmato dalle altre sigle di categoria.     ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.332644,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "SCIOPERO TRASPORT LOCALE, POCHI DISAGI Metropolitane open in Rome and Milan Protesta indetta from unions base",
        "en_content": "Strike local transport, few inconveniences Disagi contained on the day of the strike of 24 hours of local public transport, proclaimed by the basic unions. Metro open in Rome and Milan. Regular service in Turin. Some extra discomfort in Bologna. The protest was proclaimed by Adl Cobas, Sgb, Cub Transportation and Cobas Private Work, who did not participate in the negotiation to the Ministry of Transport on the renewal of the national contract, signed by the other category Englishmen.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SCIOPERO TRASPORT LOCALE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan Protesta",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Disagi",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 hours",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Metro",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turin",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bologna",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Adl Cobas",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sgb",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cub Transportation",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cobas Private Work",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Transport",
                "start_char": 381,
                "end_char": 406,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Englishmen",
                "start_char": 477,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SALVINI PARLA CON VANCE:PACE,NON RIARMO \"Spendere 800 miliardi è follia\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Salvini parla con Vance:pace,non riarmo \"Ho parlato per un quarto d'ora con Vance. Trump sta parlando con Putin, con Zelensky, si stanno incontrando le delegazioni, si parla di tregua, di  cessate il fuoco, di disarmo\".  Lo rende noto il ministro dei Trasporti Salvini all'evento della Lega a Napoli. \"E mentre Trump e Putin parlano di come tenere a terra i missili, altri parlano di esercito europeo, di spendere 800 miliardi di euro per comprare armi. E' una follia\", aggiunge il vicepremier. ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.3390834,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Salvini talks to Vance:Peace, I'm not resigning \"I spoke for a quarter of an hour with Vance. Trump is talking to Putin, with Zelensky, they are meeting delegations, we talk about truce, ceasefire, disarmament.\" The Minister of Transport Salvini at the event of the League in Naples. \"And while Trump and Putin talk about how to keep missiles on the ground, others talk about European army, spend 800 billion euros to buy weapons. It's crazy,\" he adds.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vance:Peace",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a quarter of an hour",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vance",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Transport Salvini",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 384,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "800 billion euros",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MATTARELLA: \"MAFIA SI VINCE. STA A NOI\" Giornata nazionale memoria vittime",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Colle: mafia si può vincere, sta a noi \"Il 21 marzo è un giorno solenne di ricordo e impegno civile per affermare valori essenziali per la salute della nostra comunità\". Così il Presidente Mattarella nella Giornata nazionale in ricordo delle vittime di mafia.  \"L'impegno quotidiano per la legalità, la lotta contro le mafie, contro le  consorterie e crimini che generano violenze e zone grigie\", prosegue, \"vede operare tutti i cittadini che desiderano vivere in una società coesa e rispettosa dei diritti di tutti\". \"La mafia può essere vinta. Dipende da noi\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.360808,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "MATTARELLA: \"MAFIA SI VINCE. STA A NOI\" National Day memory victims",
        "en_content": "Colle: Mafia can be won, stands at us \"On March 21, it is a solemn day of memory and civil commitment to affirm essential values for the health of our community\". So President Mattarella on the National Day in memory of the victims of mafia. \"The daily commitment to legality, the fight against mafias, against consortia and crimes that generate violence and gray areas,\" he continued, \"see to operate all citizens who wish to live in a cohesive and respectful society of the rights of all\". \"Mafia can be won. It depends on us.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "VINCE",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "STA",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "NOI",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "National Day",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mafia",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "March 21",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Day",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mafia",
                "start_char": 493,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TRAPANI,50MILA A GIORNATA DELLA MEMORIA Promossa da Libera di don Ciotti",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Trapani,50mila a Giornata della memoria Circa 50mila persone hanno partecipato alla trentesima Giornata della memoria organizzata dell'associazione Libera per ricordare le vittime innocenti delle mafie. Alla manifestazione dell'associazione presiduta da don Ciotti,  hanno preso parte oltre 500 familiari di vittime delle mafie.    \"Diventiamo complici delle mafie se non ci assumiamo la nostra parte di responsabilità di cittadini veri, non a intermittenza\", ha detto don Ciotti che ha aggiunto: \"La latitanza di Matteo Messina Denaro denuncia le altre latitanze che ci sono state\".   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.3627214,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "TRAPANI,50MILA A DAY OF MEMORIA Promoted by Libera di Don Ciotti",
        "en_content": "Trapani,50 thousand in Memory Day Approximately 50 thousand people participated in the 30th Day of organized memory of the Free Association to remember the innocent victims of the mafia. At the event of the association presided by Don Ciotti, over 500 family members of the Mafia victims took part. \"We become accomplices of the mafia if we do not assume our share of responsibility of real citizens, not intermittently,\" said Fr Ciotti who added: \"The latitude of Matteo Messina Money denounces the other latitudes that have been there\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MEMORIA",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Libera di Don Ciotti",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trapani,50 thousand",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Memory Day",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Approximately 50 thousand",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 30th Day",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Free Association",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Ciotti",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "500",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mafia",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fr Ciotti",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 436,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Matteo Messina Money",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TRUMP PRESENTA NUOVO JET:IL PIU' LETALE \"Stabilite linee guida tregua Ucraina\"  Sui dazi: \"Ci sarà flessibilità\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742616005.38038,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "TRUMP PRESENTA NEW JET: THE LETAL PIU 'Stabilite guidelines tregua Ukraine' On duties: \"There will be flexibility\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "TRUMP PRESENTA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Stabilite",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "VALDITARA: STOP AD ASTERISCO E SCHWA   \"Vietati nei documenti del ministero\"  \"Ripristinare l'autorità a scuola\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Valditara: stop ad asterisco e schwa \"Ho fatto emanare una circolare che  vieta l'utilizzo dell'asterisco e dello schwa nei documenti del ministero\".  Lo annuncia il ministro dell'Istruzione e del Merito, Valditara, durante un  evento della Lega a Napoli.   \"Oggi abbiamo ripristinato una regola importante della lingua italiana\", aggiunge Valditara. Poi: bisogna  \"ripristinare il principio di autorità nelle scuole\", \"valutare la condotta dello studente è fondamentale\".  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.4112835,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "VALDITARA: STOP AD ASTERISCO AND SCHWA \"Vietati in the documents of the ministry\" \"Restoring authority at school\"",
        "en_content": "Valditara: stop asterisk and schwa \"I have issued a circular that prohibits the use of asterisk and schwa in the documents of the ministry\". The Minister of Education and Merit announces it, Valditara, during an event of the League in Naples. \"Today we have restored an important rule of the Italian language,\" adds Valditara. Then, \"restore the principle of authority in schools\", \"evaluating the conduct of the student is fundamental\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SCHWA",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vietati",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Valditara",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Merit",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Valditara",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Valditara",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SI'ADOZIONI MINORI STRANIERI PER SINGLE Consulta: incostituzionale vietarlo",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742616005.4152763,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "SIADOZIONI MINORI STRANIERI per SINGLE Consulta: incostituzionale prohibit it",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SIADOZIONI MINORI STRANIERI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni: mafie nemiche di democrazia",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Meloni: mafie nemiche della democrazia \"Le mafie sono un nemico dichiarato  della nostra democrazia, un'offesa alla dignità della Nazione. Per questo, con assoluta determinazione e fermezza, ribadiamo la nostra condanna ad ogni tipo di mafia e ci impegniamo, ogni giorno, a combatterla. Così su X la premier,per la Giornata della memoria delle vittime \"Onorare il sacrificio delle vittime significa agire per rafforzare la giustizia,garantire sicurezza,difendere la libertà di tutti i cittadini, rifiutare ed estirpare ogni forma di illegalità, violenza,sopraffazione. La loro memoria è,e dev'essere sempre,la nostra guida\".",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742616005.419042,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "Meloni: enemy mafias of democracy",
        "en_content": "Meloni: enemy mafias of democracy \"Mafias are a declared enemy of our democracy, an offense to the dignity of the nation. For this reason, with absolute determination and firmness, we reiterate our condemnation to every kind of mafia and we commit ourselves, every day, to fight it. Thus on X the premier, for the Day of the Memory of the Victims \"To honor the sacrifice of the victims means to act to strengthen justice, to ensure security, to defend the freedom of all citizens, to refuse and eradicate all forms of illegality, violence, overwhelm. Their memory is, and it must always be our guide.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Day of the Memory of the",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PAPA MIGLIORA,SOSPESA MASCHERA OSSIGENO \"Condizioni stabili, lievi progressi\"  \"Cautela\" sul ritorno in Vaticano",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742616005.4228303,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "PAPA MIGLIORA,SOSPESA MASCHERA OSSIGENO \"Conditions stable, minor progress\" \"Cautela\" on the return to the Vatican",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "PAPA MIGLIORA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SOSPESA MASCHERA OSSIGENO",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cautela\"",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vatican",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Abbattuto missile Houthi yemeniti",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Abbattuto missile Houthi verso Israele Un missile balistico lanciato contro Israele dagli Houthi yemeniti è stato intercettato dalle difese aeree.  L'Idf afferma che il missile è stato abbattuto prima di entrare nello  spazio aereo israeliano.   Le sirene hanno suonato in tutto il  centro di Israele: a Gerusalemme, in altre città vicine e negli insediamenti in Cisgiordania. Non si segnalano danni nell'attacco.     ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742616005.4282773,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "Lower missile Houthi Yemeni",
        "en_content": "Lower Houthi missile to Israel A ballistic missile launched against Israel by the Yemeni Houthi was intercepted by air defenses. The Idf states that the missile was shot down before entering the Israeli airspace. The sirens played throughout the center of Israel: to Jerusalem, in other nearby cities and in the settlements in the West Bank. No damage to the attack.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Houthi Yemeni",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lower Houthi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Yemeni Houthi",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AUTOVELOX, DAL 2017 OMOLOGATI D'UFFICIO Verso stop a ricorsi automobilisti",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742616005.4326992,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "AUTOVELOX, DAL 2017 OMOLOGATI D'UFFICIO Verso stop a recurrence autosti",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2017",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "OMOLOGATI D'UFFICIO Verso",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ma Netanyahu tira dritto: decido io",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Netanyahu: su capo Shin Bet decido io Il premier Netanyahu rassicura sulla crisi istituzionale in Israele dopo il licenziamento del capo dello Shin Bet e la prossima rimozione della procuratrice generale. Ma avverte che non cambierà decisione.     \"Non ci sarà nessuna guerra civile\", scrive su X. \"Lo Stato di Israele è  uno stato di diritto e, in base alla legge, il governo israeliano decide  chi sarà il capo dello Shin Bet\",  sottolinea Netanyahu dopo che l'Alta Corte di Giustizia israeliana ha congelato il licenziamento di Ronen Bar. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742616005.4400094,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "But Netanyahu pulls straight: I decide",
        "en_content": "Netanyahu: On Chief Shin Bet I decide Premier Netanyahu reassures about the institutional crisis in Israel after the dismissal of the head of Shin Bet and the next removal of the Attorney General. But warns that it won't change your mind. \"There will be no civil war\", writes on X. \"The State of Israel is a rule of law and, according to the law, the Israeli government decides who will be the head of Shin Bet,\" Netanyahu underlines after the Israeli High Court of Justice frozen Ronen Bar's dismissal.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shin Bet",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shin Bet",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "X. \"The State of Israel",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shin Bet",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Israeli High Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ARRESTO SINDACO ISTANBUL,ANCORA SCONTRI Migliaia in piazza malgrado divieto",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Turchia, proteste pro Imamoglu: scontri Non si fermano, a Istanbul e in altre città turche,le proteste dopo l'arresto del sindaco di Istanbul Imamoglu, accusato di corruzione e terrorismo, per il presunto favoreggiamento del partito filocurdo Pkk, \"terrorista\" per Ankara. Scontri a Istanbul, dove decine di migliaia di persone sono scese in  piazza malgrado i divieti, e a Smirne. Imamoglu è il principale rivale di Erdogan per le prossime presidenziali e sia lui che i suoi sostenitori denunciano: l'arresto è per eliminarlo dalla competizione elettorale.   ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742616005.4758215,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "ARRESTO SINDACO ISTANBUL, ANCORA SCONTRI Migliaia in piazza despite prohibition",
        "en_content": "Turkey, Pro Imamoglu protests: clashes Do not stop, in Istanbul and other Turkish cities,the protests after the arrest of the mayor of Istanbul Imamoglu, accused of corruption and terrorism, for the alleged favoration of the procurdo party Pkk, \"terrorist\" for Ankara. Meets in Istanbul, where tens of thousands of people went to the square despite the prohibitions, and to Smyrna. Imamoglu is the main rival of Erdogan for the next presidential elections and both he and his supporters denounce: the arrest is to eliminate him from the electoral competition.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ARRESTO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ISTANBUL",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANCORA SCONTRI Migliaia",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the procurdo party Pkk",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ankara",
                "start_char": 261,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tens of thousands",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Smyrna",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "LENTA RIPRESA DEI VOLI A HEATHROW    Black-out in scalo dopo un incendio",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Heathrow, ripresa parziale dei voli  L'aeroporto di Heathrow annuncia la  ripresa di alcuni voli in serata e spera di effettuare un servizio completo sabato.     I pimi voli sono già decollati dal principale aeroporto londinese.  In una nota, lo scalo fa sapere che si sta lavorando per riportare la situazione alla normalità dopo la chiusura dovuta a un blackout causato da un incendio in una sottostazione elettrica nell'ovest di Londra. L'aeroporto afferma di essere \"in grado di riavviare i voli in sicurezza\".   ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742616005.478844,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "LENTA RIPRESA DI VOLI A HEATHROW Black-out in a stop after a fire",
        "en_content": "Heathrow, partial resumption of flights Heathrow Airport announces the resumption of some flights in the evening and hopes to make a full service Saturday. The flights are already taken from the main London airport. In a note, the airport lets you know that you are working to bring the situation back to normal after the closure due to a blackout caused by a fire in an electrical substation in the west of London. The airport claims to be \"can restart the flights safely\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "LENTA RIPRESA DI VOLI A",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "HEATHROW Black",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Heathrow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Heathrow Airport",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TRUMP PRESENTA NUOVO JET:IL PIU' LETALE \"Stabilite linee guida tregua Ucraina\"  Sui dazi: \"Ci sarà flessibilità\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Trump: nuovo caccia F-47,il più potente Donald Trump annuncia il lancio di un nuovo jet militare. \"L'F-47 sarà il più potente della storia\", afferma in un discorso allo Studio Ovale. La Boeing costruirà il caccia di nuova generazione,il \"più letale aereo mai realizzato\" Poi sui dazi: il 2 aprile, data in cui entreranno in vigore, \"giorno della liberazione per l'America\". Ma \"ci sarà flessibilità\".E sulla Nato:\"E' forte ma senza di noi non sarebbe la stessa\". I partner \"devono trattarci bene\". Poi: \"Presto un cessate il fuoco completo tra Russia e Ucraina, stabilite le linee guida\".     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742616005.5072427,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "TRUMP PRESENTA NEW JET: THE LETAL PIU 'Stabilite guidelines tregua Ukraine' On duties: \"There will be flexibility\"",
        "en_content": "Trump: New F-47 fighter, the most powerful Donald Trump announces the launch of a new military jet. \"F-47 will be the most powerful in history,\" says in a speech at the Oval Studio. Boeing will build the next generation fighter, the \"most deadly aircraft ever made\" Then on duties: on 2 April, the date on which they will enter into force, \"the day of liberation for America\". But there will be flexibility. And on NATO: \"It's strong but without us it wouldn't be the same.\" Partners \"must treat us well.\" Then: \"I take a ceasefire between Russia and Ukraine, established the guidelines.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "TRUMP PRESENTA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Stabilite",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "F-47",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Oval Studio",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boeing",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2 April",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "America",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 540,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 551,
                "end_char": 558,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Londra, migliaia passeggeri a terra",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Black-out a Heathrow, migliaia a terra Decine di migliaia di passeggeri sono rimasti a terra per lo stop all'aeroporto di Heathrow. Lo scalo londinese è rimasto per circa 18 ore in completo black-out dopo l'incendio nella città di Hates alla sottocentrale elettrica che serve anche l'aeroporto.  Cancellati oltre 1.300 voli a Londra e disagi su scala mondiale.   Sull'incendio indaga l'antiterrorismo britannico. Ma per i Vigili del fuoco il rogo \"non è ritenuto sospetto\".  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742616005.530874,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "London, thousands of passengers on the ground",
        "en_content": "Black-out in Heathrow, thousands on the ground Tens of thousands of passengers remained on the ground for the stop at Heathrow Airport. The London airport remained for about 18 hours in complete black-out after the fire in the city of Hates at the power station that also serves the airport. Clear more than 1,300 flights to London and inconvenience on a global scale. The fire investigates British anti-terrorism. But for the Fire Department the Roke \"is not considered suspicious.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Heathrow",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tens of thousands",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Heathrow Airport",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 18 hours",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 1,300",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Fire Department",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 442,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GOVERNO ISRAELE SILURA CAPO DEGLI 007  Alta Corte congela il licenziamento",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Israele, licenziato capo 007 Shin Bet Il governo israeliano ha votato all' unanimità, nella notte, il licenziamento del direttore dello Shin Bet,il servizio di Intelligence interna.  Ronen Bar si dimetterà il 10 aprile o quando si troverà un sostituto idoneo. Bar non si è presentato alla riunione sul licenziamento, ma ha mandato una lettera molto critica verso il premier Netanyahu: non a lui devo lealtà ha scritto ma ai cittadini israeliani. L'Alta Corte di Giustizia israeliana ha respinto con un ordine temporaneo il licenziamento. E' scontro col governo. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742616005.537297,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-22 05:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T04.00.05",
        "en_title": "GOVERNMENT ISRAELE SILURE CAP OF 007 High Court freezes dismissal",
        "en_content": "Israel, dismissed Head 007 Shin Bet The Israeli government unanimously voted on the dismissal of the Director of Shin Bet, the Internal Intelligence Service. Ronen Bar will resign on April 10th or when you will find a suitable replacement. Bar did not meet at the dismissal meeting, but sent a very critical letter to Premier Netanyahu: not to him I owe loyalty he wrote but to Israeli citizens. The High Israeli Court of Justice has rejected a temporary dismissal. It's a government clash.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "007",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shin Bet",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Internal Intelligence Service",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ronen Bar",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "April 10th",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 326,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "The High Israeli Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
