[
    {
        "title": "Caso Mieli, Zanchini si scusa",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=128",
        "content": " Zanchini si scusa con Ester Mieli  Il direttore di Radiouno Pionati chiede a Zanchini di scusarsi con gli ascoltatori e la senatrice Ester Mieli dopo la puntata di Radio Anch'io.   Nella trasmissione in cui si parlava delle proteste nelle università per la guerra in Palestina, il conduttore ha chiesto a Mieli se lei fosse ebrea, suscitando l'indignazione della senatrice e un coro di polemiche.Pionati scrive a Zanchini:\"Certo della tua buona fede e delle tue doti professionali, credo necessario chiudere subito la polemica\". Zanchini: \"Mortificato, chiedo scusa, la mia intenzione era l'opposto\". ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.3293295,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Caso Mieli, Zanchini apologizes",
        "en_content": "Zanchini apologizes to Ester Mieli The director of Radiouno Pionati asks Zanchini to apologize to listeners and Senator Ester Mieli after the episode of Radio Anch'io. In the broadcast of protests in the universities for the war in Palestine, the conductor asked Mieli if she was Jewish, provoking the outrage of the senator and a chorus of polemics. Pionati writes to Zanchini: \"Cert of your good faith and professional skills, I think it is necessary to close the controversy immediately\". Zanchini: \"Mortified, I'm sorry, my intention was the opposite.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Caso Mieli",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanchini",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zanchini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ester Mieli",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Radiouno Pionati",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanchini",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ester Mieli",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Radio Anch'io",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mieli",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pionati",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanchini",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanchini",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CONDANNA DEFINITIVA PER ALFREDO COSPITO Cassazione conferma 23 anni carcere",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713999606.3352592,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "CONDANNA DEFINITIVA FOR ALFREDO COSPITO Cassazione confirms 23 years prison",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "23 years",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SERGIO: INACCETTABILI POLEMICHE SU RAI  Ad:su Scurati aspettare istruttoria",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " L'Ad Rai: inaccettabili tante polemiche \"Non dico chi sta facendo il male alla Rai. E' certo che tutto quello che facciamo viene sommerso da valanghe di polemiche molto spesso strumentali. E' inaccettabile\". Così l'Ad Rai Roberto Sergio, che sulla vicenda Scurati ribadisce:\"Aspettiamo la fine dell'istruttoria,ma non c'è stata alcuna censura\". Bolla come \"fake news\" le voci che danno in uscita dalla Rai Ranucci e Sciarelli.Stando a quanto si apprende, Sergio si sarebbe inoltre scusato con la senatrice Mieli, a cui il conduttore Zanchini aveva chiesto se fosse ebrea. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.3416624,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "SERGIO: INACCETTABILI POLEMICHE SU RAI Ad:su Scurati Waiting for instructor",
        "en_content": "The Ad Rai: unacceptable so much controversy \"I don't say who's hurting Rai. It is certain that all we do is submerged by avalanches of very often instrumental polemics. It's unacceptable.\" Thus the Ad Rai Roberto Sergio, who on the Scurati affair reiterates: \"We wait for the end of the investigation, but there was no censorship\". It boils as \"fake news\" the voices that give out from Rai Ranucci and Sciarelli. According to what is learned, Sergio would also apologize to Senator Mieli, whom conductor Zanchini had asked if he was Jewish.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SERGIO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Scurati Waiting",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Scurati",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai Ranucci",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sciarelli",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio",
                "start_char": 444,
                "end_char": 450,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mieli",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanchini",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 540,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SI' COMMISSIONE SENATO A DDL PREMIERATO Il provvedimento passa all'Aula",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Sì commissione Senato a Ddl premierato La commissione Affari costituzionali del Senato ha concluso l'esame del Ddl Casellati sul premierato approvando il mandato al relatore.    A favore ha votato la maggioranza col sì di FdI,FI,Lega,Autonomie, contro Pd, M5S,Avs,mentre Italia Viva si è astenuta.       La Conferenza dei capigruppo deve calendarizzare il provvedimento in Aula. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.3543777,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "THE COMMISSION OF THE PREMIERATED DDL The measure passes to the Chamber",
        "en_content": "Yes Senate Committee at Ddl Premiere The Senate Constitutional Affairs Committee concluded the examination of the Ddl Casellati on the Premiere approving the mandate to the rapporteur. In favor he voted the majority with yes of FdI,FI,Lega,Autonomie, against Pd, M5S,Avs,mentre Italia Viva has abstained. The Conference of Leaders must calendar the measure in the Chamber.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Senate Committee",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Senate Constitutional Affairs Committee",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ddl Casellati",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Premiere",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lega",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Autonomie",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Avs",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italia Viva",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Conference of Leaders",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 364,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PIANTEDOSI: \"SUBITO TUTELE PER AGENTI\"  \"Non rinviabile sì a Ddl sicurezza\"",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Piantedosi: \"Subito tutele per agenti\" \"Livelli ottimali di sicurezza nelle università, nel pieno rispetto dell'autonomia degli atenei e dei loro organi di governo\". Così il ministro dell'Interno Piantedosi,alla Camera.\"Il governo non ha cambiato le regole improntate a a equilibrio e moderazione\".  Il ministro auspica la rapida approvazione del Disegno di legge sulla sicurezza, che ha come pilastro la tutela delle forze di polizia.\"Misure non procrastinabili,come dimostrano i fatti di ieri a Torino.Lo dobbiamo a donne e uomini in divisa esposti a aggressioni\". ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.3817644,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "PIANTEDOSI: \"SUBITO ALL PER AGENTI\" \"Not delayable yes to Ddl security\"",
        "en_content": "Planned: \"Inflated suits for agents\" \"optimal levels of security in universities, in full respect of the autonomy of the universities and their governing bodies\". \"The government has not changed the rules marked by balance and moderation.\" The Minister hopes for the rapid approval of the Security bill, which has as its pillar the protection of police forces. \"Non-procrastinal measures, as demonstrated by yesterday's events in Turin. We owe it to women and men in uniform exposed to aggression.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ddl",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Security",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turin",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MAGGIORANZA: RIPETERE VOTO SU AUTONOMIA Battuta su un emendamento del M5S",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Autonomia,maggioranza: ripetere il voto Il presidente della Commissione Affari Costituzionali della Camera Pagano ha proposto la ripetizione del voto su un emendamento del M5S sull'Autonomia, sul quale la maggioranza è stata battuta. La votazione sarebbe da ripetere perché non era stato ufficializzato l'esito del voto, secondo la maggioranza.  Insorgono le opposizioni. \"Il voto si può ripetere solo in caso di irregolarità che qui non ci sono state\",dice il M5S.Il Pd \"non riconosce più la terzietà del presidente\". Il nuovo voto sull'emendamento si terrà venerdì.  ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.3872805,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "MAGGIORANCE: REPLACE ON AUTONOMIA Beats on an M5S amendment",
        "en_content": "Autonomy, majority: repeat vote The president of the Constitutional Affairs Committee of the Pagan Chamber has proposed the repetition of the vote on an amendment of the M5S on Autonomy, on which the majority has been beaten. The vote would be repeated because the outcome of the vote was not official, according to the majority. Oppositions arise. \"The vote can only be repeated if there were no irregularities here,\" says M5S. The Pd \"no longer recognizes the president's tertiage\". The new vote on the amendment will be held on Friday.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Constitutional Affairs Committee",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Pagan Chamber",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 537,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Vigilanza: no ad audizione Corsini",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=127",
        "content": " Scurati,Vigilanza: no audizione Corsini La Commissione di Vigilanza Rai boccia l'audizione del direttore Approfondimenti Corsini e della conduttrice di 'Che Sarà' Bortone,dopo la mancata partecipazione di Scurati al programma. La maggioranza ha votato contro la proposta di Graziano del Pd e sostenuta da tutta l'opposizione. La motivazione è quella di voler attendere l'esito dell' indagine interna.     Non è passata neanche la richiesta la della minoranza di ascoltare Corsini e Bortone dopo l'audizione dei vertici Rai in programma l'8 maggio.   ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.4337459,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Supervisory: no audizione Corsini",
        "en_content": "Discurati,Vigilanza: no audizione Corsini The Commission of Vigilance Rai rejects the audition of the Director Approfondimenti Corsini and the conductor of 'Che sarà' Bortone, after the non participation of Scurati in the program. The majority voted against the proposal by Graziano del Pd and supported by the whole opposition. The motivation is to want to wait for the outcome of the internal investigation. The minority's request to listen to Corsini and Bortone after the hearing of the Rai summits on May 8 was not passed.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Discurati",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vigilanza",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Corsini The Commission of Vigilance Rai",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Approfondimenti Corsini",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bortone",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Scurati",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Graziano del Pd",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Corsini",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bortone",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 8",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 511,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BANDO USA A TIKTOK, CEO SHOU: VINCEREMO \"Costituzione è dalla nostra parte\"",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Ungheria,Parlamento Ue: carenze diritti L'Eurocamera denuncia le carenze del sistema giudiziario ungherese, i conflitti di interesse, e le minacce alla libertà dei media e ai diritti fondamentali in Ungheria.    In una risoluzione approvata con 399 sì, 117 no e 28 astenuti, gli eurodeputi deplorano anche la decisione della Commissione di sbloccare fino a 10 mld di euro di fondi Ue congelati a Budapest. Il testo ha avuto voti favorevoli di Ppe, Socialisti Ue, Renew, Verdi e Sinistre. Contro: Ecr, Identità e Democrazia, incluse delegazioni FdI e Lega.",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713999606.4352515,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "BANDO USA To TIKTOK, CEO SHOU: \"Constitution is on our side\"",
        "en_content": "Hungary,Parliament EU: rights shortages The Eurocamera denounces the shortcomings of the Hungarian judiciary, conflicts of interest, and threats to media freedom and fundamental rights in Hungary. In a resolution adopted with 399 yes, 117 no and 28 abstentions, Eurodeputes also deplore the Commission's decision to release up to 10 billion euros of frozen EU funds in Budapest. The text had favorable votes of Ppe, EU Socialists, Renew, Greens and Left. Against: Ecr, Identity and Democracy, including FdI and League delegations.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "BANDO USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SHOU",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament EU",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Eurocamera",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungarian",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "399",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "117",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "28",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eurodeputes",
                "start_char": 262,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10 billion",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Budapest",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ppe",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU Socialists",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Renew",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 436,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greens",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Left",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecr",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "VERSO LO STOP AL NUMERO CHIUSO MEDICINA Immediata protesta camici bianchi",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Medicina, iscrizione libera 1° semestre Il Comitato ristretto della Commissione Istruzione del Senato ha adottato un testo base per lo stop al numero chiuso per l'accesso alle facoltà di Medicina. Ci si potrà iscrivere liberamente al primo semestre di Medicina e Chirurgia, Odontoiatria e protesi dentaria, Veterinaria,senza passare attraverso i test Verranno poi individuate le discipline da superare per l'ammissione al secondo semestre.In caso di mancata ammissione, crediti utili per cambiare facoltà.  Contrario l'ordine dei medici: \"Produrremo solo disoccupati\".   ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.4474118,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Immediate protest white shirts",
        "en_content": "Medicine, free registration 1st semester The Senate Education Committee adopted a basic text to stop the closed number for access to the medical faculties. You can freely enroll in the first semester of Medicine and Surgery, Dentistry and Dental Prosthetics, Veterinaria, without passing through the tests The disciplines to be overcome for admission to the second semester will be identified. In case of non-admission, useful credits for changing faculties. Contrary to the order of doctors: \"We will only produce unemployed.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "1st",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Senate Education Committee",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the first semester",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dental Prosthetics",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Veterinaria",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Media:missili Atamcs già in Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Usa,ok Congresso aiuti a Kiev e Israele Il Congresso americano ha adottato un pacchetto per 61 mld di dollari di aiuti militari ed economici per l'Ucraina. Il piano,che comprende anche fondi per Israele e Taiwan e ammonta complessivamente a 95 miliardi, ha ricevuto un sostegno schiacciante al Senato, dopo la precedente adozione alla Camera.  \"Il Congresso ha risposto alla chiamata della storia\", ha detto il presidente Biden.I fondi sono il risultato di mesi di negoziati molto aspri,dei viaggi del presidente ucraino Zelensky a Washington e delle pressioni degli alleati. ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713999606.4713469,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Media:missiles Atamcs already in Ukraine",
        "en_content": "USA,ok Congress help Kiev and Israel The American Congress adopted a $61 billion package of military and economic aid for Ukraine. The plan, which also includes funds for Israel and Taiwan and totals 95 billion, received overwhelming support from the Senate after the previous adoption of the House. \"The Congress responded to the call of history,\" said President Biden. The funds are the result of months of very bitter negotiations, the trips of Ukrainian President Zelensky to Washington and the pressure of allies.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "$61 billion",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "95 billion",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 364,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "months",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 457,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ok Congresso ad aiuti Israele-Kiev",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Legge aiuti,Biden: Usa,mondo più sicuri \"La legge approvata dal Congresso renderà gli Stati Uniti e il mondo più sicuri. Se i nostri alleati sono più forti anche noi lo siamo\". Lo ha detto il presidente Usa Joe Biden parlando alla Casa Bianca dopo la firma del pacchetto di aiuti per Ucraina, Israele e Taiwan. \"Dobbiamo muoverci velocemente per fare arrivare gli aiuti all'Ucraina. Gli Usa non si piegano a nessuno, men che meno a Putin\", ha detto Biden che ha ribadito il \"ferreo sostegno\" a Israele che però deve \"aumentare l'assistenza umanitaria\" a Gaza.     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713999606.4754727,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Ok Israel-Kiev Aid Congress",
        "en_content": "Aid law,Biden: Use, safer world \"The law passed by Congress will make the United States and the world safer. If our allies are stronger we too are.\" President Joe Biden said this by speaking to the White House after signing the aid package for Ukraine, Israel and Taiwan. \"We must move quickly to get aid to Ukraine. The U.S. does not bend to anyone, less to Putin,\" said Biden, who reiterated the \"serious support\" to Israel, but must \"enhancing humanitarian assistance\" in Gaza.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AVS: \"SEGGIO MATTEOTTI SIA SIMBOLO\"",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Avs: \"Seggio di Matteotti sia simbolo\" La proposta è di dedicare alla memoria di Giacomo Matteotti il seggio alla Camera da cui pronunciò il suo ultimo discorso di denuncia delle sopraffazioni fasciste durante le elezioni politiche del 1924. L'ha formulata Devis Doris, deputato dell'Alleanza Verdi-Sinistra con una lettera al presidente della  Camera Lorenzo Fontana.    Il seggio di Matteotti, secondo Dori, non dovrebbe essere assegnato a nessun gruppo parlamentare. Inoltre verrebbe segnato con l'apposizione di una targa. Fontana sta valutando la proposta.  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.493654,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "AVS: \"Wait MATTEOTTI SIA SIMBOLO\"",
        "en_content": "Avs: \"The seat of Matteotti is a symbol\" The proposal is to dedicate to the memory of Giacomo Matteotti the seat to the Chamber from which he gave his last speech of denunciation of the fascist overflows during the political elections of 1924. Devis Doris, Member of the Verdi-Sinistra Alliance, wrote it with a letter to the President of the Chamber Lorenzo Fontana. The seat of Matteotti, according to Dori, should not be assigned to any parliamentary group. It would also be marked with a plate. Fontana is considering the proposal.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "AVS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "MATTEOTTI SIA",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Matteotti",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giacomo Matteotti",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1924",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Devis Doris",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Verdi-Sinistra Alliance",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Chamber Lorenzo Fontana",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Matteotti",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dori",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fontana",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Raid israeliani a Rafah e Nuseirat",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Gaza,bombe su Rafah e Nuseirat,vittime Tre persone sono morte e altre 4 sono rimaste ferite in un attacco israeliano che ieri sera ha colpito un edificio residenziale nel quartiere Salam della città di Rafah, nel sud della Striscia di Gaza: lo rendono noto i media arabi, citando fonti mediche palestinesi. E l'emittente araba Al Jazeera riferisce che 4 persone sono state uccise in un bombardamento israeliano vicino a una scuola nel campo profughi di Nuseirat, nel centro della Striscia. Colpiti anche il quartiere Zeitoun di Gaza City e il villaggio di Zawaida.   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713999606.539669,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Israeli Raids in Rafah and Nuseirat",
        "en_content": "Gaza,bombe on Rafah and Nuseirat,vittime Three people died and four others were injured in an Israeli attack that hit a residential building last night in the Salam district of the city of Rafah, in the south of the Gaza Strip: the Arab media, citing Palestinian medical sources. And the Arab issuer At Jazeera reports that 4 people were killed in an Israeli bombing near a school in the Nuseirat refugee camp, in the centre of the Strip. Also hit the Zeitoun district of Gaza City and the village of Zawaida.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nuseirat",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nuseirat",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Three",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "last night",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salam",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jazeera",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nuseirat",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 432,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zeitoun",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza City",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zawaida",
                "start_char": 501,
                "end_char": 508,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SPAGNA, SANCHEZ VALUTA LE DIMISSIONI   Moglie indagata dopo accuse destra",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Accuse moglie,Sanchez valuta dimissioni Il premier spagnolo Pedro Sanchez ha cancellato ogni impegno pubblico nei prossimi cinque giorni e ha annunciato di volersi prendere \"una pausa di riflessione\" per valutare se dimettersi dall'incarico dopo gli attacchi della destra alla moglie Begona Gomez.  Sanchez accusa il Partido Popular e Vox di aver avviato una \"strategia persecutoria in atto da mesi con l'obiettivo di fiaccarmi politicamente\", dice. La donna è accusata di traffico di in fluenze e corruzione legati alla sua attività in una università privata. Lunedì Sanchez prenderà una decisione. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713999606.5472736,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "SPAIN, SANCHEZ VALUTA LE DIMISSIONS Affected wife after right charges",
        "en_content": "Accuse wife,Sanchez resigns Spanish Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez canceled all public engagement in the next five days and announced he wanted to take \"a reflection break\" to assess whether to resign from the post after the attacks of the right to his wife Begona Gomez. Sanchez accuses the Partido Popular and Vox of starting a \"persecutory strategy in place for months with the goal of politically shaking me,\" he says. The woman is accused of traffic in fluences and corruption related to her activity in a private university. Monday Sanchez will make a decision.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SPAIN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "SANCHEZ VALUTA LE",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sanchez",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Sanchez",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the next five days",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Begona Gomez",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanchez",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Partido Popular",
                "start_char": 286,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vox",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "months",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 529,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanchez",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Video ostaggio,appello dei genitori",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Video ostaggio Israele,appello genitori L'Amministrazione Biden ha ricevuto  lunedì il video diffuso oggi da Hamas che mostra in vita l'ostaggio israeloamericano di 23 anni, Hersh GoldbergPolin. Lo riferisce un funzionario Usa alla Cnn: da allora le autorità sono in contatto con i familiari dell'ostaggio. L'Fbi sta esaminando il video. I genitori del ragazzo lanciano \"un appello ai leader e le parti\" impegnate nei negoziati in corso per il rilascio degli ostaggi,Qatar,Egitto,Usa,Hamas,Israele: \"Siate coraggiosi, determinati, a porre fine alla sofferenza nella regione\". ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713999606.549141,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Video hostage, call of parents",
        "en_content": "Video hostage Israel, call parents The Biden Administration received the video released today by Hamas on Monday showing the 23-year-old Israeli hostage, Hersh GoldbergPolin. A U.S. official reports it to the Cnn: since then the authorities are in contact with the family members of the hostage. The FBI is examining the video. The parents of the boy launch \"an appeal to leaders and parties\" engaged in ongoing negotiations for the release of hostages, Qatar, Egypt, Usa,Hamas, Israel: \"Be courageous, determined, to end suffering in the region.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Biden Administration",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "23-year-old",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hersh GoldbergPolin",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "FBI",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Qatar",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 479,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SVIMEZ,RESTA DIVARIO INFRASTRUTTURE SUD Sanità, letti 5 volte sotto media",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=136",
        "content": " Svimez: divario infrastutture al Sud Resta forte il divario di infrastrutture tra Nord e Sud del Paese,secondo la Svimez, in audizione alle Camere sul federalismo fiscale.Pochi i binari ferroviari nel Mezzogiorno,l'Alta velocità serve solo la Campania, tram e metropolitane sono praticamente inesistenti. La lunghezza dei binari è pari a 7.528 km, il 30% del totale nazionale.  Non va meglio nella Sanità:il numero di letti negli ospedali è ampiamente inferiore:98 in Sicilia,",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.5771008,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "SVIMEZ,RESTA DIVARIO INFRASTRUTTURES SUD Health, beds 5 times below average",
        "en_content": "Svimez: infrastutture gap in the South The gap between North and South of the country remains strong, according to Svimez, in audition to the Chambers on Tax Federalism. Few railway tracks in the Mezzogiorno, the High Speed serves only Campania, trams and metros are practically nonexistent. The track length is 7.528 km, 30% of the national total. It is not better in Health: the number of beds in hospitals is widely lower:98 in Sicily,",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SVIMEZ",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "North",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Svimez",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mezzogiorno",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Campania",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "7.528 km",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "30%",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Health",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sicily",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.5840886,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PARLAMENTO UE: UNGHERIA,CARENZA DIRITTI \"Minacce alla libertà dei media\"",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Media:missili Atamcs già inviati a Kiev Gli Stati Uniti hanno già inviato segretamente in Ucraina i missili a lungo Raggio Atamcs. La consegna sarebbe avvenuta la settimana scorsa. Lo rivelano i media Usa fra cui il New York Times e Politico.      I missili sono già stati utilizzati  mercoledì scorso per attaccare un aeroporto militare russo in Crimea e nella notte di martedì per bersagliare le  truppe russe nella città portuale di Berdiansk sul Mar d'Azov. I nuovi missili forniti all'Ucraina hanno una gittata di circa 300 chilometri.  ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713999606.6152987,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "EU PARLIAMENT: UNGHERIA,CHARGE OF RIGHTS \"Enjoy media freedom\"",
        "en_content": "Media:missiles Atamcs already sent to Kiev The United States have already secretly sent to Ukraine the missiles long Raggio Atamcs. The delivery would take place last week. The media reveal it Use the New York Times and Politics. The missiles have already been used last Wednesday to attack a Russian military airport in Crimea and on Tuesday night to target Russian troops in the port city of Berdiansk on the Azov Sea. The new missiles supplied to Ukraine have a range of about 300 kilometers.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "UNGHERIA",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev The",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raggio Atamcs",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last week",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the New York Times and Politics",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 228,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last Wednesday",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday night",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Berdiansk",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Azov Sea",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 457,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 300 kilometers",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ANTITRUST MULTA AMAZON PER 10 MILIONI  Per pratica commerciale scorretta",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Antitrust multa Amazon per 10 milioni Pratica commerciale scorretta. Con questa motivazione l'Autorità garante della concorrenza e del mercato (Agcm) ha comminato una multa ad Amazon pari a 10 milioni di euro.    Per un'ampia selezione di prodotti viene preimpostata l'opzione \"acquisto periodico\"anziché\"acquisto singolo\",fatto che limiterebbe la libertà di scelta dei consumatori,spiega Agcm in una nota \"Inoltre,la condotta attuata dal gruppo è stata ritenuta in contrasto con il canone di diligenza professionale\".  Amazon esprime forte disaccordo per la decisione e annuncia ricorso.  ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.665228,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "ANTITRUST MULTA AMAZON FOR 10 MILIONS For incorrect commercial practice",
        "en_content": "Antitrust fine Amazon for 10 million incorrect commercial practice. With this reason, the Competition and Market Authority (Agcm) has fined Amazon to 10 million euros. For a wide selection of products, the option \"period purchase\" is preset instead of \"single purchase\",which would limit the freedom of choice of consumers,explains Agcm in a note \"In addition, the conduct implemented by the group has been considered in contrast with the canon of professional diligence\". Amazon expresses strong disagreement for the decision and announces appeal.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Amazon",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10 million",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Competition and Market Authority",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Amazon",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10 million",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amazon",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GIORGETTI: DEF SU LAVORO,TUTELA REDDITI Sì Camere a risoluzione maggioranza",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Giorgetti:Def su lavoro,nascite,reddito \"Il programmatico chi lo vuole lo trova\".Lo ha detto il ministro dell'Economia Giorgetti,alla Camera sul Def che contiene solo il quadro tendenziale di finanza pubblica.     Giorgetti cita tre direzioni in cui si muove il governo.L'occupazione, ha detto,è ai massimi perché\"abbiamo investito sul lavoro,non sul sussidio\". \"Nell' ultima legge di bilancio abbiamo trovato risorse supplementari per conciliare maternità e lavoro\".Fatti\"sforzi a partire dalla decontribuzione, per tutela redditi bassi,famiglie numerose\".Camere approvano la risoluzione di maggioranza",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.690429,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "_ Yes majority resolution rooms",
        "en_content": "Giorgetti: Def on work, birth, published \"The programmatic who wants to find it\". The Minister of Economy Giorgetti said this, at the Chamber on the Def, which contains only the framework of public finance. Giorgetti mentions three directions in which the government moves. The occupation, he said, is at the most because \"we invested in work, not on subsidies\". \"In the last budget law we found additional resources to reconcile maternity and work.\" Facts from decontribution, for low income protection, numerous families\". Chambers approve majority resolution",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Chamber on the Def",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "VERSO STOP AL NUMERO CHIUSO A MEDICINA  Iscrizione libera il primo semestre",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713999606.7021692,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "VERSO STOP AL NUMBER CHIUSO A MEDICINA Free entry the first semester",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PONTI DI PRIMAVERA,SPESA SALE DEL 10,5% Lo rivelano le stime di Assoutenti",
        "date_raw": "April 25, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-25",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=135",
        "content": " Ponti di Primavera,spesa sale del 10,5% I ponti di Primavera costeranno agli italiani circa il 10,5% in più rispetto allo scorso anno, a causa dei forti aumenti di prezzi e tariffe in tutto il settore turistico e dei trasporti. Lo rileva Assoutenti che stima un aumento di spesa di 780 milioni sul 2023.  Per le festività del 25 aprile e 1°  maggio si paga il 6,9% in più negli alberghi e +8,4% in altre strutture. Aumentati i voli del 19,1%:quelli europei del 16,5%, gli internazionali +7,3%. Non va meglio per chi usa l'auto:benzina più cara dell'8,3% da inizio anno. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713999606.740644,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-25 01:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-25T01.00.06",
        "en_title": "PUNTS OF PRIMAVERA, SALE SPESA OF 10.5% They reveal the estimates of Assoutenti",
        "en_content": "Spring Bridges, 10.5% salt Spring Bridges will cost Italians about 10.5% more than last year, due to strong price increases and rates throughout the tourist and transport sector. Assoutents estimates an increase of 780 million on 2023. For the holidays of 25 April and 1 May we pay 6.9% more in hotels and +8.4% in other facilities. Increased flights of 19.1%: European ones of 16.5%, international +7.3%. It is no better for those who use the car: more expensive than 8.3% from the beginning of the year.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "PRIMAVERA",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10.5%",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Assoutenti",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Spring Bridges",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10.5%",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Spring Bridges",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 10.5%",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "more than last year",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "780 million",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the holidays of 25 April",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1 May",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "6.9%",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "19.1%",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 369,
