[
    {
        "title": "MATTARELLA: CORDOGLIO PER MORTE RAISI  Meloni:\"Spero in futura ledership\"",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Mattarella: cordoglio per morte Raisi \"Esprimo il mio cordoglio per la morte del Presidente Ebrahim Raisi, del ministro degli Esteri Hossein Amir Abdollahian e di tutte le vittime della sciagura aerea che si è consumata nella giornata di ieri\", scrive Mattarella. La premier Meloni esprime \"solidarietà al governo e al popolo iraniano. Spero futura leadership s'impegni per stabilizzazione della regione\".   Il ministro degli Esteri Tajani:\"Ci auguriamo che la nuova dirigenza iraniana lavori per il dialogo\".   ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716210005.133132,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Mattarella: \"I express my sympathy for the death of President Ebrahim Raisi, Foreign Minister Hossein Amir Abdollahian and all the victims of the air disaster that was consumed yesterday,\" writes Mattarella. Prime Minister Meloni expresses \"solidarity to the government and the Iranian people. I hope future leadership is committed to stabilizing the region.\" Foreign Minister Tajani: \"We hope that the new Iranian leadership will work for dialogue.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "COSTRUZIONI, A MARZO PRODUZIONE -1,9%  Ma cresce la media del trimestre",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Costruzioni,a marzo produzione -1,9% A marzo 2024 si stima che l'indice destagionalizzato della produzione nelle costruzioni diminuisca dell'1,9% rispetto a febbraio.    Nella media del primo trimestre del  del 2024, la produzione nelle costruzioni, al netto della stagionalità, aumenta in termini congiunturali dell' 1,5% nel confronto con il trimestre  precedente. Così l'Istat.   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716210005.1363084,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "CONSTRUCTIONS, A MARCH PRODUCTION -1,9% But the average of the quarter",
        "en_content": "Construction in March production -1.9% In March 2024 it is estimated that the seasonal index of production in buildings decreased by 1.9% compared to February. On the average of the first quarter of 2024, production in buildings, net of seasonality, increases in conjunctural terms of 1.5% in comparison with the previous quarter. So Istat.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CONSTRUCTIONS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the quarter",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 2024",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "seasonal",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.9%",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "February",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the first quarter of 2024",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.5%",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the previous quarter",
                "start_char": 309,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DOMANI SCIOPERO TAXI DALLE 8 ALLE 22   \"No alla deregolamentazione\"",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Sciopero dei taxi,no deregolamentazione Sciopero nazionale dei taxi, domani  dalle 8 alle 22, con una manifestazione a Roma, dalle 11 alle 17, a piazza San Silvestro.     \"E' fondamentale la partecipazione di tutta la categoria a difesa del proprio lavoro, per contrastare l'uso illegittimo delle autorizzazioni da noleggio e salvaguardare la propria autonomia e indipendenza dalla schiavitù degli algoritmi e delle multinazionale\", spiega un comunicato delle sigle sindacali. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716210005.1574578,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Taxi strike, no deregulation National strike of taxis, tomorrow from 8 to 22, with an event in Rome, from 11 to 17, in Piazza San Silvestro. \"It is essential to participate in the entire category to defend its work, to counter the illegitimate use of rental authorizations and to safeguard its autonomy and independence from the slavery of algorithms and multinationals,\" explains a communiqué of trade union law.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "11 to 17",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza San Silvestro",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas e Hezbollah piangono perdita",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Hamas e Hezbollah piangono morte Raisi Dolore e vicinanza di Hamas e Hezbollah libanese per la morte di Raisi.  Hamas ha espresso le sue condoglianze e la sua solidarietà al regime di Teheran per l'incidente che ha portato alla  morte di Raisi,del ministro degli Esteri Hossein Amir Abdollahian e di quanti erano a bordo del loro elicotteo.Gli Hezbollah libanesi hanno reso omaggio a Raisi definendolo il \"protettore dei movimenti di resistenza\".   Solidarietà a Teheran per la \"grande perdita\" dal presidente egiziano Al Sisi e da quello siriano Assad.  ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.1601915,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "Hamas and Hezbollah cry loss",
        "en_content": "Hamas and Hezbollah mourn death Raisi Pain and closeness of Hamas and Hezbollah Lebanese for the death of Raisi. Hamas expressed his condolences and his solidarity with the Tehran regime for the incident that led to the death of Raisi, Foreign Minister Hossein Amir Abdollahian and those who were on board their helicopter. The Lebanese Hezbollah paid tribute to Raisi as the \"protector of resistance movements\". Solidarity with Tehran for the \"great loss\" by Egyptian President Al Sisi and Syrian President Assad.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanese",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanese",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 368,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Solidarity",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egyptian",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al Sisi",
                "start_char": 479,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syrian",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 497,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Assad",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UK, UN NUOVO RICORSO PER JULIAN ASSANGE Possibile contro l'estradizione Usa",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=159",
        "content": " Uk,un nuovo ricorso per Julian Assange Julian Assange avrà la possibilità di un nuovo ricorso contro l'estradizione negli Stati Uniti: lo hanno stabilito oggi i giudici dell'Alta corte di  Londra.      I magistrati, hanno ritenuto fondate le argomentazioni della difesa del cofondatore di Wikileaks sul timore di un processo non equo oltre oceano. Negli Stati Uniti Assange sarebbe processato per spionaggio. Diciassette i capi di accusa a suo carico, legati alla pubblicazione di documenti diplomatici. Rischia in Usa 175 anni di carcere. ",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.1630433,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "UK, A NEW RICORSO FOR JULIAN ASSANGE Possible against US extradition",
        "en_content": "Uk, a new appeal for Julian Assange Julian Assange will have the possibility of a new appeal against extradition in the United States: today the judges of the High Court of London. The magistrates found the defence arguments of Wikileaks' co-founder on fear of a process not fair beyond the ocean. In the United States Assange would be tried for espionage. Seventeen chiefs of charge, linked to the publication of diplomatic documents. He's in the U.S. 175 years in prison.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Uk",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Julian Assange",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Julian Assange",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the High Court of London",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Wikileaks",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Assange",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Seventeen",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "175 years",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716210005.1657844,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MORTE RAISI,RUSSIA E CINA:GRAVE PERDITA Per Putin \"Un politico eccezionale\"",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Morte Raisi,Russia e Cina:grave perdita \"Ebrahim Raisi e' stato un politico  eccezionale,ha dato un contributo prerezioso allo sviluppo delle relazioni di vicinato tra Iran e Russia. Cosi' il leader del Cremlino, in un telegramma di condoglianze indirizzato alla Guida Suprema Ali Khamenei. \"Una grande  tragedia,Raisi era vero amico di Mosca\" Il presidente cinese Xi Jinping ha definito la morte del presidente Raisi \"una grande perdita per la sua gente\". ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.1670837,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Morte Raisi,Russia and China:a great loss \"Ebrahim Raisi was an exceptional politician, made a valuable contribution to the development of the relations of the neighborhood between Iran and Russia. So the leader of the Kremlin, in a telegram of condolences addressed to the Supreme Ali Khamenei Guide. \"A great tragedy,Raisi was true friend of Moscow\" Chinese president Xi Jinping called the death of President Raisi \"a great loss for his people\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Morte Raisi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ali Khamenei",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi Jinping",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Le condoglianze dell'Unione europea",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Morte Raisi, le condoglianze dell'Ue \"L'Ue esprime sincere condoglianze per la morte del presidente iraniano Raisi e del ministro degli esteri Abdollahian nonché di altri membri della loro delegazione e dell'equipaggio in un incidente in elicottero\". Lo scrive su X il presidente del consiglio europeo Michel \"Voglio esprimere la solidarietà mia e dell'Italia al governo iraniano e al popolo iraniano\", ha detto la premier Meloni, ospite di Mattino cinque, su Canale 5, dopo la morte del presidente iraniano. Condoglianze anche dal ministro degli Esteri Tajani.   ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.217272,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "The condolences of the European Union",
        "en_content": "Death Raisi, the condolences of the EU \"The EU expresses sincere condolences for the death of Iranian President Raisi and Foreign Minister Abdollahian and other members of their delegation and crew in a helicopter accident\". On X the President of the European Council Michel \"I want to express my solidarity and Italy to the Iranian government and the Iranian people\", said Prime Minister Meloni, guest of Mattino five, on Channel 5, after the death of the Iranian president. Condoglianze also by Foreign Minister Tajani.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Death Raisi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Council",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "solidarity",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattino five",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Channel 5",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Condoglianze",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 514,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Convocata riunione urgente governo",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Morte Raisi,riunione urgente di governo Il governo iraniano ha convocato oggi un \"incontro urgente\" dopo l'annuncio della morte del presidente Ebrahim Raisi e del ministro degli Esteri del paese, coinvolti nell'incidente in elicottero nella provincia iraniana dell'Azerbaigian orientale,dove sono morte altre sei persone.Lo riporta l'agenzia di stampa statale iraniana Irna.  La sedia occupata solitamente da Raisi era vacante,drappeggiata con una fascia nera in memoria del presidente.  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.2438731,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "Convoy urgent meeting government",
        "en_content": "Morte Raisi, urgent meeting of government The Iranian government convened today an \"emergency meeting\" after the announcement of the death of President Ebrahim Raisi and the foreign minister of the country, involved in the helicopter accident in the Iranian province of East Azerbaijan, where six more people died. The Iranian state press agency Irna reports it. The chair usually occupied by Raisi was vacant, draped with a black band in memory of the president.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Morte Raisi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "six",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Irna",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Chi era Raisi, protetto di Khamenei",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Iran, chi è il presidente Raisi  Ebrahim Raisi,63 anni,ha vinto le elezioni presidenziali iraniane nel 2021. Figura intransigente, in passato a capo della magistratura, è considerato un protetto della Guida suprema Khamenei. Sotto Raisi, l'Iran arricchisce l'uranio a livelli quasi nucleari e ostacola le ispezioni internazionali, rafforza i legami con la Cina e si ritiene che abbia armato la Russia nella sua guerra contro l'Ucraina, oltre a lanciare un massiccio attacco con droni e missili contro Israele nel conflitto contro  Hamas a Gaza.Ha anche armato i ribelli Houthi in Yemen e Hezbollah in Libano. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.2763288,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "Who was Raisi, protected by Khamenei",
        "en_content": "Iran, who is President Raisi Ebrahim Raisi,63 years old, won the Iranian presidential elections in 2021. Intransigent figure, in the past at the head of the judiciary, is considered a protector of the Supreme Khamenei Guide. Under Raisi, Iran enriches uranium at almost nuclear levels and hinders international inspections, strengthens links with China and is believed to have armed Russia in its war against Ukraine, as well as launch a massive attack with drones and missiles against Israel in the conflict against Hamas in Gaza. He also armed the Houthi rebels in Yemen and Hezbollah in Lebanon.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi Ebrahim",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi,63 years old",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Khamenei Guide",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 492,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 526,
                "end_char": 530,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 550,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 567,
                "end_char": 572,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 577,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 590,
                "end_char": 597,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "STASERA BOLOGNA-JUVE CHIUDE IL 37°TURNO Playoff B si gioca Palermo-Venezia",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=201",
        "content": "     ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716210005.2855606,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "STASERA BOLOGNA-JUVE CHIUDE THE 37°TURNO Playoff B is played Palermo-Venezia",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "BOLOGNA-JUVE CHIUDE",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "37°",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palermo-Venezia",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAN, PRESIDENZIALI A GIUGNO O LUGLIO  Interim al vicepresidente Mokhber",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Iran, presidenziali a giugno o luglio In base alla Costituzione, le elezioni per eleggere un nuovo presidente dopo la morte di Ebraim Raisi potrebbero tenersi a giugno o luglio, comunque entro 50 giorni. L'agenzia Isna conferma che il primo vicepresidente iraniano Mohammad Mokhber,come prevede la costituzione del Paese, assumerà le funzioni del presidente Ebrahim Raisi, morto ieri in un incidente in elicottero.   Un consiglio speciale composto da tre persone deve organizzare le nuove elezioni.      ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.2895014,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "IRAN, PRESIDENTIAL TO JUNE OR JULY Interim to Vice-President Mokhber",
        "en_content": "Iran, Presidential in June or July According to the Constitution, elections to elect a new president after the death of Ebraim Raisi could be held in June or July, however within 50 days. The agency Isna confirms that the first Iranian vice-president Mohammad Mokhber, as foresees the constitution of the country, will assume the functions of President Ebrahim Raisi, who died yesterday in a helicopter accident. A special council composed of three people must organize the new elections.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mokhber",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "June",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "July",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebraim Raisi",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "June",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "July",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "50 days",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isna",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohammad Mokhber",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 443,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAN, 5 GIORNI DI LUTTO PER MORTE RAISI Scomparso ieri in incidente elicottero  I funerali domani a Tabriz",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Iran conferma: presidente Raisi è morto Il presidente iraniano Raisi e i passeggeri dell'elicottero schiantatosi nelle zone montuose del nordovest dell' Iran sono morti.L'Ayatollah Khamenei ha proclamato 5 giorni di lutto nazionale. I funerali domani a Tabriz.   \"Quando si è scoperta la posizione dell'elicottero,non si è trovata traccia di vita\",ha detto il capo dei soccorsi. A bordo c'erano anche il ministro degli Esteri Hossein Amir Abdollahian, il governatore della provincia dell'Azerbaigian orientale Malek Rahmati e l'imam del venerdì della città di Tabriz Mohammad Ali Ale Hashem.    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.2954483,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "IRAN, 5 LIGHT DAYS FOR MORTE RAISI Disappeared yesterday in helicopter crash funeral tomorrow at Tabriz",
        "en_content": "Iran confirms: President Raisi died Iranian President Raisi and passengers of the crashed helicopter in the mountainous areas of the northwest of Iran are dead. Ayatollah Khamenei proclaimed 5 days of national mourning. The funeral tomorrow at Tabriz. \"When you discovered the position of the helicopter, there was no trace of life,\" said the chief of rescue. On board were also Foreign Minister Hossein Amir Abdollahian, the governor of the province of East Azerbaijan Malek Rahmati and the imam of Friday of the city of Tabriz Mohammad Ali Ale Hashem.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 LIGHT DAYS",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ayatollah Khamenei",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 days",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir Abdollahian",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 420,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Azerbaijan",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Malek Rahmati",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz Mohammad Ali Ale Hashem",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Khamenei: \"Non ci saranno vuoti\"     Meloni convoca riunione ministri",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Morte Raisi,Khamenei: Non ci sarà vuoto L'Ue aveva attivato il sistema satellitare Copernicus. Arabia Saudita, Russia e Turchia hanno offerto assistenza. La Casa Bianca segue l'evoluzione della crisi,mentre da Roma la premier Meloni ha convocato un vertice a P.zzo Chigi. Riunione della Difesa a Mosca. Israele ha chiarito:noi\"estranei all'incidente\" Da Teheran la Guida Suprema Ali Khamenei aveva espresso l'auspicio che Dio riportasse \"l'onorevole presidente e i suoi compagni tra le braccia della nazione\".Assicurando che in ogni caso\"non ci saranno interruzioni\"nel lavoro del Paese.      ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716210005.2968256,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "Khamenei: \"There will be no voids\" Meloni summons meeting ministers",
        "en_content": "Death Raisi,Khamenei: The EU had activated the satellite system Copernicus. Saudi Arabia, Russia and Turkey offered assistance. The White House follows the evolution of the crisis, while from Rome Prime Minister Meloni has convened a summit in P.zzo Chigi. Defense meeting in Moscow. Israel clarified: \"we\" outside the incident\" From Tehran the Supreme Guide Ali Khamenei expressed the hope that God would report \"the honorable president and his companions in the arms of the nation\". Ensure that in any case \"there will be no interruptions\" in the work of the country.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Death Raisi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Copernicus",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The White House",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "P.zzo",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chigi",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ali Khamenei",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AUTO BLU FINI PRIVATI,MICCICHE'INDAGATO Scatta divieto di dimora a Cefalù",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716210005.3232226,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "AUTO BLU FINI PRIVATE,MICCICHE'INDAGATO Scatta prohibition of residence in Cefalù",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MICCICHE'INDAGATO Scatta",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cefalù",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MATTARELLA: CORDOGLIO PER MORTE RAISI  Meloni: Solidarietà al popolo iraniano  Tajani: Spero in futura leadership",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716210005.3623202,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ Solidarity with the Iranian people Tajani: I hope in future leadership",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Solidarity",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAN, 5 GIORNI DI LUTTO PER MORTE RAISI Trovati resti elicottero carbonizzato  Con lui anche il ministro degli esteri  Putin e Xi: \"Una grave perdita\"",
        "date_raw": "May 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716210005.5053113,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-20 15:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-20T15.00.05",
        "en_title": "IRAN, 5 LIGHT DAYS FOR MORTE RAISI He also found the foreign minister Putin and Xi: \"A serious loss\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 LIGHT DAYS",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    }
]
