[
    {
        "title": "Funzionario Teheran: no ritorsioni",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Media: \"Iran non pianifica ritorsioni\" Un alto funzionario iraniano ha affermato che Teheran non prevede una ritorsione immediata dopo l'azione militare di Israele di ieri notte. Lo scrive  l'agenzia russa Tass.    Intanto, una fonte israeliana ha detto al Washington Post che l'attacco è stato \"un segnale all'Iran che Israele ha la capacità di colpire all'interno del Paese\". Ma si è trattato, secondo il ministro per la Sicurezza nazionale Ben Gvir, di un \"attacco debole\" e una \"risposta deludente\" da parte di Israele all'aggressione dell'Iran.   ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713589206.9830704,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.06",
        "en_title": "Tehran: no retaliation",
        "en_content": "Media: \"Iran does not plan retaliation\" A senior Iranian official said that Tehran does not provide for immediate retaliation after Israel's military action last night. The Russian agency Tass writes it. Meanwhile, an Israeli source told the Washington Post that the attack was \"a signal to Iran that Israel has the ability to strike within the country\". But it was, according to the Minister for National Security Ben Gvir, a \"weak attack\" and a \" disappointing response\" by Israel to Iran's aggression.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last night",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Washington Post",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ben Gvir",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 482,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ATTACCO ALL'IRAN, COLPITA BASE AEREA   Tajani: connazionali sono al sicuro",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Israele attacca Iran,colpita base aerea Alle 4.30 ora italiana, Israele avrebbe lanciato un attacco contro l'Iran. Nei giorni scorsi aveva avvisato che avrebbe risposto alle centinaia di missili e droni arrivati da Teheran sabato notte. Colpita una base aerea militare vicino a Esfahan, Iran centrale. Antiaerea in azione anche a Tabriz. Ma dal governo israeliano non sono arrivate né rivendicazioni né dichiarazioni.   La Difesa siriana riferisce che è stata colpita una base nel sud siriano.Target anche l'Iraq, dicono i media turchi. Gli italiani presenti in Iran sono al sicuro, assicura il ministro Tajani. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713589206.9923918,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.06",
        "en_title": "ATTACCO ALL'IRAN, COLPITA BASE AEREA Tajani: compatriots are safe",
        "en_content": "Israel attacks Iran, blamed aerial base At 4.30 Italian time, Israel would launch an attack on Iran. In recent days he warned that he would respond to the hundreds of missiles and drones arrived from Tehran on Saturday night. Hit a military air base near Esfahan, Central Iran. Antiaircraft in action also in Tabriz. But from the Israeli government no claims or statements have come. The Syrian Defense reports that a base was struck in the south of Syria. They also target Iraq, say the Turkish media. The Italians present in Iran are safe, assures Minister Tajani.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ATTACCO ALL'IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4.30",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent days",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "hundreds",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "night",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esfahan",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Central Iran",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 309,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Syrian Defense",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 488,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 527,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Aiea e Iran: no danni siti nucleari",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Aiea,Iran: no danni a impianti nucleari L'Aiea non registra danni agli impianti nucleari iraniani dopo il raid di droni di Israele presso Esfahan.Così l'Agenzia internazionale per l'energia atomica conferma quanto già detto dall'Iran. La difesa di Teheran riferisce di aver abbattuto \"piccoli droni, forse partiti dall'interno, o oggetti volanti\",nessuna vittima né danni agli impianti nucleari.\"Israele ha già visto la risposta dell'Iran\",dice il comandante dell' esercito. E i media diffondono immagini di Esfahan tranquilla. Oggi l'ayatollah Khamenei compie 85 anni.\"Buon compleanno Khamenei\",scrivono molti sui social.",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713589206.999855,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.06",
        "en_title": "Aiea and Iran: no damage nuclear sites",
        "en_content": "Aiea, Iran: no damage to nuclear plants The Aiea does not damage Iranian nuclear installations after the Israeli drone raid at Esfahan. Thus the International Atomic Energy Agency confirms what has already been said by Iran. Tehran's defense reports that he has knocked down \"small drones, perhaps from within, or flying objects\", no victim or damage to nuclear plants. \"Israel has already seen the response of Iran,\" says the army commander. And the media spread pictures of Esfahan quiet. Today ayatollah Khamenei is 85 years old.\"Good birthday Khamenei\", write many on social media.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aiea",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esfahan",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Atomic Energy Agency",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esfahan",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "85 years old",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 555,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BLINKEN AL G7: EVITARE UN'ESCALATION   Usa chiari su Rafah: no operazione",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Blinken:evitare escalation,ruolo Italia La posizione Usa -ha detto il segretario di Stato Blinken al termine del G7 a Capriè quella di \"evitare l'escalation.Chiediamo a tutte le parti di controllare le loro azioni\".Su Rafah \"siamo stati molto chiari:non siamo favorevoli a un'operazione militare\".In Medio Oriente \"ruolo cruciale dell'Italia per una de-escalation\".    \"E' Hamas che impedisce un cessate il fuoco.Ha respinto le offerte d'Israele\" Attacco all'Iran? \"Usa non coinvolti in alcuna azione offensiva\". Palestina all'Onu \"non ora, lavori la diplomazia\". ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713589207.0040472,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ Use clear on Rafah: no operation",
        "en_content": "Blinken:avoid escalation,role Italy The US position - said the Secretary of State Blinken at the end of the G7 in Capri is to \"avoid escalation. We ask all parties to control their actions.\" On Rafah \"we were very clear: we are not in favour of a military operation\". In the Middle East \"a crucial role in Italy for a de-escalation\". \"It's Hamas that prevents a ceasefire. Has he rejected Israel's offerings\" Attack on Iran? \"Use not involved in any offensive action.\" Palestine at the UN \"not now, you work diplomacy.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of the",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Capri",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Attack on Iran",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "S&P CONFERMA IL RATING BBB PER L'ITALIA Dalle tabelle anche outlook stabile",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " S&P: Italia rating BBB, outlook stabile L'agenzia S&P conferma il rating dell' Italia a BBB con outlook stabile.Nessuna variazione rispetto alla pagella di ottobre. Una forma di cautela che rinvia all'autunno il giudizio vero,quando il Governo chiarirà con quali misure intende dare nuovo impulso alla crescita e ridurre il debito.    Debito che resta alto e viene stimato in aumento nel prosismo biennio a causa dei bonus edilizi, ma in parte compensato dai margini di miglioramento di un ritmo di crescita intorno all'1% e migliorabile grazie all'attuazione del Pnrr.      ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713589207.024298,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "S&P CONFERENCE THE RATING BBB PER L'ITALIA From tables also stable outlook",
        "en_content": "S&P: Italy BBB rating, stable outlook The S&P agency confirms the Italy rating to BBB with stable outlook. No change over the October page. A form of caution that refers to autumn the true judgment, when the Government will clarify with what measures it intends to give new impetus to growth and reduce debt. This debt remains high and is estimated to increase in biennial prosism due to building bonuses, but partly offset by the margins of improvement of a growth rate around 1% and improved thanks to the implementation of the Pnrr.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "S&P",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "S&P",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "BBB",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "October",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Government",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "biennial",
                "start_char": 364,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "around 1%",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAN CONFERMA MA NON ACCUSA ISRAELE   \"A Isfahan attacco piccoli droni\"",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Iran conferma:attacco con piccoli droni Le autorità iraniane hanno confermato ufficialmente che nella notte la città di Isfahan è stata attaccata senza però citare Israele come autore diretto. Il comandante delle forze di terra Heydari ha detto: \"Siamo riusciti ad affrontare droni molto piccoli. Hanno attaccato il nostro spazio aereo sulla città di Isfahan e le nostre difese aeree hanno hanno risposto\".    Poco prima il comandante in capo Mousavi aveva annunciato un'indagine sull' \"incidente\" notturno a Isfahan. Il presidente Raisi, parlando alla nazione, non vi aveva fatto cenno.   ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713589207.0685077,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Iran confirms: attack with small drones The Iranian authorities officially confirmed that in the night the city of Isfahan was attacked without mentioning Israel as a direct author. The commander of the land forces Heydari said: \"We managed to deal with very small drones. They attacked our airspace on the city of Isfahan and our air defenses responded.\" Shortly before Commander-in-Chief Mousavi announced an investigation into the night \"accident\" in Isfahan. President Raisi, speaking to the nation, did not mention it.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isfahan",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Heydari",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isfahan",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mousavi",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isfahan",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TAJANI: \"RIBADITO NO ATTACCO A RAFAH\"  Appello al termine del G7 di Capri",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713589207.0958939,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "TAJANI: \"NO ATTACCO A RAFAH\" Appeal at the end of the G7 of Capri",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Capri",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "S&P CONFERMA IL RATING BBB PER L'ITALIA Dalle tabelle anche outlook stabile",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713589207.1040409,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "S&P CONFERENCE THE RATING BBB PER L'ITALIA From tables also stable outlook",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "GP CINA, VERSTAPPEN VINCE SPRINT RACE  Davanti a Hamilton e Perez",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=201",
        "content": "     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713589207.123416,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "GP CINA, VERSTAPPEN VINCE SPRINT RACE In front of Hamilton and Perez",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamilton",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Perez",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAQ,BOMBARDATA BASE MILITARE,UN MORTO  Usa e Israele negano responsabilità",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Iraq,bombardata base militare,un morto Un bombardamento ha centrato nella notte una base militare nell'Iraq centrale che ospita truppe dell'esercito ed ex paramilitari filo-iraniani di Hachd alChaabi, integrati nelle forze regolari irachene.Lo hanno reso noto fonti della sicurezza irachene,che non hanno identificato i responsabili del raid. Colpiti veicoli, armi e attrezzature. Non è noto se l'attacco sia stato condotto con droni. Una delle fonti ha aggiunto che nel raid si contano un morto e 8 feriti tra le forze della base. Usa e Israele negano un coinvolgimento. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713589207.1275594,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Iraq, bombed military base, a dead One bombing centered on the night a military base in central Iraq which houses army troops and former pro-Iranian paramilitaries of Hachd alChaabi, integrated into Iraqi regular forces. It has been reported by Iraqi security sources, which have not identified the raiders. Hit vehicles, weapons and equipment. It is not known if the attack was conducted with drones. One of the sources added that the raid counts a dead and 8 wounded among the base forces. US and Israel deny involvement.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the night",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "pro-Iranian",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hachd",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 172,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraqi",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraqi",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 459,
                "end_char": 460,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ANPI: MAI VETI A CELEBRAZIONI 25 APRILE Sul palco il padre di Ilaria Salis",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Anpi: mai veti a celebrazioni 25 aprile \"Come Anpi non abbiamo mai posto veti per la partecipazione al nostro corteo. Sono sempre stati invitati tutti coloro che si sentono antifascisti e credono nella democrazia. Comunque, la Brigata ebraica -sempre invitatanon partecipa da anni\".Così la presidente Anpi di Roma Pierlonzi sulla richiesta degli studenti palestinesi di vietare i simboli sionisti nei cortei del 25 aprile. \"Dedichiamo la giornata alla pace.Spero che nessuno venga per provocare\",sottolinea. \"Salirà sul palco a Porta San  Paolo il padre di Ilaria Salis\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713589207.2523053,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "ANPI: MAI VETI A CELEBRAZIONI 25 APRIL On stage the father of Ilaria Salis",
        "en_content": "Bees: never seen at celebrations 25 April \"As Anpi we have never placed vetoes for participation in our procession. All those who feel anti-fascist and believe in democracy have always been invited. However, the Jewish Brigade - always invited has not participated for years.\" Thus President Anpi of Rome Pierlonzi on the request of Palestinian students to ban Zionist symbols in the courtes of 25 April. \"We give the day to peace. I hope no one comes to provoke,\" he says. \"The father of Ilaria Salis will be on stage in Porta San Paolo\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANPI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "25 April",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anpi",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "years",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anpi",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 333,
                "end_char": 344,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zionist",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 368,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "25 April",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 414,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilaria Salis",
                "start_char": 489,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Porta",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISRAELE ATTACCA L'IRAN,DRONI SU ISFAHAN Iran minimizza: no ritorsioni immediate Aiea: non colpiti impianti nucleari",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713589207.2917645,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "ISRAELE ATTACCA IRAN,DRONI SU ISFAHAN Iran minimizes: no immediate retaliation Aiea: not affected nuclear plants",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISRAELE ATTACCA IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "E taglia quello d'Israele per guerra132  LUNEDI' SCIOPERO TRENORD DALLE ORE TRE  Fino alle 2 di martedì 23 aprile",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Lunedì sciopero Trenord dalle ore 3  Il sindacato autonomo Orsa e la Uil  Trasporti hanno indetto uno sciopero del personale ferroviario in Lombardia, dalle 3 di lunedì 22 alle 2 di martedì 23 aprile.     Lo rende noto Trenord. Lunedì mattina viaggeranno i treni \"con partenza prevista dopo le ore 6 e arrivo a destinazione entro le ore 9\". La sera circoleranno quelli \"con partenza dopo le ore 18 e arrivo a destinazione entro le ore 21\". Per i collegamenti con l'aeroporto di Malpensa previsti bus sostitutivi. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713589207.3029468,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "And cut the one of Israel for war132 Until 2:00 on Tuesday 23 April",
        "en_content": "Monday strike Trenord from 3 pm The autonomous union Orsa and the Uil Trasporti have called a strike of the railway staff in Lombardy, from 3 of Monday 22 to 2 of Tuesday 23 April. It makes Trenord known. On Monday morning they will travel the trains \"with scheduled departure after 6 hours and arrival at destination within 9 hours\". In the evening they will circle those \"with departure after 18 hours and arrival at destination within 21 hours\". For connections with Malpensa airport provided replacement buses.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2:00",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday 23 April",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trenord",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 pm",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orsa",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Uil Trasporti",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombardy",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "22 to 2",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday 23 April",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trenord",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday morning",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 hours",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "9 hours",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "18 hours",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "21 hours",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Malpensa",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "G7 CAPRI 2024, SI CHIUDE IL VERTICE   Tajani:ribadito no attacco a Rafah",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Tajani: \"Ribadito no attacco a Rafah\" \"Abbiamo ribadito il no all'offensiva militare israeliana a Rafah e che il nostro obiettivo è quello di avere due Stati e due popoli\". Così il ministro degli Esteri Tajani, al termine del G7 a Capri.      Ribadito anche \"il nostro impegno a favore del cessate il fuoco immediato per garantire il rilascio degli ostaggi e l'arrivo degli aiuti umanitari alla popolazione palestinese\",aggiunge. E sottolinea il riconoscimento del G7 al lavoro italiano per il progetto Food for Gaza,\"riconosciuto strumento di pace\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713589207.4132292,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Tajani: \"No attack on Rafah\" \"We have reiterated the no to the Israeli military offensive in Rafah and that our goal is to have two states and two peoples.\" So the Foreign Minister Tajani, at the end of the G7 in Capri. Also referred to \"our commitment to ceasefire to ensure the release of hostages and the arrival of humanitarian aid to the Palestinian population\", added. And emphasizes the recognition of the G7 to Italian work for the project Food for Gaza,\" we can recognize instrument of peace\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Capri",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Food",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PENTAGONO PREPARA AIUTI MILITARI A KIEV Stoltenberg: sostegno anche da Nato",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Pentagono e Nato: aiuti militari a Kiev Il Pentagono sta preparando un pacchetto di aiuti militari per l'Ucraina, che include artiglieria e difese aeree. Lo riferiscono fonti ufficiali Usa citate da Politico. Molte armi statunitensi si trovano già negli arsenali europei e potrebbero essere consegnate rapidamente a Kiev.     Anche Stoltenberg (Nato) annuncia che \"i ministri della Difesa Nato hanno deciso un ulteriore sostegno militare a Kiev,compresa la difesa aerea.\"Abbiamo mappato le capacità degli Alleati.Oltre ai Patriot, presto forniti i Samp-T\". ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713589207.5025737,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "PENTAGE PREPARATION MILITARY AID TO KIEV Stoltenberg: support also from NATO",
        "en_content": "Pentagon and NATO: military aid in Kiev The Pentagon is preparing a package of military aid for Ukraine, which includes artillery and air defenses. US official sources quoted by Politico. Many US weapons are already found in European arsenals and could be delivered quickly to Kiev. Stoltenberg (Nato) also announces that \"the NATO Defence Ministers decided further military support in Kiev, including air defense. \"We have mapped the capabilities of the Allies. In addition to the Patriots, soon provided the Samp-T\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Politico",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nato",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 386,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Patriots",
                "start_char": 482,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "April 20, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713589207.7461412,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-20 07:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-20T07.00.07",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    }
]
