[
    {
        "title": "SUPERBONUS,TAJANI: PRONTI A MODIFICHE  Su europee: sfida tv sia per tutti",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Superbonus,Tajani: pronti a modifiche \"Sul Superbonus l'emendamento del Mef prevede di dettare nuove regole anche per i primi 6 mesi del 2024, che ormai sono quasi del tutto trascorsi.Avrebbe un valore retroattivo.Ma la retroattività delle norme mette a rischio la  credibilità delle istituzioni,significa allontanare investitori in un Paese che diventa poco affidabile\".Lo afferma il vicepremier Tajani sul Corsera, dove si dice anche pronto a modificare in Parlamento il testo del Mef.   Sulle europee,dice,la sfida tv va fatta tra tutti,non solo tra Meloni e Schlein",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.6719508,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "SUPERBONUS,TAJANI: MODIFIC PRONTS On Europeans: TV challenge for all",
        "en_content": "Superbonus, Tajani: ready to change \"On the Superbonus the Mef amendment plans to dictate new rules also for the first 6 months of 2024, which are almost completely over. It would have a retroactive value. But the retroactivity of the rules jeopardizes the credibility of the institutions, meaning to remove investors in a country that becomes unreliable.\" This is said by Vice-Premier Tajani on the Corsera, where he also says he is ready to change the text of the Mef in Parliament. On the Europeans, i.e. the TV challenge must be made among all, not only between Meloni and Schlein",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mef",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the first 6 months of 2024",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 386,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mef",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 566,
                "end_char": 572,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 577,
                "end_char": 584,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DIBATTITO ACCESO NEL GOVERNO SULLA LEVA Botta e risposta Salvini-Crosetto",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Dibattito acceso nel governo sulla leva Reintrodurre il servizio di leva obbligatorio.E' il tema affrontato nel giorno dell'adunata degli Alpini. E con il ritorno dei conflitti divide l'Europa. Dopo decenni di pace, il confronto si riaccende anche in Italia: il leader leghista Salvini è favorevole alla leva di 6 mesi per ragazzi e ragazze:\"Grande progetto di educazione civica\". Ma il ministro della Difesa, Crosetto: simile ipotesi mai potrebbe riguardare le Forze armate \"che non possono essere pensate come luogo per educare i giovani, cosa che deve essere fatta in famiglia e a scuola.Noi formiamo professionisti\"",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.7124739,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "DIBATTITO ACCESO IN GOVERNMENT ON LEVA Bottle and response Salvini-Crosetto",
        "en_content": "Debate lit in the government on the lever Introduce the mandatory lever service. It's the theme addressed on the day of the Alpine gathering. And with the return of conflicts divides Europe. After decades of peace, the confrontation also rekindles in Italy: the Leghista leader Salvini is favorable to the lever of 6 months for boys and girls: \"Great project of civic education\". But the Minister of Defense, Crosetto: such hypothesis could never concern the Armed Forces \"which can not be thought as a place to educate young people, which must be done in the family and at school. We train professionals\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "DIBATTITO ACCESO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini-Crosetto",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alpine",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "decades",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leghista",
                "start_char": 262,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 months",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Armed Forces",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "V.DER LEYEN: ITALIA MESSA BENE SUL PNRR \"Ha usufruito di oltre 50% dei fondi\"  Serve Europa forte, anche la Difesa",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " V.der Leyen: serve Europa forte e coesa \"C'è molto in gioco, dipenderà molto dal fatto che tutti vadano a votare.C'è in gioco la coesione dell'Europa,abbiamo bisogno di una Europa forte che protegga, sia solidale, e che viva i  nostri valori comuni come lo stato di diritto e la solidarietà\". Lo ha detto Ursula von der Leyen, presidente della Commissione Europea, ospite da Fazio. Sull'Italia, von der Leyen ha affermato che \"Roma è molto ben messa per l'implementazione del Pnrr e ha già usufruito di oltre la metà dei fondi\". Va poi rafforzata la difesa Ue.   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.7392907,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "V.DER LEYEN: ITALY MESSA BENE ON PNRR \"It has benefited more than 50% of the funds\" Serves Europe strong, also Defense",
        "en_content": "V.der Leyen: Europe needs strong and cohesive \"There is a lot at stake, it will depend a lot on the fact that everyone goes to vote. The cohesion of Europe is at stake, we need a strong Europe that protects, is solidarity, and that lives our common values as the rule of law and solidarity\". Ursula von der Leyen, President of the European Commission, guest of Fazio. On Italy, von der Leyen said that \"Rome is very well placed for the implementation of the Pnrr and has already enjoyed more than half of the funds\". The Ue defense must be strengthened.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "V.DER LEYEN: ITALY MESSA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 50%",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Serves Europe",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "V.der Leyen",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "solidarity",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ursula von der Leyen",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fazio",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "von der Leyen",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 407,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than half",
                "start_char": 487,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ANM: NO ALLA SEPARAZIONE DELLE CARRIERE Conte:svolta autoritaria,ricorda P2 120  UNIVERSITA' ITALIANE PERDONO POSIZIONI  La Sapienza prima in Italia è 124ma",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715587207.747437,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "ANM: NO TO THE SEPARATION OF CARRIERE Count: sometimes authoritarian, recall P2 120 Italian UNIVERSITY PERDONO POSIZIONI Wisdom first in Italy is 124ma",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANM",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "P2 120",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "124ma",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.7843316,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CROSETTO: ANM SUGGERISCA TIPO CONTROLLO \"Affinché la giustizia sia terza\"",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Crosetto:\"Schifato da chi scarica Toti\" \"Mi fanno ribrezzo persone che speculano su vicende di questo tipo.Ho visto dichiarazioni di un ministro di FI che scarica Toti.Queste cose non le sopporto più\". Cosi il ministro Crosetto a La Stampa.\"In Italia c'è un clima pesante, preoccupante,che incide in modo intollerabile anche sulla vita personale\". Magistratura politicizzata? \"Ci sono correnti, quindi è politicizzata\". \"C'è un potere che non ha più controlli. In cui anche un singolo Pm,se è arrabbiato con qualcuno, può distruggerlo.Suggerisca l'Anm che tipo di controllo serve perché la giustizia sia terza\".  ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.8228502,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "CROSETTO: ANM TYPE CONTROLLER \"Why justice is third\"",
        "en_content": "Crosetto: \"Schifato da chi download Toti\" \"I rebrezzo people who speculate on events of this type. I've seen statements from a FI minister who dumps Toti. I can't stand these things anymore.\" Thus the Minister Crosetto in La Stampa \"In Italy there is a heavy, worrying climate, which affects in an intolerable way also on personal life\". Politicalized judiciary? \"There are currents, so it's politicized.\" \"There is a power that no longer has control. In which even a single Pm, if he is angry with someone, can destroy him. Suggest Anm what kind of control it is for justice to be third.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "dumps Toti",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Stampa",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 582,
                "end_char": 587,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCHLEIN:SU TOTI MINISTRI FANNO AVVOCATI \"Corruzione?Noi prendiamo distanze\"",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Corruzione, Schlein: noi ci distanziamo \"La differenza tra noi e loro è che, quando arrivano delle indagini, siamo i primi a prendere le distanze, a pretendere dimissioni. Dall'altra parte,invece,quando arriva l'arresto di un presidente di Regione,i ministri si mettono a fare gli avvocati d'ufficio\". Così la segretaria del Pd Schlein, sull'inchiesta che coinvolge il governatore Toti. Riguardo alle parole del governatore della Campania De Luca sul parroco di Caivano,Patriciello:\"Dileggio o vituperio non ci appartengono.Ringraziamo chi s'impegna nel contrasto alle mafie\". ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.8324661,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ We take distance\"",
        "en_content": "Corruption, Schlein: we distance ourselves \"The difference between us and them is that, when investigations arrive, we are the first to distance ourselves, to demand resignation. On the other hand, when the arrest of a president of the Region arrives, the ministers put themselves to do office lawyers.\" So the secretary of the Pd Schlein, on the investigation involving Governor Toti. Regarding the words of the governor of Campania De Luca on the parish priest of Caivano,Patriciello: \"Dileggio or vituperio do not belong to us. Let's thank those who commit themselves in contrast to the mafia.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Pd Schlein",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 384,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Campania De Luca",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caivano,Patriciello",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "vituperio",
                "start_char": 500,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UCRAINA, ARMATA RUSSA AVANZA SU KHARKIV Kiev: tutta la linea sotto il fuoco   Putin rimuove Ministro Difesa Shoigu150  ISRAELE: \"SOLDATI VANNO AVANTI A RAFAH\" Riavere ostaggi e distruggere Hamas",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715587207.8571942,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "UCRAINA, RUSSA ADVANCED ON KHARKIV Kiev: all line under fire Putin removes Minister Defense Shoigu150 ISRAELE: \"SOLDATI VANNO AVANTI A RAFAH\" Rehabilitate hostages and destroy Hamas",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ISRAELE",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SOLDATI VANNO AVANTI",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CONTE: SVOLTA AUTORITARIA,RICORDA LA P2 Ad Anm: contro separazione carriere",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Conte: svolta autoritaria,ricorda la P2 \"Un patto scellerato, un compromesso di potere per garantire permanenza al governo\". Così il leader M5S Conte, al congresso nazionale Anm.   \"Il quadro complessivo di queste riforme\" è \"avventurismo politico\". Imprime \"una svolta autoritaria che rivela un' assonanza con il piano della P2\".Il M5S resta contrario alla separazione delle carriere dei magistrati.Il governo vuole \"il magistrato requirente assoggettato al potere politico\".Denuncia \"perversi intrecci tra politica e affarismo.Respingere attacchi a magistratura\"",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.860957,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "CONTACT: SVOLTA AUTORITARIA,RICORDA LA P2 Ad Anm: against career separation",
        "en_content": "Count: authoritarian turn, recalls the P2 \"A slender pact, a compromise of power to guarantee permanence to the government\". So the leader M5S Conte, at the National Congress Anm. \"The overall picture of these reforms\" is \"political adventure\". Impresses \"an authoritarian breakthrough that reveals an assonance with the P2 plan\". The M5S remains contrary to the separation of the careers of magistrates. The government wants \"the demand magistrate subjected to political power.\" Denunciation \"perverse interweaving between politics and businessism. Rejecting juggling attacks\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "P2",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "M5S Conte",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Congress Anm",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Impresses",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "P2",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "M5S",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "businessism",
                "start_char": 537,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ANM: NO ALLA SEPARAZIONE DELLE CARRIERE Approvata la mozione congressuale",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Anm:non separare carriere,pm indebolito Approvata all'unanimità la mozione finale del Congresso dell'Anm.\"La separazione delle carriere non è affatto funzionale a garantire la terzietà del  giudice,ma appare strumento per indebolire in modo sostanziale il ruolo del pubblico ministero\", recita il testo. La magistratura dice no anche al \"complessivo indebolimento del Csm, unico presidio a tutela dell'autonomia e indipendenza dei magistrati\". L'Anm promuove una \"mobilitazione culturale e comunicativa per informare sulla propria opposizione alla riforma\".  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.876843,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "ANM: NO TO THE SEPARATION OF CARRIERS",
        "en_content": "Anm:not separating careers,pm weakened unanimously approved the final motion of the Anm Congress.\"The separation of careers is not at all functional to guarantee the court's tertience, but it appears instrument to substantially weaken the role of the public ministry\", the text states. The judiciary also says to the \"complex weakening of the Csm, the only presidium to protect the autonomy and independence of the magistrates\". Anm promotes a \"cultural and communicative mobilization to inform about its opposition to reform\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANM",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Anm Congress",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Csm",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "INCHIESTA GENOVA, NUMERI COVID GONFIATI Si apre anche il filone sulla sanità   Imprenditore Spinelli torna dal Gip",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715587207.8820055,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "GENOVA INQUIRY, COVID NUMERS WOMEN Also opens the thread on health Entrepreneur Spinelli back from Gip",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GENOVA INQUIRY",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Spinelli",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"Magistrati non in silenzio coatto\"",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Anm:\"Magistrati non in silenzio coatto\" \"Abbiamo fatto questo congresso per fare una riflessione sulle critiche ricevute\",ma \"i magistrati possono e devono partecipare alla discussione pubblica. Devono farlo con il profilo di un magistrato.Ma non possono restare in un silenzio coatto\".Così il presidente dell' Anm Santalucia, chiude il congresso. La riforma \"metterebbe in pericolo l' indipendenza della magistratura.Quindi, al ministro Nordio diciamo:teniamoci l' indipendenza che abbiamo\". La giustizia \"è ancora lenta,ma recupera efficienza. Ridotti arretrati e tempi dei processi\"",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715587207.8966718,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "\"Magistrates not in forced silence\"",
        "en_content": "Anm: \"Magistrates not in forced silence\" \"We did this congress to reflect on the criticisms received\", but \"the magistrates can and must participate in the public discussion. They have to do it with a magistrate's profile. But they cannot remain in a forced silence.\" Thus the president of Anm Santalucia, closes the congress. The reform \"would jeopardize the independence of judiciary. So, to the minister Nordio we say: let's keep the independence we have.\" Justice \"is still slow, but recovers efficiency. Retreat and process times\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "congress",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anm Santalucia",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "congress",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 413,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "INONDAZIONI, 41 MORTI A SUMATRA",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=159",
        "content": " Sumatra, piove e cola lava: 41 morti Inondazioni e colate di lava fredda  sull'isola indonesiana di Sumatra:almeno 41 morti,17 dispersi,decine i feriti Gli allagamenti sono stati causati dalle piogge monsoniche e dai torrenti di lava fredda e fango che sono scesi lungo le pendici del vulcano Monte Merapi. Interi villaggi di montagna sono stati spazzati via dalle acque che hanno sommerso case ed edifici. La lava fredda è una miscela di materiale vulcanico e di ciottoli che scorre lungo le pendici di un vulcano sotto la pioggia.   ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715587207.907019,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "INONDATIONS, 41 MORTS",
        "en_content": "Sumatra, rain and lava cola: 41 dead Floods and cold lava flows on the Indonesian island of Sumatra: at least 41 dead,17 missing, dozen wounded The floods were caused by monsoon rains and streams of cold lava and mud that descended along the slopes of the Monte Merapi volcano. Entire mountain villages were swept away by the waters that submerged houses and buildings. Cold lava is a mixture of volcanic material and pebbles flowing along the slopes of a volcano in the rain.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "41",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "MORTS",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sumatra",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "41",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indonesian",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sumatra",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 41",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "dead,17",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozen",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monte Merapi",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISRAELE: \"SOLDATI VANNO AVANTI A RAFAH\" Distruggere Hamas, riavere ostaggi",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Idf: avanti a Rafah,per riavere ostaggi \"Le Forze di Difesa di Israele stanno continuando la loro operazione mirata contro Hamas a Rafah come parte degli sforzi per ottenere una duratura sconfitta di Hamas e per portare a casa  tutti i nostri ostaggi\". Lo ha detto il portavoce dell'Idf, Hagari,in un video su Telegram. \"La nostra guerra è contro Hamas, non contro la popolazione di Gaza\", ha precisato.    \"Le nostre operazioni contro Hamas a Rafah sono limitate e mirano a progressi e aggiustamenti tattici e militari,e a evitare aree densamente popolate\". ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715587207.9280832,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "ISRAELE: \"SOLDI VANNO AVANTI A RAFAH\" Destroy Hamas, have hostages",
        "en_content": "Idf: Go ahead to Rafah, to have hostages \"The Defense Forces of Israel are continuing their targeted operation against Hamas at Rafah as part of the efforts to achieve a lasting defeat of Hamas and to bring home all our hostages.\" The Idf spokesman Hagari said in a video on Telegram. \"Our war is against Hamas, not against the people of Gaza,\" he said. \"Our operations against Hamas at Rafah are limited and aim for tactical and military progress and adjustments, and to avoid densely populated areas.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISRAELE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SOLDI VANNO AVANTI A RAFAH\" Destroy Hamas",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Defense Forces of Israel",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hagari",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PUTIN RIMUOVE IL MINISTRO DELLA DIFESA  Shoigu trasferito alla Sicurezza",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Putin rimuove il ministro della Difesa Shoigu tolto alla Difesa e messo a capo della Sicurezza della Russia. E al posto di Shoigu arriverebbe Belusov. Il presidente russo Vladimir Putin ha licenziato Nikolai Patrushev dalla carica di segretario del Consiglio di Sicurezza russo \"in connessione con la transizione a un altro lavoro\". Lo riporta Ria Novosti secondo cui il capo del Cremlino ha nominato al suo posto Serghei Shoigu, che finora ha ricoperto l'incarico di ministro della Difesa. E Putin ha proposto la nomina di Andrey Belusov al posto di Shoigu.  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715587207.9452195,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Putin removes Defense Minister Shoigu removed from Defense and put in charge of Russia's Security. And instead of Shoigu, Belusov would come. Russian President Vladimir Putin fired Nikolai Patrushev from the office of Secretary of the Russian Security Council \"in connection with the transition to another job\". Ria Novosti reports that the head of the Kremlin appointed Serghei Shoigu, who has so far served as Minister of Defense. And Putin proposed the appointment of Andrey Belusov instead of Shoigu.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Shoigu",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shoigu",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belusov",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nikolai Patrushev",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Security Council",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ria Novosti",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Serghei Shoigu",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 442,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrey Belusov",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shoigu",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 503,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa ribadiscono:no operazione Rafah 157  CATALOGNA,SCONFITTA PER INDIPENDENTISTI Persa la maggioranza in Parlamento",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Catalogna,sconfitta per indipendentisti Per la prima volta da tredici anni, i partiti a favore dell'indipendenza hanno perso la maggioranza nel Parlamento catalano alle elezioni vinte dal candidato socialista del Psc, Salvador Illa. Con il 95% dei voti scrutinati, le tre forze indipendentiste, Junts dell'ex presidente Puigdemont, Esquerra Republicana de Catalunya (Erc) del governatore uscente Pere Aragones e l'anticapitalista Cup ottengono complessivamente 59 seggi dei 135 della Camera catalana,distanti dalla maggioranza assoluta di 68.     ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715587207.9543936,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "Use reiterate:no operation Rafah 157 CATALOGNA,SCONFICT FOR INDIPENDENTISTI Lost majority in Parliament",
        "en_content": "Catalonia, self-employed For the first time in thirteen years, independence parties have lost a majority in the Catalan Parliament in the elections won by the Socialist candidate of the PSC, Salvador Illa. With 95% of the votes cast, the three independent forces, Junts of former president Puigdemont, Esquerra Republicana de Catalunya (Erc) of the outgoing governor Pere Aragones and the anti-capitalist Cup total 59 seats of 135 of the Catalan Chamber, leaving the absolute majority of 68.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "157",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "CATALOGNA,SCONFICT FOR INDIPENDENTISTI Lost",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Catalonia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "thirteen years",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Catalan Parliament",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Socialist",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "PSC",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvador Illa",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "95%",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Junts",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 269,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Puigdemont",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esquerra Republicana de Catalunya",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pere Aragones",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "59",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "135",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Catalan Chamber",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "68",
                "start_char": 488,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mosca accusa: \"Usate armi Nato\"",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Russia:attacco a Belgorod con armi Nato \"Il brutale attacco terroristico da  parte del regime di Kiev contro i quartieri pacifici di Belgorod è stato effettuato con armi fornite dalla Nato\". Lo denuncia la missione russa presso l'Osce in un messaggio sul suo canale Telegram rilanciato dalla Tass.  \"Esortiamo la leadership Osce, in primo luogo l'attuale presidenza di Malta, a denunciare l'atto criminale il più duramente possibile\", si legge. \"E' inaccettabile ignorare ostentatamente le vittime civili tra i russi, sia a Belgorod,nel Donbass o altrove\", aggiunge.",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715587207.9578965,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.07",
        "en_title": "Moscow charges: \"Use NATO weapons\"",
        "en_content": "Russia: attack on Belgorod with NATO weapons \"The brutal terrorist attack by the Kiev regime against the peaceful neighborhoods of Belgorod was carried out with weapons provided by NATO\". He denounces the Russian mission at the Osce in a message on his channel Telegram relaunched by the Tass. \"We urge the Osce leadership, first of all the current presidency of Malta, to denounce the criminal act as hard as possible,\" we read. \"It is unacceptable to ignore the civilian victims among the Russians, either in Belgorod, Donbass or elsewhere,\" he adds.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Osce",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 261,
                "end_char": 269,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Osce",
                "start_char": 307,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Malta",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 368,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 519,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donbass",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "4000 evacuati in regione di Kharkiv",
        "date_raw": "May 13, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Ucraina:\"Aree Karkhiv passate ai russi\" L'unità Gostri Kartuzi delle forze speciali Omega della guardia nazionale ucraina ha dichiarato di essere stata costretta a abbandonare alcune posizioni nel nord della regione di Karkhiv per il pesante assalto russo e che aree popolate sono passate sotto il controllo nemico. Evacuate 4mila persone. \"Le perdite russe sono massicce,ma continuano a fare pressione e in alcuni punti hanno avuto successo\", si legge nel messaggio su X dell'unità.  Il governatore di Karkhiv: tutta la linea del fronte è \"sotto il fuoco russo\"",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715587208.048158,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 10:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T10.00.08",
        "en_title": "4000 evacuates in Kharkiv region",
        "en_content": "Ukraine:\"Karkhiv areas passed to the Russians\" The Gostri Kartuzi unit of the special Omega forces of the Ukrainian national guard has declared that it was forced to abandon some positions in the north of the Karkhiv region for the heavy Russian assault and that populated areas have passed under enemy control. Evacuate 4,000 people. \"Russian losses are massive, but they continue to press and in some points have been successful,\" reads in the X message of the unit. The governor of Karkhiv: the whole line of the front is \"under Russian fire\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "4000",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Omega",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karkhiv",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "4,000",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karkhiv",
                "start_char": 485,
                "end_char": 492,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 532,
                "end_char": 539,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    }
]
