[
    {
        "title": "Usa:da oggi alluminio-acciaio a 25%",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Usa, al via dazi su acciaio e alluminio Sono entrati in vigore i dazi del 25% su acciaio e alluminio voluti dal presidente Trump.     Il presidente americano aveva già tassato l'import per acciaio e alluminio nel suo primo mandato (2017-2021). La nuova tassa -ha assicurato a inizio febbraio quando l'ha annunciatasarà \"senza eccezioni e senza esenzioni\". Ha già protestato l'Australia, che si è vista negare un'esenzione all'ultimo minuto. Dazi \"totalmente ingiustificati\",ha detto il premier Albanese, \"questo non è un atto amichevole\".  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1741784404.3059428,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "Use:from today aluminum-steel to 25%",
        "en_content": "The customs duties of 25% on steel and aluminium were entered into force on the steel and aluminum wanted by President Trump. The American president had already taxed the import for steel and aluminum in his first term (2017-2021). The new tax -insured in early February when it announced will be \"without exception and without exemptions\". It has already protested Australia, which has been seen to deny a last-minute exemption. Dazi \"totally unjustified\", said Prime Minister Albanese, \"this is not a friendly act\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2017-2021",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "early February",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 366,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last-minute",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dazi",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Albanese",
                "start_char": 478,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BCE: ELEVATA INCERTEZZA,PRONTI AD AGIRE \"Difficile prevedere effetti dazi\"",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Bce:incertezza elevata,pronti ad agire \"L'incertezza economica e geopolitica è eccezionalmente alta\",ma \"la nostra risposta alla recente inflazione deve dare fiducia che faremo tutto il necessario per assicurare la stabilità dei  prezzi\". Così la presidente della Bce Lagarde.      Dazi e aumento della spesa per la difesa \"hanno effetti a due facce:potrebbere spingere l'inflazione verso l'alto, ma i dazi Usa potrebbero anche ridurre la domanda di esportazioni Ue\" e portare a un calo dell'infalzione.\"Difficile prevedere direzione degli shock\"",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1741784404.3307526,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "ECB: ELEVATA INCERTEZZA,PRONTI AD AGIRE \"Difficult to predict duties effects\"",
        "en_content": "BCE: high uncertainty, ready to act \"economic and geopolitical uncertainty is exceptionally high\", but \"our response to recent inflation must give confidence that we will do everything we need to ensure price stability\". So the president of the Bce Lagarde. Dazi and increased defence spending \"have two-sided effects: it could push upward inflation, but US duties could also reduce EU export demand\" and lead to a decline in inflation. \"Difficult to predict shock direction\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ECB",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Dazi",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ANCHE CINA PROMETTE RISPOSTE A DAZI   \"Tutto il necessario per tutelarci\"",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Cina: su dazi Usa \"tutto il necessario\" Dopo la Ue, anche Pechino annuncia misure in risposta ai dazi Usa sull'import di Acciaio e alluminio.  Le tariffe decise dagli Usa \"violano gravemente le regole\" dell'Organizzazione del commercio e \"danneggiano gravemente il sistema commerciale multilaterale basato sulle regole\", ha detto la portavoce del ministero degli Esteri cinesi Mao Ning.    La Cina adotterà \"tutte le misure necssarie\" per proteggere i propri interessi.      ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1741784404.332416,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "China: on US duties \"everything necessary\" After the EU, Beijing also announces measures in response to US duties on steel and aluminium imports. The tariffs decided by the U.S. \"graviously violate the rules\" of the Trade Organization and \"damag seriously the multilateral trade system based on rules\", said the spokesman of the Chinese Foreign Ministry Mao Ning. China will adopt \"all necssarious measures\" to protect its interests.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Trade Organization",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Chinese Foreign Ministry",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mao Ning",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 364,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tensione Usa-Canada, poi rientra",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=135",
        "content": " Tensioni Usa-Canada su dazi import In risposta a una tariffa del 25% annunciata dal premier della provincia canadese dell'Ontario Ford sull'elettricità fornita a 3 Stati confinanti (New York, Michigan e Minnesota), il presidente Usa ha annunciato che avrebbe raddoppiato dal 25 al 50% i dazi su acciaio e alluminio canadesi.   Poi il premier dell'Ontario ha annunciato di aver sospeso la tariffa e Trump ha detto che, probabilmente,potrà riconsiderare la faccenda. Trump aveva anche prospettato dal 2/4 dazi sulle auto che avrebbe \"fatto chiudere definitivamente l'automotive\" canadese. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1741784404.3349578,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "U.S.-Canada Voltage, then back",
        "en_content": "US-Canada Tensions on import duties In response to a 25% tariff announced by Ontario Ford's Canadian province's premier on electricity supplied to 3 neighbouring states (New York, Michigan and Minnesota), US President announced that it would double from 25 to 50% Canadian steel and aluminum duties. Then Ontario's premier announced that he had suspended the tariff and Trump said that he would probably reconsider the matter. Trump had also predicted from the 2/4 car duties that would \"end the automotive\" Canadian.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Ontario Ford's",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michigan",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Minnesota",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25 to 50%",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ontario",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2/4",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RIARMO UE,ARRIVA IL SI' DALL'EUROCAMERA Risposte \"come in tempo di guerra\"",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1741784404.3911052,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "REARMEU,ARRIVA IL SI' FROM EUROPE Answers \"as in time of war\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ARRIVA IL SI'",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EUROPE",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI:\"SODDISFAZIONE PER ESITO GEDDA\"  \"Ora decisione spetta alla Russia\"",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Meloni: soddisfazione per esito Gedda La presidente del Consiglio Giorgia Meloni\"accoglie con soddisfazione l'esito dei colloqui tenutisi a Gedda tra gli Stati Uniti e l'Ucraina,con particolare riferimento alla proposta di un cessate il fuoco di 30 giorni e alla ripresa dell'assistenza americana a Kiev\". Lo riferisce una nota di Palazzo Chigi: \"L'Italia sostiene pienamente gli sforz degli Stati Uniti, sotto la guida del Presidente Trump, a favore di una pace giusta che garantisca la sicurezza di lungo periodo dell'Ucraina. Ora la decisione spetta alla Russia\".   ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1741784404.4115589,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Meloni: Satisfaction for Gedda The President of the Giorgia Meloni Council welcomes the outcome of the talks held in Gedda between the United States and Ukraine, with particular reference to the proposal for a ceasefire of 30 days and the resumption of American assistance in Kiev\". A note from Palazzo Chigi: \"Italy fully supports the efforts of the United States, under the leadership of President Trump, in favor of a just peace that guarantees long-term security of Ukraine. Now the decision is for Russia.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Giorgia Meloni Council",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gedda",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 days",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MIGLIORI ATENEI AL MONDO, ITALIA AL TOP Sapienza è prima per le \"classiche\"",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1741784404.4316401,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "BEST ATENEI AL MONDO, ITALY AL TOP Sapienza is first for the \"classes\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ITALY",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UE: \"A USA DAZI FORTI E PROPORZIONATI\"  Da aprile, ma \"aperti al dialogo\"",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Dazi Usa,Ue deplora e annuncia risposta La Commissione europea ha annunciato che applicherà dazi doganali \"forti ma proporzionati\" su una serie di prodotti Usa dal primo aprile, in risposta ai dazi al 25% su acciaio e alluminio.  Contromisure per 26mld di euro a fronte di 28mld di dollari dalle misure Usa. La Ue, si legge in una nota della presidente von der Leyen, \"deplora profondamente\" le misure Usa. \"Sono un male per le imprese e ancora peggio per i consumatori. Sono fonte di incertezza per l'economia. Posti di lavoro a rischio.Prezzi saliranno in Ue e in Usa\". Poi: Ue pronta a dialogo significativo.",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1741784404.4462337,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "EU: \"To USA DAZI FORTI AND PROPORZIONATI\" From April, but \"open to dialogue\"",
        "en_content": "Dazi Usa, EU regrets and announces response The European Commission has announced that it will apply \"strong but proportionate\" customs duties on a series of U.S. products from 1 April, in response to duties to 25% on steel and aluminum. Countermeasures for €26mld in front of $28mld by US measures. The EU, reads in a note by President von der Leyen, \"deplores deeply\" the US measures. \"They are bad for businesses and even worse for consumers. I'm a source of uncertainty for the economy. Workplaces at risk. Prices will go up to the EU and the US.\" Then: It is ready for meaningful dialogue.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "To USA DAZI FORTI",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "April",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Dazi Usa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The European Commission",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1 April",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "26mld",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "28mld",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 549,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FEMMINICIDI,SI'SENATO AL DDL SU SPOGLIE Partner-omicida non potrà decidere",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Femminicidi,sì Senato al Ddl su spoglie Il Senato ha approvato all'unanimità il disegno di legge che impedisce all' imputato dell'omicidio della propria moglie o compagna di disporne delle  spoglie mortali. Il via libera al Ddl di Giulia Bongiorno (Lega) con 107 sì. Il provvedimento mira ad impedire che l'imputato, facendo cremare le spoglie della vittima, possa distruggere una prova.Si prevede che non possa decidere l'inumazione o la cremazione della vittima \"dall'iscrizione nel registro degli indagati fino al passaggio in giudicato della sentenza di assoluzione\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1741784404.4582994,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Women, yes, Senate to the Ddl on spouts The Senate unanimously approved the bill which prevents the defendant from murdering his wife or companion to dispose of mortal remains. The freeway to the Ddl of Giulia Bongiorno (Lega) with 107 yes. The measure aims to prevent the defendant from cremating the victim's remains, from destroying evidence. It is expected that it cannot decide the inumation or cremation of the victim \"from the inscription in the register of the inquiries until the passage in judgement of the sentence of acquittal\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ddl",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ddl of Giulia Bongiorno",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lega",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "107",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "KIEV ACCETTA PIANO USA TREGUA 30 GIORNI Riparte consegna armi Usa a Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Ok Kiev a proposta 30 giorni di tregua L'Ucraina sostiene la proposta degli Stati Uniti di 30 giorni di cessate il fuoco nella guerra con la Russia.  Così il comunicato congiunto dell'incontro tra le due delegazioni a Gedda. Gli Usa revocano immediatamente la sospensione degli aiuti all'Ucraina e  e della condivisione di informazioni di Intelligence.     Usa e Ucraina hanno concordato di concludere l'accordo sui minerali \"prima possibile\". Rubio: ora la palla per la tregua è nel campo della Russia.  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1741784404.4597497,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "KIEV ACCEPT FLOOR USA TREGUA 30 DAYS US arms delivery to Ukraine",
        "en_content": "Ok Kiev proposed 30 days of truce Ukraine supports the United States proposal of 30 days of ceasefire in the war with Russia. Thus the joint communiqué of the meeting between the two delegations in Gedda. The US immediately revokes the suspension of aid to Ukraine and the sharing of intelligence information. USA and Ukraine agreed to conclude the agreement on minerals \"as soon as possible\". Rubio: now the ball for the truce is in the field of Russia.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "KIEV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "FLOOR USA TREGUA",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 days",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 days",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gedda",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rubio",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 447,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa-Russia,colloqui di intelligence",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Usa-Russa, colloqui tra le Intelligence Colloquio telefonico tra il capo della Cia Ratcliff e il direttore del Servizio informazioni estere Russo (Svr)  Naryshkin.Lo riferiscono i media russi. \"Raggiunto un accordo su contatti regolari tra i direttori dell'Svr e della Cia per aiutare a garantire stabilità e sicurezza internazionali\".   Intanto,secondo il ministro degli Esteri russo Lavrov, \"Europa e Regno Unito vogliono che il conflitto in Ucraina continui. Stanno preparando qualcosa\" per spingere gli Usa \"a un'azione aggressiva\" contro Mosca.   ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1741784404.4642434,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "USA-Russia, intelligence bulletin",
        "en_content": "U.S.-Russian, talks between Intelligence Phone interviews between the head of the CIA Ratcliff and the director of the Russian Foreign Information Service (Svr) Naryshkin. The Russian media report it. \"I agree on regular contacts between Svr and Cia directors to help ensure international stability and security.\" Meanwhile, according to Russian Foreign Minister Lavrov, \"Europe and the United Kingdom want the conflict in Ukraine to continue. They are preparing something\" to push the U.S. \"to aggressive action\" against Moscow.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Intelligence Phone",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "CIA",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ratcliff",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Foreign Information Service (Svr) Naryshkin",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Svr",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cia",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lavrov",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GROENLANDIA, TRIONFA IL CENTRODESTRA   Partito nazionalista al 2° posto",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Il centrodestra trionfa in Groenlandia Secondo la rete pubblica KNR, l'opposizione di centrodestra ha vinto le legislative in Groenlandia, in un voto segnato dall'avanzata dei nazionalisti che chiedono l'indipendenza in tempi brevi dell'isola artica,ambita da Trump Affluenza al 70%.     Il partito dei democratici,che si definisce social-liberale, ha quasi il 30% e ha più che triplicato i risultati del 2021. Il nazionalista Naleraq ha ottenuto il 24,5% dei voti. Ambientalisti e socialdemocratici, che erano insieme al governo, perdono entrambi il 15%.. Nessuno ha i 31 seggi di maggioranza ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1741784404.4742408,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "GROENLAND, TRIONFA THE CENTRODESTRA Nationalist Party at the 2nd place",
        "en_content": "The triumphal centre in Greenland According to the public network KNR, the center-right opposition won the laws in Greenland, in a vote marked by the advance of nationalists asking for independence in short times of the Arctic island, set by Trump Affluence to 70%. The Democratic Party, which is called social-liberal, has almost 30% and has more than tripled the results of 2021. Nationalist Naleraq obtained 24.5% of the votes. Environmentalists and social democrats, who were together with the government, both lose 15%. No one has 31 majority seats",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GROENLAND",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "TRIONFA",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2nd",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "KNR",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arctic",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump Affluence",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "70%",
                "start_char": 261,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "The Democratic Party",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "almost 30%",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nationalist",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naleraq",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "24.5%",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "democrats",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "15%",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 523,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "31",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "OMICIDIO POGGI,STASI:VERITA' PER CHIARA Oggi test coatto del Dna per Sempio",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1741784404.480135,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ Today Dna compulsory test for Sempio",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sempio",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RIARMO UE,ARRIVA IL SI' DALL'EUROCAMERA Risposte \"come in tempo di guerra\"",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Eurocamera,sì a piano per il riarmo Ue Via libera dell'Eurocamera con 419 voti a favore, 204 contrari e 46 astenuti al testo su libro bianco sul futuro della difesa europea che invita l'Ue ad agire con urgenza per garantire la propria sicurezza.     Il testo chiede che le risposte ai rischi esterni siano \"simili a quelle in tempo di guerra\" e \"accoglie con favore il piano Rearm Europe, proposto il 4 marzo 2025 dalla presidente della Commissione Ue Ursula von der Leyen\".  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1741784404.522518,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "REARMEU,ARRIVA IL SI' FROM EUROPE Answers \"as in time of war\"",
        "en_content": "Eurocamera, on the floor for the Eurocamera's rearmament with 419 votes in favour, 204 against and 46 abstentions on the White Paper on the future of European defence, which calls on the EU to act urgently to ensure its security. The text calls for answers to external risks to be \"like those in wartime\" and \"please accept the Rearm Europe plan, proposed on 4 March 2025 by the President of the Commission Ue Ursula von der Leyen\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ARRIVA IL SI'",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EUROPE",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Eurocamera",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eurocamera",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "419",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "204",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "46",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "4 March 2025",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ue Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MOSCA:TREGUA? MEGLIO NON CORRERE TROPPO Peskov:non esclusa call Putin-Trump",
        "date_raw": "March 12, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Cremlino: su tregua non correre troppo Il portavoce del Cremlino Peskov esorta a \"non correre troppo\" sull'ipotesi di accettazione di una tregua di 30 giorni con l'Ucraina, come emerso dai colloqui di Gedda tra Washington e Kiev.  \"Aspettiamo che il Segretario di Stato Usa Rubio e il consigliere per la Sicurezza Waltz ci forniscano i dettagli sulle negoziazioni e le intese rag giunte\", spiega Peskov.    \"Non è esclusa una conversazione telefonica ai massimi livelli\", tra Putin e Trump.      ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1741784404.5379522,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-12 14:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T13.00.04",
        "en_title": "MOSCA: _",
        "en_content": "Kremlin: on truce do not run too much The spokesman of the Kremlin Peskov urges to \"do not run too much\" on the hypothesis of acceptance of a 30-day truce with Ukraine, as emerged from the talks of Gedda between Washington and Kiev. \"We wait for US Secretary of State Rubio and Security Counselor Waltz to provide us with details on negotiations and agreements,\" explains Peskov. \"No telephone conversation is excluded at the highest level,\" between Putin and Trump.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MOSCA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "30-day",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gedda",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 262,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rubio",
                "start_char": 268,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Waltz",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peskov",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
