[
    {
        "title": "25 aprile,\"estremisti sono altrove\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Meloni: gli estremisti sono altrove  Per il 25 aprile \"l'anno scorso sono stata a deporre una corona di fiori con il presidente della Repubblica, come faccio sempre. Quello che dovevo dire sul fascismo l'ho detto 100 volte\". Così la premier Meloni nel punto stampa al termine del vertice Ue. \"In Italia gli estremisti stanno da un'altra parte e non in questo governo\", afferma. Poi parla di \"fake news\", anche sull' aborto: \"Chi vuole cambiare la 194 è la sinistra, non noi. Noi vogliamo garantire solo scelte libere\".   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.283029,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "25 April, \"extremists are elsewhere\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni: extremists are elsewhere For April 25, \"I was last year laying a crown of flowers with the President of the Republic, as I always do. What I had to say about fascism I said 100 times.\" So Premier Meloni at the press point at the end of the EU summit. \"In Italy extremists are on the other side and not in this government,\" he says. Then he talks about \"fake news\", also about abortion: \"Who wants to change the 194 is the left, not us. We want to guarantee only free choices.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "25 April",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "April 25",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "last year",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "100",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "194",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AGENZIA S&P TAGLIA IL RATING DI ISRAELE Per la guerra con hamas e tensioni",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Standard & Poor's taglia rating Israele S&P Global taglia i rating sovrani a lungo termine in valuta estera e locale di Israele ad \"A+\" da \"AA-\" e quelli a breve termine ad \"A-1\" da \"A-1+\".  L'outlook a lungo termine passa da stabile a negativo a causa del rischio che la guerra con Hamas e il confronto con Hezbollah possano\"aggravarsi o influenzare i parametri economici, fiscali e della bilancia dei pagamenti di Israele in modo più significativo di quanto attualmente previsto\", afferma l'agenzia di rating, che prevede un deficit in aumento fino all'8%.    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.2902157,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "AGENZIA S&P TAGLIA THE RATING OF ISRAELE For war with hamas and tensions",
        "en_content": "Standard & Poor's rating Israel S&P Global cuts long-term sovereign ratings in Israel's foreign and local currency to \"A+\" from \"AA-\" and short-term \"A-1\" ratings from \"A-1+\". The long-term outlook passes from stable to negative due to the risk that war with Hamas and comparison with Hezbollah can \"aggrave or influence the economic, tax and balance of payments of Israel more significantly than currently expected\", says the rating agency, which provides an increase deficit up to 8%.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "hamas",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Standard & Poor's",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "A+",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 366,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "8%",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UCRAINA, 8 MORTI IN RAID DNIPROPETROVSK Kiev:colpito aereo, Mosca:un guasto",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=159",
        "content": " Kiev:8 morti in attacchi Dnipropetrovsk Sono almeno 8,inclusi 2 bambini,i morti negli attacchi delle forze russe nella regione ucraina di Dnipropetrovsk. Lo riferisce il ministro dell'Interno Klymenko.Ferite altre 18 persone. A Dnipro distrutto un edificio residenziale e la stazione ferroviaria è stata danneggiata.\"Colpite anche Kryvyi Rih e Synelnykove\", scrive il presidente Zelensky. Le forze ucraine riferiscono di aver abbattuto per la prima volta un bombardiere a lungo raggio Tu-22M3 usato per lanciare missili cruise sulle città. Ma Mosca precisa:caduto per guasto tecnico",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.3057587,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "UCRAINA, 8 MORTI IN RAID DNIPROPETROVSK Kiev:air strike, Moscow:a failure",
        "en_content": "Kiev:8 dead in Dnipropetrovsk Attacks There are at least 8, including 2 children, the dead in the attacks of Russian forces in the Ukrainian region of Dnipropetrovsk. The Interior Minister Klymenko reports it. Ferite another 18 people. In Dnipro destroyed a residential building and the railway station was damaged. \"Kryvyi Rih and Synelnykove\" writes President Zelensky. The Ukrainian forces report that for the first time a long-range bomber Tu-22M3 used to launch cruise missiles on cities. But Moscow precise:fall for technical failure",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "UCRAINA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev:8",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dnipropetrovsk Attacks",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 8",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dnipropetrovsk",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Klymenko",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dnipro",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kryvyi Rih",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Synelnykove",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SALVINI: NON FARE PONTE DANNO INSENSATO \"Andare avanti dovere assoluto\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=127",
        "content": " Salvini: non fare Ponte danno insensato \"L'ossessione dei giornalisti è quando parte il Ponte, per me l'importante è che parta e non farlo sarebbe un danno economico, sociale ed ambientale senza senso\". Così il ministro dei Trasporti Salvini,sul Ponte sullo Stretto.\"Andare avanti è assolutamente un dovere\". \"Il ponte 15 anni fa non avrebbe risolto i problemi della Sicilia, oggi è  l'anello di congiunzione che unisce i 30 miliardi di euro di cantieri aperti in Sicilia e gli altri 30 in Calabria. Solo in Italia c'è un dibattito politico sulle opere pubbliche\".   ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.3491418,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "SALVINI: Do not do anything inseparable \"Go ahead absolute duty\"",
        "en_content": "Salvini: do not make Bridge unwise damage \"The obsession of journalists is when the Bridge leaves, for me the important thing is that I leave and not do it would be an economic, social and environmental harm without sense\". Thus the Minister of Transport Salvini, on the Bridge on the Strait.\"To move forward is absolutely a duty\". \"The bridge 15 years ago would not have solved the problems of Sicily, today is the link that unites the 30 billion euros of yards open in Sicily and the other 30 in Calabria. Only in Italy there is a political debate on public works\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bridge",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Bridge on the Strait",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "15 years ago",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sicily",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 billion",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sicily",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "30",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Calabria",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 516,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI: \"SPERO A GIUGNO EUROPA DIVERSA\" Draghi? \"Dibattito è filosofia\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Meloni: \"Spero a giugno Europa diversa\" \"Questo è l'ultimo Consiglio europeo di questa legislatura e nonostante il lavoro fatto in questi mesi, come quello sui migranti,spero che quando ci incontreremo a giugno saremo di fronte a un' Europa diversa\". Così la premier Meloni al termine del vertice Ue, auspicando un'Europa \"meno ideologica\".  Una possibile nomina di Draghi ai vertici Ue? \"Sono contenta che si parli di un italiano ma questo dibattito è filosofia\",sono \"i cittadini che decidono\" Candidatura di Salis alle Europee?\"Non cambia il lavoro del governo\".E ripete: \"Politicizzazione vicenda non aiuta\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.3522475,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "MELONI: \"WHEN A JUNE EUROPE DIVERSA\" Dragons? \"Beat is philosophy\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni: \"I hope in June Europe different\" \"This is the last European Council of this legislature and despite the work done in these months, like that on migrants, I hope that when we meet in June we will face a different Europe.\" So Prime Minister Meloni at the end of the EU summit, hoping for a \"less ideological\" Europe. A possible appointment of Dragons at the EU leaders? \"I'm glad you're talking about an Italian but this debate is philosophy,\" are \"the citizens who decide\" Salis' candidacy to Europeans? \"It doesn't change the government's work.\" And he repeats: \"Politicization does not help.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MELONI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "June",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last European Council",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "these months",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "June",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dragons",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 501,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Bilaterale con Ursula von der Leyen 123  EUROPEE, ILARIA SALIS CANDIDATA CON AVS Scelta per \"tutelare suoi diritti\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Europee, Avs: candidiamo Ilaria Salis \"Alleanza Verdi e Sinistra in accordo con Roberto Salis ha deciso di candidare sua figlia Ilaria, detenuta in Ungheria, in condizioni che violano gravemente i diritti delle persone, nelle proprie liste alle prossime elezioni europee\". Così Fratoianni e Bonelli  dell'Alleanza Verdi Sinistra.   E' una scelta, spiegano, \"che vuole  tutelare i diritti e la dignità di una europea, anche dall'inerzia delle autorità italiane per ottenere una rapida scarcerazione\".L'Ue \"riaffermi l'inviolabilità di diritti umani fondamentali\"",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.3598983,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "Bilateral with Ursula von der Leyen 123 EUROPEAN, ILARIA SALIS CANDIDATA WITH AVS Choice to \"protect its rights\"",
        "en_content": "European, Avs: we nominate Ilaria Salis \"Green and Left Alliance in agreement with Roberto Salis decided to nominate his daughter Ilaria, held in Hungary, under conditions that severely violate the rights of people, in their lists at the next European elections\". So Fratoianni and Bonelli of the Green Left Alliance. It is a choice, they explain, \"who wants to protect the rights and dignity of a European, also from the inertia of the Italian authorities to obtain rapid scarceness\". The EU \"reaffirms the inviolability of fundamental human rights\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen 123",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Avs",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilaria Salis \"Green",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Left Alliance",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Salis",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilaria",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fratoianni",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bonelli",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Green Left Alliance",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 398,
                "end_char": 406,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 490,
                "end_char": 492,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"Mia figlia non fugge dal processo\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Salis: mia figlia non fugge da processo \"Ilaria assume questa decisione non come via di fuga dal processo, ma per poter affrontare nella piena tutela dei suoi diritti. La strada politica decisa è la più coerente con il suo trascorso politico\".     Così Roberto Salis ha commentato in una nota la decisione di sua figlia di candidarsi alle prossime europee con Alleanza Verdi Sinistra. \"Confermo che mia figlia Ilaria Salis, nel carcere di Budapest, ha posto firma autenticata, alla presenza del console italiano in Ungheria, ai moduli per la candidatura\"",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.3895514,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "\"My daughter does not escape trial\"",
        "en_content": "Salis: My daughter does not escape from trial \"Ilaria takes this decision not as a way of escape from the process, but to be able to face in full protection of her rights. The decisive political path is the most consistent with its political past.\" So Roberto Salis commented in a note the decision of his daughter to apply for the next European with Alleanza Verdi Sinistra. \"I confirm that my daughter Ilaria Salis, in the prison of Budapest, has signed, in the presence of the Italian consul in Hungary, to the application forms\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ilaria",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Salis",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alleanza Verdi Sinistra",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilaria Salis",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Budapest",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ONU, VETO USA A INGRESSO PALESTINA    Dodici i sì, astenute Gb e Svizzera",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Onu,veto Usa a ingresso della Palestina Con il veto al Consiglio di Sicurezza Onu, gli Stati Uniti hanno bloccato la richiesta di accettare la Palestina  come Stato, nelle Nazioni Unite.  A chiedere il cambio di ruolo -ora si parla di Stato osservatore non membroera stata per bocca dell'Algeria la Lega Araba, in un nuovo tentativo dopo quello fallito nel 2011. \"La nostra posizione non è cambiata\", hanno ribadito gli Usa, mentre l'Algeria apprezza comunque il \"consenso schiacciante\". Per l'ingresso a pieno titolo 12 sì, Gb e Svizzera astenute e il no Usa. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.41475,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "UN, VETO USA INGRESS PALESTINA Twelve yes, astensi Gb and Switzerland",
        "en_content": "Onu,veto Usa a Entrance of Palestine With the veto to the UN Security Council, the United States blocked the request to accept Palestine as a state in the United Nations. To ask for the change of role - now we speak of state observer not member was in the mouth of Algeria the Arab League, in a new attempt after the failed one in 2011. \"Our position has not changed,\" the U.S. reiterated, while Algeria still appreciates \"the overwhelming consensus\". For full entry 12 yes, Gb and Switzerland abstained and no U.S.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "VETO USA INGRESS PALESTINA",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Twelve",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "astensi Gb",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the UN Security Council",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Nations",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Arab League",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2011",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "12",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 482,
                "end_char": 493,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FONTI USA NEGANO OK A ISRAELE SU RAFAH  \"Preoccupati per vittime civili\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Fonti Usa negano ok a Israele su Rafah L'amministrazione Biden è ancora preoccupata che una invasione israeliana di Rafah, nel sud di Gaza, possa portare a un grande numero di vittime civili.  Lo riferisce il sito Axios, citando dirigenti Usa che hanno negato categoricamente le indiscrezioni secondo cui la Casa Bianca avrebbe dato il via libera a una operazione a Rafah se Israele rinunciasse a colpire l'Iran come rappresaglia per l'attacco dello scorso fine settimana.      ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.4336386,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "U.S. FONTI NEGANO OK TO ISRAEL ON RAFAH \"Women for civilian victims\"",
        "en_content": "The Biden administration is still concerned that an Israeli invasion of Rafah, in southern Gaza, could lead to a large number of civilian casualties. This is reported by the Axios website, citing US leaders who have categorically denied the indiscretions that the White House would give way to an operation to Rafah if Israel gave up hitting Iran as a reprisal for the attack last weekend.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ISRAEL",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Axios",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last weekend",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Funzionario Teheran: no ritorsioni",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Media: \"Iran non pianifica ritorsioni\" Un alto funzionario iraniano ha affermato che Teheran non prevede una ritorsione immediata dopo l'azione militare di Israele della notte scorsa.Lo scrive l'agenzia russa Tass.    Intanto, una fonte israeliana ha detto al Washington Post che l'attacco è stato \"un segnale all'Iran che Israele ha la capacità di colpire all'interno del Paese\". Ma si è trattato, secondo il ministro per la Sicurezza nazionale Ben Gvir, di un \"attacco debole\" e una \"risposta deludente\" da parte di Israele all'aggressione dell'Iran.   ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.4789603,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "Tehran: no retaliation",
        "en_content": "Media: \"Iran does not plan retaliation\" A senior Iranian official said that Tehran does not provide for immediate retaliation after Israel's military action last night. The Russian agency Tass writes it. Meanwhile, an Israeli source told the Washington Post that the attack was \"a signal to Iran that Israel has the ability to strike within the country\". But it was, according to the Minister for National Security Ben Gvir, a \"weak attack\" and a \" disappointing response\" by Israel to Iran's aggression.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last night",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Washington Post",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ben Gvir",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 482,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IRAN CONFERMA MA NON ACCUSA ISRAELE   \"A Isfahan attacco piccoli droni\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Iran conferma:attacco con piccoli droni Le autorità iraniane hanno confermato ufficialmente che nella notte la città di Isfahan è stata attaccata senza però citare Israele come autore diretto. Il comandante delle forze di terra Heydari ha detto: \"Siamo riusciti ad affrontare droni molto piccoli. Hanno attaccato il nostro spazio aereo sulla città di Isfahan e le nostre difese aeree hanno hanno risposto\".    Poco prima il comandante in capo Mousavi aveva annunciato un'indagine sull' \"incidente\" notturno a Isfahan. Il presidente Raisi, parlando alla nazione, non vi aveva fatto cenno.   ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.485187,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Iran confirms: attack with small drones The Iranian authorities officially confirmed that in the night the city of Isfahan was attacked without mentioning Israel as a direct author. The commander of the land forces Heydari said: \"We managed to deal with very small drones. They attacked our airspace on the city of Isfahan and our air defenses responded.\" Shortly before Commander-in-Chief Mousavi announced an investigation into the night \"accident\" in Isfahan. President Raisi, speaking to the nation, did not mention it.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isfahan",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Heydari",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isfahan",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mousavi",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isfahan",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Cnn:Usa erano informati ma contrari",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Cnn: Usa non approvavano attacco a Iran Gli Stati Uniti non avevano dato il via libera alla risposta israeliana all'Iran. Lo riporta la Cnn, che cita fonti dell'amministrazione Biden. \"Noi non avevamo approvato la risposta\", ha detto un rappresentante del governo.  Avvertiti del possibile attacco \"entro 24 o 48 ore\", gli Usa aevano sottolineato che non lo avrebbero supportato\", riferiscono Nbc e Cnn. E proprio alla Cnn, poco prima dell'attacco, il ministro iraniano degli esteri aveva annunciato una reazione \"immediata e ai massimi livelli\" se Israele si fosse mosso",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.496246,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "Cnn:Usa were informed but contrary",
        "en_content": "Cnn: U.S. did not approve attack on Iran The U.S. did not give way to the Israeli response to Iran. The Cnn reports it, which mentions sources of the Biden administration. \"We didn't approve the answer,\" said a government representative. Warnings of the possible attack \"within 24 or 48 hours\", the U.S. pointed out that they would not support it,\" Nbc and Cnn report. And just before the attack, the Iranian Foreign Minister announced a \"immediate and high-level\" reaction if Israel had moved",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 or 48 hours",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 299,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nbc",
                "start_char": 349,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 477,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ATTACCO ALL'IRAN, COLPITA BASE AEREA   Tajani: connazionali sono al sicuro",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Israele attacca Iran,colpita base aerea Alle 4.30 ora italiana, Israele avrebbe lanciato un attacco contro l'Iran. Nei giorni scorsi aveva avvisato che avrebbe risposto alle centinaia di missili e droni arrivati da Teheran sabato notte. Colpita una base aerea militare vicino a Esfahan, Iran centrale. Antiaerea in azione anche a Tabriz. Ma dal governo israeliano non sono arrivate né rivendicazioni né dichiarazioni.   La Difesa siriana riferisce che è stata colpita una base nel sud siriano.Target anche l'Iraq, dicono i media turchi. Gli italiani presenti in Iran sono al sicuro, assicura il ministro Tajani. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.5264878,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "ATTACCO ALL'IRAN, COLPITA BASE AEREA Tajani: compatriots are safe",
        "en_content": "Israel attacks Iran, blamed aerial base At 4.30 Italian time, Israel would launch an attack on Iran. In recent days he warned that he would respond to the hundreds of missiles and drones arrived from Tehran on Saturday night. Hit a military air base near Esfahan, Central Iran. Antiaircraft in action also in Tabriz. But from the Israeli government no claims or statements have come. The Syrian Defense reports that a base was struck in the south of Syria. They also target Iraq, say the Turkish media. The Italians present in Iran are safe, assures Minister Tajani.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ATTACCO ALL'IRAN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4.30",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent days",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "hundreds",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "night",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esfahan",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Central Iran",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tabriz",
                "start_char": 309,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Syrian Defense",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 488,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 527,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "STUPRO PALERMO,PARTE PROCESSO PER 6",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713528005.5512383,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas: \"Una palese aggressione\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Veto Usa all'Onu,Anp:palese aggressione L'Autorità palestinese guidata da Abu Mazen ha criticato il veto degli Usa all'adesione dei palestinesi all'Onu, bollandolo come \"palese aggressione\" che spinge il Medio Oriente \"sull'orlo dell'abisso\".\"Questa politica aggressiva degli Stati Uniti nei confronti della Palestina, del suo popolo e dei suoi diritti legittimi rappresenta un palese attacco al diritto internazionale\".  Hamas condanna il veto e \"assicura al mondo che il nostro popolo proseguirà nella sua lotta fino alla creazione di uno stato palestinese indipendente con Gerusalemme come capitale\".  ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.5597918,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "Hamas: \"A blatant aggression\"",
        "en_content": "Veto Usa all'Onu,Anp:palese aggression The Palestinian Authority led by Abu Mazen criticized the veto of the U.S. to the adhesion of Palestinians to the UN, branding it as \"palese aggression\" that pushes the Middle East \"on the edge of the abyss\". \"This aggressive policy of the United States against Palestine, its people and its legitimate rights is a blatant attack on international law.\" Hamas condemns the veto and \"ensures the world that our people will continue in their struggle until the creation of an independent Palestinian state with Jerusalem as capital\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Veto Usa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anp",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Palestinian Authority",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Abu Mazen",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MATTARELLA A MILITARI: SCOPO DETERRENZA Visita alla base Nato in Bulgaria",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Mattarella a militari: scopo deterrenza \"Siamo sul fronte orientale della Nato, posto in tensione dall'inammissibile invasione russa dell'Ucraina e quindi questa missione ha un compito di deterrenza, per prevenire ed evitare che vi siano incidenti\". Così il Capo dello Stato, Mattarella, parlando dalla base Nato di Novo Selo nell'est della Bulgaria.      \"Una missione che ha come scopo la pace e la sicurezza\", ha detto ai militari. \"Un compito importante per l'Italia,che ve ne è riconoscente. E io sono qui per trasmettervi questa riconoscenza\".  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.5659091,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "MATTARELLA A MILITARI: SCOPO DETERRENCE Visit to the base Born in Bulgaria",
        "en_content": "Mattarella to military: purpose deterrence \"We are on the eastern front of NATO, tensioned by the inadmissible Russian invasion of Ukraine and therefore this mission has a task of deterrence, to prevent and prevent accidents.\" Thus the Head of State, Mattarella, speaking from the NATO base of Novo Selo in the east of Bulgaria. \"A mission that aims peace and security,\" he told the military. \"An important task for Italy, which is grateful to you. And I am here to convey this gratitude.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bulgaria",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Novo Selo",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Bulgaria",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Aiea e Iran: no danni siti nucleari",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Aiea,Iran: no danni a impianti nucleari L'Aiea non registra danni agli impianti nucleari iraniani dopo il raid di droni di Israele presso Esfahan.Così l'Agenzia internazionale per l'energia atomica conferma quanto già detto dall'Iran. La difesa di Teheran riferisce di aver abbattuto \"piccoli droni, forse partiti dall'interno, o oggetti volanti\",nessuna vittima né danni agli impianti nucleari.\"Israele ha già visto la risposta dell'Iran\",dice il comandante dell' esercito. E i media diffondono immagini di Esfahan tranquilla. Oggi l'ayatollah Khamenei compie 85 anni.\"Buon compleanno Khamenei\",scrivono molti sui social.",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1713528005.5728996,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "Aiea and Iran: no damage nuclear sites",
        "en_content": "Aiea, Iran: no damage to nuclear plants The Aiea does not damage Iranian nuclear installations after the Israeli drone raid at Esfahan. Thus the International Atomic Energy Agency confirms what has already been said by Iran. Tehran's defense reports that he has knocked down \"small drones, perhaps from within, or flying objects\", no victim or damage to nuclear plants. \"Israel has already seen the response of Iran,\" says the army commander. And the media spread pictures of Esfahan quiet. Today ayatollah Khamenei is 85 years old.\"Good birthday Khamenei\", write many on social media.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aiea",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esfahan",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Atomic Energy Agency",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esfahan",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "85 years old",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 555,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.6210976,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI: \"SPERO A GIUGNO EUROPA DIVERSA\" Draghi? \"Dibattito è filosofia\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713528005.6950784,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "MELONI: \"WHEN A JUNE EUROPE DIVERSA\" Dragons? \"Beat is philosophy\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MELONI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "VON DER LEYEN: RIDURRE I PREZZI ENERGIA \"Chimica e siderurgia più colpite\"",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Von der Leyen: ridurre prezzi energia \"In Europa dobbiamo ridurre il costo dell'energia\".Lo ha detto la presidente della Commissione europea von der Leyen affrontando il tema della competitività \"I settori energivori, come la chimica o la siderurgia, sono particolarmente colpiti.I prezzi sono tornati ai livelli pre guerra, ma sono intrinsecamente troppo alti\", ha detto.\"Ma dal prossimo anno arriverà sul mercato un'ondata di nuovi progetti di esportazione di Gnl (gas naturale liquefatto,Ndr): è una buona notizia perché questo porterà a prezzi significativamente più bassi\". ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1713528005.6983538,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "VON DER LEYEN: RIDURRE THE ENERGY PRICES \"Cloom and steel most affected\"",
        "en_content": "Von der Leyen: reduce energy prices \"In Europe we must reduce energy costs\". The President of the European Commission, Mr von der Leyen, said this: \"The energy sectors, such as chemistry or steel, are particularly affected. Prices have returned to pre-war levels, but are intrinsically too high\", he said. \"But from next year a wave of new Gnl export projects will come to the market (liquified natural gas,Ndr): it is good news because this will bring to prices significantly lower\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "VON",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Von der",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "von der",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next year",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ndr",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Attaccata nella notte base in Iran",
        "date_raw": "April 19, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-19",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1713528005.730029,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-19 14:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-19T14.00.05",
        "en_title": "Attack on the base night in Iran",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    }
]
