[
    {
        "title": "Ma Katz:\"Con accordo stop a operazione\" Blinken a Riad per tentare tregua",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Katz:se c'è accordo,no operazione Rafah La prevista incursione nella città meridionale di Gaza,Rafah,potrebbe essere sospesa nel caso in cui si raggiungesse un accordo per garantire il rilascio degli ostaggi israeliani detenuti da Hamas. Lo ha detto il ministro degli Esteri dello stato ebraico,Israel Katz. \"Il rilascio degli ostaggi è per noi la priorità assoluta\", ha aggiunto.  Intanto,il Segretario di Stato Usa, Antony Blinken sarà in Arabia Saudita lunedì e martedì per incontrare i partner regionali e fare il punto sugli sforzi per un cessate il fuoco nella Striscia di Gaza e il rilascio degli ostaggi. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714294805.2482939,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "Ma Katz: \"With stop-to-operation agreement\" Blinken to Riad to try a truce",
        "en_content": "Katz: if there is agreement, no operation Rafah The planned raid in the southern city of Gaza,Rafah, could be suspended if an agreement was reached to ensure the release of Israeli hostages held by Hamas. The Minister of Foreign Affairs of the Jewish State told him, Israel Katz. \"The release of hostages is our top priority,\" he added. Meanwhile, the US Secretary of State, Antony Blinken will be in Saudi Arabia on Monday and Tuesday to meet regional partners and take stock of the efforts for a ceasefire in the Gaza Strip and the release of hostages.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ma Katz",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riad",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel Katz",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 278,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antony Blinken",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 413,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 428,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1714294805.2713351,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GAZA,NETANYAHU TEME MANDATO ARRESTO CPI Usa starebbero tentando di bloccarlo154  GAZA,SI ALLARGA PROTESTA NEI CAMPUS USA Oltre 200 arresti University Boston",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Gaza,si allarga protesta nei Campus Usa Si allarga la protesta nelle Università americane contro la guerra nella Striscia di Gaza,con gli studenti che chiedono all'amministrazione Biden di sospendere il sostegno incondizionato allo Stato di Israele. Nella sola North Eastern University di Boston gli arrestati sono stati quasi 200. Oltre una ventina all'Indiana University.  Nella Washington University di St.Louis nel Missouri, arrestata anche l'ebreoamericana Jill Stein,candidata alla Casa Bianca per i verdi. Proteste anche alla cena dei corrispondenti con Biden.",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714294805.282579,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "GAZA,NETANYAHU TEME MANDATO ARRESA CPI They would be trying to block it154 GAZA, THE PROTEST AUTHOR CAMPUS USA More than 200 arrests University Boston",
        "en_content": "Gaza, widens protest in the US Campus The protest in American universities against war in the Gaza Strip, with students asking the Biden administration to suspend unconditional support to the State of Israel. In the North Eastern University alone in Boston the arrested were almost 200. Over 20 at Indiana University. In the Washington University of St. Louis in Missouri, Jew Jill Stein, who was also arrested at the White House for Greens. Also protect the correspondents' dinner with Biden.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "NETANYAHU",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "it154 GAZA",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "More than 200",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "University Boston",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the US Campus",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State of Israel",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the North Eastern University",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boston",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "almost 200",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indiana University",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Washington University of St. Louis",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Missouri",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jew Jill Stein",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 387,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 414,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Greens",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 487,
                "end_char": 492,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"Sconcertante numero bimbi morti\"",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Gaza, \"numero bimbi morti sconcertante\" Il numero dei bambini rimasti uccisi nella Striscia di Gaza è\"sconcertante\". Così, senza mezzi termini il commissario generale dell'Agenzia Onu per il soccorso e l'occupazione dei rifugiati palestinesi (Unrwa), Lazzarini. \"In sei mesi sono morte oltre 30.000 persone\", e il bilancio \"potrebbe essere sproporzionatamente più alto\".    \"Tra i morti ci sono 13.000 bambini\", afferma. \"Sono morti più bambini in 6 mesi che in tutti i conflitti del mondo negli ultimi 4 anni\". Un bilancio \"senza precedenti sia in termini di dimensioni che di distruzione\".   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714294805.2945912,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "\"Unconcertating number of dead children\"",
        "en_content": "Gaza, \"number of deceased children\" The number of children left killed in the Gaza Strip is \"sconcert.\" Thus, without means terms the Commissioner-General of the UN Agency for the Relief and Employment of Palestinian Refugees (Unrwa), Lazzarini. \"In six months more than 30,000 people died,\" and the budget \"may be disproportionately higher.\" \"There are 13,000 children among the dead,\" he says. \"More children died in 6 months than in all the conflicts of the world over the last 4 years.\" A budget \"without precedent both in terms of size and destruction\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the UN Agency",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Relief and Employment of Palestinian Refugees (Unrwa",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lazzarini",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "six months",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 30,000",
                "start_char": 261,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "13,000",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 months",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last 4 years",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BIDEN:\"LIBEREREMO GIORNALISTI DETENUTI\" Io vecchio? \"Trump bimbo di 6 anni\"",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Biden:libereremo i giornalisti detenuti \"Vi posso assicurare che non molleremo fino a quando non torneranno a casa\". Lo afferma Joe Biden riferendosi ai  giornalisti americani imprigionati all'estero, fra i quali Evan Gershkovich, il report del Wall Street Journal detenuto in Russia.     I genitori di Gershkovich hannao partepato alla cena dei corrispondenti alla Casa Bianca, dalla quale Biden ha parlato ironizzato anche sul rivale Trump: \"Siamo in piena campagna elettorale. L'età è un problema, sono un adulto che corre contro un bambino di sei anni\". ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714294805.304839,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ Me old man? \"Trump 6-year-old\"",
        "en_content": "Biden: We will release journalists inmates \"I can assure you that we will not give up until they return home.\" Joe Biden says that referring to American journalists imprisoned abroad, including Evan Gershkovich, the Wall Street Journal report held in Russia. Gershkovich's parents participated in the White House dinner, from which Biden also spoke ironically about his rival Trump: \"We are in full election campaign. Age is a problem, I am an adult running against a six-year-old.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "6-year-old",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Evan Gershkovich",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Wall Street Journal",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gershkovich",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "six-year-old",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RISCHIO POVERTA' PER 15% POPOLAZIONE   Unimpresa:\"E' sfida per il governo\"",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Rischio povertà per 15% popolazione  Quasi il 15% della popolazione è a rischio povertà, nonostante il dato posisitivo sul mercato del lavoro negli ultimi mesi. Lo sostiene il Centro studi Unimpresa, che ha elaborato dati Istat. \"La vera sfida del governo,che comunque sta operando in maniera positiva\", consiste nel ridurre il numero di coloro che sono in disagio sociale, afferma il presidente Unimpresa, Longobardi.  L'area di disagio sociale corrisponde al 14,4% della popolazione. Si tratta di 8,5 milioni di persone sul totale di 59,1 mln di cittadini italiani.  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1714294805.36852,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "POVERTARY RISK FOR 15% POPULATION An enterprise: \"It is a challenge for the government\"",
        "en_content": "Poverty risk for 15% population Almost 15% of the population is at risk of poverty, despite the positive figure on the labour market in recent months. It is supported by the Centro Studi Unimpresa, which has developed Istat data. \"The real challenge of the government, which is still working positively,\" is to reduce the number of those who are in social distress, says President Unimpresa, Longobardi. The area of social discomfort corresponds to 14.4% of the population. It is 8.5 million people on the total of 59.1 million Italian citizens.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "15%",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "15%",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Almost 15%",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "recent months",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Centro Studi Unimpresa",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Istat",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Unimpresa",
                "start_char": 381,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Longobardi",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "14.4%",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "8.5 million",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "59.1 million",
                "start_char": 515,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ATTACCHI DI ISRAELE SUL CENTRO DI GAZA  Unrwa: operazione larga scala Rafah",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Attacchi di Israele sul centro di Gaza Secondo quanto riferisce Al Jazeera del Qatar sono ripresi \"attacchi aerei israeliani sugli insediamenti di AzZawayda e Al-Muharraqa, nella parte  centrale della Striscia di Gaza\".  \"Israele sta preparando un'operazione militare su larga scala nella città di Rafah, nel sud della Striscia\", afferma il commissario Unrwa, Lazzarini.La sorte della città è appesa al filo della proposta di accordo di Israele, su cui Hamas deve pronunciarsi. Senza intesa su cessate il fuoco e liberazione degli ostaggi l'esercito entrerà in azione. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1714294805.3743513,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "ISRAEL ATTACCHI ON THE CENTER OF GAZA Unrwa: large scale operation Rafah",
        "en_content": "Israel's attacks on the centre of Gaza According to Al Jazeera del Qatar, \"Israeli air attacks on the settlements of AzZawayda and Al-Muharraqa, in the central part of the Gaza Strip\". \"Israel preparing a large-scale military operation in the city of Rafah, in the south of the Strip,\" says Commissioner Unrwa, Lazzarini. The fate of the city is on the line of the proposal for an agreement of Israel, on which Hamas must pronounce. Without understanding on ceasefire and liberation of the hostages the army will enter into action.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISRAEL",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al Jazeera",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Qatar",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "AzZawayda",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Muharraqa",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unrwa",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lazzarini",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PALAZZO CHIGI CONVOCA SINDACATI DOMANI  Sul tavolo provvedimenti sul lavoro",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Palazzo Chigi convoca sindacati lunedì La presidente del Consiglio Meloni ha convocato i segretari di Cgil, Cisl e Uil per lunedì a Palazzo Chigi,alle 18. Al centro dell'incontro, i provvedimenti del governo sul lavoro. Tra questi, spiega il ministro Urso, \"presenteremo il piano per il rilancio\" dell'ex Ilva. Il sottosegretario alla presidenza Mantovano spiega che molto probabilmente nel CdM di martedì andrà il decreto  Coesione. \"C'è una parte importante che riguarda il mondo del lavoro e l'incontro sarà l'occasione per presentarlo\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1714294805.3840802,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ On the table measures at work",
        "en_content": "Palazzo Chigi convenes trade unions Monday The President of the Council Meloni convened the secretaries of Cgil, Cisl and Uil for Monday at Palazzo Chigi, at 18. At the centre of the meeting, the government's work measures. Among these, Minister Urso explains, \"we will present the plan for relaunch\" of the former Ilva. The undersecretary to the Mantovano presidency explains that most probably in the CdM on Tuesday will go the Coesione decree. \"There is an important part about the world of work and the meeting will be the opportunity to present it.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council Meloni",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cgil,",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cisl",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Uil",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 125,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Urso",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilva",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mantovano",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "CdM",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 406,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 410,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IL PAPA A VENEZIA,IN 10MILA A SAN MARCO La sua visita al carcere della Giudecca \"Sovraffollamento un problema,dignità\"  A detenute:vi ricorderò,non mollate",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1714294805.3943603,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ His visit to the Giudecca prison \"surfing a problem, dignity\" Inmates: I will remember you, not give up",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giudecca",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AUTONOMIA,OK COMMISSIONE.LUNEDI'IN AULA Lega: \"Sconfitto l'ostruzionismo\"",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Autonomia,ok Commissione.Lunedì in Aula Via libera della commissione Affari costituzionali della Camera al disegno di legge per l'Autonomia differenziata  che approderà lunedì nell'Aula di Montecitorio. La Commissione ha concluso l'esame del Ddl approvando il mandato ai relatori a riferire in Aula.  Le opposizioni non hanno partecipato al voto in segno di protesta contro la tagliola sugli emendamenti. In Pd in una nota accusa di \"forzature inaccettabili\" e annuncia battaglia in Aula.Esulta la Lega:\"Finalmente ci siamo\". \"Ostruzionismo sinistra è stato sconfitto\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1714294805.399056,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "AUTONOMIA,OK COMMISSION. \"Unconfitted obstructionism\"",
        "en_content": "Commission. Monday in the Aula Freeway of the Committee on Constitutional Affairs of the House to the bill for the differentiated Autonomy that will land Monday in the Hall of Montecitorio. The Commission concluded its examination by approving the mandate to the rapporteurs to report to the House. Oppositions did not participate in the vote as a protest against the cutlery on amendments. In Pd in a notable accusation of \"unacceptable forces\" and announces battle in the classroom. \"Finally we are.\" \"Left obstructionism was defeated.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "AUTONOMIA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Aula Freeway",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Committee on Constitutional Affairs of the House",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Hall of Montecitorio",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SANGIULIANO: ANTICOMUNISTA E'SACROSANTO \"Qualcuno ponga domanda a Schlein\"",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1714294805.4200919,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "SANGIULIANO: ANTICOMUNISTA It is SACROSANT \"Someone asks question to Schlein\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SANGIULIANO",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ATTACCHI DI ISRAELE SUL CENTRO DI GAZA  Unrwa: ora operazione larga scala Rafah Blinken a Riad per tentare tregua",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1714294805.455264,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "ISRAEL ATTACCHI ON THE CENTER OF GAZA Unrwa: now a large-scale operation Rafah Blinken at Riad to try tregua",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISRAEL",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah Blinken",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riad",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "JUVENTUS-MILAN, PAREGGIO SENZA RETI",
        "date_raw": "April 28, 2024",
        "date": "2024-04-28",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=201",
        "content": "     ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1714294805.4602337,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-04-28 11:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-28T11.00.05",
        "en_title": "JUVENTUS-MILAN",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "JUVENTUS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
