[
    {
        "title": "MELONI:\"ASPETTIAMO LE RISPOSTE DI TOTI\" \"Mai pensato a rimpasto di governo\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Meloni:aspettare risposte Toti,valutare \"Toti ha detto che avrebbe letto le  carte e avrebbe dato le risposte.Aspettare quelle risposte e valutare penso sia il minimo indispensabile per un uomo che ha governato molto bene quella Regione\". Così la premier Meloni.  Il confronto tv previsto con Schlein? \"Mettere a confronto ricette e visioni è un modo di aiutare i cittadini nella scelta\".E \"mi fanno sorridere lamentele denunce\",non fare il confronto sarebbe un errore\", afferma intervistata a 'Il Giorno de La Verità' a Milano.\"Mai pensato di fare un rimpasto di governo\", obiettivo è stessa squadra per \"5 anni\"",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715760005.8638852,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.05",
        "en_title": "MELONI: \"We're going to get TOTI's answers\" \"Never thought of government reshuffle\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni: Expect Toti answers,evaluate \"Toti said he would read the cards and give the answers. Waiting for those answers and evaluating I think it is the least indispensable for a man who has governed that region very well\". So Premier Meloni. The TV comparison with Schlein? \"To compare recipes and visions is a way to help citizens in choosing.\" And \"they make me smile complaints,\" don't make comparison would be a mistake,\" he says interviewed \"The Day of Truth\" in Milan.\"But I thought I'd make a reshuffle of government,\" goal is the same team for \"5 years\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "TOTI",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Day of Truth",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 years",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 561,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "KIEV SI RITIRA DA ALCUNE ZONE A KHARKIV \"Manovra per salvare vite soldati\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Kiev si ritira da alcune zone a Kharkiv L'esercito ucraino ha annunciato di  essere stato costretto a ritirarsi in alcune zone del fronte nella regione di Kharkiv, dove le forze russe hanno lanciato un'intensa offensiva.  \"Le nostre unità hanno manovrato verso posizioni più favorevoli per salvare la vita dei nostri soldati ed evitare vittime\", fa sapere lo stato maggiore. Nella regione sono 30mila i soldati  russi impegnati negli attacchi, segnala il Consiglio di sicurezza di Kiev.  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715760005.8720164,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.05",
        "en_title": "KIEV RITIRA DA ALCUNE ZONE TO KHARKIV \"Manovra to save lives soldiers\"",
        "en_content": "Kiev withdraws from some areas in Kharkiv The Ukrainian army has announced that it has been forced to retreat to some areas of the front in the Kharkiv region, where Russian forces have launched an intense offensive. \"Our units have manoeuvred towards more favorable positions to save the lives of our soldiers and to avoid victims,\" he says. In the region are 30 thousand Russian soldiers engaged in attacks, reports the Security Council of Kiev.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "KIEV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manovra",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 thousand",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Security Council of Kiev",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PUTIN: \"APERTI AL DIALOGO SULL'UCRAINA\" \"Ma tenga conto dei nostri interessi\"  Domani la visita a Pechino da Xi",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Putin: \"Aperti al dialogo sull'Ucraina\" \"Stiamo cercando una soluzione globale, sostenibile e giusta di questo conflitto attraverso mezzi pacifici. Siamo  aperti a un dialogo sull'Ucraina,ma tali negoziati devono tenere conto degli interessi di tutti i Paesi coinvolti nel conflitto, compresi i nostri\". Così il presidente russo, Putin, all'agenzia di stampa cinese Xinhua.   In vista della visita di Stato a Pechino, Putin ha detto di apprezzare la posizione della Cina, poiché ha mostrato di comprendere le radici della crisi ucraina e il suo impatto geopolitico. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715760005.8921566,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ Tomorrow visit to Beijing from Xi",
        "en_content": "Putin: \"We are looking for a global, sustainable and just solution to this conflict through peaceful means. We are open to a dialogue on Ukraine, but these negotiations must take into account the interests of all the countries involved in the conflict, including ours.\" So the Russian president, Putin, the Chinese press agency Xinhua. In view of the visit to Beijing, Putin said he appreciated China's position, as he showed that he understood the roots of the Ukrainian crisis and its geopolitical impact.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 307,
                "end_char": 314,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xinhua",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MASSICCIO ATTACCO UCRAINO A SEBASTOPOLI Mosca: usati anche missili Atacms",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Massiccio attacco di Kiev a Sebastopoli Il ministero della Difesa russo riferisce di un massiccio attacco aereo delle forze ucraine sulla città portuale di Sebastopoli, in Crimea, nonché sulle regioni di Belgorod, Kursk e Bryansk. Sempre secondo Mosca, negli attacchi sono stati utilizzati anche i missili guidati di precisione a lungo raggio, Atacms, forniti all'Ucraina dagli Stati Uniti.      L'attacco sarebbe stato in gran parte sventato. 10 gli Atacms abbattuti sul territorio della Crimea.   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715760005.9256473,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.05",
        "en_title": "MASSICCIO ATTACCO UCRAINO TO SEBASTOPOLI Moscow: also used missiles Atacms",
        "en_content": "Kiev attack massive in Sebastopoli The Russian Ministry of Defense reports a massive aerial attack of Ukrainian forces on the port city of Sebastopoli, in Crimea, as well as on the regions of Belgorod, Kursk and Bryansk. According to Moscow, long-range precision missiles, Atacms, supplied to Ukraine by the United States, were also used. The attack would have been largely deranged. 10 Atacms fell on the territory of Crimea.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atacms",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sebastopoli",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Russian Ministry of Defense",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sebastopoli",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kursk",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bryansk",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atacms",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atacms",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IL BOEING DI TRUMP URTA UN ALTRO AEREO  Durante rullaggio in scalo Florida",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Florida, Boeing Trump urta altro aereo Un'ala del Boeing 757 dell'ex presidente americano, Trump, ha urtato un aereo parcheggiato all'aeroporto internazionale di West Palm Beach, in Florida, mentre era in fase di rullaggio. Lo riportano i media Usa.    L'aereo colpito è un jet aziendale, ha fatto sapere la Federal Aviation Administration (Faa), responsabile dei voli civili americani, specificando che non ci sono stati feriti e che sull'incidente è stata avviata un'indagine.  ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715760005.9327695,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ In Florida airport",
        "en_content": "Florida, Boeing Trump crashed another plane A Boeing 757 wing of the former American president, Trump, hit a plane parked at the international airport of West Palm Beach, Florida, while it was in the rolling phase. The U.S. media reports it. The plane hit is a corporate jet, reported the Federal Aviation Administration (Faa), responsible for American civil flights, specifying that there were no injuries and that an investigation was initiated on the incident.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Boeing",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boeing",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "757",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "West Palm Beach",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Federal Aviation Administration",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AGENTI UCCISI ROUEN, E' CACCIA ALL'UOMO Commando ha sparato per liberarlo",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Francia,caccia all'evaso detto la Mosca Si chiama Mohamed Amra, detto la Mosca, il detenuto liberato oggi con l'assalto a un blindato, in Normandia,che lo trasferiva dal tribunale al carcere.  Nell'attacco al blindato,sull'autostrada A154, sono rimasti uccisi 2 agenti penitenziari e altri 3 gravemente feriti. La Mosca è un noto trafficante di droga,sotto inchiesta per rapine e omicidio, ma condannato finora solo a 18 mesi per tentato omicidio.   Il presidente Macron:\"Vicini alle famiglie degli agenti.Saremo inflessibili\".",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715760005.9547062,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "France, the case for the excavated Moscow is called Mohamed Amra, called Moscow, the prisoner released today with the assault on an armored, in Normandy, who transferred him from the court to the prison. In the armored attack, on the A154 motorway, 2 penitentiary agents were killed and 3 were seriously injured. Moscow is a well-known drug dealer, under investigation for kidnapping and murder, but convicted until now only 18 months for attempted murder. President Macron: \"Come to the families of the agents. We'll be inflexible.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed Amra",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Normandy",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "A154",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "only 18 months",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "KIEV SI RITIRA DA ALCUNE ZONE A KHARKIV \"Manovra per salvare vite dei soldati\"  Massiccio attacco ucraino in Crimea",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715760005.9804552,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.05",
        "en_title": "KIEV RITIRA DA ALCUNE ZONE TO KHARKIV \"Manovra to save lives of soldiers\" Massive Ukrainian attack in Crimea",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "KIEV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manovra",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PREMIERATO, SEGRE: \"ASPETTI ALLARMANTI\" \"Non posso e non voglio tacere\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Premierato, Segre: \"Aspetti allarmanti\" \"A mio giudizio, il disegno di riforma costituzionale proposto dal Governo  presenta vari aspetti allarmanti. Non posso e non voglio tacere\". Lo ha affermato nell'aula del Senato la senatrice Liliana Segre durante la discussione sul premierato elettivo.  \"Non tutto può essere sacrificato in nome dello slogan 'scegliete il capo del governo'. Anche le tribù della preistoria avevano un capo, ma solo le democrazie costituzionali hanno separazione dei poteri, controlli e bilanciamenti\", ha detto la Segre.   ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.0493653,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Premierato, Segre: \"Awakening alarming\" \"In my view, the draft constitutional reform proposed by the Government presents various alarming aspects. I can't and I don't want to shut up.\" The senator Liliana Segre said this in the Senate House during the discussion on the elective premier. \"Nothing can be sacrificed in the name of the slogan 'choose the head of government'. Even the prehistoric tribes had a leader, but only constitutional democracies have separation of powers, controls and balances,\" the Secret said.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Premierato",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Segre",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Liliana Segre",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Senate House",
                "start_char": 224,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "COLLE:\"ITALIA CON ISRAELE, MA ORA PACE\" \"Urge dialogo su soluzione 2 Stati\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Colle: profondo legame Italia-Israele Italia e Israele \"sono uniti da un legame profondo, fondato su valori comuni e cresciuto nel tempo grazie a un'ampia collaborazione per il benessere dei nostri popoli e una sempre più profonda conoscenza reciproca\". Così il presidente Mattarella all'omologo Herzog per il Giorno dell'indipendenza israeliana. \"Grandissima preoccupazione\" \"ribadisco l'impegno dell'Italia per il \"diritto inalienabile a esistere\" di Israele, condanna per \"atroce attacco\" del 7/10 e \"indispensabile immediata cessazione delle ostilità\".Fermare ciclo violenza, dialogo per soluzione a due Stati. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.0638587,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "COLLE: \"ITALY WITH ISRAELE, MA ORA PACE\" \"Use dialogue on solution 2 States\"",
        "en_content": "Colle: deep bond Italy-Israel Italy and Israel \"are united by a deep bond, founded on common values and raised over time thanks to a broad collaboration for the welfare of our peoples and an ever deeper mutual knowledge\". So President Mattarella to the Honour Herzog for the Day of Israeli Independence. \"Great concern\" \"I reaffirm Italy's commitment to the \"right inalienable to exist\" of Israel, condemnation for \"atroce attack\" of 7/10 and \"indispensable immediate cessation of hostilities\". Stop cycle violence, dialogue by solution to two states.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "COLLE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ISRAELE",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "MA ORA",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Herzog",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Day of Israeli Independence",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "7/10",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 540,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Presidente convoca Consiglio Difesa 126  UE, VIA LIBERA PATTO MIGRAZIONE E ASILO Italia vota sì a ultimo passaggio",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=127",
        "content": " Ue, via libera Patto migrazione e asilo Il Consiglio dell'Ue ha adottato il  pacchetto legislativo del Patto per le migrazioni e l'asilo. E' l'ultimo via libero europeo alle norme.   I 10 atti legislativi che lo compongono sono stati approvati a maggioranza. L' Italia ha votato a favore. Contrari Ungheria e Polonia. Astenuti Slovacchia e Repubblica Ceca.    Le nuove regole dovrebbero aiutare a gestire gli arrivi di migranti in modo ordinato,con procedure uniformi,riequilibrando gli oneri tra Stati membri. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.0724316,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "President convenes Defense Council 126 EU, VIA LIBERA PATTO MIGRATION AND ASILO Italy votes yes at last step",
        "en_content": "The EU Council adopted the legislative package for migration and asylum. It is the last European road to the rules. The 10 legislative acts composing it were approved by a majority. Italy voted in favour. Contractors Hungary and Poland. Sustained Slovakia and Czech Republic. The new rules should help manage the arrivals of migrants in an orderly manner, with uniform procedures, rebalancing the burdens between Member States.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Defense Council",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "126",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "VIA",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "PATTO",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The EU Council",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovakia",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Czech Republic",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCHLEIN:\"DIMISSIONI DI TOTI NECESSARIE\" \"La Liguria non può restare appesa\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Inchiesta Genova, Schlein: Toti via ora \"Lo abbiamo detto sin dall'inizio: alla luce di quanto sta emergendo,dimissioni di Toti sono necessarie e opportune Non Non può restare un minuto di più\". Così a Repubblica la segretaria Pd Schlein. \"Al di là delle responsabilità penali, che sarà la magistratura ad accertare, la Liguria non può restare appesa a un' incertezza amministrativa che fa male ai cittadini e impedisce decisioni\". Poi: Meloni \"zitta per giorni, silenzio assordante, ora invoca pazienza. Su  Emiliano,neppure sfiorato da inchiesta, sua maggioranza ha occupato tutti i Tg. Garantisti solo quando tocca a loro\". ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.0761273,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "SCHLEIN: \"DIMISSIONS OF TOTI NECESSARI\" \"Liguria cannot be hung\"",
        "en_content": "Genoa, Schlein: \"We said it from the beginning: In the light of what is emerging, resignation of Toti is necessary and appropriate It cannot remain a minute longer\". So to Republic the secretary Pd Schlein. \"Beyond the criminal responsibilities, which will be the judiciary to ascertain, Liguria cannot remain burdened with an administrative uncertainty that hurts citizens and prevents decisions\". Then: Meloni \"sit for days, deafening silence, now invokes patience. On Emiliano, even though it was unleashed by investigation, his majority occupied all Tg. Garantisti only when it comes to them.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SCHLEIN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Liguria",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a minute",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd Schlein",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Liguria",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 405,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "days",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emiliano",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tg",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Garantisti",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 568,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL SUPERBONUS,PASSA EMENDAMENTO GOVERNO Sì di Italia Viva, FI si astiene",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715760006.0812516,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "DL SUPERBONUS, PASSA GOVERNMENT Yes of Italy Viva, FI astiene",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "\"Riforma giustizia a giorni in CdM\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Meloni:riforma giustizia a giorni a CdM \"Nei prossimi giorni arriverà in Consiglio dei ministri anche la riforma della giustizia\". Lo annuncia la premier Meloni,ospite della Verità,sottolineando:\"Siamo tutti d'accordo che la giustizia in Italia non funziona, dobbiamo avere il coraggio di intervenire come su tutte le questioni che rallentano investimenti e sviluppo\".   E sul premierato: riforma \"necessaria\", spero entri \"in vigore nel 2028\". Referendum \"non sarebbe su di me\". Per dopo Europee esclude \"fibrillazioni\".Poi sui cortei:\"Regole vengano rispettate anche da chi manifesta\", alcuni \"provocano\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.0921023,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "\"Reform justice to days in CdM\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni:reform justice in days at CdM \"In the coming days the reform of justice will come to the Council of Ministers\". Premier Meloni, guest of Truth, announces this: \"We all agree that justice in Italy does not work, we must have the courage to intervene as on all issues that slow down investments and development.\" And on the premier: \"necessary\" reform, I hope it enters \"in force in 2028\". Referendum would not be on me. For later Europeans excludes \"fibrillations\". Then on the processions: \"Regole are also respected by those who manifest\", some \"provocate\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CdM",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "days",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "CdM",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming days",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council of Ministers",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Truth",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2028",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 436,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Regole",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL SUPERBONUS,PASSA EMENDAMENTO GOVERNO Approvato con la norma \"spalma-crediti\" Sì di Italia Viva, FI si astiene",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Dl Superbonus,passa emendamento governo Via libera della commissione Finanze del Senato all'emendamento del governo al decreto Superbonus,che è stato approvato con il voto favorevole di Italia Viva e l'astensione di Forza Italia Non ha partecipato al voto nemmeno il senatore Pietro Patton delle Autonomie. Semaforo verde dunque alla norma \"spalma-crediti\" che diluisce in 10 anni i crediti del 110%. In mattinata la commissione tornerà a riunirsi per votare il mandato al relatore. Nel pomeriggio approderà in Aula dove è probabile ricorso la voto di fiducia.  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.1442509,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "DL SUPERBONUS,PASSA EMENDATION GOVERNMENT Approved with the standard \"spalma-credit\" Yes of Italia Viva, FI astiene",
        "en_content": "Dl Superbonus, passing amendment government Free Way of the Senate Finance Committee to the government amendment to the Superbonus Decree, which was approved with the favorable vote of Italia Viva and the abstention of Forza Italia Senator Pietro Patton of the Autonomies did not participate in the vote. Green light therefore to the standard \"spalma-credits\" which dilutes in 10 years the credits of 110%. In the morning the committee will come back to vote for the mandate to the rapporteur. In the afternoon he will arrive in the court where the vote of trust is likely to be taken.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Viva",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Free Way",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Senate Finance Committee",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Superbonus Decree",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italia Viva",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pietro Patton",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Autonomies",
                "start_char": 261,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "110%",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the morning",
                "start_char": 410,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the afternoon",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.1721995,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PNRR, CORTE CONTI: ATTUAZIONE IN LINEA  \"Rispettato programma primi 6 mesi\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=135",
        "content": " C.Conti: 2024, attuazione Pnrr in linea \"Nel primo semestre 2024 l'attuazione prosegue in linea con la programmazione\".Lo rileva la Corte dei Conti nella relazione semestrale sul Pnrr in cui precisa che \"sulla base delle rilevazioni di metà marzo,tra gli obiettivi ancora da conseguire le amministrazioni titolari assegnavano solamente a 2 scadenze un grado di complessità attuativa alto\".      Quindici gli investimenti con più difficoltà attuative (il 7% delle misure da completare),ma sono stati già avviati i necessari interventi correttivi. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.1918821,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "PNRR, CORTE CONTI: IMPLEMENTATION IN LINE \"Respected program first 6 months\"",
        "en_content": "C.Conti: 2024, Implementation Pnrr online \"In the first half of 2024 the implementation continues in line with the programming\". The Court of Auditors notes this in the six-month report on the Pnrr in which it states that \"on the basis of the mid-March surveys, among the objectives still to be achieved by the parent administrations assigned only 2 deadlines a high degree of implementing complexity\". Fifteen investments with more implementing difficulties (7% of the measures to be completed), but the necessary corrective measures have already been started.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CORTE",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first 6 months",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the first half of 2024",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Court of Auditors",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "six-month",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "mid-March",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "only 2",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fifteen",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "7%",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "LA \"SUGAR TAX\" SLITTA A LUGLIO 2025   Accordo in Commissione al Senato",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " La \"Sugar Tax\" slitta a luglio 2025  E' stato raggiunto l'accordo in Commissione Finanze al Senato per il rinvio dell'entrata in vigore della \"Sugar Tax\" al primo luglio 2025.   Il rinvio è passato con il voto favorevole di Italia Viva all'emendamento del governo sul dl Superbonus.  Astenuta Forza Italia, che ha premuto per lo slittamento della tassa sulle bevande analcoliche ma rimane critica sulla retroattività delle modifiche al Superbonus, si è astenuta. Slitta  invece al 2026 la \"Plastic Tax\".  ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.1970184,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "THE \"SUGAR TAX\" SLITTA IN JULY 2025 Agreement in Commission of the Senate",
        "en_content": "The \"Sugar Tax\" slips in July 2025 The agreement reached in the Finance Commission to the Senate for the postponement of the entry into force of the \"Sugar Tax\" on 1 July 2025. The postponement has passed with the favourable vote of Italy Viva to the amendment of the government on the Superbonus. Astenuta Forza Italia, who pressed for the slip of the fee on soft drinks but remains critical on the retroactivity of the changes to Superbonus, has abstained. On the other hand, at 2026 the \"Plastic Tax\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "JULY 2025 Agreement",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The \"Sugar Tax\"",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "July 2025",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Finance Commission",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the \"Sugar Tax\"",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1 July 2025",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy Viva",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Astenuta Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2026",
                "start_char": 481,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the \"Plastic Tax\"",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 503,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Sempre scintille Tajani-Giorgetti",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Superbonus, distanze Tajani-Giorgetti \"Voteremo contro se non sarà modificato\" il decreto Superbonus. Così il vicepremier e leader di FI, Tajani, dopo gli emendamenti presentati in Commissione. \"Se si trovano soluzioni positive sono sempre pronto a compromessi. I nostri senatori sono pronti a confrontarsi\", ha aggiunto.    Ma il ministro dell'Economia Giorgetti: il Superbonus è \"una misura eccezionale per tempi eccezionali\" e \"da questa tipo di droga economica bisogna uscire\". \"La disintossicazione è dolorosa però qualcuno la deve fare\".   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.2025096,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "Always Tajani-Giorgetti sparks",
        "en_content": "Superbonus, distances Tajani-Giorgetti \"We will go against if it will not be modified\" the Superbonus decree. So the deputypremier and leader of FI, Tajani, after the amendments tabled in the Commission. \"If there are positive solutions, they are always ready to compromise. Our senators are ready to confront each other,\" he added. But the Minister of Economy Giorgetti: the Superbonus is \"an exceptional measure for exceptional times\" and \"from this type of economic drug you have to go out\". \"Detoxification is painful but someone has to do it.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani-Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani-Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Superbonus",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Maggioranza passa da 19 a 20",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Superbonus,sale maggioranza commissione Tensione in commissione Finanze al Senato dove si discute il Dl Superbonus. Cresce la maggioranza: il numero dei componenti in commissione aumenta da 19 e 20. E insorgono le opposizioni che parlano di \"forzatura politica\" perché l'aggiunta di un nuovo membro \"va prima comunicata all'Aula\". Il senatore aggiunto dovrebbe essere Sallemi,di FdI Ma La Russa: i numeri non mutati oggi. Intanto sono arrivati i pareri negativi del Mef ai subemendamenti di FI che modificano l'emendamento del governo al decreto.      ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715760006.3926709,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 10:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T10.00.06",
        "en_title": "May from 19 to 20",
        "en_content": "Superbonus, the majority commission Tension in commission Finances to the Senate where the Dl Superbonus is discussed. The majority grows: the number of members in commission increases from 19 and 20. And they bear the oppositions that speak of \"political strength\" because the addition of a new member \"was first communicated to the House\". The added senator should be Sallemi, of FdI Ma Russian: the numbers not changed today. In the meantime, the negative opinions of the Mef have come to the sub-emendaments of FI that modify the amendment of the government to the decree.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "May",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "19 to",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Dl Superbonus",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "19",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sallemi",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "FdI Ma",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 422,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mef",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
