[
    {
        "title": "AGENTI UCCISI ROUEN, E' CACCIA ALL'UOMO Assalto commando per liberare boss",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Francia,caccia all'evaso detto la Mosca Si chiama Mohamed Amra, detto la Mosca, il detenuto liberato oggi con l'assalto a un blindato, in Normandia,che lo trasferiva dal tribunale al carcere.  Nell'attacco al blindato,sull'autostrada A154, sono rimasti uccisi 2 agenti penitenziari e altri 3 gravemente feriti. La Mosca è un noto trafficante di droga,sotto inchiesta per rapine e omicidio, ma condannato finora solo a 18 mesi per tentato omicidio.   Il presidente Macron:\"Vicini alle famiglie degli agenti.Saremo inflessibili\".",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715788804.863198,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "France, the case for the excavated Moscow is called Mohamed Amra, called Moscow, the prisoner released today with the assault on an armored, in Normandy, who transferred him from the court to the prison. In the armored attack, on the A154 motorway, 2 penitentiary agents were killed and 3 were seriously injured. Moscow is a well-known drug dealer, under investigation for kidnapping and murder, but convicted until now only 18 months for attempted murder. President Macron: \"Come to the families of the agents. We'll be inflexible.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed Amra",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Normandy",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "A154",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "only 18 months",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Wsj: Armi Usa a Israele per 1,25mld",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Israele, Wsj: da Usa armi per 1,25 mld L'amministrazione Biden ha notificato al Congresso l'intenzione di vendere nuove armi a Israele per circa 1,25 mld di dollari. E' quanto riferisce il Wall Street Journal, che cita fonti governative e del Congresso Usa. Il pacchetto include munizioni per carri armati,veicoli tattici e proiettili da mortaio. Il presidente Biden ha però annunciato che metterà il veto sul provvedimento presentato dai repubblicani al Congresso per inviare armi a Israele. L'Israel Security Assistance Support Act dovrebbe essere votato in settimana.  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715788804.9025242,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "Wsj: US weapons to Israel for 1.25mld",
        "en_content": "Israel, Wsj: from USA weapons for 1.25 mld The Biden administration has notified Congress of plans to sell new weapons to Israel for about 1.25 billion dollars. That's what the Wall Street Journal says, cites government sources and the U.S. Congress. The package includes ammunition for tanks, tactical vehicles and mortar bullets. President Biden, however, announced that he will veto the measure submitted by the Republicans to Congress to send weapons to Israel. The Israel Security Assistance Support Act should be voted in the week.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.25mld",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wsj",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.25",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 1.25 billion dollars",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Wall Street Journal",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the U.S. Congress",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Republicans",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Israel Security Assistance Support Act",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 508,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the week",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BANKITALIA: DEBITO +23 MILIARDI A MARZO In aumento anche entrate statali",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Bankitalia:debito sale di 23mld su mese A marzo il debito delle amministrazioni pubbliche è aumentato di 23 miliardi rispetto al mese precedente, risultando pari a 2.894,7 miliardi. Lo comunica la Banca d'Italia.     Le entrate dello Stato sono state pari a 37 miliardi, in aumento del 5,7% (2 miliardi) rispetto a marzo 2023.  Nel primo trimestre le entrate statali sono state 122,9 mld (+8,9mld) il +7,8% rispetto al I trimestre del 2023. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715788804.9070597,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ Increasing state revenue",
        "en_content": "Bankitalia:debit sale of 23mld per month In March the debt of public administrations increased by 23 billion compared to the previous month, resulting in pairs to 2.894,7 billion. The Bank of Italy communicates it. State revenue was 37 billion, up 5.7% (2 billion) compared with March 2023. In the first trimester the state revenue was 122.9 mld (+8.9mld) +7.8% compared to the first quarter of 2023.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bankitalia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "23mld",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "23 billion",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the previous month",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2.894,7 billion",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Bank of Italy",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "37 billion",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "5.7%",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "2 billion",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 2023",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "122.9",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "+7.8%",
                "start_char": 356,
                "end_char": 361,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the first quarter of 2023",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UE ALZA DELLO 0,9% ATTESE PIL ITALIA   Gentiloni:\"Incertezza globale alta\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Ue alza dello 0,9% attese su Pil Italia La Commissione Ue rivede al rialzo le previsioni di crescita in Italia 2024: Pil +0,9% (in precedenza era +0,7%), meglio di Francia e Germania. Nel 2025 +1,1%.      \"L'incertezza e i rischi al ribasso per le prospettive economiche derivanti  dall'ambiente esterno dell'Ue sono aumentati. Anche l'incertezza politica globale è elevata,alla luce della quota senza precedenti della popolazione mondiale che va alle elezioni quest'anno\". Così il commissario all'Economia Gentiloni. \"Sarà un'estate calda per i conti pubblici\", prevede.    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715788804.9118743,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "EU ALZA OF 0.9% ATTESE GDP ITALY Gentiloni:\"High global uncertainty\"",
        "en_content": "Ue raises by 0.9% expected on GDP Italy The EU Commission reviews the growth forecast in Italy 2024: GDP +0.9% (previously it was +0.7%), better than France and Germany. In 2025 +1.1%. \"Uncertainty and downside risks for the economic outlook of the EU's external environment have increased. Global political uncertainty is also high, in the light of the unprecedented share of the world population that goes to elections this year.\" So the commissioner to the Gentiloni Economy. \"It'll be a hot summer for public accounts,\" she says.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU ALZA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "0.9%",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "ITALY Gentiloni:\"High",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "0.9%",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU Commission",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.9%",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.7%",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "+1.1%",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "this year",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gentiloni Economy",
                "start_char": 456,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SLOVACCHIA, FICO E' IN PERICOLO DI VITA 3-4 colpi pistola a petto, addome, arto Operato d'urgenza,preso attentatore",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715788804.9244921,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "SLOVACCHIA, FICO IS IN PERICLE OF LIFE 3-4 shots chest gun, abdomen, arto Operato of urgency,preso bomber",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FICO",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "arto Operato",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "preso",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715788804.950708,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IL BOEING DI TRUMP URTA UN ALTRO AEREO  Durante rullaggio in scalo Florida",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=159",
        "content": " Florida, Boeing Trump urta altro aereo Un'ala del Boeing 757 dell'ex presidente americano, Trump, ha urtato un aereo parcheggiato all'aeroporto internazionale di West Palm Beach, in Florida, mentre era in fase di rullaggio. Lo riportano i media Usa.    L'aereo colpito è un jet aziendale, ha fatto sapere la Federal Aviation Administration (Faa), responsabile dei voli civili americani, specificando che non ci sono stati feriti e che sull'incidente è stata avviata un'indagine.  ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715788804.9788222,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ In Florida airport",
        "en_content": "Florida, Boeing Trump crashed another plane A Boeing 757 wing of the former American president, Trump, hit a plane parked at the international airport of West Palm Beach, Florida, while it was in the rolling phase. The U.S. media reports it. The plane hit is a corporate jet, reported the Federal Aviation Administration (Faa), responsible for American civil flights, specifying that there were no injuries and that an investigation was initiated on the incident.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Boeing",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boeing",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "757",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "West Palm Beach",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Federal Aviation Administration",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Putin:aperti a dialogo sull'Ucraina 155  USA: \"ALTRI 2MLD AIUTI MILITARI A KIEV\" Blinken: presto Biden vede Zelensky",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Usa:\"Altri 2 mld aiuti militari a Kiev\" Il segretario di Stato americano Anthony Blinken, in visita a kiev, ha annunciato lo stanziamento di altri due miiardi di aiuti militari all'Ucraina. A determinare la presa di posizione Usa l'imminenza di una nuova offensiva russa e la ritirata dal fronte ucraino. \"Non incoraggiamo, né favoriamo attacchi al di fuori dell'Ucraina, ma alla fine spetta all'Ucraina prendere le decisioni sul modo in cui intende condurre questa guerra\", ha detto Blinken il quale ha parlato di un incontro fra Biden e Zelensky nelle prossime settimane",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715788804.9949648,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "Putin:open to dialogue on Ukraine 155 USA: \"ALTRI 2MLD MILITARY AID TO KIEV\" Blinken: soon Biden sees Zelensky",
        "en_content": "Use:\"Other 2 ml of military aid in Kiev\" American Secretary of State Anthony Blinken, visiting kiev, announced the appropriation of two more billion military aids to Ukraine. To determine the position taken Use the imminence of a new Russian offensive and retreat from the Ukrainian front. \"We do not encourage, nor promote attacks outside Ukraine, but ultimately it is up to Ukraine to make decisions on how it intends to conduct this war,\" Blinken said, who spoke of a meeting between Biden and Zelensky in the coming weeks.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "155",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ALTRI",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2MLD",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "KIEV",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anthony Blinken",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "kiev",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two more billion",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 442,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 487,
                "end_char": 492,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming weeks",
                "start_char": 509,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Sebastopoli, massiccio attacco Kiev",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Massiccio attacco di Kiev a Sebastopoli Il ministero della Difesa russo riferisce di un massiccio attacco aereo delle forze ucraine sulla città portuale di Sebastopoli, in Crimea, nonché sulle regioni di Belgorod, Kursk e Bryansk. Sempre secondo Mosca, negli attacchi sono stati utilizzati anche i missili guidati di precisione a lungo raggio, Atacms, forniti all'Ucraina dagli Stati Uniti.      L'attacco sarebbe stato in gran parte sventato. 10 gli Atacms abbattuti sul territorio della Crimea.   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715788805.0187466,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "Sebastopoli, massive Kiev attack",
        "en_content": "Kiev attack massive in Sebastopoli The Russian Ministry of Defense reports a massive aerial attack of Ukrainian forces on the port city of Sebastopoli, in Crimea, as well as on the regions of Belgorod, Kursk and Bryansk. According to Moscow, long-range precision missiles, Atacms, supplied to Ukraine by the United States, were also used. The attack would have been largely deranged. 10 Atacms fell on the territory of Crimea.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sebastopoli",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sebastopoli",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Russian Ministry of Defense",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sebastopoli",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kursk",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bryansk",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atacms",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Atacms",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crimea",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL SUPERBONUS, VOTO IN SENATO DOMATTINA Governo ha preannunciato la fiducia",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Dl Superbonus, governo pone la fiducia Il governo ha posto la questione di fiducia sul decreto Superbonus, in Aula al Senato dopo il via libera della commissione Finanze. Il voto finale è previsto domattina. Il testo scade il 28/5 e deve passare in seconda seduta alla Camera.      Ieri la commissione aveva votato l'  emendamento del governo, col sì di Italia Viva e Forza Italia astenuta.Non ha partecipato al voto Patton (Autonomie). Semaforo verde dunque alla norma \"spalma-crediti\" che li diluisce in 10 anni.",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715788805.0466642,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "DL SUPERBONUS, VOTO IN DOMATTINA Government has announced the trust",
        "en_content": "Dl Superbonus, government places confidence The government has placed the question of trust on the Superbonus Decree, in the Senate Hall after the free path of the Finance Committee. The final vote is scheduled in the morning. The text expires on 28/5 and must pass in second session to the House. Yesterday the commission had voted the amendment of the government, with the yes of Italy Viva and Forza Italia astenuta. He did not participate in the vote Patton (Autonomie). Green light therefore to the rule \"spalma-crediti\" which dilutes them in 10 years.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "VOTO",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Superbonus Decree",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Senate Hall",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Finance Committee",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the morning",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yesterday",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 387,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 409,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Patton",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years",
                "start_char": 548,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "KIEV SI RITIRA DA ALCUNE ZONE A KHARKIV \"Manovra per salvare vite soldati\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Kiev si ritira da alcune zone a Kharkiv L'esercito ucraino ha annunciato di  essere stato costretto a ritirarsi in alcune zone del fronte nella regione di Kharkiv,per l'intesa offensiva russa \"Le nostre unità hanno manovrato verso posizioni più favorevoli per salvare la vita dei nostri soldati ed evitare vittime\", fa sapere lo stato maggiore. Nella regione sono 30mila i soldati  russi impegnati negli attacchi, segnala il Consiglio di sicurezza di Kiev. Il ministero della Difesa russo annuncia che le truppe russe hanno conquistato altri due villaggi nella regione.",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715788805.06161,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "KIEV RITIRA DA ALCUNE ZONE TO KHARKIV \"Manovra to save lives soldiers\"",
        "en_content": "Kiev withdraws from some areas in Kharkiv The Ukrainian army has announced that it has been forced to retire to some areas of the front in the Kharkiv region, for the Russian offensive understanding \"Our units have manoeuvred towards more favorable positions to save the lives of our soldiers and to avoid casualties\", says the major state. In the region are 30 thousand Russian soldiers engaged in attacks, reports the Security Council of Kiev. The Russian Defense Ministry announces that Russian troops have conquered two other villages in the region.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "KIEV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manovra",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 thousand",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Security Council of Kiev",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Russian Defense Ministry",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 490,
                "end_char": 497,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 523,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SLOVACCHIA, FICO E' IN PERICOLO DI VITA 3-4 colpi pistola a petto, addome, arto Operato d'urgenza,preso attentatore",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " 3-4 colpi pistola contro premier Fico Il primo ministro slovacco Robert Fico è stato ferito in un attacco a colpi d' arma da fuoco al di fuori della Casa della Cultura nella città di Handova. Fico, che ha 59 anni, è stato colpito allo stomaco, all'addome,al petto e ad un arto da almeno 3-4 colpi di pistola. Il premier è stato soccorso con un elicottero e trasportato in ospedale dove è stato sottoposto a un delicato intervento.E' in pericolo di vita.   L'attentatore che si nascondeva tra la folla dove stava passando Fico, è stato fermato dai passanti e poi arrestato. Ha 71 anni.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715788805.0663881,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "SLOVACCHIA, FICO IS IN PERICLE OF LIFE 3-4 shots chest gun, abdomen, arto Operato of urgency,preso bomber",
        "en_content": "3-4 gunshots against Premier Fico The Slovak Prime Minister Robert Fico was wounded in a gunshot attack outside the House of Culture in the city of Handova. Fico, who is 59 years old, was hit in the stomach, at the abdomen, in the chest and at a limb from at least 3-4 shots of gun. The premier was rescued with a helicopter and transported to the hospital where he was subjected to a delicate intervention. She's in danger of life. The bomber hiding in the crowd where Fico was passing, was stopped by passersby and then arrested. She's 71.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FICO",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "arto Operato",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "preso",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 1,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovak",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Robert Fico",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the House of Culture",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Handova",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "59 years old",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 3-4",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "71",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 540,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL SUPERBONUS, DOMANI IL VOTO FINALE   Senato, governo ha posto la fiducia",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715788805.0800574,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "DL SUPERBONUS, QUESTIONS YOUR FINAL Senate, government placed confidence",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ILARIA SALIS AI DOMICILIARI A BUDAPEST  Cauzione di 40mila euro e braccialetto  Padre:io non tranquillo finchè è lì",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715788805.1086254,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "ILARI SALIS TO DOMICILIARI A BUDAPEST Deposit of 40 thousand euros and bracelet Father: I not quiet until it is there",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ILARI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "DOMICILIARI A BUDAPEST Deposit",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "40 thousand euros",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCHLEIN:\"DIMISSIONI DI TOTI NECESSARIE\" \"La Liguria non può restare appesa\"",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Inchiesta Genova, Schlein: Toti via ora \"Lo abbiamo detto sin dall'inizio: alla luce di quanto sta emergendo,dimissioni di Toti sono necessarie e opportune Non Non può restare un minuto di più\". Così a Repubblica la segretaria Pd Schlein. \"Al di là delle responsabilità penali, che sarà la magistratura ad accertare, la Liguria non può restare appesa a un' incertezza amministrativa che fa male ai cittadini e impedisce decisioni\". Poi: Meloni \"zitta per giorni, silenzio assordante, ora invoca pazienza. Su  Emiliano,neppure sfiorato da inchiesta, sua maggioranza ha occupato tutti i Tg. Garantisti solo quando tocca a loro\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715788805.1262803,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "SCHLEIN: \"DIMISSIONS OF TOTI NECESSARI\" \"Liguria cannot be hung\"",
        "en_content": "Genoa, Schlein: \"We said it from the beginning: In the light of what is emerging, resignation of Toti is necessary and appropriate It cannot remain a minute longer\". So to Republic the secretary Pd Schlein. \"Beyond the criminal responsibilities, which will be the judiciary to ascertain, Liguria cannot remain burdened with an administrative uncertainty that hurts citizens and prevents decisions\". Then: Meloni \"sit for days, deafening silence, now invokes patience. On Emiliano, even though it was unleashed by investigation, his majority occupied all Tg. Garantisti only when it comes to them.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SCHLEIN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Liguria",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a minute",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd Schlein",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Liguria",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 405,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "days",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emiliano",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tg",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Garantisti",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 568,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "COPPA ITALIA, FINALE ATALANTA-JUVE",
        "date_raw": "May 15, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-15",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=201",
        "content": "     ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715788805.1806822,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-15 18:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-15T18.00.05",
        "en_title": "COP ITALIA, FINAL ATALANTA-JUVE",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "COP",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    }
]
