[
    {
        "title": "UCRAINA, TELEFONATA TRA USA E RUSSIA   Tregua, Trump:domani risposta Putin",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742115603.9562352,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.03",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "HAMAS:ISRAELE HA VIOLATO ACCORDO TREGUA Con l'attacco a Beit Lahia:9 morti",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Hamas:Israele ha violato accordo tregua Hamas ha accusato Israele di aver commesso una \"palese violazione\" dell'accordo di cessate il fuoco a Gaza, dopo che l'agenzia di difesa civile palestinese ha riferito che nove persone sono state uccise in attacchi con droni israeliani nella città settentrionale di Beit Lahia.     Il portavoce di Hamas, Hazem Qassem, ha dichiarato che Israele ha preso di mira un gruppo di giornalisti e operatori umanitari,definendolo un \"massacro orribile\"e una violazione dei termini della tregua.L'Idf:stavano operando con droni",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742115603.9922104,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:03",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.03",
        "en_title": "HAMAS:SRAEL HAS VIOLATO AGREEMENT TREGUA With the attack on Beit Lahia:9 dead",
        "en_content": "Hamas: Israel has violated the truce agreement Hamas has accused Israel of committing a \"palese violation\" of the ceasefire agreement in Gaza, after the Palestinian civil defence agency reported that nine people were killed in attacks with Israeli drones in the northern city of Beit Lahia. Hamas spokesman, Hazem Qassem, said that Israel targeted a group of journalists and humanitarian workers, ending it a \"horrible mass\" and a violation of the terms of the truce. Idf: they were working with drones",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "HAMAS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Beit",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "nine",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beit Lahia",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hazem Qassem",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ROGO DISCOTECA, 51 MORTI IN N.MACEDONIA Durante concerto di gruppo hip-hop",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Rogo discoteca, 51 morti in N.Macedonia Oltre inquanta persone sono morte e  100 sono rimaste ferite nell'incendio in una discoteca a Kocani, Macedonia del Nord.      Le fiamme sono divampate nella notte, durante il concerto dei DNK, un duo macedone di hip-hop molto popolare. Soprattutto giovani tra le circa 1.500 persone presenti nella discoteca Pulse. A far partire le fiamme sarebbero stati gli effetti pirotecnici usati durante l'esibizione, che avrebbero incendiato il rivestimento di soffitti e pavimento.      ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742115604.0047386,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "ROGO DISCOTECA, 51 MORTI IN N.MACEDONIA During hip-hop group concert",
        "en_content": "Rogo disco, 51 dead in N.Macedonia Over fifty people died and 100 were injured in the fire at a disco in Kocani, North Macedonia. The flames are damped in the night, during the DNK concert, a very popular hip-hop Macedonian duo. Especially young people from around 1,500 people in the Pulse disco. To start the flames would have been the pyrotechnic effects used during the performance, which would have burned the covering of ceilings and floor.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "51",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "MORTI",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rogo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "51",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifty",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "100",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kocani",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "North Macedonia",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the night",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "DNK",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Macedonian",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "1,500",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Poi sente Bin Salman su pace Ucraina124  COLLE:DEMOCRAZIA ANTICORPO NAZIONALISMI Mattarella riceve premio a Gorizia",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Colle:democrazia anticorpo nazionalismi A Gorizia per ricevere il Premio Patroni, di cui è stato insignito con l' omologo sloveno Pahor, il Presidnete Mattarella sottolinea la \"sorte felice di assistere alla trasformazione di un confine -traccia divisoria nel cuore di una città e di una popolazionein luogo di incontro e di condivisione\". \"E' ai cittadini di queste terre che dobbiamo il successo di questo percorso:società mature,cresciute in democrazia, con efficaci anticorpi alle lusinghe di sterili,pericolosi nazionalismi. che hanno arrecato tanti gravi danni\". ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742115604.0708342,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "Then he hears Bin Salman on peace Ukraine124 COLLE: DEMOCRACY NATIONAL ANTICAL ANALYSISM Mattarella receives award in Gorizia",
        "en_content": "Colle:National antibody democracy In Gorizia to receive the Patroness Award, of which he was awarded with the Slovenian counterpart Pahor, the Presidnete Mattarella emphasizes the \"happysort to witness the transformation of a boundary -trace divider in the heart of a city and a population in place of meeting and sharing\". \"It is to the citizens of these lands that we owe the success of this path: mature society, grown in democracy, with effective antibodies to the flattering of sterile, dangerous nationalisms. that have caused so much serious damage.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bin Salman",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gorizia",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 125,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gorizia",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Patroness Award",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovenian",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pahor",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Presidnete Mattarella",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PRESIDENTE SERBO VUCIC CEDE ALLA PIAZZA \"Tra 4-5 mesi verso nuove elezioni\"",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Vucic cede alle proteste:sì a elezioni Il presidente serbo Aleksandar Vucic si è detto pronto, nell'arco di 4-5 mesi a sottoporsi a una prova di legittimità, andando incontro alle opposizioni e affrontando nuove elezioni o un referendum sulla sua persona.   \"Sono sempre pronto a una verifica di legittimità\",ha detto Vucic diretta tv, rispondendo a una domanda se con la  grande manifestazione di protesta di ieri a Belgrado,alla quale hanno partecipato fino a 300mila persone, non sia stata messa seriamente in dubbio la sua legittimità alla guida del Paese. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742115604.082895,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "\"In 4-5 months towards new elections\"",
        "en_content": "Vucic surrenders to protests: yes to elections Serbian President Aleksandar Vucic said he was ready, over 4-5 months to undergo a proof of legitimacy, meeting opposition and addressing new elections or a referendum on his person. \"I am always ready for a verification of legitimacy,\" said Vucic direct tv, answering a question if with the great protest event yesterday in Belgrade, to which they participated up to 300 thousand people, it was not seriously questioned its legitimacy to guide the country.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "4-5 months",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vucic",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Serbian",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aleksandar Vucic",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4-5 months",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vucic direct tv",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 368,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgrade",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "up to 300 thousand",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GIORGETTI:GRANDI BANCHE DIMENTICANO PMI \"Fanno profitti ma non credito\"",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Giorgetti:grandi banche dimenticano Pmi \"Le grandi banche fanno grandissimi  profitti, però forse si dimenticano di fare quello per cui sono nate e cioè fare credito alle imprese e soprattutto alle piccole e medie imprese\".  Lo dice il ministro dell'Economia, Giorgetti, all'iniziativa leghista ad Ancona \"Tutta un'altra economia\".  \"Se io devo prendere una decisione devo fare in qualche modo che continui a  sopravvivere quella che qualcuno ha  chiamato la biodiversità bancaria\",  aggiunge Giorgetti.    ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742115604.0923104,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "DAYS:GRAND BANKS DIMENTICAN SMEs \"They make profits but not credit\"",
        "en_content": "Giorgetti: big banks forget Pmi \"The big banks make huge profits, but perhaps they forget to do what they were born and that is to make credit to the enterprises and especially to the small and medium enterprises\". This is said by the Minister of Economy, Giorgetti, to the Leghista initiative in Ancona \"All another economy\". \"If I have to make a decision I have to make somehow that it continues to survive what someone called banking biodiversity,\" adds Giorgetti.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "DAYS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pmi",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Minister of Economy, Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Leghista",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ancona",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UCRAINA, TELEFONATA TRA USA E RUSSIA   Tregua, Trump:domani risposta Putin",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Ucraina, telefonata tra Lavrov e Rubio Telefonata tra il ministro russo degli Esteri Lavrov e l'omologo Usa Rubio. Nel colloquio sono stati discussi i  prossimi passi da compiere dopo i recenti incontri in Arabia Saudita sulla crisi ucraina e si è concordato di continuare a lavorare per ripristinare le relazioni Usa-Russia, fa sapere il Dipartimento di Stato Usa. A Rubio Lavrov ha detto di evitare uso forza in Yemen. Nessuna risposta ancora da Mosca sulla proposta di un mese di tregua portata dagli Usa e accettata da Kiev. Secondo Trump, Putin risponderà domani.  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742115604.1033819,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Ukraine, phone call between Lavrov and Rubio Called between Russian Foreign Minister Lavrov and U.S. Rubio. In the interview were discussed the next steps to be taken after recent meetings in Saudi Arabia on the Ukrainian crisis and agreed to continue working to restore US-Russia relations, let the US State Department know. At Rubio Lavrov said to avoid force use in Yemen. No response from Moscow on the proposal of a month of truce taken by the US and accepted by Kiev.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lavrov",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rubio",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lavrov",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S. Rubio",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the US State Department",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rubio Lavrov",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "a month",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 451,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SERRA: \"DIAMOCI UNA MOSSA\" PER L'UNIONE \"Nessuno è libero sotto le bombe\"",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Serra in piazza: tanti,diversi,insieme In una Piazza del Popolo tanto gremita che sono stati chiusi gli accessi, sale sul palco Michele Serra che ha lanciato la mobilitazione di oggi per l'Europa. \"Diamoci una mossa-dice-o l'unica bandiera da sventolare resterà la carta di credito. Tutti vogliamo la pace ma non può esserci pace senza libertà. Nessuno è libero sotto le bombe e con un fucile puntato addosso. La guerra è il contrario della pace ma anche della libertà\". \"Siamo 50 mila,un popolo. Siamo diversi ma insieme. Non perdiamoci di vista\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742115604.134876,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "SERRA: \"Let's say a MOSSA\" for UNION \"No one is free under bombs\"",
        "en_content": "Serra in piazza: many, different, together In a Square of the People so greedy that the accesses were closed, rises on stage Michele Serra that launched today's mobilization for Europe. \"Let's give a move-say-or the only flag to be swept will remain the credit card. We all want peace but there can be no peace without freedom. No one's free under the bombs and a shotgun. War is the opposite of peace but also of freedom.\" \"We are 50,000, a people. We're different but together. Let's not lose sight.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SERRA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "MOSSA",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Serra",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michele Serra",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "50,000",
                "start_char": 432,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RAID USA CONTRO HOUTHI A SANAA:31 MORTI Trump:\"Fermatevi o sarà l'inferno\"",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Raid Usa su Houthi in Yemen, 31 morti E' salito ad almeno 31 morti e 100 feriti il bilancio degli attacchi Usa  contro i ribelli Houthi nello Yemen. Con la capitale Sanaa, colpiti i governatorati di Saada nel nord e Al-Bayda al centro. Sempre nel centro,colpita la città di Radaa. Le vittime sono \"per lo più bambini e donne\", scrive su X il ministero della Sanità Houthi.  , \"A tutti i terroristi Houthi, il vostro tempo è scaduto e i vostri attacchi devono finire,a partire da oggi.Se non lo farete,l'inferno si abbatterà su di voi come non avete mai visto prima\",ha detto Trump seguendo i raid da Washington.",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742115604.1815655,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "RAID USA CONTRO HOUTHI AT SANAA:31 MORTI: Trump:\"Make it or it will be hell\"",
        "en_content": "Raid Usa on Houthi in Yemen, 31 dead Has gone up to at least 31 dead and 100 injured the budget of the attacks Use against the Houthi rebels in Yemen. With the capital Sanaa, hit the governors of Saada in the north and Al-Bayda in the center. Always in the center, you take the town of Radaa. The victims are \"mostly children and women\", writes on X the Ministry of Health Houthi. , \"To all Houthi terrorists, your time has expired and your attacks must end, starting today. If you do not, hell will fall on you as you have never seen before,\" Trump said following the raid from Washington.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "RAID USA CONTRO HOUTHI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Raid Usa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "31",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 31",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "100",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanaa",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saada",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Bayda",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Radaa",
                "start_char": 286,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "X the Ministry of Health Houthi",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 544,
                "end_char": 549,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 579,
                "end_char": 589,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GP AUSTRALIA,VINCE NORRIS SU VERSTAPPEN Ferrari si fermano a 8° e 10°posto",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=260",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742115604.20029,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "GP AUSTRALIA,VINCE NORRIS SU VERSTAPPEN Ferrari stop at 8° and 10°posto",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GP AUSTRALIA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "VINCE NORRIS SU",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "8° and",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PAPA MIGLIORA, RIDOTTA LA VENTILAZIONE  Necessarie le terapie ospedaliere",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742115604.2552657,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "BEST PAPA, REDUCED VENTILATION Hospital Therapies",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI:NO INVIO SOLDATI ITALIANI A KIEV Impegno per la pace e la sicurezza",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Meloni:impegno per pace,no invio truppe La presidente del Consiglio, Giorgia Meloni, ha sentito telefonicamente il premier britannico Starmer.   La premier ha partecipato alla Call  con Londra che collega diversi leader internazionali della \"coalizione dei volenterosi\". La coalizione è impegnata a garantire la sicurezza di Kiev nella guerra scatenata da Mosca.   Meloni ha ribadito che l'Italia intende continuare a lavorare con i partner  europei e gli Stati uniti per la pace e la sicurezza in Ucraina, ma che non prevede di inviare militari sul terreno",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742115604.2614794,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ A KIEV Commitment for Peace and Security",
        "en_content": "Meloni: commitment to peace, no sending troops The President of the Council, Giorgia Meloni, telephoned the British Premier Starmer. The premier participated in the Call with London linking several international leaders of the \"coalition of the voluntarians\". The coalition is committed to securing the security of Kiev in the Moscow war. Meloni reiterated that Italy intends to continue working with European partners and the United States for peace and security in Ukraine, but does not plan to send military on the ground",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Moscow war",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 409,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "50MILA MANIFESTANO A ROMA PER L'EUROPA  Bandiere della Ue a Piazza del Popolo  Ma raduni anche contro il riarmo",
        "date_raw": "March 16, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Piazze per l'Europa e contro il riarmo Tre manifestazioni di segno opposto a Roma. A Piazza del Popolo l'iniziativa lanciata da Michele Serra \"Una piazza per l'Europa\". Aderiscono, senza bandiere, Pd, Azione, +Europa, Italia Viva con i loro leader, oltre a sindacati, sindaci, intellettuali, artisti e  numerose organizzazioni. Ma non il M5s. Sit-in a Piazza Barberini, invece, per PaP e chi si oppone al piano di riarmo. E a Piazza Bocca della Verità il raduno indetto dalla coppia Marco Rizzo generale Vannacci, anch'essi contrari al \"ReArm Europe\".    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742115604.326938,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-16 10:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-16T09.00.04",
        "en_title": "50MILA MANIFESTANO ROMA FOR EUROPE EU flags in Piazza del Popolo But also rallies against the rearmament",
        "en_content": "Squares for Europe and against the rearmament Three manifestations of opposite sign in Rome. In Piazza del Popolo the initiative launched by Michele Serra \"Una piazza per l'Europa\". They join, without flags, Pd, Action, +Europe, Italy Live with their leaders, as well as unions, mayors, intellectuals, artists and numerous organizations. But not the M5s. Sit-in in Piazza Barberini, instead, for PaP and those who oppose the rearmament plan. And in Piazza Bocca della Verità the gathering organized by the couple Marco Rizzo General Vannacci, also contrary to the \"ReArm Europe\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "50MILA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "MANIFESTANO ROMA",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza del Popolo",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Three",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza del Popolo",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Michele Serra",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd, Action",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "+Europe",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "M5s",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza Barberini",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "PaP",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza Bocca",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "della Verità",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco Rizzo",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 524,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vannacci",
                "start_char": 533,
                "end_char": 541,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the \"ReArm Europe\"",
                "start_char": 560,
                "end_char": 578,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
