[
    {
        "title": "LIBANO,RAID ISRAELIANI E SORVOLO BEIRUT Durante i funerali di Nasrallah",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=159",
        "content": " Libano, diversi raid aerei israeliani L'aviazione israeliana ha compiuto due attacchi nel Sud del Libano poco prima dell'inizio delle imponenti esequie a Beirut di Nasrallah, il defunto leader di Hezbollah.Colpita la regione di Tiro Altri raid anche nel Nord Est del Paese Jet israeliani hanno poi sorvolato a bassa quota Beirut durante i funerali. L'Esercito israeliano ha confermato gli attacchi, mirati a obiettivi di Hezbollah, accusato di \"violare gli accordi\". Il ministro della Difesa israeliano  Katz afferma che \"è un messaggio per chi minaccia e attacca Israele\".  ",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.5507548,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "LIBANON, ISRAELIANI AND SORVOLO BEIRUT During Nasrallah's funeral",
        "en_content": "Lebanon, several Israeli air raids The Israeli air force performed two attacks in southern Lebanon just before the beginning of the massive exequies in Beirut, Nasrallah, the deceased leader of Hezbollah. Hit the region of Tyre Other raids also in the North East of the Israeli Jet Country then flew at low altitude Beirut during funerals. The Israeli Army confirmed the attacks, aimed at Hezbollah's targets, accused of \"violating the agreements\". Israeli Defense Minister Katz states that \"it is a message for those who threaten and attack Israel.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISRAELIANI",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nasrallah",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beirut",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nasrallah",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tyre Other",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North East",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beirut",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Israeli Army",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 542,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GERMANIA,VINCE LA CDU. VOLA LA DESTRA  Cdu 28,6%,Afd 19,5%,Spd 16,5,Verdi 13,5 Merz,Cdu:\"Abbiamo vinto,serata storica\" Weidel, Afd: \"Pronti a governare\"",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740355204.5586047,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "GERMANY,VINCE LA CDU. VOLA LA DESTRA Cdu 28.6%,Afd 19,5%,Spd 16,5,Verdi 13,5 Merz,Cdu:\"We won, historical evening\" Weidel, Afd: \"Ready to rule\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GERMANY",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "VINCE LA CDU",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "VOLA LA",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "28.6%,Afd",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "13,5",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Merz",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Weidel, Afd:",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev:350 mld risorse terre occupate",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Kiev:350 mld risorse territori occupati L'Ucraina stima di avere risorse naturali \"essenziali\" per un valore di 350 miliardi di dollari,tra cui il titanio, nel territorio occupato dalla Russia. Lo ha detto la vicepremier ucraina Svyrydenko,in conferenza stampa,a proposito delle tensioni con gli Usa per un accordo sui minerali ucraini.  Il ministro della Difesa annuncia che l'Ucraina lavora a \"un'alternativa\" ai sistemi di telecomunicazione Starlink, fondamentali per l'esercito. \"Una soluzione esiste già\",ha detto il ministro.",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.5749385,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "Kiev:350 mld occupied land resources",
        "en_content": "Kiev:350 mld resources occupied territories Ukraine estimates to have \"essential\" natural resources for a value of 350 billion dollars, including titanium, in the territory occupied by Russia. The Ukrainian vice-premier Svyrydenko, in the press conference, said this about tensions with the US for an agreement on Ukrainian minerals. The Defence Minister announces that Ukraine is working on \"an alternative\" to the Starlink telecommunications systems, which are fundamental to the army. \"A solution already exists,\" said the minister.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "mld",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "350 billion dollars",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Svyrydenko",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starlink",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"Spero in svolta nell'incontro Ue\"",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Zelensky: spero \"svolta\" in incontro Ue Il presidente ucraino Zelensky auspica che l'incontro di domani con i leader europei,nel terzo anniversario di guerra, segni \"un punto di svolta\". Ribadisce che con la premier Meloni ha \"ottimi rapporti\". \"Mi ha detto che voleva venire,ma ha un incontro. Sarà online\". Zelensky non si è offeso quando Trump lo ha definito un \"dittatore\". \"Non ne ho motivo. Sono stato eletto legittimamnte\". Ci saranno elezioni dopo la fine della legge marziale,dice. \"Non sarò al potere per 10 anni, ma non permetteremo a Putin di salire al potere in Ucraina\"",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.5780451,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "\"I hope in turn at the Ue meeting\"",
        "en_content": "Zelensky: I hope \"turned\" at the meeting Ue Ukrainian President Zelensky hopes that tomorrow's meeting with European leaders, on the third anniversary of war, signs \"a turning point\". He repeats that with Premier Meloni he has \"excellent relationships\". \"He told me he wanted to come, but he has a meeting. It'll be online.\" Zelensky did not offend when Trump called it a \"dictator\". \"I have no reason. I was elected legitimate.\" There will be elections after the end of martial law,say. \"I will not be in power for 10 years, but we will not allow Putin to rise to power in Ukraine\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ue",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years",
                "start_char": 516,
                "end_char": 524,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 548,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 574,
                "end_char": 581,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele:sempre pronti guerra a Gaza",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Israele: sempre pronti a guerra a Gaza Netanyahu è \"pronto a riprendere la  guerra\". Il primo ministro israeliano ha affermato che \"in qualsiasi momento\" potrebbero riprendere i combattimenti a Gaza. Parlando alla cerimonia per la promozione di nuovi ufficiali,ha detto: \"I nostri piani operativi sono pronti. Raggiungeremo interamente gli obiettivi della guerra, che sia attraverso il  negoziato o con altri mezzi\".   Poi, ha chiesto la \"completa smilitarizzazione della Siria meridionale\" e non permetterà alle nuove forze governative di \"entrare a sud di Damasco\". ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.5808105,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "Israel: always ready war in Gaza",
        "en_content": "Israel: always ready to war in Gaza Netanyahu is \"ready to resume the war\". The Israeli Prime Minister said that \"at any time\" could resume fighting in Gaza. Speaking at the ceremony for the promotion of new officers, he said: \"Our operational plans are ready. We will fully reach the objectives of the war, whether through negotiation or by other means.\" Then, he called for \"complete dismilitarization of southern Syria\" and will not allow new government forces to \"enter south of Damascus\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Damascus",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ue: Consiglio straordinario 6 marzo",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Ucraina, il 6 marzo Consiglio Europeo Un Consiglio europeo straordinario si terrà il 6 marzo a Bruxelles. Lo ha annunciato il Presidente del Consiglio europeo, Antonio Costa in un post su X. Gli argomenti all'ordine del giorno saranno Ucraina e difesa europea.  \"Stiamo vivendo un momento decisivo per la sicurezza dell' Ucraina e in Europa. Nelle consultazioni con i leader europei, ho percepito un impegno comune ad affrontare queste sfide a livello Ue: rafforzare la difesa europea e contribuire in modo decisivo alla pace nel Continente e in Ucraina\" così Costa. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.5880063,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "EU: Extraordinary Council 6 March",
        "en_content": "Ukraine, on 6 March European Council An extraordinary European Council will be held on 6 March in Brussels. It was announced by the President of the European Council, Antonio Costa in a post on X. The topics on the agenda will be Ukraine and European defence. \"We are experiencing a decisive moment for the security of Ukraine and Europe. In consultations with European leaders, I felt a common commitment to address these challenges at EU level: strengthen European defence and contribute decisively to peace in the Continent and Ukraine\" so Costa.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Extraordinary Council 6 March",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 March European Council",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European Council",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "6 March",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Council",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Costa",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 439,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Continent",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Costa",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CISGIORDANIA, TORNANO I TANK DI ISRAELE Dispiegati dopo più di 20 anni",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Cisgiordania, tank Israele dopo 20 anni Tornano dopo 20 anni i carri armati di Israele nelle terre della Cisgiordania. L'Esercito israeliano li ha dispiegati per ampliare l'operazione antiterrorismo in corso nell'area di Jenin.  \"E' la prima volta dall'Operazione Scudo Difensivo del 2002 che i tank  dell'Idf operano in Cisgiordania\". Le operazioni sono iniziate in diversi  villaggi vicino a Jenin.   Sgomberati 3 campi profughi. L'Idf sta sgomberando \"i nidi del terrore\", dice il ministro della Difesa Katz.\"Ho ordinato all'esercito una lunga permanenza\"",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.5907004,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "CISGIORDANIA, TANK OF ISRAEL Unfolded after more than 20 years",
        "en_content": "West Bank, Israel tank after 20 years Israel tanks back after 20 years in the West Bank. The Israeli Army deployed them to expand the ongoing anti-terrorism operation in the Jenin area. \"It is the first time since the 2002 Defensive Shield Operation that Idf tanks operate in the West Bank.\" Operations began in several villages near Jenin. 3 refugee camps are cleared. The Idf is clearing \"the nests of terror\", says Defense Minister Katz.\"I ordered the army a long stay\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISRAEL",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 20 years",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "West Bank",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "20 years",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "20 years",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Israeli Army",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jenin",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the 2002",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Defensive Shield Operation",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Operations",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jenin",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 439,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ZELENSKY: LASCIO SE NATO ACCOGLIE KIEV  A Trump chiede garanzie sicurezza",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Zelensky:lascio se Nato accoglierà Kiev \"Se c'è bisogno che mi dimetta, sono pronto. Scambierei la mia uscita con l' adesione dell'Ucraina alla Nato. Lascerei, se fosse per la pace\".Così il presidente Zelensky, in conferenza stampa. \"Sono concentrato sulla sicurezza di Kiev ora, non tra 20 anni\".   Si dice \"grato\" per il supporto degli Usa,ma chiede a Trump \"comprensione reciproca\" e garanzie di sicurezza. \"Vorrei incontrarlo prima che veda Putin\". \"Non firmerò ciò che pagheranno 10 generazioni di ucraini\", spiega riguardo all'accordo sui minerali. Accordo sui cui \"ci sono progressi\".   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.630154,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "ZELENSKY: LASCIO SE NATO ACCOGLIE KIEV At Trump calls for security guarantees",
        "en_content": "Zelensky: I leave if NATO will welcome Kiev \"If there is need to dismiss me, I am ready. I would exchange my exit with the accession of Ukraine to NATO. I would leave, if it were for peace.\" So President Zelensky, at the press conference. \"I'm focused on Kiev security now, not in 20 years.\" It is said to be \"free\" for the support of the US, but it asks Trump \"common understanding\" and security guarantees. \"I'd like to meet him before he sees Putin.\" \"I won't sign what 10 generations of Ukrainians will pay,\" he explains. Agreement on which \"there are progress\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ZELENSKY",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "LASCIO SE",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "20 years",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 451,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 475,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainians",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "M.O., MATTARELLA: DIALOGO E NO RANCORE  \"Evitare ripresa dei combattimenti\"",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " M.O., Mattarella: dialogo e no rancore \"Abbiamo condannato con fermezza il disumano e vile attacco terroristico del 7 ottobre di Hamas,che rinnova atrocità con il crudele spettacolo della consegna di ostaggi sopravvissuti e i corpi di quelli uccisi. Abbiamo esercitato sforzi perché il conflitto avesse fine\" Così Mattarella alla cena in onore del presidente degli UAE, bin Zayed Al Nahyan, al Quirinale. \"L'impegno non può che essere evitare una ripresa dei combattimenti, tenere aperti i colloqui e rimuovere i sedimenti di rancore\", ha aggiunto il capo dello Stato italiano. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740355204.6480753,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "M.O., MATTARELLA: DIALOGO AND NO RANCORE \" Avoid resumption of the fights\"",
        "en_content": "M.O., Mattarella: dialogue and no grudge \"We firmly condemned the inhuman and vile terrorist attack on October 7 of Hamas, which renews atrocities with the cruel show of the delivery of surviving hostages and the bodies of those killed. We have exerted efforts to end the conflict\" So Mattarella at dinner in honor of the president of the UAE, bin Zayed Al Nahyan, at the Quirinale. \"The commitment can only be avoided a resumption of the fights, keep open the talks and remove the sediments of grudge\", added the head of the Italian state.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "M.O.",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "M.O.",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 7",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "UAE",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "bin Zayed Al Nahyan",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quirinale",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 526,
                "end_char": 533,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCIOPERO BUS,TRAM,VOLI. RISCHIO DISAGI  24 ore per il trasporto pubblico",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Sciopero bus,tram.Domani rischio disagi Rischio disagi domani per uno sciopero del trasporto pubblico locale a livello nazionale indetto dai sindacati di base contro il mancato adeguamento salariale e le condizioni contrattuali per il  triennio 2024-2036.    Lo sciopero è di 24 ore per metro,bus e tram, e di 4 ore nel comparto aereo per EasyJet e Aeroitalia.Il personale viaggiante si fermerà dalle 12 alle 16.  Nel trasporto pubblico locale previste le fasce di garanzie con orari diversi da città a città.    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740355204.6661406,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "BUS,TRAM,VOLI. DISAGI 24 hours for public transport",
        "en_content": "Strike bus,tram.Today risk inconvenience Risk inconvenience tomorrow for a strike of local public transport at national level called by the basic unions against the lack of wage adjustment and contractual conditions for the three-year period 2024-2036. The strike is 24 hours per meter, bus and tram, and 4 hours in the airfield for EasyJet and Aeroitalia. Travellers will stop from 12 to 16. In the local public transport provided the guarantees with different times from city to city.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "24 hours",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "three-year",
                "start_char": 224,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024-2036",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 hours",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "4 hours",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "EasyJet",
                "start_char": 333,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aeroitalia",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "12",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "16",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI:OMAGGIO A EROICA RESISTENZA KIEV Lettera alla manifestazione di Roma   A tre anni dall'inizio della guerra",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Meloni: omaggio eroica resistenza Kiev Il consigliere diplomatico della premier Meloni, Fabrizio Saggio,ha inviato una lettera a Oles Horodetsky, presidente Associazione cristiani ucraini in Italia,che ha indetto una manifestazione per il terzo anniversario della guerra in Ucraina.    \"Sostenere l'Ucraina e il popolo ucraino significa sostenere la difesa della libertà. Purtroppo, per impegni istituzionali,il presidente del Consiglio non potrà essere alla manifestazione\",recita la lettera. Prosegue rendendo \"omaggio all'eroica resistenza del popolo ucraino, anche in questo anniversario\".",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740355204.670242,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "MELONI:OMAGGIO A EROICA RESISTENZA KIEV Letter to the manifestation of Rome Three years from the beginning of the war",
        "en_content": "Meloni: heroic homage Kiev The diplomatic adviser of Prime Minister Meloni, Fabrizio Saggio, sent a letter to Oles Horodetsky, president of Ukrainian Christian Association in Italy, who called a demonstration for the third anniversary of the war in Ukraine. \"To support Ukraine and the Ukrainian people means to support the defense of freedom. Unfortunately, for institutional commitments, the President of the Council will not be able to attend the event,\" says the letter. It continues by making \"a tribute to the heroic resistance of the Ukrainian people, even on this anniversary\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EROICA RESISTENZA KIEV Letter",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Three years",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fabrizio Saggio",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Oles Horodetsky",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 125,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian Christian Association",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 286,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Rugby: Italia cede a Francia 24-73",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=260",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740355204.673676,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "Rugby: Italy cedes to France 24-73",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Merz,Cdu:\"Abbiamo vinto,serata storica\" Weidel, Afd: \"Pronti a governare\"",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Voto Germania,Merz (Cdu): abbiamo vinto \"Serata storica. Cdu e Csu hanno vinto le elezioni\". Così il candidato cancelliere Merz, dopo l'affermazione come primo partito in Germania.\"Non sarà facile formare un governo. Dobbiamo farlo presto,il mondo non aspetta noi.La Germania deve tornare a essere affidabile\" Secondo partito l'estrema destra di Afd \"Abbiamo raddoppiato i voti.Mano tesa a una partecipazione al governo\", dice la leader Weidel.     Il leader Spd Scholz parla di \"amara sconfitta\". E ribadisce:\"Nessuna collaborazione con l'Afd\".   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.6871192,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "Merz,Cdu:\"We won, historical evening\" Weidel, Afd: \"Ready to rule\"",
        "en_content": "Vote Germany,Merz (Cdu): we won \"Historical evening. Cdu and Csu won the election.\" Thus the candidate Chancellor Merz, after the statement as first party in Germany. \"It will not be easy to form a government. We have to do it soon, the world is not waiting for us. Germany must return to be reliable\" Second party the extreme right of Afd \"We doubled the votes. Hands aimed at participation in the government,\" says leader Weidel. The leader Spd Scholz speaks of bitter defeat. \"No collaboration with the Afd.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Merz",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Weidel, Afd:",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Merz",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Csu",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Merz",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Second",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Weidel",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spd Scholz",
                "start_char": 443,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "EXIT POLL GERMANIA, IN TESTA CDU AL 29% Afd 19%, Spd 16, Verdi 13, Linke 8",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Exit poll Germania, in testa Cdu al 29% Chiusi i seggi elettorali in Germania, i primi exit poll danno in testa la Cdu dei cristiano-democratici con il 29%. Segue l'estrema destra dell'Afd al 19,5%.      I socialdemocratici di Spd scendono al 16,5%. Verdi 13,5%, la sinistra di Linke all'8,5%.Rischiano di non superare la soglia del 5% i liberali di Fdp al 4,9% e Bsw al 4,7%.   Affluenza molto alta, all'84%, la maggiore dal 1990.    ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740355204.6904604,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "EXIT POLL GERMANY, IN TESTA CDU AL 29% Afd 19%, Spd 16, Verdi 13, Links 8",
        "en_content": "Exit poll Germany, head Cdu at 29% Closed poll seats in Germany, the first exit polls lead the Cdu of Christian-Democrats with 29%. It follows the extreme right of the Afd at 19.5%. The Social-Democrats of Spd descend to 16.5%. Greens 13,5%, the left of Linke at 8.5%. They claim not to exceed the threshold of 5% Fdp liberals at 4.9% and Bsw at 4.7%. Very high turnout, to 84%, the largest since 1990.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GERMANY",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "TESTA",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "29%",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "19%",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Spd 16",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Verdi 13",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Exit",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cdu",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "29%",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Christian-Democrats",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "29%",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "19.5%",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Social-Democrats",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spd",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "16.5%",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "13,5%",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Linke",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "8.5%",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "5%",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "4.9%",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Bsw",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4.7%",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "84%",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "1990",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PAPA,LIEVE INSUFFICIENZA RENI:MA VIGILE \"Nessuna nuova crisi respiratoria\"",
        "date_raw": "February 24, 2025",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740355204.7416608,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 01:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T00.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    }
]
