[
    {
        "title": "COLLE:DANNI DA PROTEZIONISMI IMMOTIVATI \"Chiusure dal sapore autarchico\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742684406.3398821,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "COLLE:DANNI DA PROTEZIONISMI IMMOTIVATI \"Closures with autarchical taste\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "COLLE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "DANNI DA PROTEZIONISMI",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MEDIA:CINA VALUTA UNIRSI A\"VOLENTEROSI\" Per forze di peacekeeping a Kiev",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742684406.3668547,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "MEDIA: CHINA UNIRSI A\"VOLENTEROSI\" For peacekeeping forces in Kiev",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SCI, BRIGNONE VINCE LA COPPA DEL MONDO  Discese cancellate a Sun Valley     Gp Cina, Hamilton trionfa in Sprint",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=260",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742684406.4030085,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "SCI, BRIGNONE VINCE THE COP OF THE WORLD Excessed descent to Sun Valley Gp China, Hamilton triumphs in Sprint",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SCI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sun Valley Gp",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamilton",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sprint",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IL PAPA OGGI SARA' DIMESSO DAL GEMELLI  Dalla finestra prima saluterà la folla  Poi a Santa Marta, 2 mesi di riposo",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1742684406.4266236,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "_ From the first window will health the crowd Then to Santa Marta, 2 months rest",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Santa Marta",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2 months",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SALVINI:PER PACE TRUMP FA PIU' DI TUTTI Guerra con Meloni su Usa? Surreale",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Salvini: per pace Trump fa più di tutti \"Quei 10 minuti alla Casa Bianca con Trump, Vance e Zelensky hanno segnato un cambiamento totale del modus operandi: al di là di qualsiasi critica, è oggettivo che Trump in due mesi stia facendo più per la pace di quello che altri hanno fatto in anni e anni\". E' il pensiero del vicepremier, Salvini. \"Stiamo vicini a questo rinnovato clima di disarmo e pacificazione.Bisogna aiutare, accompagnare questo benedetto  processo di pace senza parlare di carri armati o 800 miliardi...\".\"Stiamo dalla parte giusta dela storia\". Gara con Meloni per telefonata con Vance? Surreale",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742684406.5077229,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "_ All War with Meloni on Usa? Surreal",
        "en_content": "Salvini: for peace Trump makes more than all \"Here 10 minutes at the White House with Trump, Vance and Zelensky marked a total change of the modus operandi: beyond any criticism, it is objective that Trump in two months is doing more for peace than others have done in years and years.\" It's the vicepremier's thought, Salvini. \"We are close to this renewed climate of disarmament and peace. We must help, accompany this blessed peace process without talking about tanks or 800 billion...\" \"We are on the right side of history\". Race with Meloni for phone call with Vance? Surreal",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10 minutes",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vance",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two months",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "years",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "800 billion",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vance",
                "start_char": 566,
                "end_char": 571,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PDL CORTE CONTI, ESTESO SCUDO POLITICI  Si presume \"la buona fede\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Pdl Corte Conti, esteso scudo politici Un emendamento alla Proposta di legge sulla riforma della Corte dei Conti  afferma che la buona fede dei politici si \"presume fino a prova contraria\" ad eccezione dei casi di dolo.   L'emendamento a firma Montaruli e Sbardella estende lo scudo già pevisto per i politici: la buona fede va presunta \"fino a prova contraria\" se adottano atti\"vistati o sottoscritti dai responsabili degli uffici tecnici o amministrativi in assenza di pareri formali, interni o esterni, di contario avviso\". L'emendamento è stato approvato.  ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742684406.5908022,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "PDL COURT CONTACT, EXTRACTIVE POLICY It is presumed \"good faith\"",
        "en_content": "Pdl Court Accounts, extended political shield An amendment to the bill on the reform of the Court of Auditors states that the good faith of politicians is \"presumed to an contrary test\" except for cases of dolo. The amendment by Montaruli and Sbardella extends the already pevised shield for politicians: the good faith must be presumed \"until proven otherwise\" if they adopt acts \"viewed or signed by the managers of the technical or administrative offices in the absence of formal, internal or external opinions, of a given notice\". The amendment was approved.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "PDL COURT CONTACT",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pdl Court Accounts",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Court of Auditors",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Montaruli",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sbardella",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Erdogan: \"L'opposizione crea caos\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Turchia, Erdogan: opposizione crea caos Recep Tayyip Erdogan, presidente turco, ha accusato il maggior partito di opposizione CHP di creare \"caos\" in Turchia dopo le proteste che si sono tenute per l'arresto di Ekrem Imamoglu, sindaco di Istanbul, in varie città.   \"A partire da Istanbul hanno tentato di creare caos e tensione nelle nostre città\", ha detto Erdogan durante un evento nella città sul Bosforo, trasmesso dalla tv di stato Trt. \"Hanno attaccato le nostre forze di polizia e tentato di minacciare i membri della nostra magistratura\" ha detto Erdogan. ",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.59757,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "Erdogan: \"The opposition creates chaos\"",
        "en_content": "Turkey, Erdogan: opposition creates chaos Recep Tayip Erdogan, Turkish president, accused the largest opposition party CHP of creating \"caos\" in Turkey after the protests held for the arrest of Ekrem Imamoglu, mayor of Istanbul, in various cities. \"Since Istanbul they tried to create chaos and tension in our cities,\" Erdogan said during an event in the city on the Bosphorus, broadcast by the state TV Trt. \"They attacked our police forces and tried to threaten the members of our judiciary,\" Erdogan said.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Recep Tayip Erdogan",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "CHP",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ekrem Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bosphorus",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 495,
                "end_char": 502,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MEDIA:CINA VALUTA UNIRSI A\"VOLENTEROSI\" \"Potrebbe favorire il sì di Mosca\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Media:Cina valuta unirsi a\"volenterosi\" La Cina sta considerando l'ipotesi di unirsi alla coalizione dei volenterosi a sostegno dell'Ucraina, in vista di un'eventuale missione di mantenimento della pace. Lo rivelano media tedeschi, citando fonti diplomatiche europee.  \"I diplomatici cinesi stanno sondando il terreno\" per capire se il coinvolgimento di Pechino sia \"auspicabile\" per l'Ue\", scrive Welt am Sonntag. \"L'inclusione della Cina potrebbe aumentare le possibilità che Mosca accetti la presenza di forze di peace keeping\", secondo le fonti.  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.6080737,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "MEDIA: CHINA VALUTA UNIRSI A\"VOLENTEROSI\" \"It could favor the yes of Moscow\"",
        "en_content": "Average:China currency join \"volenterosis\" China is considering joining the coalition of the willing to support Ukraine in view of a possible peacekeeping mission. They reveal German media, citing European diplomatic sources. \"Chinese diplomats are proving the ground\" to see if Beijing's involvement is \"auspicable\" for the EU,\" writes Welt am Sonntag. \"China's inclusion could increase the possibilities Moscow accepts the presence of peace keeping forces,\" according to sources.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "German",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Welt am Sonntag",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il sindaco Imamoglu in tribunale",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Imamoglu: \"Accuse infondate e immorali\" Imamoglu, il sindaco di Istanbul arrestato per favoreggiamento al terrorismo e corruzione, ha definito \"immorali e infondate\" le accuse che hanno portato alla sua detenzione.    \"Sono accuse progettate per minare la mia reputazione e credibilità\", ha detto Imamoglu durante il suo interrogatorio. Lo ha reso noto la municipalità di Istanbul.     Arrestato 4 giorni fa,il sindaco è stato in Tribunale. I giudici devono decidere se confermare la detenzione. ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.621583,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "Mayor Imamoglu in court",
        "en_content": "Imamoglu: \"Unfounded and immoral\" Imamoglu, the mayor of Istanbul arrested for favoring terrorism and corruption, called \"immoral and unfounded\" accusations that led to his detention. \"They are accusations designed to undermine my reputation and credibility,\" Imamoglu said during his interrogation. The city of Istanbul has announced it. He was arrested 4 days ago, the mayor was in Tribunal. Judges shall decide whether to confirm the detention.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4 days ago",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tribunal",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISTANBUL,PROTESTE E SCONTRI PER SINDACO Manifestano contro il suo arresto",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Istanbul,proteste e scontri per sindaco Scontri tra manifestanti e forze di polizia nei pressi del comune di Istanbul dove migliaia di persone si sono radunate per protestare contro l'arresto del sindaco Ekrem Imamoglu. Lo riferiscono i media locali pubblicando un video che mostra la polizia utilizzare gas lacrimogeno contro un gruppo di  manifestanti.     Momenti di tensione sono stati riportati anche nei pressi del tribunale di Istanbul, dove Imamoglu è stato ascoltato dai giudici, e dove un gruppo di avvocati e agenti che si sono spintonati.      ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.6284146,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Istanbul, protectors and clashes for mayor Scontri between protesters and police forces near the municipality of Istanbul where thousands of people gathered to protest against the arrest of mayor Ekrem Imamoglu. Local media report it by posting a video showing police using tear gas against a group of protesters. Tension motions were also reported near the Istanbul court, where Imamoglu was heard by the judges, and where a group of lawyers and agents who pushed.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Scontri",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ekrem Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Imamoglu",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GIUSTIZIA,TAJANI: AVANTI CON LA RIFORMA \"E' destinata a depoliticizzare\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Giustizia,Tajani: avanti con la riforma \"Sulla giustizia abbiamo un impegno con gli elettori che ci hanno dato un consenso per fare le riforme e la più importante è quella sulla giustizia\".Così Tajani, vicepremier e ministro Esteri. \"Andremo avanti senza perdere tempo. La riforma è per i cittadini non è contro nessuno, anzi è destinata a esaltare il ruolo dei magistrati,a depoliticizzare\" \"I benefici saranno per i concittadini\" Sulla telefonata di Salvini a Vance:\"La politica estera la fanno premier e ministro Esteri.Poi legittimo se un ministro vuol parlare\" con esponenti esteri",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742684406.6327186,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "JUSTICE,TAJANI: AVANTI WITH THE REFORM \"It is destined to depoliticize\"",
        "en_content": "Justice,Tajani: ahead with the reform \"On justice we have a commitment with voters who have given us a consensus to make reforms and the most important is justice.\" So Tajani, vicepremier and foreign minister. \"We'll go on without wasting time. The reform is for citizens is not against anyone, indeed it is destined to exalt the role of magistrates, to depoliticize\" \"The benefits will be for citizens\" On the call of Salvini to Vance:\"The foreign policy make it Premier and Foreign Minister. Then legitimate if a minister wants to speak\" with foreign exponents",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "JUSTICE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AVANTI",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Justice",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FATAH A HAMAS:CEDI POTERE,PRESERVA GAZA Battaglia porterà fine palestinesi",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Fatah a Hamas:cedi potere,preserva Gaza Al Fatah, il partito del presidente  dell'Anp Abu Mazen, chiede ad Hamas di lasciare il potere a Gaza per preservare \"la presenza dei palestinesi\" nella Striscia.L'appello arriva mentre Israele intensifica i raid, minacciando di annettere parti del territorio.  \"Hamas deve mostrare compassione per Gaza,i suoi bambini,le sue donne,i suoi uomini\", dice un portavoce di Fatah. \"Hamas lasci la scena. Deve rendersi conto che la battaglia imminente porterà alla fine dell'esistenza dei palestinesi a Gaza\".     ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.6559966,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "FATAH TO HAMAS:WHERE POTHERS,PRESERVA GAZA Battle will bring Palestinian end",
        "en_content": "Fatah at Hamas: power cedes, Preserves Gaza Al Fatah, the party of the president of Anp Abu Mazen, asks Hamas to leave power in Gaza to preserve \"the presence of the Palestinians\" in the Strip. The appeal arrives as Israel intensifies the raid, threatening to annex parts of the territory. \"Hamas must show compassion for Gaza, his children, his women, his men,\" says a spokesman for Fatah. \"Hamas leave the scene. He must realize that the imminent battle will lead to the end of the Palestinian existence in Gaza.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FATAH",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "HAMAS",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "PRESERVA GAZA Battle",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Fatah",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza Al Fatah",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anp Abu Mazen",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fatah",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 509,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "LIBANO,RAID IDF A SUD DOPO LANCIO RAZZI Unifil: \"Allarme per escalation\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Libano,raid Idf a Sud dopo lancio razzi Come annunciato,l'Idf in risposta a 5 razzi lanciati dal Libano verso Israele ha dato il via a raid nel sud del Paese.Una donna è rimasta uccisa.  Il premier Netanyahu e il ministro Katz hanno ordinato di \"agire con forza\"  contro decine di obiettivi terroristici Il primo ministro libanese Salam teme che il Libano possa essere trascinato \"in una nuova guerra che porterà guai al Paese e al suo popolo\". Hezbollah nega di aver lanciato i missili.  Unifil,\"allarmata da possibile escalation\",incoraggia a rispettare la tregua",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.6896265,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "_ \"Escalation Alarm\"",
        "en_content": "Lebanon,raid Idf to the South after launching rockets As announced, the Idf in response to 5 rockets launched from Lebanon to Israel started raiding the south of the country. A woman was killed. Prime Minister Netanyahu and Minister Katz ordered \"forced action\" against dozens of terrorist targets Lebanese Prime Minister Salam fears that Lebanon may be dragged \"in a new war that will bring trouble to the country and its people.\" Hezbollah denies launching missiles. Unifil, alarmed by possible escalation, encourages to respect the truce",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Escalation Alarm",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanese",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salam",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 432,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Unifil",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 475,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PARIGI,BERLINO,LONDRA: \"TREGUA A GAZA\"  \"Sia immediata.Indignati per morti\"",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Parigi,Berlino,Londra: \"Tregua a Gaza\" Francia, Germania e Regno Unito hanno chiesto un \"immediato cessate il fuoco\" nella Striscia di Gaza. I tre Paesi si sono detti \"indignati\" per il numero di vittime tra i civili da quando Israele ha violato la tregua martedì scorso. I ministri dei 3 Paesi hanno denunciato la \"drammatica battuta d'arresto per la popolazione di Gaza,gli ostaggi,le loro famiglie e l'intera Regione\".\"Invitiamo tutte le parti a riprendere i negoziati affinché il cessate il fuoco sia attuato\" e \"sia consentita immediatamente la consegna degli aiuti\" nella Striscia. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.7628636,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "Immediately. Indignant for dead\"",
        "en_content": "Paris,Berlin,London: \"Tregua in Gaza\" France, Germany and the United Kingdom demanded a \"immediate ceasefire\" in the Gaza Strip. The three countries called themselves \"indignated\" for the number of victims among civilians since Israel violated the truce last Tuesday. The ministers of the 3 countries denounced the \"dramatic arrest for the people of Gaza, the hostages, their families and the entire region\". \"We invite all parties to resume the negotiations so that the ceasefire is implemented\" and \"it is immediately allowed to deliver the aid\" in the Strip.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Berlin",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last Tuesday",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 560,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "COLLE:DANNI DA PROTEZIONISMI IMMOTIVATI Chiusure mercati dal sapore autarchico  Intervento a Forum cultura olio,vino121  MELONI GIOVEDI'A RIUNIONE \"VOLENTEROSI\" A Parigi per vertice sull'Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Meloni giovedì a riunione \"volenterosi\" La premier Meloni conferma la sua presenza, giovedì a Parigi, alla riunione sulla pace e per la sicurezza dell'  Ucraina. Così in una nota diffusa da Palazzo Chigi.     Il vertice è stato convocato dal Presidente francese Macron, con i rappresentanti di altri Paesi alleati che fanno parte della cosiddetta \"coalizione dei volenterosi\".     Parteciperà anche il presidente ucraino Zelensky.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1742684406.834482,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "COLLE:DANNI DA PROTEZIONISMI IMMOTIVATI Close markets with autarchical taste Intervention at Forum culture oil,vino121 MELONI GIOVEDI'A RIUNIONE \"VOLENTEROSI\" A Paris summit on Ukraine",
        "en_content": "Meloni Thursday at \"volenterosi\" meeting Premier Meloni confirms his presence, Thursday in Paris, at the meeting on peace and security of Ukraine. So in a note diffused by Palazzo Chigi. The summit was convened by the French President Macron, with representatives of other allied countries who are part of the so-called \"coalition of the voluntarians\". The Ukrainian President Zelensky will also participate.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "COLLE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "DANNI DA",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "VOLENTEROSI",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AEROPORTO DI HEATHROW,RIPRESI VOLI",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Scalo di Heathrow pienamente operativo \"Sono ripresi dopo l'interruzione di corrente di ieri\" i voli allo scalo  londinese di Heathrow. E' quanto si  legge sul sito dell'aeroporto che invita chi deve partire a contattare la  compagnia aerea prima di andare in aereoporto. Il portavove di Heathrow ha detto che è \"pienamente operativo\". Ma i disagi dureranno giorni.   Il primo volo, dopo l'incendio in una sottostazione elettrica che ieri ha  causato il caos nei cieli d'Europa con circa 1.400 voli cancellati e 300mila passeggeri rimasti a terra, è partito nella notte. Escluse cause \"sospette\". ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1742684406.958346,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.06",
        "en_title": "HEATHROW AIRPORT,",
        "en_content": "Heathrow's fully operational staircase \"I recovered after yesterday's power failure\" Heathrow's London airport flights. It's what you read on the airport site that invites those who have to go to contact the airline before going to the airport. Heathrow's carrier said it was \"fully operational.\" But inconvenience will last days. The first flight, after the fire in an electric substation that yesterday caused the chaos in the skies of Europe with about 1,400 canceled flights and 300 thousand remaining passengers on the ground, left in the night. Excluding suspicious causes.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "HEATHROW AIRPORT",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Heathrow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Heathrow",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Heathrow",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last days",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 1,400",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "300 thousand",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "COLOMBE E UOVA, RINCARI DEL 20-30%    Pesano caro-cacao e crisi del burro",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Colombe e uova, rincari del 20-30% Caro-cacao e crisi del burro spingono al rialzo i prezzi dei dolci pasquali. E' quanto emerge da un'idagine del Codacons.      Per l'uovo di Pasqua, di cioccolato al latte o fondente,i rincari per le marche più note sono del 30%, ma superano il 40% per le uova di gamma medio-alta. Quelle destinate ai più piccoli registrano aumenti che vanno dall'8% al 33% Anche le colombe, tradizionali o farcite, tra le marche più commercializzate mostrano rincari di circa il 21% rispetto allo scorso anno.   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742684407.2898507,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.07",
        "en_title": "COLOMB AND OVA, 20-30% Pesano caro-cacao and butter crisis",
        "en_content": "Doves and eggs, 20-30% Caro-cacao and butter crisis push up the price of Easter cakes. It's from a Codacons ID. For Easter egg, milk chocolate or dark chocolate, the most famous brands are 30%, but they exceed 40% for medium-high range eggs. Smaller ones have increases ranging from 8% to 33% Also the doves, traditional or stuffed, among the most commercial brands show rise of about 21% compared to last year.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "COLOMB",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "20-30%",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "20-30%",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Easter",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Codacons",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Easter egg",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "30%",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "40%",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "8% to 33%",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "about 21%",
                "start_char": 379,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "last year",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "GIORGETTI:\"I DAZI, ARMI NUOVE ALLEANZE\" Per ridefinire equilibri, dinamiche",
        "date_raw": "March 22, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-22",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Giorgetti:\"I dazi, armi nuove alleanze\" \"E' un periodo anche di guerre commerciali e finanziarie decisamente aggressive attraverso l'utilizzo di dazi e criptovalute. Strumenti usati,come delle vere e proprie armi economiche per ridefinire equilibri globali\", ma che \"stanno influenzando anche la politica mondiale\". Così il ministro Giorgetti. I dazi sono una \"leva che condiziona le politiche internazionali\" e \"possono alterare gli scambi globali,influenzare alleanze politiche e ridisegnare gli assetti geopolitici\".Criptovalute? Dirompenti e rischio attività illecite. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1742684407.460034,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-23 00:00:07",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-22T23.00.07",
        "en_title": "_ To redefine balance, dynamics",
        "en_content": "Giorgetti: \"The duties, new weapons alliances\" \"It is also a period of commercial and financial wars decidedly aggressive through the use of duties and cryptocurrencies. Instruments used, like real economic weapons to redefine global balances,\" but that \"they are also affecting world politics\". So Minister Giorgetti. The duties are a \"importance that affects international policies\" and \"can alter global exchanges, influence political alliances and redesign geopolitical assets\". Cryptocurrencies? Breakdowns and risk of unlawful activity.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cryptocurrencies",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    }
]
