[
    {
        "title": "PPE: REVOCARE STOP UE AD AUTO A BENZINA \"Obiettivo dal 2035 è irrealistico\"",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Ppe: revocare stop Ue ad auto a benzina \"L'obiettivo di porre fine alle vendite di auto con motore a combustione interna entro il 2035 sembra più irrealistiche mai\". Lo scrive su X il Partito  popolare europeo.     \"Il divieto del 2035 sui motori a  combustione interna dovrebbe essere  revocato\".     La richiesta arriva pochi giorni prima dalla presentazione del piano della  Commissione europea per l'automotive, previsto per il 5 marzo.   ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740967204.6582935,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "PPE: REVOCARE EU STOP AT BENZINA \"Objective since 2035 is unrealistic\"",
        "en_content": "Ppe: revoke stop to petrol cars \"The goal of ending auto sales with internal combustion engine by 2035 seems more unrealistic than ever.\" The European People's Party writes it on X. \"The ban of 2035 on internal combustion engines should be revoked.\" The request comes a few days before the presentation of the European Commission's plan for automotive, scheduled for 5 March.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "PPE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2035",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ppe",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2035",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "The European People's Party",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2035",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days",
                "start_char": 268,
                "end_char": 278,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission's",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "5 March",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MATTARELLA IN GIAPPONE DAL 3 AL 9 MARZO Prima volta a 16 anni da Napolitano",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Mattarella, visita di Stato in Giappone Il presidente della Repubblica, Sergio Mattarella, sarà in visita di Stato in Giappone dal 3 al 9 marzo. La visita giunge in un momento di rafforzamento delle relazioni bilaterali e della cooperazione economica fra i due Paesi nel quadro dell'accordo di partenariato strategico del gennaio del 2023.  Nella mattinata di martedì, Mattarella sarà ricevuto nel Palazzo imperiale  dall'imperatore Naruhito. Si tratta del primo viaggio di un capo di Stato italiano in Giappone dalla visita di Giorgio Napolitano risalente a 16 anni fa. ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740967204.6649957,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "MATTARELLA IN GIAPPONE FROM 3 TO 9 MARCH First time to 16 years from Napolitano",
        "en_content": "Mattarella, State visit to Japan The President of the Republic, Sergio Mattarella, will be visiting Japan from 3 to 9 March. The visit reached a moment of strengthening bilateral relations and economic cooperation between the two countries under the strategic partnership agreement of January 2023. On Tuesday morning, Mattarella will be received in the Imperial Palace by Emperor Naruhito. This is the first journey of an Italian Head of State in Japan from the visit of Giorgio Napolitano dating back to 16 years.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MATTARELLA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "GIAPPONE",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 TO 9 MARCH First",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "16 years",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Napolitano",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Mattarella",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 to 9 March",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "January 2023",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "morning",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Imperial Palace",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Naruhito",
                "start_char": 381,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgio Napolitano",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "16 years",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "STARMER-MACRON:UCRAINA,1 MESE DI TREGUA Summit Londra: Ue per pace, con gli Usa Von der Leyen:bisogna riarmare l'Europa Kiev,minerali:sì accordo con Trump",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740967204.6701107,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "STARMER-MACRON:UCRAINA,1 MONTH OF TREGUA Summit London: EU for peace, with the US Von der Leyen: it is necessary to re-arm Europe Kiev, MEPs: yes agreement with Trump",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "STARMER-MACRON:",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Von der",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe Kiev",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PROCLAMATO SCIOPERO TRASPORTO SU GOMMA  Protesta indetta dai sindacati di base  A rischio anche il trasporto locale",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Rischio sciopero del trasporto su gomma A marzo c'è il rischio di blocco sia per il trasporto merci che dei bus.  L'Unione Sindacale di Base denuncia come le richieste di incontro dei camionisti al Ministero dei Trasporti e del Lavoro non abbiano avuto \"alcun riscontro sino ad ora\". Anche i sindacati del trasporto pubblico locale Filt Cgil,Fit Cisl,Uiltrasporti,Faisa Cisal e Ugl Fna hanno parlato della conclusione,\"con esito negativo\", della procedura di raffreddamento e conciliazione preliminare alla serrata.Quindi è sciopero con ogni probabilità con tempistiche diverse. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1740967204.6852405,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "PROCLAMED SCIOPERO TRANSPORT ON GOMMA Protested by the basic unions At risk also the local transport",
        "en_content": "Risk transport strike on rubber In March there is the risk of blocking both for freight transport and bus. The Union of Fundamental Trade Unions denounces how the demands of meeting of the truckers to the Ministry of Transport and Labour have not had \"some feedback until now\". The local public transport unions Filt Cgil,Fit Cisl,Uiltrasporti,Faisa Cisal and Ugl Fna also spoke of the conclusion, \"with negative outcome\", of the cooling and preliminary conciliation procedure to the lock. So it's strike in all probability with different timings.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "PROCLAMED SCIOPERO TRANSPORT",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "GOMMA",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Union of Fundamental Trade Unions",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Transport and Labour",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Filt Cgil",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fit Cisl",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Uiltrasporti",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Faisa Cisal",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ugl Fna",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI A LONDRA: TERRO'OCCIDENTE UNITO  Londra e Roma \"possono costruire ponti\" Premier UK:\"Approccio molto simile\"",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Meloni: terrò Occidente unito,mio ruolo \"Dobbiamo essere bravi in questa fase a non dividere l'Occidente perché sarebbe esiziale per tutti\". Così il premier Meloni al termine del vertice a Londra sull'Ucraina. \"Farò tutto il possibile per tenere l'Occidente unito. E' mio impegno e ruolo.Non vedo altri scenari\" Sullo scontro Trump-Zelensky si è detta \"molto dispiaciuta.Non è utile lasciarsi andare alle tifoserie, ma guardare all'obiettivo comune. Tutti vogliono la pace giusta per Kiev, anche gli Usa\". Da Francia-Gb spunti per pace,perplessa su truppe. \"Preoccupata sui dazi:\"Siamo nazione esportatrice.Troveremo accordo\"",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7003725,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "MELONI To LONDRA: TERRO'OCCIDENTE UNITe London and Rome \"can build bridges\" Premier UK:\"I approach very similar\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni: I will hold the united West, my role \"We must be good at this stage not to divide the West because it would be exsitial for all\". So Premier Meloni at the end of the London summit on Ukraine. \"I will do everything I can to keep the united West. It's my commitment and role. I don't see any other scenarios\" Trump-Zelensky said \"very sorry. It is not useful to let go to typhoons, but to look at the common goal. Everyone wants the right peace for Kiev, even the US.\" From France-Gb snacks for peace, perplexed on troops. \"About duties:\"We are exporting nation. We will find agreement\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the united West",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the united West",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump-Zelensky",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "LA PREMIER VEDE ZELENSKY:ITALIA CON VOI \"Costruire pace giusta e duratura\"",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Meloni vede Zelensky: Italia è con Kiev La premier Giorgia Meloni ha incontrato a Londra il presidente ucraino Zelensky a margine della riunione sulla difesa ospitata dal Regno Unito.   \"L'incontro informa Palazzo Chigi ha permesso di ribadire il sostegno  dell'Italia all'Ucraina e al suo popolo e l'impegno,insieme ai partner europei, occidentali e agli Stati Uniti, di costruire una pace giusta e duratura, che assicuri un futuro di sovranità, sicurezza e libertà all'Ucraina\".  In precedenza Meloni aveva telefonato al presidente americano Donald Trump. ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1740967204.71036,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "THE PREMIER VEDE ZELENSKY:ITALY WITH VOI \"Building just and lasting peace\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni sees Zelensky: Italy is with Kiev Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni met in London Ukrainian President Zelensky at the edge of the defence meeting hosted by the United Kingdom. \"The meeting informs Palazzo Chigi has allowed Italy to reiterate its support for Ukraine and its people and the commitment, together with European, Western and United States partners, to build a just and lasting peace, which assures a future of sovereignty, security and freedom to Ukraine.\" Meloni had previously phoned American President Donald Trump.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "VEDE ZELENSKY",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ITALY",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 261,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 501,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 532,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Orban:\"Ancora guerra?E' pericoloso\"",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Orban: ancora guerra? Errore pericoloso \"I leader europei hanno deciso a Londra che vogliono continuare con la guerra invece di optare per la pace\".  Così scrive su un social il premier  dell'Ungheria, Orban.    \"Hanno deciso che l'Ucraina deve continuare la guerra. Questo è male, pericoloso ed erroneo. L'Ungheria rimane dalla parte della pace\". E conclude il suo post con la frase in latino che ribadisce, sottolinea e rinforza quanto detto: \"Ceterum censeo\".   ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7150211,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "Orban: \"Even war? It's dangerous.\"",
        "en_content": "Orban: still war? \"European leaders have decided in London that they want to continue with war instead of opting for peace.\" So he writes on a social premier of Hungary, Orban. \"They decided that Ukraine must continue the war. This is bad, dangerous and erroneous. Hungary remains on the side of peace.\" And he concludes his post with the Latin phrase that reiterates, emphasizes and strengthens what is said: \"Ceterum censeo.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Orban",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Orban",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orban",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Latin",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 344,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"ZELENSKY RINSAVISCA O SI DIMETTA\"    Così lo speaker della Camera Usa",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Usa: \"Zelensky rinsavisca o si dimetta\" Il presidente ucraino Zelensky deve  dimettersi se non firma l'accordo sui minerali rari e se non accetta di porre fine alla guerra. Lo ha suggerito lo speaker della Camera degli Stati Uniti, Johnson, in Tv alla Nbc News.   \"Qualcosa deve cambiare. Deve tornare in sé e presentarsi al tavolo dei negoziati in segno di gratitudine, oppure qualcun altro deve guidare il Paese al suo posto\",ha detto Johnson,che tuttavia pensa che la guerra sia \"ingiusta\" e Putin \"una persona pericolosa.Un vecchio comunista.Nessuna fiducia in lui\".",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7196543,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ So the Speaker of the US Room",
        "en_content": "Use: \"Zelensky will revive or resign\" Ukrainian President Zelensky must resign if he does not sign the agreement on rare minerals and if he does not agree to end the war. It was suggested by the speaker of the United States Chamber, Johnson, on TV at Nbc News. \"Something needs to change. He must return to himself and present himself at the table of negotiations as a sign of gratitude, or someone else must lead the country to his place,\" said Johnson, who nevertheless thinks that the war is \"unfair\" and Putin \"a dangerous person. An old communist. No trust in him.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States Chamber",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Johnson",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nbc News",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Johnson",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MACRON PROPONE \"UN MESE DI TREGUA\"    All'Italia: \"Sia con noi su Kiev\"",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Macron: Italia sia con noi su Kiev \"Se vogliamo essere credibili come europei nel nostro sostegno a lungo termine all'Ucraina, dobbiamo essere in grado di fornire delle garanzie di sicurezza solida. Abbiamo bisogno dell' Italia, forte, che agisca al fianco di Francia e Germania, nel concerto delle grandi nazioni. Per questo ho invitato Meloni, lo scorso 7 febbraio\".  Così Macron in una intervista a Il Foglio. Serve che \"l'Italia sia al nostro fianco, che s'impegni da grande Paese europeo, sulla scia di quanto fece Draghi. Ora restiamo uniti\". E con Starmer propone un mese di tregua in Ucraina. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7386715,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "MACRON PROPONE \"UN MESE OF TREGUA\" To Italy: \"Be with us on Kiev\"",
        "en_content": "Macron: Italy and with us on Kiev \"If we want to be credible as European in our long-term support to Ukraine, we must be able to provide solid security guarantees. We need Italy, strong, working alongside France and Germany, in the concert of the great nations. That's why I invited Meloni last February 7.\" So Macron in an interview with Il Foglio. It is necessary that \"Italy be at our side, that it is engaged by a great European country, in the wake of what Draghi did. Now we stay together.\" And with Starmer proposes a month of truce in Ukraine.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "MACRON PROPONE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "last February 7",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Il Foglio",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Draghi",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a month",
                "start_char": 523,
                "end_char": 530,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev:sì accordo minerali con Trump",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Kiev, ok accordo minerali con Trump  Non ci sono state comunicazioni tra  la presidenza ucraina e la Casa Bianca dopo l'incontro di venerdì scorso con Donald Trump, ma Kiev nonostante lo  scontroddi venerdì alla Casa Bianca,si dice pronta alla firma di un accordo con gli Stati Uniti per lo sfruttamento congiunto dei minerali nel suo Paese. Lo avrebbe detto il presidente ucraino Zelensky a Londra, secondo quanto ri porta il quotidiano londinese Guardian. Lo sforzo per la pace guidato da GB e Francia,discusso dai leader europei al vertice di Londra, darà i suoi frutti \"nelle prossime settimane\", ha aggiunto",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7412264,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "Kiev: yes mineral agreement with Trump",
        "en_content": "Kiev, ok mineral agreement with Trump There were no communications between the Ukrainian presidency and the White House after the meeting of Friday with Donald Trump, but Kiev despite the clash of Fridays at the White House, is said ready to sign an agreement with the United States for the joint exploitation of minerals in his country. The Ukrainian president Zelensky in London would have said this, according to the newspaper Guardian of London. The effort for peace led by GB and France,discussed by European leaders at the London summit, will give its fruits \"in the coming weeks,\" he added.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fridays",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guardian of London",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "GB",
                "start_char": 478,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 485,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 529,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming weeks",
                "start_char": 569,
                "end_char": 585,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Von der Leyen: \"Riarmare l'Europa\"",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Von der Leyen:bisogna riarmare l'Europa \"Siamo pronti a difendere la democrazia e il principio secondo cui esiste uno stato di diritto. Non si può invadere e intimidire i vicini o cambiare i confini con la forza\".Così Ursula von der Leyen, al termine del summit di Londra. C'è stata \"discussione sincera\" sulla necessità di mettere Kiev in una posizione di forza: l'Ucraina ha bisogno di \"garanzie di sicurezza complete\" a sostegno delle sue posizioni economiche e militari,ha detto.\"La via per la pace è la forza.Dobbiamo riarmare con urgenza l'Europa\" ha concluso.    ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7509701,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "Von der Leyen: \"Rearming Europe\"",
        "en_content": "Von der Leyen: Europe must be rearmed \"We are ready to defend democracy and the principle that there is a rule of law. You cannot invade and intimidate the neighbors or change the boundaries by force.\" So Ursula von der Leyen, at the end of the London summit. There was \"a sincere debate\" about the need to put Kiev in a strong position: Ukraine needs \"full security guarantees\" in support of its economic and military positions, said.\"The way for peace is strength. We must urgently re-arm Europe\" he concluded.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 497,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "STARMER:\"PIANO UE PER PACE,CON GLI USA\" Londra,pace giusta? Rafforzare Kiev",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Ucraina,Starmer: a Usa piano Gb-Francia Il Regno Unito lavorerà \"con la Francia e forse altri\" a un piano per fermare i combattimenti in Ucraina, che sarà presentato agli Usa. Così il premier. Presto, aggiunge Starmer, squadre britanniche e Usa avranno incontri sull' Ucraina: anche con un'aumentata spesa difensiva Ue, ci sarà bisogno di garanzie di sicurezza Usa a Kiev.  \"Un momento di reale fragilità in Europa\".\"Non credo che Zelensky abbia fatto nulla di sbagliato\". \"Mi fido di lui e di Trump\", \"non mi fiderei della parola di Putin\", dice il premier britannico. ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7804086,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "STARMER: \"EU PLAN FOR PACE, CON GLI USA\" London, is it right? Strengthen Kiev",
        "en_content": "Ukraine,Starmer: a Usa piano Gb-France The UK will work \"with France and perhaps others\" on a plan to stop fighting in Ukraine, which will be presented to the US. So the premier. Soon, adds Starmer, British teams and Usa will have meetings on Ukraine: also with increased defensive spending Ue, we will need US security guarantees in Kiev. \"A moment of real fragility in Europe.\" \"I don't think Zelensky did anything wrong.\" \"I trust him and Trump,\" \"I wouldn't trust Putin's word,\" says the British prime minister.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "STARMER",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "CON GLI USA\"",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ue",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 442,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PAPA,E'STABILE:SENZA FEBBRE E MASCHERA  Nessuna conseguenza da ultima crisi",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740967204.7853494,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni:Evitare divisione Occidente",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1740967204.797444,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "Meloni: Avoid Western Division",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western Division",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa: siamo d'accordo con Israele",
        "date_raw": "March 03, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Usa: con Israele su stop aiuti a Gaza \"Sostegno e appoggio alla decisione di Israele di interrompere gli aiuti umanitari alla Striscia di Gaza\". Lo sostiene il portavoce del Consiglio per la sicurezza nazionale della Casa Bianca, Brian Hughes.     Hughes ha affermato che \"Israele ha negoziato in buona fede fin dall'inizio di questa amministrazione per garantire il rilascio degli ostaggi.Sosterremo la loro decisione sui prossimi passi, dato che Hamas ha annunciato di non essere più interessato a un cessate il fuoco\".",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740967204.8307455,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 03:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T02.00.04",
        "en_title": "USA: we agree with Israel",
        "en_content": "Use: with Israel on stop aid to Gaza \"support and support Israel's decision to stop humanitarian aid to the Gaza Strip\". The White House National Security Council spokesman, Brian Hughes. Hughes said that \"Israel negotiated in good faith from the beginning of this administration to ensure the release of hostages. We will support their decision on the next steps, as Hamas announced he was no longer interested in a ceasefire.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The White House National Security Council",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brian Hughes",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hughes",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
