[
    {
        "title": "SANTANCHE', RINVIATA UDIENZA. INPS ESCE Accolta richiesta nuovo difensore",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Legale Santanché:salta udienza,Inps via E' stata rinviata al 20 maggio, come chiesto dal nuovo difensore, l'udienza davanti al Gup per la ministra del Turismo Santanchè, coinvolta nel procedimento per truffa aggravata all'Inps. Confermando il rinvio, chiesto e ottenuto per studiare le carte, il legale ha annunciato che l'Inps ritirerà la sua costituzione di parte civile, \"perché è stato integralmente risarcito\", per patrimonio e immagine dalla ex società di Santanché, Visibilia. La presunta truffa sarebbe sulla Cig Covid e il Gup deve decidere se mandare a processo o prosciogliere la ministra.  ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1743019204.8158817,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "SANTANCHE, RANGE UDIENCE. EXCELLENCE INPS Welcome new defender request",
        "en_content": "Legale Santanché:salta audience,Inps via It was postponed to 20 May, as asked by the new defender, the hearing in front of the Gup for the Santanchè Tourism Minister, involved in the process for aggravated scam at the Inps. Confirming the postponement, asked and obtained to study the cards, the lawyer announced that the Inps will withdraw its constitution of civil part, \"because it was fully compensated\", for heritage and image from the former society of Santanché, Visibilia. The alleged scam would be on the Cig Covid and the Gup must decide whether to send to trial or prosciogliere the ministra.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "UDIENCE",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Legale Santanché",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "salta",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Inps",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "20 May",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gup",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Inps",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Inps",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Santanché",
                "start_char": 459,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Visibilia",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Cig Covid",
                "start_char": 510,
                "end_char": 523,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gup",
                "start_char": 532,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ministra",
                "start_char": 594,
                "end_char": 602,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ministro:attacchi come Inquisizione",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Almasri, Nordio interviene alla Camera Dall'opposizione polemiche \"esasperate nel linguaggio e nei toni, dicendo ad esempio che si vuole favorire la mafia, la delinquenza organizzata. Tutte cose che suonano offensive ed antipatiche\". Così alla Camera il ministro della Giustizia Nordio nella replica alla mozione di sfiducia.\"Ricordano Inquisizione\" \"Questi attacchi -dicedanno sensazione di un attacco programmato per evitare la riforma della separazione delle carriere e il sorteggio per l'elezione del Csm. Quali che siano gli attacchi non vacilleremo. Se voi farete vostro peggio, noi faremo il nostro meglio\". ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1743019204.829403,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "Minister:attached as Inquisition",
        "en_content": "Almasri, Nordio intervenes at the Chamber From the polemical opposition \"experienced in language and tones, saying for example that you want to favor the mafia, the organized delinquency. All things that play offensive and antipathic.\" Thus at the House the Minister of Justice Nordio in reply to the motion of distrust. \"Remember Inquisition\" \"These attacks will indicate a planned attack to prevent reform of career separation and the Csm election draw. Which are the attacks we will not falter. If you do your worst, we will do our best.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Inquisition",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Csm",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ALMASRI,CAMERA RESPINGE SFIDUCIA NORDIO Con 215 no contro 119 voti a favore",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " Camera respinge mozione sfiducia Nordio L'Aula della Camera ha bocciato la mozione di sfiducia presentata dalle opposizioni nei confronti, in seguito alla vicenda Almasri, del ministro Nordio I voti favorevoli alla mozione di sfiducia sono stati 119, quelli contrari 215, mentre non ci sono stati astenuti. Il gruppo di Azione non ha seguito il resto delle opposizioni, scegliendo  di non partecipare al voto.  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1743019204.8318784,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ With 215 no against 119 votes in favour",
        "en_content": "The House rejected the motion of distrust presented by the opposition against the Almasri affair of the Minister Nordio The votes in favour of the motion of distrust were 119, those against 215, while there were no abstentions. The Action Group has not followed the rest of the opposition, choosing not to participate in the vote.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "215",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "119",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "119",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "215",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Action Group",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Schlein:\"Paese ha diritto a verità\"",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Almasri,Schlein:Paese ha diritto verità \"La sua difesa d'ufficio di un torturatore libico rappresenta una delle pagine più vergognose a cui questo Parlamento è stato sottoposto\". Così la segretaria Pd Schlein rivolgendosi al ministro della Giustizia, alla Camera  per la mozione di sfiducia presentata dalle opposizioni per il caso Almasri. \"Il Paese ha diritto alla verità\",dice, e malgrado \"omissioni,falsità,tentativi di sviare, i fatti restano chiari\" e Almasri \"è stato riportato a Tripoli con tutti gli onori\". Nordio \"ha scelto ragione partito su quella del diritto\". \"Dov'è presidente Meloni?Perché fugge?\"",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1743019204.8352447,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "Schlein: \"Paese has the right to truth\"",
        "en_content": "Almasri,Schlein:Paese has the right truth \"His defense of the office of a Libyan torturer is one of the most shameful pages to which this Parliament has been subjected.\" Thus the secretary Pd Schlein addressing the Minister of Justice, the Chamber for the motion of distrust presented by the oppositions for the Almasri case. \"The country has the right to truth,\" he says, and despite \"omissions,falities, intent to distract, the facts remain clear\" and Almasri \"has been reported to Tripoli with all honors\". Nordio \"has chosen reason left on that of law.\" \"Where is President Meloni? Why is she running? \"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paese",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paese",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd Schlein",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tripoli",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 510,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 578,
                "end_char": 584,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Aula semivuota su rilascio libico",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Sfiducia Nordio,maggioranza lascia Aula Aula semivuota alla Camera dove gran parte dei deputati della maggioranza di governo ha disertato il dibattito sulla mozione di sfiducia al ministro della Giustizia Nordio portata dalle opposizioni sul caso del rimpatrio in Libia di Almasri,il libico arrestato a Torino per crimini contro l'umanità su mandato Cpi e poi rilasciato e rimaptriato.  Semivuoti anche i banchi del governo. Oltre a Nordio, intervenuto per replicare alle opposizioni, presente  soltanto il ministro per i Rapporti col Parlamento Ciriani. Schlein nel suo intervento parla di \"pagina vergognosa\". ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1743019204.8381982,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "Semi-empty classroom on Libyan release",
        "en_content": "Sfiducia Nordio,Maggioranza leaves Aula Aula semivuota to the House where most of the deputies of the majority of government has deserted the debate on the motion of distrust to the Minister of Justice Nordio brought by the oppositions on the case of repatriation in Libya of Almasri, the Libyan arrested in Turin for crimes against humanity under mandate Cpi and then released and remaptriato. Even the government's benches were semi-empted. In addition to Nordio, intervened to replicate the oppositions, present only the Minister for Relations with the Ciriani Parliament. Schlein in his speech speaks of \"shameful page\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sfiducia Nordio",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maggioranza",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aula Aula",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libya",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turin",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Minister for Relations",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ciriani Parliament",
                "start_char": 552,
                "end_char": 574,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 576,
                "end_char": 583,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "INCENDI IN SUD COREA, ALMENO 24 VITTIME Distrutti millenari templi buddisti",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Roghi in Sud Corea, almeno 24 vittime Violenti incendi in Sud Corea, dove sono impegnati quasi 7mila pompieri, Ci sono 18 morti, fra i quali 4 vigili del fuoco e operatori al lavoro contro le fiamme e il pilota di un elicottero antincendio precipitato durante le operazioni. Ferite 12 persone, 6 gravemente. Fuori casa a Uiseong 27mila persone. Gli incendi interessano il sudest della Corea del Sud: devastati 17mila ettari di bosco e ridotto in cenere il complesso di templi buddisti di Unramsa.Le fiamme forse partite dall'erba bruciata per pulire le tombe di famiglia nel  tempio o da scintille di saldatura. ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1743019204.8948627,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "INCENDS IN SUD COREA, ALMENO 24 VITTIME Millennial destruction Buddhist temples",
        "en_content": "Roghi in South Korea, at least 24 victims Violent fires in South Korea, where nearly 7 thousand firemen are engaged, There are 18 deaths, including 4 firefighters and workers at work against fire and the pilot of a firefighting helicopter crashed during operations. You hurt 12 people, 6 seriously. Outside the house in Uiseong 27 thousand people. The fires affect Southeast South Korea: devastated 17 thousand hectares of wood and reduced to ashes the complex of Buddhist temples of Unramsa. The flames perhaps departed from the burned grass to clean the family tombs in the temple or from soldering sparks.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "INCENDS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SUD COREA",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ALMENO",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "24",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "VITTIME Millennial",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Buddhist",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "South Korea",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 24",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Korea",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "7 thousand",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "12",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "6",
                "start_char": 286,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Uiseong 27 thousand",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Southeast South Korea",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "17 thousand hectares",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buddhist",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unramsa",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AVVOCATURA:\"SUICIDIO NON E' UN DIRITTO\" \"Né un obbligo medici a concorrere\"",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=127",
        "content": " Avvocatura: \"Suicidio non è un diritto\" \"Non c'è un diritto al suicidio, né un obbligo dei medici di concorrere a una volontà suicidaria\". Questa è la posizione espressa dall'avvocato dello Stato, Ruggero di Martino, in aula davanti alla Consulta durante l'udienza pubblica sul tema del fine vita.   L'Avvocatura dello Stato è intervenuta in rappresentanza della presidenza del Consiglio dei ministri e ha giudicato \"inammissibile o manifestamente infondata\" la questione sollevata dal gip di Milano sull'articolo 580 del Codice penale che vieta l'aiuto al suicidio. ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1743019204.926446,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "WARNING: \"SUICIDIO IS NOT A DIRITTO\" \"No medical obligation to compete\"",
        "en_content": "Warning: \"Suicide is not a right\" \"There is no right to suicide, nor an obligation of doctors to commit suicide.\" This is the position expressed by the lawyer of the State, Ruggero di Martino, in court in front of the Consulta during the public hearing on the topic of the end of life. The State's Advocate intervened on behalf of the Presidency of the Council of Ministers and judged \"inadmissible or manifestly unfounded\" the question raised by the gip in Milan on Article 580 of the Criminal Code prohibiting aid to suicide.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SUICIDIO",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "DIRITTO",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Suicide",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ruggero di Martino",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Consulta",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council of Ministers",
                "start_char": 349,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 463,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Article 580",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TRUMP: VOGLIAMO LA GROENLANDIA,CI SERVE Venerdì vanno Vance-moglie,proteste",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=153",
        "content": " Trump: vogliamo la Groenlandia,ci serve \"Abbiamo bisogno della Groenlandia per la sicurezza internazionale. Ne abbiamo bisogno. Dobbiamo averla\".   Il presidente statunitense Trump insiste sulla Groenlandia,l'isola più grande del mondo che è territorio autonomo danese. \"Mi dispiace metterla così, ma dobbiamo averla\", ha detto in un'intervista rilasciata ad un podcaster.  Le parole di Trump alla vigilia della visita del vice presidente JD Vance e della moglie in una base militare Usa, che ha già scatenato molte polemiche. ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1743019204.9328904,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Trump: we want Greenland, we need \"We need Greenland for international security. We need it. We must have it.\" US President Trump insists on Greenland, the largest island in the world that is Danish autonomous territory. \"I'm sorry to put it that way, but we have to have it,\" he said in an interview with a podcaster. Trump's words on the eve of the visit of Vice President JD Vance and his wife on a US military base, which has already sparked many controversy.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Danish",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "JD Vance",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ITALIA NON INVIERA' SOLDATI SENZA L'ONU P.Chigi:mai a Kiev come forza nazionale Ucraina,domani summit \"volenterosi\"",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1743019204.94139,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "ENGLISH IS NOT ENOUGH THE UN P.Call: never in Kiev as a national force Ukraine, next summit \"willing\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ENGLISH",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ITALIA NON INVIERA' SOLDATI SENZA L'ONU P.Chigi:mai a Kiev come forza nazionale Ucraina,domani summit \"volenterosi\"",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " P.Chigi:no militari italiani in Ucraina L'incontro ha \"permesso di ribadire che non è prevista alcuna partecipazione nazionale ad una eventuale forza militare sul terreno\". Così una nota di P. Chigi dopo la riunione convocata dalla premier Meloni alla vigilia della sua partecipazione al summit a Parigi della 'Coalizione dei Volenterosi', su pace e sicurezza in Ucraina. Presenti i vicepremier, Salvini e Tajani, e Crosetto. Riaffermato impegno per garanzie sicurezza a Kiev in\"contesto euroatlantico\" Sul monitoraggio del cessate il fuoco si fa spazio \"un possibile ruolo dell' Onu, che il governo sostiene da tempo\".",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1743019204.9596062,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "ENGLISH IS NOT ENOUGH THE UN P.Call: never in Kiev as a national force Ukraine, next summit \"willing\"",
        "en_content": "P.Chigi:no Italian military in Ukraine The meeting has \"allowed to reiterate that no national participation in any military force on the ground is planned\". Thus a note of Fr. Chigi after the meeting convened by Prime Minister Meloni on the eve of his participation in the Paris summit of the 'Coalition of the Willy', on peace and security in Ukraine. Present the vicepremier, Salvini and Tajani, and Crosetto. Reaffirmed commitment to security guarantees in Kiev in \"Euroatlantic context\" On the monitoring of the ceasefire, \"a possible role of the UN, which the government has long supported\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ENGLISH",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chigi",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 278,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 'Coalition of the Willy'",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Euroatlantic",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 551,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FUGA NOTIZIE CHAT,WALTZ:IO RESPONSABILE Casa Bianca: \"Nessuna conseguenza\"",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Fuga notizie, Waltz: mia responsabilità All'indomani della fuga di notizie sui piani Usa anti-Houthi, emersi da una chat in cui era per sbaglio il direttore dell'Atlantic Goldberg,il consigliere Usa Waltz ha assunto \"piena responsabilità\".\"Io ho creato il gruppo. Mio compito assicurarmi che tutto sia coordinato. E'imbarazzante,approfondiremo\", ha detto a Fox News.Su Goldberg:\"Non ho visto questo perdente nel gruppo\", non lo conosco, è \"feccia dei giornalisti\". Nella chat \"nessun piano di guerra è stato discusso\", nessuna info classificata e nessuna conseguenza sull'operazione militare\" puntualizza Casa Bianca",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1743019204.992665,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ \"No consequence\"",
        "en_content": "Escape News, Waltz: My Responsibility In the aftermath of the leak of news on U.S. anti-Houthi plans, emerged from a chat where the director of the Atlantic Goldberg was mistakenly, US Councillor Waltz assumed \"full responsibility\". \"I created the group. My task is to ensure that everything is coordinated. He's embarrassing, we'll deepen,\" he told Fox News.Su Goldberg: \"I haven't seen this loser in the group,\" I don't know him, it's \"teachers' crime.\" In the chat \"no war plan was discussed\", no classified info and no consequence on military operation\" punctuality White House",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Escape News",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Waltz",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Atlantic Goldberg",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Waltz",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fox News",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Su Goldberg",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 581,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "HOUTHI:NELLA NOTTE 17 RAID USA SU YEMEN E \"diverse ore\" scontri in M.Rosso",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Yemen,nella notte 17 attacchi aerei Usa Dopo l'attacco rivendicato dagli Houthi contro la portaerei Uss Harry S.Truman, gli Usa hanno effettuato almeno 17 raid aerei contro lo Yemen. Sono gli Houthi a riferirlo, nel loro sito. Colpite  nella notte le regioni di Saada e Amran e dopo i raid \"diverse ore\" di scontri Usa-Houthi in M.Rosso,scrive Ansarollah Dal 15 marzo sono quasi quotidiani gli attacchi aerei sullo Yemen, base dei ribelli sostenuti dall'Iran. \"Saranno completamente annientati\", assicura il presidente Usa rivolgendosi anche a Teheran, che avverte: non minacciateci. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1743019205.0107613,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.05",
        "en_title": "HOUTHI:NELLA NIGHT 17 RAID USA ON YEMEN And \"different hours\" clashes in M.Rosso",
        "en_content": "Yemen, in the night 17 air attacks USA After the attack claimed by the Houthi against Uss carrier Harry S.Truman, the U.S. made at least 17 air raids against Yemen. The Houthi report it on their website. Hit in the night the regions of Saada and Amran and after the raid \"diverse hours\" of US-Houthi clashes in M.Rosso, writes Ansarollah Since March 15, there are almost daily air attacks on Yemen, the base of the rebels supported by Iran. \"They will be completely annihilated,\" says US President, addressing Tehran, who warns: do not threaten us.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "HOUTHI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NELLA NIGHT 17",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "RAID USA ON YEMEN",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "hours",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "17",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Uss",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Harry S.Truman",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 17",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Saada",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amran",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ansarollah",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "March 15",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 439,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 485,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 510,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "ISRAELE MINACCIA \"MASSIMA FORZA\" A GAZA A Gaza City 2° giorno di proteste",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Israele minaccia \"massima forza\" a Gaza Israel Katz,ministro Difesa israeliano, ha minacciato di agire con \"la massima forza\" su nuove aree della Striscia di Gaza,dove la tregua è finita il 18 marzo con la ripresa dei bombardamenti. Intanto a Gaza City è partito il secondo giorno consecutivo di proteste contro Hamas e contro la guerra. Hamas le ha bollate come \"megafoni di Israele\". Il ministro israeliano Katz, rivolgendosi direttamente agli abitanti della Striscia di Gaza, ha detto: \"Via Hamas per fermare la guerra\" e \"chiedete il rilascio immediato degli ostaggi\".  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1743019205.0525746,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.05",
        "en_title": "ISRAELE MINACCIA \"MASSIMA FORZA\" in GAZA In Gaza City 2nd day of protests",
        "en_content": "Israel threatens \"maximum force\" in Gaza Israel Katz, Israeli defence minister, threatened to act with \"the greatest force\" on new areas of the Gaza Strip, where the truce ended on March 18 with the resumption of bombing. Meanwhile, Gaza City left the second consecutive day of protests against Hamas and the war. Hamas branded them as \"Megaphones of Israel\". Israeli minister Katz, addressing himself directly to the inhabitants of the Gaza Strip, said: \"Via Hamas to stop the war\" and \"close the immediate release of the hostages.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ISRAELE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "MASSIMA FORZA",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "GAZA",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza City",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2nd day",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel Katz",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 18",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza City",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the second consecutive day",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 433,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL BOLLETTE, STOP A RINVIO POLIZZE",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1743019205.0585017,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.05",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "Macron: altri 2 mld di aiuti a Kiev",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Macron:altri 2 miliardi di aiuti a Kiev \"Sostegno immediato all'Ucraina\", ha detto il presidente francese Emmanuel Macron dopo il bilaterale con il presidente ucraino Volodymyr Zelensky. \"Oggi posso annunciare un aiuto aggiuntivo di 2 miliardi di euro di supporti difensivi all'Ucraina\", ha aggiunto Macron. \"L'obiettivo è permettere agli ucraini di continuare a resistere sul terreno\", ha detto il presidente francese alla vigilia del vertice della 'coalizione dei volenterosi'. \"E' presto per parlare di revoca delle sanzioni. Mosca mostra volontà di proseguire la guerra\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1743019205.0744758,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.05",
        "en_title": "Macron: another 2 mld of aid in Kiev",
        "en_content": "Macron: another 2 billion aid in Kiev \"immediate support for Ukraine\", said French President Emmanuel Macron after bilateral with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky. \"Today I can announce an additional 2 billion euro support for Ukraine,\" added Macron. \"The goal is to allow Ukrainians to continue to resist on the ground,\" said the French president on the eve of the summit of the 'coalition of the volenterosis'. \"It's early to talk about revoking sanctions. Moscow shows the will to continue the war.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "2 billion",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emmanuel Macron",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "an additional 2 billion euro",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainians",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "TORINO,BUS CADE NEL PO: MORTO L'AUTISTA Lievemente ferite tre passanti",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1743019205.1006644,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.05",
        "en_title": "_ _",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "DL BOLLETTE,STOP RINVIO POLIZZE E BONUS Alt sconto fattura elettrodomestici",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Dl Bollette,stop rinvio polizze e bonus Stop agli emendamenti al Decreto Bollette sul rinvio dell'obbligo delle  polizze anti catastrofali per le imprese, sul bonus per l'acquisto degli elettrodomestici e su auto aziendali. Gli emendamenti, presentati da FdI, sono stati dichiarati inammissibili in Commissione Attività Produttive della Camera, salvo ripescaggio in seguito a ricorso per le riammissioni.  Uno degli emendamenti puntava a modificare il bonus elettrodomestici introducendo sconto in fattura e eliminando il riferimento alla nuova classe energetica B.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1743019205.1079288,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.05",
        "en_title": "DL BOLLETTE,STOP RINVIO POLIZZE AND BONUS Alt discount billing appliances",
        "en_content": "Dl Bollette,stop referencing policies and bonus Stop to the amendments to the Decree Bollette on the postponement of the obligation of anti-catastrophe policies for enterprises, on the bonus for the purchase of household appliances and on corporate cars. The amendments tabled by FdI have been declared inadmissible in the Committee on Production Activities of the Chamber, unless repeated following re-admissions. One of the amendments aimed at modifying the appliance bonus by introducing discount in invoice and eliminating the reference to the new energy class B.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "STOP RINVIO POLIZZE AND BONUS Alt",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Dl Bollette",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bollette",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Committee on Production Activities",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "KIEV A UE:SERVONO TRUPPE CHE COMBATTANO Inutile presenza con i peacekeeper",
        "date_raw": "March 26, 2025",
        "date": "2025-03-26",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Kiev a Ue:servono truppe che combattano L'Ucraina ha bisogno di un contributo \"serio\" dall'Europa con truppe pronte a combattere e non di peacekeeper dopo la fine delle ostilità con la Russia.Lo ha detto il negoziatore ucraino e collaboratore di Zelensky,Zhovkva,alla vigilia del vertice dei \"volenterosi\" a Parigi. \"Non abbiamo bisogno di una semplice presenza per dimostrare che l'Europa è presente.Non è la quantità che conta.E' anche la loro prontezza a combattere, a difendersi, a essere equipaggiati,a capire che l'Ucraina è parte inevitabile della sicurezza europea\", ha sostenuto.",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1743019205.1365604,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2025-03-26 21:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-26T20.00.05",
        "en_title": "KIEV TO THE EU: THEY WILL COMBIT Needless presence with peacekeepers",
        "en_content": "Kiev in Ue: they serve troops fighting Ukraine needs a \"serious\" contribution from Europe with troops ready to fight and not peacekeeper after the end of hostilities with Russia. This was said by the Ukrainian negotiator and collaborator of Zelensky, Zhovkva, on the eve of the summit of \"volenterosis\" in Paris. \"We do not need a simple presence to prove that Europe is present. It's not the amount that matters. It is also their readiness to fight, defend themselves, to be equipped, to understand that Ukraine is an inevitable part of European security,\" he said.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "KIEV",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zhovkva",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 512,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
