[
    {
        "title": "SUPERBONUS,TAJANI:VOGLIO VEDERCI CHIARO \"Molta, molta attenzione sul testo\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Superbonus,Tajani:voglio vederci chiaro \"Voglio vederci chiaro nel nuovo testo\" sul superbonus \"che è stato presentato stanotte dal ministero dell'Economia, però bisogna veramente prestare molta molta molta attenzione\". Così il vicepremiere e leader di FI,Tajani.  \"Lunedì mattina, come partito, ascolterò tutti i rappresentati delle varie categorie per capire cosa c'è da aggiustare in Parlamento rispetto a questa proposta che mi ha dato il ministero\", ha detto, sottolineando che\"non si possono dare norme retroattive\".L'emendamento del governo spalma i crediti 2024 del superbonus in 10 anni.   ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715493605.9693866,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.05",
        "en_title": "SUPERBONUS,TAJANI:VOGLIO VEDERCI CHIARO \"Very much attention on the text\"",
        "en_content": "Superbonus,Tajani: I want to see ourselves clearly \"I want to see ourselves clearly in the new text\" on the superbonus \"which was presented tonight by the Ministry of Economy, but it really needs to be very careful\". So the deputypremiere and leader of FI,Tajani. \"Monday morning, as a party, I will listen to all the representatives of the various categories to understand what is to be adjusted in Parliament with respect to this proposal which has given me the ministry,\" he said, stressing that \"there are no retroactive norms.\" The government's amendment spreads the 2024 credits of the superbonus in 10 years.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Economy",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday morning",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 572,
                "end_char": 576,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years",
                "start_char": 606,
                "end_char": 614,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "PARIGI: \"FERMARE L'OPERAZIONE A RAFAH\"  \"Senza indugio, sarebbe catastrofe\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Parigi a Israele:alt a operazione Rafah La Francia ha chiesto a Israele di cessare \"senza indugio\" l'operazione militare a Rafah, che rischia di creare una \"situazione catastrofica\" per la popolazione della Striscia di Gaza, \"già sfollata in più occasioni\". Lo ha detto il ministero degli Esteri in un comunicato diffuso su X.    \"Chiediamo alle autorità israeliane di riprendere la strada dei negoziati,unica via possibile per arrivare alla liberazione immediata degli ostaggi e ottenere un cessate il fuoco durevole\", si legge nella nota.    ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715493605.9988928,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:05",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.05",
        "en_title": "PARIGI: \"FERMARE L'OPERATION A RAFAH\" \"Without delay, it would be catastrophe\"",
        "en_content": "Paris to Israel:Alt a Operation Rafah France has asked Israel to cease \"without delay\" the military operation in Rafah, which risks creating a \" catastrophic situation\" for the people of the Gaza Strip, \"already displaced on several occasions\". The Foreign Ministry said this in a statement on X. \"We call on the Israeli authorities to resume the path of negotiations, only possible way to arrive at the immediate release of the hostages and obtain a lasting ceasefire\", we read in the note.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Foreign Ministry",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "X.",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RAID ISRAELE A RAFAH, FONTI: 15 MORTI  \"Tra le vittime 4 bimbi e 5 donne\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Idf chiede evacuare Rafah e altre zone L'esercito israeliano ha chiesto alla popolazione di altri quartieri della città di Rafah di evacuare le loro abitazioni, utilizzando anche volantini in arabo, mentre si intensificano i combattimenti nella città del sud della Striscia di Gaza.     Il portavoce in arabo dell'Idf ha diffuso una lista di nuove zone da evacuare, in aggiunta e diverse da quelle orientali indicate la scorsa settimana. Le nuova zone da evacuare riguardano i campi di Shaboura e i quartieri di Jeneina e Khirbat al-Adas.   ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715493606.0263102,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "RAID ISRAELE A RAFAH, FONTI: 15 MORTI \"Among the victims 4 children and 5 women\"",
        "en_content": "Idf asks to evacuate Rafah and other areas The Israeli army asked the population of other parts of the city of Rafah to evacuate their homes, using also flyers in Arabic, while intensifying the fighting in the southern city of the Gaza Strip. The Arab spokesman of the Idf spread a list of new areas to be evacuated, in addition and different from the eastern ones indicated last week. The new areas to be evacuated concern the fields of Shaboura and the neighborhoods of Jeneina and Khirbat al-Adas.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arabic",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "last week",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 384,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shaboura",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jeneina",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khirbat al-Adas",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "HAMAS POSTA NUOVO VIDEO DI UN OSTAGGIO  Poi: \"Morto per un raid israeliano\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Hamas posta video ostaggio morto raid Hamas ha diffuso un nuovo video nel  quale ha sostenuto che l'ostaggio Nadav Popplewell è \"morto per le ferite riportate durante un raid israeliano\" più di un mese fa. \"Le sue condizioni, ha detto Abu Obeida, portavoce delle Brigate Qassam, si sono deteriorate e non è stato possibile curarlo a causa delle distruzioni degli ospedali a Gaza da parte del nemico\".    Poche ore prima Hamas aveva diffuso un video di Popplewell seguito da un punto interrogativo.In Israele il video non è mostrato e viene definito di propaganda",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715493606.069453,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Then: \"Image for an Israeli raid\"",
        "en_content": "Hamas posted video hostage dead raid Hamas released a new video in which he claimed that hostage Nadav Popplewell was \"dead for wounds reported during an Israeli raid\" more than a month ago. \"His conditions, said Abu Obeida, spokesman of the Qassam Brigades, deteriorated and it was not possible to cure him because of the destruction of hospitals in Gaza by the enemy.\" A few hours before Hamas had released a video of Popplewell followed by a question mark. In Israel the video is not shown and is defined as propaganda",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nadav Popplewell",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than a month ago",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abu Obeida",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Qassam Brigades",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "A few hours",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Popplewell",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 463,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Rapporto Usa:\"Israele viola diritto\"155  FORZE RUSSE AVANZANO ANCORA IN UCRAINA  Mosca: \"Conquistati 5 villaggi\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Ucraina, avanzano ancora le forze russe Il ministero della Difesa russo afferma che l'offensiva di terra delle sue truppe continua a mietere successi conquistando cinque villaggi nella provincia di Kharkiv, nei pressi del confine con la Russia. Oltre ai villaggi di  Borisivka, Ogirtseve, Pletenivka, Pylna e Strilecha, i russi si sono impadroniti anche di Keramik nel Donetsk.  Fonti ucraine confermano il procedere dell'offensiva russa con la penetrazione per 5 chilometri in territorio ucraino di quattro battaglioni russi per un totale di circa 2.000 uomini.  ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715493606.0765545,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "U.S. Report: \"Israel violates law\"155 RUSSE FORCE ADVANCED IN UCRAINA Moscow: \"Conquered 5 villages\"",
        "en_content": "The Russian Ministry of Defence states that the offensive of land of its troops continues to reap successes by conquering five villages in the province of Kharkiv, near the border with Russia. In addition to the villages of Borisivka, Ogirtseve, Pletenivka, Pylna and Strilecha, the Russians also took over Keramik in Donetsk. Ukrainian sources confirm the proceeding of the Russian offensive with the penetration for 5 kilometers in Ukrainian territory of four Russian battalions for a total of about 2,000 men.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Russian Ministry of Defence",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "five",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Borisivka",
                "start_char": 224,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ogirtseve",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pletenivka",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pylna",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Strilecha",
                "start_char": 268,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Keramik",
                "start_char": 307,
                "end_char": 314,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donetsk",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 kilometers",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 2,000",
                "start_char": 496,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Santalucia: \"Illazioni offensive\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=128",
        "content": " Santalucia:da Salvini illazioni cattive \"Quelle di Salvini sono illazioni vaghe cattive, gratuitamente offensive. Così torna tutto a una dimensione di conflitto,a una rissa tra magistrati e politica\".Così Santalucia Anm a La Stampa \"Riconosciamo la supremazia della legge all'interno dell'intero ordinamento,non la supremazia della singola disposizione creata dal legislatore nel momento contingente. Se non ci intendiamo su questo ci sarà sempre qualcuno\" che con \"dichiarazioni appese al nulla\" parla \"di giudici comunisti\".Dubbi di Nordio? \"Sospetti e insinuazioni fanno male\". ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.081982,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Santalucia: \"Illations offensive\"",
        "en_content": "Santalucia: from Salvini illazioni wicked \"Quelle di Salvini are evil vague illations, free of charge offensive. So it all comes back to a dimension of conflict, a fight between magistrates and politics.\" Thus Santalucia Anm in La Stampa \"We recognize the supremacy of the law within the whole order, not the supremacy of the single provision created by the legislator at the contingent moment. If we don't think about this, there will always be someone who, with \"exclaims hanging from nothing,\" speaks \"of communist judges.\" Nordio Dubbi? \"Suspects and insinuations hurt.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Santalucia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Illations",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Santalucia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini illazioni",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quelle",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "di Salvini",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "illations",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santalucia Anm",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Stampa",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "communist",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 517,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio Dubbi",
                "start_char": 527,
                "end_char": 539,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Razzo su festa filorussi, tre morti",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Donetsk,razzo su ristorante: tre morti E' di almeno 3 morti e 8 feriti il bilancio provvisorio di un attacco compiuto dalle forze armate ucraine contro un ristorante nel distretto Leninsky di Donetsk, la città occupata dalle unità militari russe.     All'interno del ristorante si trovavano militanti filorussi che stavano festeggiando l'anniversario dell'autoproclamata repubblica di Donetsk. Tra i morti anche una cameriera e un bambino. Il governatore russo della regione ha detto che le forze ucraine hanno usato i lanciarazzi Himars forniti dagli Usa. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715493606.085123,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Rack on filthy party, three dead",
        "en_content": "Donetsk, rocket on restaurant: three dead It's at least 3 dead and 8 wounded the provisional balance of an attack carried out by the Ukrainian armed forces against a restaurant in the Leninsky district of Donetsk, the city occupied by Russian military units. Inside the restaurant were philanthropist militants who were celebrating the anniversary of the self-proclaimed republic of Donetsk. Among the dead also a maid and a child. The Russian governor of the region said that Ukrainian forces used the Himars rocket launchers provided by the US.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donetsk",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 3",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leninsky",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donetsk",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donetsk",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 436,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 477,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Himars",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MATTARELLA:\"VOTATE,IN GIOCO DEMOCRAZIA\" Alta posta in palio nel voto per Ue",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=129",
        "content": " Appello capi Stato:cittadini,votate Ue Occorre riflettere insieme sulle \"prospettive future\" e sulle \"sfide che ci attendono\" e \"chiediamo ai nostri cittadini di prendere parte a questa decisione di andare a votare!\".Così i presidenti Mattarella,Steinmeier e Van der Bellen in un intervento sul Corsera. \"La posta in gioco non è altro che i fondamenti del nostro ordine democratico\". \"Libertà e democrazia vanno difese e consolidate\", affermano i presidenti di Italia,Germania e Austria, sottolineando che \"la contrapposizione dei nazionalismi esasperati genera la guerra\"",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.099525,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "_ High stake in the vote for EU",
        "en_content": "Appeal of Heads of State: Citizens, MEPs It is necessary to reflect together on \"the future prospects\" and \"the challenges that await us\" and \"we ask our citizens to take part in this decision to vote!\" So the presidents Mattarella, Steinmeier and Van der Bellen in an intervention on the Corsera. \"The stake is nothing but the foundations of our democratic order.\" \"Freedom and democracy must be defended and consolidated,\" said the presidents of Italy, Germany and Austria, underlining that \"the opposition of exasperated nationalisms generates war\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Steinmeier",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Van der Bellen",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "democratic",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Austria",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Anm: a rischio autonomia magistrati",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Anm a Nordio: no a separazione carriere \"Il ministro Nordio ci ha confermato l'intenzione di andare avanti con la riforma della separazione delle carriere, che è incompatibile con il mantenimento dell'autonomia e dell'indipendenza della magistratura.Quindi noi continuiamo a ribadire la nostra contrarietà a una riforma che stravolga l'impianto costituzionale a danno dei cittadini\". Lo ha detto la vicepresidente dell'Associazione nazionale magistrati Maddalena,commentando l'intervento del Guardasigilli Nordio al Congresso dell'Anm.",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.1514344,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Anm: at risk magistrate autonomy",
        "en_content": "Anm in Nordio: no to career separation \"The Minister Nordio has confirmed our intention to move forward with the reform of career separation, which is incompatible with the maintenance of autonomy and independence of the judiciary. So we continue to reiterate our opposition to a reform that distorts the constitutional system to the detriment of citizens.\" This was said by the Vice-President of the National Association of Magyar Magdalene, acting the intervention of the Norther Guards at the Congress of the Am.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Association of Magyar Magdalene",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Norther Guards",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Congress of the Am",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Schlein: no a separazione carriere",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Schlein:no a separazione carriere toghe \"La separazione delle carriere oltre a non risolvere i problemi della giustizia riteniamo sia l'anticamera della sottomissione dei magistrati all'Esecutivo e comprometta il principio dell' obbligatorietà dell'azione penale\" e su questo c'è la \"nostra contrarietà\".Così la leader Pd Schlein,al congresso Anm. \"E'importante essere qui con attenzione e rispetto\"ha detto Schlein,riconoscendo al congresso di essere \"momento di dialogo.\"La vostra attività è preziosa\" \"i continui cambiamenti nella società aumentano la richiesta di giustizia\". ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.231978,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Schlein: no to career separation",
        "en_content": "Schlein:no to separating careers \"The separation of careers besides not solving the problems of justice we consider both the antechamber of the submission of magistrates to the Executive and compromises the principle of the obligatoryness of criminal action\" and on this there is the \"our contradiction\". So the leader Pd Schlein, at the Anm congress. \"It is important to be here with attention and respect\" Schlein said, recognising at the congress to be \"moment of dialogue. \"Your business is precious\" \"the continuous changes in society increase the demand for justice\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Executive",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd Schlein",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Anm congress",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "congress",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SALVINI:OGNI GIORNO ARRESTO 3 INNOCENTI Paghi chi ha sbagliato con il dolo",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=127",
        "content": " Salvini:ogni giorno arresto 3 innocenti \"Ogni anno mille italiani vengono arrestati e poi liberati perché magistrati avevano sbagliato qualcosa. Significa 3 persone al giorno. Vuol dire che oggi 3 persone normali,no politici,vengono arrestate.Gli si rovina la vita.E poi una pacca sulle spalle, mi scusi abbiamo sbagliato\". Così Salvini a La Stampa. \"Nessuno ne risponde. La responsabilità civile dei magistrati personale e pecuniaria per quelli che sbagliano con dolo eviterebbe alcuni problemi\".Toti? \"Dimettersi adesso sarebbe una resa\"nel rapporto sbilanciato magistrati-mondo. ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.2351656,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Come on. _",
        "en_content": "Salvini: every day I stop 3 innocent \"Every year a thousand Italians are arrested and then freed because magistrates had wrong something. It means 3 people a day. It means that today 3 normal people, no politicians, are arrested. He's ruined his life. And then a poop on the shoulders, I'm sorry we were wrong.\" So Salvini to La Stampa. \"No one answers. The civil liability of personal and pecuniary magistrates for those who are wrong with dolo would avoid some problems\". Toti? \"Resign now would be a surrender\" in the unbalanced magistrate-world relationship.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Stampa",
                "start_char": 326,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "dolo",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "La replica a Meloni: \"Fanfaluche\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " De Luca:\"Spaventato da spavento Meloni\" \"Apprendo con animo turbato e contrito che l'on.Meloni ha trovato 'spaventosa' una mia battuta relativa alla sua performance sul premierato e al carattere propagandistico che l'ha caratterizzata Sono grato e commosso per l'attenzione ma sono spaventato per il suo spavento\" Così il governatore campano De Luca a Meloni,critica con lui per aver\"deriso\" Don Patriciello,ironizzando sui vip da lei scelti per promuovere il premierato Meloni\"oltre che delle fanfaluche\"dovrebbe preoccuparsi di sbloccare i nostri fondi di sviluppo e coesione bloccati da un anno\",ha aggiunto.  ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.2384999,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "The replica to Meloni: \"Fanfaluche\"",
        "en_content": "De Luca: \"Spavented by scary Meloni\" \"I apprehend with disturbed and contrite soul that on.Meloni found a joke about his performance on the premierate and propagandistic character that characterized him I am grateful and moved for attention but I am afraid for his fear\" Thus the governor of Campania De Luca to Meloni,critical with him for having \"derise\" Don Patriciello, hiring on the VIPs she chose to promote the premierato Meloni\" as well as fanfaluche \"would worry about unlocking our development and cohesion funds blocked by a year,\" he added.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "De Luca",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Campania De Luca",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Patriciello",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "fanfaluche",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a year",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 540,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI:\"DE LUCA DERIDE DON PATRICIELLO\" Governatore aveva detto: come Baudo",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Meloni:\"De Luca deride Don Patriciello\" \"'Pippo Baudo dell'area nord di Napoli' Così deridendolo, il presidente della Regione Campania definisce Don Maurizio Patriciello, un prete,un uomo che cerca di combattere la camorra e dare risposte alle famiglie perbene dove quelli come De Luca non sono riusciti a farlo o non hanno voluto farlo\". Così la premier sulle \"ironie sui vip scelti da Meloni per promuovere il premierato\". Così facendo De Luca \"dà un segnale  spaventoso\". \"Invece di aiutare padre Maurizio, fargli sentire il sostegno delle Istituzioni,lo deride\". Ma \"lo Stato c'è, è al suo fianco,non è solo\".",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.2409415,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "MELONI: \"DE LUCA DERIDE DON PATRICIELLO\" Governor said:",
        "en_content": "Meloni: \"De Luca deride Don Patriciello\" \"'Pippo Baudo dell'area nord di Napoli' Thus derided it, the president of the Campania Region defines Don Maurizio Patriciello, a priest, a man who tries to fight the chamorra and give answers to the families of Peru where those like De Luca did not succeed in doing so or did not want to do so\". So the premier on the \"ronies on the vip chosen by Meloni to promote the premierate\". So De Luca \"gives a scary signal.\" \"Instead of helping Father Maurizio, make him feel the support of the institutions, he laughs.\" But \"the State is there, it is at its side, it is not alone.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "De Luca",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Patriciello",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pippo Baudo dell'area nord",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Campania Region",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Maurizio Patriciello",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peru",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "De Luca",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "De Luca",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maurizio",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 564,
                "end_char": 569,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "HAMAS POSTA NUOVO VIDEO DI OSTAGGIO",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715493606.266363,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "HAMAS POSTAIN NEW DEVELOPMENT",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "HAMAS POSTAIN NEW DEVELOPMENT",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.2705188,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "INDAGINE GENOVA,TOTI INDAGATO PER FALSO Salta l'interrogatorio di Spinelli",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715493606.3127394,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "INDAGINE GENOVA,TOTI INDAGATO FOR FALSO Skip the interrogation of Spinelli",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "INDAGINE GENOVA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "TOTI INDAGATO",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Spinelli",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Patriciello:\"Pugnalata,rischio vita\"123  NORDIO:\"NON NEGOZIABILE L'INDIPENDENZA\" \"Resta separazione carriere toghe\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Nordio:\"Indipendenza non è negoziabile\" \"L'indipendenza della magistratura è un principio non negoziabile.Una contiguità col potere esecutivo è inimmaginabile. Resta però il problema della separazione delle carriere\"Così il Guardasigilli all'Anm accolto da applauso. \"Spero non si parli di conflitto tra politica e magistratura.Si potrà parlare di dialogo acceso.Ci sono differenze nelle nostre posizioni. Spesso espresse anche in termini severi. Io accetto il dissenso,che è il sale della democrazia Mai mi sognerei di entrare in conflitto Io che sono stato magistrato 40 anni\". ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.3145418,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "Patriciello: \"Pugnalata,richio vita\"123 NORDIO: \"NON NEGOZIABILE L'INDIPENDENZA\" \"Resta Separation careere toghe\"",
        "en_content": "Nordio: \"Independence is not negotiable\" \"The independence of judiciary is a non-negotiable principle. A contiguity with executive power is unimaginable. But the problem of the separation of careers remains \"So the Guardasigilli all'Anm welcomed by applause. \"I hope you don't talk about conflict between politics and judiciary. We can talk about dialogue on. There are differences in our positions. Often expressed in strict terms. I accept dissent, which is the salt of democracy I would never dream of entering conflict I have been magistrate 40 years.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Resta Separation careere",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nordio",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Independence",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guardasigilli",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 228,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "40 years",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 554,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DON PATRICIELLO: \"PUGNALATA DA DE LUCA\" Meloni lo difende: \"Segnale spaventoso\" Governatore replica: \"Fanfaluche\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715493606.3670967,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "_ \"Walking signal\" Governor replies: \"Fanfaluche\"",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "GIORGETTI:TAJANI SE NE FARA'UNA RAGIONE \"Oppure ridiscutiamo tante spese\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Giorgetti:Tajani se ne farà una ragione \"Tajani quando leggerà l'emendamento capirà il buonsenso che l'ha ispirato., Credo che se ne farà una ragione anche lui, perché altrimenti dovremo andare a ridiscutere tante spese che abbiamo. Io ad esempio non è che introduco il tema se sia opportuno tenere tutte queste missioni militari nel mondo, che magari potremo ridispiegare nel Mediterraneo\". Così il ministro dell'Economia Giorgetti,dopo che Tajani ha detto di \"volerci veder chiaro\"nell'emendamento che spalma in 10 anni i crediti del Superbonus.",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715493606.369598,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Giorgetti: Tajani will make a reason for it \"Tajani when he reads the amendment will understand the common sense that inspired it., I think he will make a reason for it too, because otherwise we will have to go to rediscuss so much expenses we have. For example, it is not that I introduce the theme if it is appropriate to keep all these military missions in the world, that perhaps we can re-explain in the Mediterranean.\" So the Minister of Economy Giorgetti, after Tajani said \"will see us clear\" in the amendment that spreads in 10 years the Superbonus credits.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mediterranean",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 475,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 542,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MALMO,EUROVISION 2024:VINCE LA SVIZZERA Poi Croazia, Francia.Italia settima",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=160",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715493606.371676,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "MALMO,EUROVISION 2024:VINCE THE SWITZERLAND Then Croatia, France. Italy seventh",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EUROVISION 2024",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "VINCE",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "SWITZERLAND",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Croatia",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "seventh",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SUPERBONUS,TAJANI:VOGLIO VEDERCI CHIARO Giorgetti: \"Se ne farà una ragione\"",
        "date_raw": "May 12, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=130",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715493606.4000487,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 08:00:06",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T08.00.06",
        "en_title": "SUPERBONUS,TAJANI: IVOGLIO VEDERCI CHIARO Giorgetti: \"You're gonna make a point.\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "IVOGLIO VEDERCI",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
