[
    {
        "title": "M.O.,ATENEO CALIFORNIA BOICOTTA ISRAELE Lettera Rettore per sgombero campus",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Usa, ateneo California boicotta Israele La Sonoma State University (Ssu) in California -una scuola di arti liberali parte della California State University Networkè il primo ateneo ad annunciare il boicottaggio di Israele, come  parte di un accordo con gli studenti sullo sgombero della tendopoli pro-Palestina creata nel campus.   Il presidente della Ssu Mike Lee ha accettato le richieste studentesche e ha pubblicato una lettera in cui chiede il cessate il fuoco nella Striscia di Gaza e condanna \"gli atti di genocidio, pulizia etnica,razzismo e antisemitismo\".",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715886004.5411444,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "USA, Boicot California University Israel Sonoma State University (Ssu) in California -a liberal arts school part of the California State University Network is the first university to announce the boycott of Israel, as part of an agreement with students on the clearing of pro-Palestina tendopoli created on campus. Ssu Mike Lee's president accepted student demands and published a letter calling for ceasefire in the Gaza Strip and condemning \"the acts of genocide, ethnic cleansing, racism and anti-Semitism\".",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Boicot California University",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel Sonoma State University",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "California",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the California State University Network",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "pro-Palestina",
                "start_char": 272,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ssu Mike Lee's",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FORTI LASCIA CARCERE USA,ATTESO RIENTRO \"Per me ora comincia la rinascita\"",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Forti lascia carcere Usa,atteso rientro Chico Forti non è più detenuto in carcere a Miami e nelle prossime settimane è atteso il rientro in Italia del 65enne trentino,condannato all'ergastolo in Florida per l'omicidio di Dale Pike, avvenuto il 15 febbraio del 1998. A Miami l'udienza in cui Forti ha siglato l'accordo con il giudice federale statunitense per scontare il resto della pena in Italia.Nel frattempo Forti è trattenuto dall'Immigration and Customs Enforcement.\"Per me ora comincia la rinascita\", sono le parole riferite poco prima del trasferimento a persone a lui vicine.Si sarebbe detto\"molto positivo\"",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715886004.5568266,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "FORTI LASCIA CARCERE USA, ATTE RIENTRO \"For me now begins rebirth\"",
        "en_content": "Forti leaves U.S. prison, awaited return Chico Forti is no longer held in prison in Miami and in the coming weeks the return to Italy of the 65-year-old trentino, sentenced to life in Florida for the murder of Dale Pike, occurred on February 15, 1998. In Miami the hearing in which Forti signed the agreement with the US federal judge to take the rest of the penalty in Italy. In the meantime Forti is held by the Immigration and Customs Enforcement.\"For me now the rebirth begins,\" are the words reported just before the transfer to people close to him. It would have been said \"very positive\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FORTI LASCIA CARCERE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chico Forti",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Miami",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming weeks",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "65-year-old",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dale Pike",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "February 15, 1998",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Miami",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forti",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forti",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Immigration and Customs Enforcement",
                "start_char": 410,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nostra intesa non è contro qualcuno",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Xi-Putin:relazioni per stabilità e pace Il presidente russo Putin è a Pechino, accolto con una calorosa stretta di mano da Xi. Entrambi hanno affermato che le relazioni Cina-Russia sono \"fattori di stabilità e pace\" per il mondo. \"Non sono opportunistiche e non sono dirette contro qualcuno\",ha detto Putin.Cerimonia di benvenuto nel grande Palazzo del Popolo, sulla piazza Tienanmen.  \"Continueremo a consolidare l'amicizia\" ha affermato Xi Jinping. La visita di Stato del leader russo prevede colloqui in formato ristretto e allargato e un incontro col premier cinese, Li Qiang. ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715886004.57136,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "Our understanding is not against someone",
        "en_content": "Xi-Putin:relations for stability and peace Russian President Putin is in Beijing, welcomed with a warm handshake from Xi. Both said that China-Russia relations are \"factors of stability and peace\" for the world. \"They are not opportunistic and are not directed against someone,\" said Putin.Welcome ceremony in the great People's Palace, on Tienanmen Square. \"We will continue to consolidate friendship,\" said Xi Jinping. The Russian leader's visit to the state provides for small and wide-ranging talks and a meeting with Chinese premier Li Qiang.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Xi-Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "People's Palace",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tienanmen Square",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi Jinping",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 529,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Li Qiang",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SLOVACCHIA,ROBERT FICO GRAVE MA STABILE Operato per 5 ore,è in rianimazione",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Slovacchia, Fico operato per cinque ore Il premier slovacco, Fico, è stato operato per 5 ore da 2 equipe chirurgiche. Così la direttice dell'ospedale. Fico è ora nel reparto di Anestesiologia e  rianimazione. \"Aveva ferite multiple da arma da fuoco\".Le sue condizioni restano molto critiche e le prossime 24 ore saranno cruciali.Il premier lotta ancora tra la vita e la morte.   Ieri, ad Handlov, 180 km a nord-Est di Bratislava, l'attentato da parte di un 71enne che era tra la folla e gli ha esploso contro 5 proiettili. Tre hanno raggiunto all'addome e al torace il 59 leader slovacco, populista e filorusso.",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715886004.5758388,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "SLOVACCHIA,ROBERT FICO GRAVE MA STABILE Worked for 5 hours, is in reanimation",
        "en_content": "Slovakia, Fico operated for five hours Slovakian premier, Fico, was operated for 5 hours by 2 surgical teams. So the hospital's management. Fico is now in the department of Anestesiology and reanimation. \"He had multiple gunshot wounds.\" His conditions remain critical and the next 24 hours will be crucial. The premier still struggles between life and death. Yesterday, in Handlov, 180 km north-east of Bratislava, the attack by a 71-year-old who was among the crowd and exploded against 5 bullets. Three reached the abdomen and thorax the 59 Slovak, populist and philanthropist leaders.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "5 hours",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Slovakia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "five hours",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovakian",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "5 hours",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fico",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anestesiology",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the next 24 hours",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yesterday",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Handlov",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "180 km",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bratislava",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "71-year-old",
                "start_char": 432,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 489,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Three",
                "start_char": 500,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "59",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovak",
                "start_char": 544,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RAI, SALTA IL DUELLO TV MELONI-SCHLEIN  Non c'è maggioranza chiesta da Agcom   Nota Rai: rispetteremo par condicio",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Rai, nessun confronto Meloni-Schlein Salta il duello tv tra la premier Meloni e la leader Pd Schlein sulle Europee \"Soltanto 4 delle 8 liste rappresentate in Parlamento hanno accettato l'invito di Rai a un confronto a 2 tra leader sulla base della forza rappresentativa. Per questo motivo, in assenza della  maggioranza richiesta dall'Autorità per le garanzie nelle comunicazioni, Rai ritiene di non poter programmare alcun confronto nei termini precedentemente proposti\". Così una nota della Rai, che assicura che continuerà a garantire il rispetto della par condicio.   ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.6086044,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "RAI, SALTA IL DUELLO TV MELONI-SCHLEIN There is no majority asked by Agcom Nota Rai: we will respect",
        "en_content": "Rai, no Meloni-Schlein comparison Skip the TV duel between Premier Meloni and the leader Pd Schlein on Europeans \"Only 4 of the 8 lists represented in Parliament accepted Rai's invitation to a comparison of 2 between leaders based on the representative force. For this reason, in the absence of the majority required by the Authority for the guarantees in communications, Rai believes that he cannot plan any comparison in the terms previously proposed\". So a note from the Rai, which ensures that it will continue to ensure respect for the par condicio.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "RAI",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SALTA IL DUELLO",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nota Rai",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd Schlein",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Authority",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Preso 71enne:contrario a suo governo153  TUSK: HO RICEVUTO MINACCE DI MORTE SU X \"Gli slovacchi hanno dato esempio\"",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Tusk:ho ricevuto minacce di morte su X Il primo ministro polacco Donald Tusk ha reso noto attraverso i suoi profili sui social di avere ricevuto minacce di morte dopo l'attentato al premier slovacco Robert Fico. Sul profilo X di  Tusk è apparso lo screenshot di un commento minaccioso:\"Oggi gli slovacchi ci hanno dato l'esempio di cosa si dovrebbe fare con Donald Tusk\".   Le minacce vertono anche sulle decisioni del premier circa la costruzione di un aeroporto. I media polacchi hanno riferito che la sicurezza del primo ministro è stata rafforzata.   ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715886004.6353815,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "71 year old: meeting with his government153 TUSK: I have MINACCE RESEARCH ON X \"Slovaks have given example\"",
        "en_content": "Tusk:I received death threats on X Polish Prime Minister Donald Tusk made known through his social profiles to have received death threats after the attack on Slovak Premier Robert Fico. On the X profile of Tusk appeared the screenshot of a threatening comment: \"Today the Slovaks gave us the example of what you should do with Donald Tusk\". Threats also come about the Prime Minister's decisions about building an airport. The Polish media reported that the security of the Prime Minister was strengthened.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "71 year old",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "TUSK",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "MINACCE",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovaks",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tusk",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Tusk",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovak",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Robert Fico",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tusk",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovaks",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Tusk",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 428,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "UCRAINA,XI-PUTIN:SOLUZIONE POLITICA",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " Ucraina,Xi-Putin:soluzione sia politica Cina e Russia concordano sul fatto che il conflitto in Ucraina richieda una \"soluzione politica\". Così il presidente Xi Jinping con l'omologo russo Putin \"Entrambe le parti concordano sul fatto che la strada da seguire è una soluzione politica alla crisi in Ucraina\", ha detto Xi in conferenza stampa congiunta La Russia è grata agli \"amici e colleghi cinesi per le iniziative che stanno proponendo\" per mettere fine al conflitto in Ucraina, ha detto Putin. Necessario \"evitare ulteriore escalation\" in Ucraina,concordano Xi e Putin.",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715886004.653377,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "UCRAINA,XI-PUTIN:POLITICAL DEPARTMENT",
        "en_content": "Ukraine,Xi-Putin:solution both political China and Russia agree that the conflict in Ukraine requires a \"political solution\". So President Xi Jinping with Russian counterpart Putin \"Entrambe the parties agree that the road to follow is a political solution to the crisis in Ukraine\", said Xi at the joint press conference Russia is grateful to \"Chinese friends and colleagues for the initiatives they are proposing\" to put an end to the conflict in Ukraine, said Putin. It is necessary to \"avoid further escalation\" in Ukraine, agree Xi and Putin.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi-Putin",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi Jinping",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Entrambe",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 463,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SLOVACCHIA,ROBERT FICO GRAVE MA STABILE Tusk:ricevuto minacce di morte su X",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715886004.6658573,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "\"IL RISPETTO DEI DIRITTI UMANI OVUNQUE\" Così Mattarella a studenti su Gaza",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=120",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715886004.6698184,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "\"The Respondent of Human Rights\" So Mattarella to students on Gaza",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Respondent of Human Rights",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FORTI LASCIA CARCERE USA,ATTESO RIENTRO \"Per me ora comincia la rinascita\"",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1715886004.6727262,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "FORTI LASCIA CARCERE USA, ATTE RIENTRO \"For me now begins rebirth\"",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FORTI LASCIA CARCERE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.7216258,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DISOCCUPAZIONE GIU'SOLO ITALIA E GRECIA Lo riferisce una nota dell'Ocse",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=133",
        "content": " Disoccupazione giù solo Italia e Grecia A marzo nell'Unione Europea e nell'area euro, il tasso di disoccupazione è rimasto ai minimi record, rispettivamente del 6% e del 6,5% nel marzo 2024. Lo riferisce una nota dell'Ocse.   Il tasso di disoccupazione è rimasto stabile o in aumento nella maggior parte dei Paesi Ocse dell'area euro. Solo l'Italia e la Grecia hanno registrato diminuzioni.     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.7542229,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "JUDGMENT ONLY ITALY AND GREECE A note from the OECD reports it",
        "en_content": "Unemployment down only Italy and Greece In March in the European Union and in the euro area, the unemployment rate remained at the lowest records, respectively 6% and 6.5% in March 2024. A note from the OECD reports it. The unemployment rate remained stable or rising in most OECD countries in the euro area. Only Italy and Greece recorded decreases.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "GREECE",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "OECD",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greece",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "6%",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "6.5%",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "March 2024",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "OECD",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "OECD",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greece",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "CALA RISCHIO RECESSIONE, MA FRAGILITA'  Bce:attenti a tensioni geopolitiche",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Cala rischio recessione, ma fragilità Cala il rischio recessione,e nonostante le aspettative di base per un ritorno alla crescita, restano rischi alti per la stabilità finanziaria. Lo rileva la Bce, secondo cui l'andamento economico favorevole degli ultimi mesi ha alimentato aspettative di un'inflazione in linea con l'obiettivo di Francoforte, profilando un \"atterraggio morbido\". Ma i rischi geopolitici aumentano. Tensioni più gravi potrebbero incidere  sulle materie prime energetiche, rialimentare inflazione, minare la fiducia e creare rigidità dei mercati finanziari.",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.7722237,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "CALA RESCHIO RECESSIONE, MA FRAGILITA' Bce:attentive to geopolitical tensions",
        "en_content": "Cala risk recession, but fragility Cala the risk recession, and despite the basic expectations for a return to growth, remain high risks for financial stability. The ECB notes this, according to which the favourable economic trend of recent months has fueled expectations of inflation in line with the Frankfurt objective, proving a \"soft landing\". But geopolitical risks increase. More serious tensions could affect energy raw materials, re-inflation, undermine confidence and create rigidity of financial markets.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CALA RESCHIO RECESSIONE",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "FRAGILITA",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cala",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ECB",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "recent months",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Frankfurt",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DIESELGATE,VOLKSWAGEN RISARCISCE 50 MLN Chiusa la class action con accordo",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=134",
        "content": " Dieselgate,Volkswagen risarcisce 50 mln Si è chiusa con un accordo fra Altroconsumo e Volkswagen la class action avviata dall'associazione di consumatori italiana in relazione al 'Dieselgate'. La casa automobilistica tedesca metterà a disposizione dei proprietari di veicoli comprati fra il 2009 e il 2015, oltre 50 milioni di euro, cioè fino a 1.100 euro per ogni veicolo.  Si conclude così una vicenda giudiziaria iniziata nel 2015 quando l'Agenzia Usa per la protezione del l'ambiente (Usepa) rilevò falsificazioni nelle emissioni dei motori diesel.  ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.8005111,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Dieselgate,Volkswagen compensates 50 mln It is closed with an agreement between Otherconsumption and Volkswagen the class action started by the Italian consumer association in relation to the 'Dieselgate'. The German car company will make available to the owners of vehicles purchased between 2009 and 2015, over 50 million euros, that is up to 1,100 euros for each vehicle. This concludes a judicial event that began in 2015 when the US Agency for the Protection of the Environment (Usepa) found falsifications in the emissions of diesel engines.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Volkswagen",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "50 mln",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Otherconsumption",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volkswagen",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "German",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "between 2009 and 2015",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 50 million euros",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "up to 1,100 euros",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "2015",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the US Agency",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Protection of the Environment",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 482,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Usepa",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI:A G7 UN PIANO SU USO IA E LAVORO \"Sfida impegnativa ma coraggiosa\"",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=126",
        "content": " Meloni:a G7 un piano su uso IA e lavoro Lavoro e Intelligenza artificiale \"sono temi che stanno a cuore a questo governo e che porteremo anche in ambito G7. Stiamo lavorando per lanciare durante la nostra presidenza un piano d'azione sull'uso dell'intelligenza artificiale, particolarmente nel mondo del lavoro\". Così la premier Meloni in un video inviato al Festival del Lavoro a Firenze. \"Una sfida che io considero particolarmente impegnativa,però sono anche convinta che il sistema Italia abbia il coraggio,la visione,la capacità per  occuparsi anche dei temi più difficili\"",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.8059227,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "MELONI:A G7 A FLOOR ON USE IA AND WORK \"Defident but courageous challenge\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni:a G7 a plan on IA use and work Work and Artificial Intelligence \"are themes that are at heart to this government and that we will also bring in the G7 field. We are working to launch an action plan on the use of artificial intelligence during our presidency, particularly in the world of work.\" So premier Meloni in a video sent to the Festival del Lavoro in Florence. \"A challenge that I consider particularly challenging, but I am also convinced that the Italy system has the courage, vision, ability to deal with even the most difficult issues\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "IA",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Work and Artificial Intelligence",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Festival del Lavoro",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Florence",
                "start_char": 366,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "\"L'ITALIA E' CONTRO VIOLAZIONI DIRITTI\" Mattarella alla Sapienza,fuori studenti \"Presidente la invitiamo tra tende\"",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=125",
        "content": " Colle:contro violazioni diritti ovunque \"Quel che penso di quanto avviene a  Gaza l'ho detto pubblicamente\", anche e \"reiterando la richiesta di un immediato cessate il fuoco\". Così il Presidente Mattarella, parlando alla Sapienza, risponde alla lettera degli studenti pro-Gaza che gli chiedevano un incontro \"Per la nostra Repubblica tutte le violazioni dei diritti umani vanno denunciate e contrastate:tutte,ovunque,sempre\", sottolinea. E \"la condanna per la sopraffazione e il rifiuto della  violenza, non cambia a seconda dei territori e degli Stati\".    ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.8132453,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "\"ITALY IS CONTRO VIOLAZIONI DIRITTI\" Mattarella alla Sapienza, besides students \"President we invite you among tents\"",
        "en_content": "Colle:against violations rights everywhere \"What I think about what happens in Gaza I have publicly said\", also and \"returning the request of an immediate ceasefire\". Thus President Mattarella, speaking to Wisdom, responds to the letter of pro-Gaza students who asked him for a meeting \"For our Republic all violations of human rights must be denounced and contrasted: all, wherever, always,\" he emphasizes. And \"the condemnation for overwhelming and rejection of violence, does not change according to territories and states.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "VIOLAZIONI DIRITTI",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "pro-Gaza",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "DL SUPERBONUS,SENATO APPROVA LA FIDUCIA Col voto di FI,ma Tajani:\"Perplessità\"  Il decreto passa ora alla Camera",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=124",
        "content": " Dl Superbonus,Senato approva la fiducia L'Aula del Senato ha approvato la fiducia al Decreto Superbonus anche con il voto di FI. Tajani:molte perplessità,ma non viene meno la fiducia nel governo. Il governo ha posto la questione di fiducia ieri nell'aula di Palazzo Madama dopo il via libera della commissione Finanze.Il testo scade il 28/5 e deve passare in seconda seduta alla Camera. Martedì la commissione aveva votato l' emendamento del governo, col sì di Italia Viva e Forza Italia astenuta.Non ha partecipato al voto Patton (Autonomie). Semaforo verde dunque alla norma \"spalma-crediti\" che li diluisce in 10 anni.",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.8189542,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ With the vote of FI,ma Tajani:\"Perplexity\" The decree now passes to the Chamber",
        "en_content": "Dl Superbonus,Senato approves the trust The Senate Hall has approved the confidence of the Superbonus Decree also with the vote of FI. Tajani:many perplexity, but no less trust in the government. The government placed the question of trust yesterday in the court of Palazzo Madama after the free way of the Finance Committee. The text expires on 28/5 and must pass in second session to the House. On Tuesday the commission had voted the amendment of the government, with the yes of Italy Viva and Forza Italia astenuta. He did not participate in the vote Patton (Autonomie). Green light therefore to the rule \"spalma-crediti\" which dilutes them in 10 years.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Senato",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Senate Hall",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Superbonus Decree",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Madama",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Finance Committee",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 407,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 482,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Patton",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 561,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years",
                "start_char": 648,
                "end_char": 656,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Pd:sarebbe stata occasione chiarezza122 Floridia:Agcom chiara sul duello tv",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=123",
        "content": " Floridia: Agcom chiara sul duello tv Agcom ha evidenziato \"che è necessario coinvolgere tutti i leader ed avere  l'ok almeno della maggioranza per poter procedere con un determinato format. Il messaggio è chiaro: organizzare (e pubblicizzare)un confronto solo a due crea un'evidente disparità\".    Lo scrive la presidente della Vigilanza Barbara Floridia. \"Il confronto-aggiunge-tra i leader è fondamentale per il dibattito democratico,ma le regole devono essere rispettate sempre e comunque.Spetta ora a forze politiche trovare modello idoneo dopo pronuncia Agcom\"",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1715886004.8912525,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "Pd:it would have been occasion clarity122 Floridia:Agcom clear on the duel tv",
        "en_content": "Floridia: Agcom clear on the Agcom duel highlighted \"that it is necessary to involve all the leaders and have the ok at least of the majority in order to proceed with a certain format. The message is clear: organizing (and advertising)a comparison only to two creates an obvious disparity\". The president of the Vigilance Barbara Floridia writes. \"The comparison between the leaders is fundamental to the democratic debate, but the rules must always be respected. It is now up to political forces to find suitable model after pronunciation Agcom\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Floridia",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Floridia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "only to",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Barbara Floridia",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Presente quasi tutto governo russo",
        "date_raw": "May 16, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-16",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Xi-Putin, guerra Ucraina tra i dossier 43esimo bilaterale tra i presidenti di Cina e Russia, a Pechino. Xi Jinping e Putin discutono a porte chiuse di ampliamento dei rapporti economici e commerciali e del futuro della guerra in Ucraina. Per Putin primo viaggio all'estero dall'inizio del quinto mandato. Quasi tutto il governo russo è a Pechino. I due leader hanno rilasciato una dichiarazione congiunta \"sull'approfondimento del partenariato strategico  globale di coordinamento Cina-Russia\", in occasione dei 75anni delle relazioni tra i due Paesi. Poi la cerimonia per la firma di diversi accordi.   ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715886004.9295895,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-16 21:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-16T21.00.04",
        "en_title": "Present almost all Russian government",
        "en_content": "Xi-Putin, Ukraine war between the dossiers 43rd bilateral between the presidents of China and Russia, in Beijing. Xi Jinping and Putin discuss with closed doors the expansion of economic and commercial relations and the future of the war in Ukraine. For Putin first travel abroad from the beginning of the fifth term. Almost all Russian government is in Beijing. The two leaders issued a joint statement \"on the deepening of the global strategic partnership of China-Russia coordination\", on the occasion of the 75 years of relations between the two countries. Then the ceremony for signing several agreements.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Xi-Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "43rd",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi Jinping",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the beginning of the",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifth",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 361,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 75 years",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 549,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    }
]
