[
    {
        "title": "RAID ISRAELE A RAFAH, ALMENO 45 MORTI  ANP:atroce massacro,intervenga Usa",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=151",
        "content": " Raid Israele a Rafah, almeno 45 morti Sarebbero almeno 45 i morti a causa  dell'attacco israeliano al campo  profughi nel nord-ovest di Rafah, nel quartiere di Tal al Sultan.   \"Un altro atroce massacro è stato commesso dalle forze israeliane a Rafah, che finora è costato la vita a 50 persone oltre a decine di feriti, la maggior parte dei quali bambini e donne\", ha detto un portavoce del ministero  della Sanità di Gaza, controllato da Hamas. L'ANP chiede l'intervento degli Usa per \"costringere Israele a fermare questa follia e questo genocidio\".  ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716825604.4346628,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "RAID ISRAELE A RAFAH, ALMENO 45 MORTI ANP:atroce massacre,intervenga Usa",
        "en_content": "Raid Israel at Rafah, at least 45 deaths It would be at least 45 deaths because of the Israeli attack on the refugee camp in the northwest of Rafah, in the district of Tal al Sultan. \"Another atrocious massacre was committed by the Israeli forces in Rafah, which has so far cost 50 people as well as dozens of wounded, most of them children and women,\" said a spokesman for the Gaza Ministry of Health, controlled by Hamas. The ANP calls for US intervention to \"force Israel to stop this madness and genocide.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "45",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 45",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 45",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tal al Sultan",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "50",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Ministry of Health",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ANP",
                "start_char": 428,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 442,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "NETANYAHU: A RAFAH UN TRAGICO INCIDENTE Il premier lo ammette alla Knesset",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=157",
        "content": " Netanyahu: a Rafah un tragico incidente Israele ammette ufficialmente la sua responsabilità per la morte di almeno 45 persone in un attacco contro Rafah. Il raid israeliano a Rafah è stato \"un tragico incidente di cui rammaricarsi\", ha ammesso lo stesso primo ministro  Benyamin Netanyahu, intervenendo alla Knesset.      Dei fatti di Rafah, il premier ne ha parlato durante un incontro con le famiglie degli ostaggi che lo hanno contestato.      ",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716825604.4519017,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "NETANYAHU: A RAFAH AN INCIDENT TRAGIC The premier admits it to Knesset",
        "en_content": "Netanyahu: At Rafah, a tragic accident, Israel officially admits its responsibility for the death of at least 45 people in an attack against Rafah. The Israeli raid on Rafah was \"a tragic incident to regret\", admitted Prime Minister Benyamin Netanyahu, intervening at Knesset. Of the facts of Rafah, the prime minister spoke about it during a meeting with the families of the hostages who challenged him.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "NETANYAHU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "A RAFAH AN INCIDENT TRAGIC",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Knesset",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 45",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benyamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Knesset",
                "start_char": 268,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "STOLTENBERG INSISTE:KIEV HA MANI LEGATE Sulle armi ha diritto ad autodifesa",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=158",
        "content": " Stoltenberg:Kiev ha mani legate su armi \"l'Ucraina ha le mani legate a causa delle restrizioni all'uso delle armi\" fornite dall'Occidente.così il segretario Nato,Stoltenberg,a Sofia.   \"Spetta agli alleati decidere sulle restrizioni\"all'uso delle armi consegnate all'Ucraina, \"questa non è una decisione della Nato,è una decisione dei singoli alleati\"che finora\"hanno preso decisioni diverse\".\"Penso che sia giunto il momento di considerare alcune delle restrizioni\",Kiev \"ha diritto all'autodifesa,ciò include il diritto a colpire obiettivi militari fuori dell'Ucraina\".",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716825604.4575408,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "_ You have the right to self-defense",
        "en_content": "Stoltenberg:Kiev has hands tied on weapons \"Ukraine has hands tied because of the restrictions on the use of weapons\" provided by the West.so Secretary NATO,Stoltenberg, in Sofia. \"It is up to allies to decide on the restrictions\" to the use of weapons delivered to Ukraine, \"this is not a NATO decision, it is a decision of individual allies \"that so far\" have made different decisions.\" \"I think it's time to consider some of the restrictions,\"Kiev \"is entitled to self-defense, which includes the right to strike military targets outside Ukraine.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sofia",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Onu \"turbato\" a Israele: \"Indagine\"",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=156",
        "content": " Onu a Israele: indagine sia trasparente L'Onu chiede a Israele un'indagine \"approfondita e trasparente\" sui civili ucisi a Rafah e di \"adottare misure immediate per proteggere meglio i civili\" Lo ha riferito il coordinatore per il processo di pace in MO,Wennesland. \"Condanno gli attacchi aerei israeliani che hanno colpito le tende degli sfollati, anche se l'Idf ha detto di aver colpito un'istallazione di Hamas e di aver ucciso due militanti del gruppo durante gli attacchi\".\"Sono profondamente turbato della morte di così tanti bambini e donne\".    ",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716825604.4860017,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "Onu \"turbed\" to Israel: Investigation",
        "en_content": "UN to Israel: both transparent investigation The UN asks Israel for an in-depth and transparent investigation into the Ucisian civilians in Rafah and \"to take immediate measures to better protect civilians\" The coordinator for the peace process in MO,Wennesland reported this. \"They condemn Israeli air strikes that hit the displaced tents, although the Idf said he hit a Hamas installation and killed two group militants during the attacks.\" \"I am deeply disturbed by the death of so many children and women.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ucisian",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "MO",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wennesland",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "BORRELL:INORRIDITO DA RAID SU RAFAH",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=154",
        "content": " Borrell: inorridito da attacchi Israele \"Sono inorridito dalle notizie che arrivano da Rafah sugli attacchi israeliani che hanno ucciso decine di sfollati, tra cui bambini piccoli. Condanno questo fatto con la massima fermezza\". Così l'Alto rappresentante Ue Borrell. \"Non esiste un luogo sicuro a Gaza.  Questi attacchi devono cessare immediatamente. Gli ordini della Corte di giustizia e il Diritto internazionale devono essere rispettati da tutte le parti\", sottolinea.    ",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716825604.5051868,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "Borrell: horrified by Israeli attacks \"I am horrified by the news that come from Rafah on Israeli attacks that killed dozens of displaced people, including small children. They condemn this fact with the utmost firmness.\" So the High Representative Ue Borrell. \"There is no safe place in Gaza. These attacks must cease immediately. The orders of the Court of Justice and International Law must be respected by all parties,\" he said.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Borrell",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ue Borrell",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Court of Justice and International Law",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Antisemitismo? Accusa inaccettabile",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=155",
        "content": " M.O,Borrell: inaccettabili accuse a Cpi \"Dobbiamo rispettare il lavoro della Corte penale internazionale,lasciare che decida senza intimidazioni\",invece \"la Corte è stata accusata di antisemitismo,come sempre accade quando qualcosa non piace al governo di Netanyahu.E' inaccettabile,è un'accusa troppo grave da usare in questa occasione\".Così l' Alto Rappresentante Ue, Borrell.  \"Si chiede la soluzione dei 2 Stati,ma nel mentre i coloni occupano più territori in Cisgiordania.Se vogliamo centrare l'obiettivo dobbiamo impegnarci di più:ascoltiamo proposte amici arabi\"",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716825604.5306783,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "Anti-Semitism? Unacceptable charge",
        "en_content": "M.O,Borrell: unacceptable accusations to Cpi \"We must respect the work of the International Criminal Court, let it decide without intimidation\",instead \"the Court was accused of anti-Semitism,as always happens when something does not like the Netanyahu government. It's unacceptable, it's too serious to use on this occasion.\" So the High Representative Ue, Borrell. \"The solution of the 2 States is asked, but in the meantime the settlers occupy more territories in the West Bank. If we want to achieve the goal, we must commit ourselves more: we listen to Arab friends proposals\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "M.O",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Borrell",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Court",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Borrell",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 2 States",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ma Israele: uccisi due terroristi",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Dal%20Mondo&pagina=150",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=152",
        "content": " Israele: a Rafah uccisi due terroristi Nel raid compiuto ieri sera su Rafah, sono stati \"eliminati il terrorista  Yassin Rabia, comandante della leadership di Hamas in Giudea e Samaria (Cisgiordania, ndr),nonché Khaled Nagar un alto funzionario dell'ala di Hamas in Giudea e Samaria\",responsabili della 'pianificazione,finanziamento e realizzazione di attacchi terroristici nella Giudea,Samaria e nello Stato d'Israele Lo afferma l'Idf precisando che il raid \"è stato effettuato nella zona di Tal as Sultan, nel nordovest di Rafah,sulla base di precise informazioni di intelligence\".     ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716825604.5504627,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "But Israel: killed two terrorists",
        "en_content": "Israel: two terrorists killed in Rafah In the raid last night on Rafah, the terrorist Yassin Rabia, commander of Hamas' leadership in Judea and Samaria (Cyssadonia, ed.), as well as Khaled Nagar, a high official of Hamas' wing in Judea and Samaria, responsible for the 'planning, financing and implementation of terrorist attacks in Judea, Samaria and the State of Israel The Idf states that the raid \"was carried out in the Tal as Sultan area, in the northwest of Rafah, on the basis of precise intelligence information\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last night",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yassin Rabia",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Judea",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Samaria",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khaled Nagar",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Judea",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Samaria",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Judea",
                "start_char": 333,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Samaria",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State of Israel",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tal",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 470,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RAFAH, CROSETTO: \"ISRAELE SEMINA ODIO\"  \"Innocenti nulla a che fare con Hamas\"  Poi:da me nessun attacco a Tel Aviv",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=122",
        "content": " M.O,Crosetto:Israele sta seminando odio \"Palestines compressi senza tenere conto delle drammatiche difficoltà,dei diritti di uomini,donne e bambini innocenti che nulla hanno a che fare con Hamas.Questa cosa non è più giustificabile\".Così Crosetto,ministro della Difesa su Sky,sul raid israeliano a Rafah \"Ormai la crisi ha proporzioni difficili da gestire,ho l'impressione che,con questa scelta,Israele stia seminando un odio che coinvolgerà i loro figli e i loro nipoti\",ha continuato il ministro. Poi:\"Mai attaccato Isarele.Non si banalizzi tutto per un titolo ad effetto\". ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716825604.5601752,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": "M.O.Crosetto: Israel is sowing hatred \"Palestines compressed without taking into account the dramatic difficulties, the rights of men, women and innocent children who have nothing to do with Hamas. This is no longer justified.\" So Crosetto, Minister of Defense on Sky, on the Israeli raid to Rafah \"Today the crisis has difficult proportions to manage, I have the impression that, with this choice, Israel is sowing a hatred that will involve their children and their grandchildren\", continued the minister. Then, \"Never attack Isarele. You don't trivialize everything for an effective title.\"",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "M.O.Crosetto",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 299,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isarele",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "MELONI:POSSIBILE MAGGIORANZA DIVERSA UE \"Europa faccia meno cose ma meglio\"",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=120",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=121",
        "content": " Meloni:possibile maggioranza diversa Ue \"Oggi c'é il margine per costruire una maggioranza diversa al parlamento Ue, e per politiche diverse. Se le cose non dovessero andare così, ho già dimostrato che con buon senso l'Italia può fare da capofila su molte politiche\".Così la premier Meloni \"Giù la maschera\"su Rai Radio 1.      La premier ritiene che \"l'Europa debba cambiare nelle proprie priorità.  La sfida è un'Europa che si occupi di molte meno cose rispetto a quanto fatto in questi anni\". \"Si deve tornare a un principio di sussidarietà per cui  l'Europa fa meno cose e le fa meglio\". ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Politics",
        "epoch": 1716825604.5677128,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "MEASURES: IMPROVEMENT OF WORLD \"Europe do fewer things but better\"",
        "en_content": "Meloni: Possible different majority EU \"Today there is the margin to build a different majority in the EU parliament, and for different policies. If things don't have to go like this, I've already shown that with common sense Italy can lead on many policies.\" So premier Meloni \"More the mask\" on Rai Radio 1. The premier believes that \"Europe must change in its priorities. The challenge is a Europe that deals with much less than what has been done in recent years.\" \"We must return to a principle of sussidity so that Europe does less and does better.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai Radio 1",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent years",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "RAID ISRAELE A RAFAH, ALMENO 45 VITTIME Borrell:\"Inorridito,morti tanti bimbi\"  Onu \"turbato\" a Israele: \"Indagine\"",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=150",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716825604.6158564,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "RAID ISRAELE A RAFAH, ALMENO 45 VITTIME Borrell: \"Inorried, so many children\" Onu \"turbed\" to Israel: Investigation",
        "en_content": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "45",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "AL VIA ECOBONUS PER GLI INCENTIVI AUTO  Piattaforma per prenotare dal 3/6",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=132",
        "content": " Mimit, al via ecobonus incentivi auto Pubblicato in Gazzetta Ufficiale il  Dpcm sulla rimodulazione degli incentivi per l'acquisto di veicoli a basse emissioni inquinanti.La nuova piattaforma Ecobonus per prenotare gli incentivi sarà attiva dal 3 giugno alle ore 10. Sul sito saranno disponibili i moduli per chiedere il bonus e le tabelle che riportano i criteri di attribuzione dei contributi. Un miliardo le risorse disponibili per il 2024. Gli incentivi, con rottamazione o senza, sono tarati anche tenendo conto del reddito, in base all'Isee.     ",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716825604.6273365,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "AL VIA ECOBONUS FOR INCENTIVI AUTO Platform to book from 3/6",
        "en_content": "Mimit, via ecobonus auto incentives Published in the Official Journal the Dpcm on the removal of incentives for the purchase of vehicles with low emissions pollutants. The new Ecobonus platform to book incentives will be active from June 3 to 10. On the site will be available the modules to ask for the bonus and the tables that report the criteria of allocation of contributions. One billion available resources for 2024. The incentives, with scrap or without, are also calibrated taking into account the income, according to the Isee.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "AL VIA ECOBONUS",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3/6",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Official Journal the Dpcm",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecobonus",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "June 3 to 10",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "One billion",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Isee",
                "start_char": 532,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "A PARIGI SINNER TORNA A VINCERE",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=260",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716825604.7127833,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "To PARIGI SINNER TORNA TO VINCERE",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "IMPAGNATIELLO:S'E' VOLTATA,L'HO COLPITA \"A pranzo da mamma col corpo in auto\"  Veleno a Giulia per farla abortire",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Prima&pagina=103",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=140",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "First_Page",
        "epoch": 1716825604.7814205,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "_",
        "en_content": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "TAVARES: \"AVANTI ANCHE CON GLI INSULTI\" \"Governo greco fiero per nome Ypsilon\"  Ironizza dopo polemiche con Urso",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=131",
        "content": " Tavares: \"Avanti anche con gli insulti\" \"Nonostante le difficoltà, le critiche e a volte gli insulti andiamo avanti, continuiamo a muoverci e a fare le cose\". Così l'ad di Stellantis, Tavares. \"In Stellantis amiamo le auto, i brand, non ci scusiamo per questo. Anche quando succedono cose negative, non bisogna dimenticare che amiamo tutto questo\",ha detto. \"Credo che il governo greco sarà molto fiero che chiamiamo Ypsilon la nuova Lancia\", ha ironizzato con velato riferimento alla polemica con il ministro Urso sul nome della Alfa Romeo  'Milano', prodotta in Polonia, poi rinominata Junior.     ",
        "ranked": 0,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716825604.7862563,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "TAVARES: \"AWARDS WITH THE INSULTS\" \"Governo Greco fiero per nome Ypsilon\" Ironizza after polemics with Urso",
        "en_content": "Tavares: \"Next even with insults\" \"Despite the difficulties, criticisms and sometimes insults we go on, we keep moving and doing things.\" So Stellantis' ad, Tavares. \"In Stellantis we love cars, brands, we do not apologize for this. Even when negative things happen, we must not forget that we love all this,\" he said. \"I believe that the Greek government will be very proud that we call Ypsilon the new Lancia\", ironed with veiled reference to the controversy with the minister Urso on the name of the Alfa Romeo 'Milano', produced in Poland, then renamed Junior.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "INSULTS",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Greco fiero",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Urso",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Stellantis",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tavares",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stellantis",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Greek",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 344,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ypsilon",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lancia",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Urso",
                "start_char": 479,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Alfa Romeo 'Milano'",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 542,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nota sugli indici di Borsa",
        "date_raw": "May 27, 2024",
        "date": "2024-05-27",
        "url": "http://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?categoria=Politica&pagina=130",
        "news_url": "https://www.servizitelevideo.rai.it/televideo/pub/solotesto.jsp?pagina=139",
        "content": " Nota sugli indici di Borsa Televideo Le informazioni di Televideo sugli indici e i dati delle Borse italiane ed estere sono in fase di ristrutturazione editoriale.      Ciò sta comportando il non aggiornamento nelle relative pagine.   Ci scusiamo con i lettori per il disservizio.     ",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Economics",
        "epoch": 1716825604.8293612,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "Televideo",
        "local_time": "2024-05-27 18:00:04",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-27T18.00.04",
        "en_title": "Note on stock exchange indices",
        "en_content": "Note on Stock Exchange Indexes Televideo Televideo's information on indices and data from Italian and foreign exchanges is being refurbished. This is implying the non-updating in the relevant pages. We apologize to readers for disservice.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    }
]
