[
    {
        "title": "Donald Trump: Das letzte Gefecht des Verteidigers – New Yorker Staranwalt Todd Blanche kämpft für Freispruch",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 08:44:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/donald-trump-das-letzte-gefecht-des-verteidigers-new-yorker-staranwalt-todd-blanche-kaempft-fuer-freispruch-a-dcaddd89-84e8-4d6a-8c37-ba6687d7a4a1#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Der New Yorker Strafprozess gegen Donald Trump geht ins Finale. Anwalt Todd Blanche hat alles versucht, um Trumps Freispruch zu bewirken. Doch vieles ist ihm misslungen. Nun hofft er auf wenigstens einen abtrünnigen Geschworenen.",
        "content": "Alles oder nichts: Verteidiger Todd Blanche mit seinem Mandanten Donald Trump am New Yorker Anklagetisch",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447609.9372313,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.09",
        "en_title": "Donald Trump: The Last Battle of the Defender – New York Star Attorney Todd Blanche fights for acquittal",
        "en_content": "Everything or nothing: Defend Todd Blanche with his client Donald Trump at the New York indictment table",
        "en_subtitle": "The New York criminal trial against Donald Trump goes to the final. Attorney Todd Blanche tried everything to bring Trump's release. But a lot of things have happened to him. Now he hopes for at least one disgusting jury.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Last Battle of the Defender – New York Star",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Todd Blanche",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Todd Blanche",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least one",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Todd Blanche",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Palästina als Staat anerkennen: Israel ruft Botschafter aus Norwegen und Irland zurück",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 12:32:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/palaestina-als-staat-anerkennen-israel-ruft-botschafter-aus-norwegen-und-irland-zurueck-a-245f7167-fcaa-4a2c-9e53-34cc4ce7437f#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Norwegen, Irland und Spanien werden Palästina als Staat anerkennen. Der Schritt erzürnt Israel: Außenminister Katz ruft nun die israelischen Botschafter aus Oslo und Dublin zurück – und warnt Spanien vor ähnlichen Konsequenzen.",
        "content": "Der israelische Außenminister Israel Katz ruft die Botschafter in Oslo und Dublin zurück. Der Schritt folgt auf die Ankündigung Irlands und Norwegens, . »Ich sende eine klare und unmissverständliche Botschaft an  und : Israel wird gegenüber denjenigen, die seine Souveränität untergraben und seine Sicherheit gefährden, nicht schweigen«, schrieb er in einem Post auf X.Die Entscheidung, Palästina als Staat anzuerkennen, sei eine Botschaft an die Palästinenser und die Welt, dass Terrorismus sich auszahle, fügte er hinzu. »Diese Länder«, schrieb Katz weiter, haben sich mit dem Schritt »dafür entschieden, die  und  zu belohnen«. Sollte  auf Norwegen und Irland folgen, werde »ein ähnlicher Schritt« unternommen.Norwegens Ministerpräsident Jonas Gahr Støre hatte am Mittwochmorgen mitgeteilt, sein Land werde am 28. Mai Palästina als Staat anerkennen. Die irische Regierung hatte vergangene Woche bereits erklärt, dass sie »sicherlich« bis Monatsende einen Palästinenserstaat anerkennen werde. Inzwischen hat auch Madrid bestätigt, dass es Palästina anerkennen will.Die Anerkennung sei »Ausdruck einer uneingeschränkten Unterstützung für eine Zweistaatenlösung, des einzig glaubwürdigen Wegs zu Frieden und Sicherheit für Israel, Palästina und deren Völker«, sagte der irische Regierungschef Simon Harris.»Die Palästinenser haben ein grundlegendes, unabhängiges Recht auf einen eigenen Staat. Sowohl Israelis als auch Palästinenser haben das Recht, in Frieden in getrennten Staaten zu leben. Es kann keinen Frieden im Nahen Osten ohne eine Zweistaatenlösung geben«, hieß es in einer Pressemitteilung der norwegischen Regierung.Schweden hatte Palästina bereits vor zehn Jahren als Staat anerkannt. Kritiker bemängeln jedoch, den Palästinensergebieten mangele es an wichtigen Kriterien für einen solchen Schritt. Beispielsweise ist die Grenze zwischen Israel und den Palästinensern weiter strittig. Das gilt auch für den politischen Status von Ostjerusalem.Die Mehrheit der Mitgliedstaaten der Vereinten Nationen erkennt Palästina inzwischen als Staat an. Das gilt jedoch nicht für die wichtigsten westlichen Nationen wie die  und die Mehrzahl der EU-Staaten, darunter ,  und . Auch Deutschland setzt sich für eine Zweistaatenlösung ein, sieht die Anerkennung Palästinas jedoch als Ergebnis direkter Verhandlungen zwischen den Konfliktparteien.Sowohl die im  regierende Palästinensische Autonomiebehörde (PA) als auch die Hamas, die im  an der Macht ist, begrüßten die geplante Anerkennung eines palästinensischen Staates durch Irland, Spanien und Norwegen. Es handele sich um einen »wichtigen Schritt zur Bekräftigung unseres Rechts auf Land und zur Gründung eines palästinensischen Staates mit Jerusalem als Hauptstadt«, erklärte die Hamas. Ein hochrangiger Hamas-Vertreter sagte der Nachrichtenagentur AFP, die geplanten Anerkennungen seien dem »mutigen Widerstand« der Palästinenser zu verdanken.Die Anerkennung Palästinas durch die drei europäischen Länder erfolgt mehr als sieben Monate nach dem Terrorangriff der Hamas auf Israel. Hamas-Kämpfer ermordeten am 7. Oktober 2023 etwa 1140 Menschen. Rund 250 weitere Menschen wurden als Geiseln in den Gazastreifen verschleppt. Als Reaktion geht Israel seither massiv militärisch im Gazastreifen vor. Dabei wurden nach Angaben des von der Hamas kontrollierten Gesundheitsministeriums, die sich nicht unabhängig überprüfen lassen, mehr als 35.000 Menschen getötet.»Israel wird gegenüber denjenigen, die seine Souveränität untergraben und seine Sicherheit gefährden, nicht schweigen«, so Außenminister Israel Katz",
        "ranked": 17,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447610.0273442,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.10",
        "en_title": "Recognising Palestine as a State: Israel calls ambassadors from Norway and Ireland back",
        "en_content": "Israeli Foreign Minister Israel Katz calls back the ambassadors in Oslo and Dublin. The step follows the announcement of Ireland and Norway, \"I send a clear and unequivocal message and: Israel will not remain silent to those who undermine its sovereignty and endanger its security,\" he wrote in a post on X.The decision to recognise Palestine as a state, being a message to the Palestinians and the world that terrorism pay out, he added. “These countries”, Katz continued to write, have decided to reward them with the step “for that”. If Norway and Ireland follow, \"a similar step\" will be taken.Norway's Prime Minister Jonas Gahr Støre had informed on Wednesday morning that his country will be on 28. May acknowledge Palestine as a state. The Irish Government had already declared last week that it would \"surely\" recognise a Palestinian state by the end of the month. In the meantime, Madrid has also confirmed that it wants to acknowledge Palestine. Recognition is \"expression of unrestricted support for a two-state solution, the only credible path to peace and security for Israel, Palestine and its peoples\", said Irish head of government, Simon Harris. \"The Palestinians have a fundamental, independent right to their own state. Both Israelis and Palestinians have the right to live in peace in separate states. There can be no peace in the Middle East without a two-state solution,\" said in a press release by the Norwegian government.Sweden had already recognized Palestine as a state ten years ago. However, critics complain that the Palestinian territories lack important criteria for such a step. For example, the border between Israel and the Palestinians is still controversial. This also applies to the political status of East Jerusalem.The majority of the United Nations Member States now recognise Palestine as a state. However, this does not apply to the most important Western nations, such as the ones and most of the EU countries, including, and Germany is also committed to a two-state solution, but the recognition of Palestine as a result of direct negotiations between the conflict parties. It was a \"important step towards affirming our right to land and establishing a Palestinian state with Jerusalem as capital,\" Hamas said. A high-ranking Hamas representative told the AFP news agency that the planned recognitions were due to the \"mutual resistance\" of the Palestinians.The recognition of Palestine by the three European countries takes place more than seven months after the Hamas terrorist attack on Israel. Hamas fighters murdered about 1140 people on 7 October 2023. Around 250 more people were dragged into the Gaza Strip as hostages. In response, Israel has been heavily military in the Gaza Strip since then. According to the Hamas-controlled Ministry of Health, which cannot be independently checked, more than 35,000 people were killed. \"Israel will not remain silent to those who undermine his sovereignty and endanger his security,\" said Foreign Minister Israel Katz",
        "en_subtitle": "Norway, Ireland and Spain will recognise Palestine as a state. Israel: Foreign Minister Katz now calls back the Israeli ambassadors from Oslo and Dublin – and warns Spain against similar consequences.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Oslo",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel Katz",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Oslo",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dublin",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "X.The",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 333,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 540,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 551,
                "end_char": 558,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 598,
                "end_char": 604,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jonas Gahr Støre",
                "start_char": 622,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wednesday",
                "start_char": 655,
                "end_char": 664,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "morning",
                "start_char": 665,
                "end_char": 672,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "28",
                "start_char": 701,
                "end_char": 703,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "May",
                "start_char": 705,
                "end_char": 708,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 721,
                "end_char": 730,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Irish Government",
                "start_char": 743,
                "end_char": 763,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last week",
                "start_char": 785,
                "end_char": 794,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 830,
                "end_char": 841,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of the month",
                "start_char": 851,
                "end_char": 871,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 890,
                "end_char": 896,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 945,
                "end_char": 954,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Recognition",
                "start_char": 956,
                "end_char": 967,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1013,
                "end_char": 1016,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1082,
                "end_char": 1088,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 1090,
                "end_char": 1099,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Irish",
                "start_char": 1123,
                "end_char": 1128,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Simon Harris",
                "start_char": 1149,
                "end_char": 1161,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 1168,
                "end_char": 1180,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israelis",
                "start_char": 1244,
                "end_char": 1252,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 1257,
                "end_char": 1269,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 1347,
                "end_char": 1362,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1373,
                "end_char": 1376,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norwegian",
                "start_char": 1425,
                "end_char": 1434,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sweden",
                "start_char": 1446,
                "end_char": 1452,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 1476,
                "end_char": 1485,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ten years ago",
                "start_char": 1497,
                "end_char": 1510,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 1547,
                "end_char": 1558,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1644,
                "end_char": 1650,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 1659,
                "end_char": 1671,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 1741,
                "end_char": 1755,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Nations",
                "start_char": 1776,
                "end_char": 1790,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 1819,
                "end_char": 1828,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western",
                "start_char": 1892,
                "end_char": 1899,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 1942,
                "end_char": 1944,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 1971,
                "end_char": 1978,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 2002,
                "end_char": 2005,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 2045,
                "end_char": 2054,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 2200,
                "end_char": 2211,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 2223,
                "end_char": 2232,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 2246,
                "end_char": 2251,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 2273,
                "end_char": 2278,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AFP",
                "start_char": 2303,
                "end_char": 2306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 2392,
                "end_char": 2404,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 2424,
                "end_char": 2433,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 2441,
                "end_char": 2446,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 2447,
                "end_char": 2455,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than seven months",
                "start_char": 2478,
                "end_char": 2500,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 2511,
                "end_char": 2516,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2537,
                "end_char": 2543,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 2545,
                "end_char": 2550,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "about 1140",
                "start_char": 2569,
                "end_char": 2579,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "7 October 2023",
                "start_char": 2590,
                "end_char": 2604,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Around 250",
                "start_char": 2606,
                "end_char": 2616,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 2647,
                "end_char": 2661,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2688,
                "end_char": 2694,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 2724,
                "end_char": 2738,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 2768,
                "end_char": 2773,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ministry of Health",
                "start_char": 2785,
                "end_char": 2803,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 35,000",
                "start_char": 2844,
                "end_char": 2860,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2882,
                "end_char": 2888,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel Katz",
                "start_char": 3001,
                "end_char": 3012,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Litauen und Finnland verlangen Erklärung von Russland – geplante Ausweitung der Seegrenze",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 15:41:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/litauen-und-finnland-verlangen-erklaerung-von-russland-geplante-ausweitung-der-seegrenze-a-2369f186-6f91-46ec-9455-d53230d83e30#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Russland plant offenbar, seine Seegebiete in litauische und finnische Gewässer zu erweitern. Vilnius hat nun den russischen Vertreter einbestellt. Verteidigungsminister Pistorius spricht von »hybrider Kriegsführung«.",
        "content": "Angesichts umstrittener russischer Pläne, die Seegrenzen in litauische und finnische Gewässer auszudehnen, hat  den russischen Vertreter einbestellt. Das Außenministerium in Vilnius verlangte eine vollständige Erklärung von . Der litauische Außenminister Gabrielius Landsbergis rief zudem  und EU zu einer entschlossenen Reaktion auf.Russland hat in Vilnius keinen Botschafter mehr, nachdem Litauen im April 2022 den damaligen Botschafter wegen Gräueltaten der russischen Armee im ukrainischen Butscha ausgewiesen und die diplomatischen Beziehungen zu Russland herabgestuft hatte.Die nun erfolgte Einbestellung ist eine Reaktion auf einen am Dienstag veröffentlichten Beschlussentwurf des russischen Verteidigungsministeriums, die russischen Seegebiete bis in die Gewässer der Nato- und EU-Mitglieder Litauen und  auszuweiten.Durch eine einseitig vorgenommene, neue Festlegung der geografischen Koordinaten der russischen Seegrenze würden litauische und finnische Gebiete in der  Russland zugeschlagen. Konkret würden dem Dokument zufolge die Seegrenzen der westrussischen Exklave  und des östlichen Finnischen Meerbusens verschoben.Die finnische Außenministerin Elina Valtonen sagte dazu, ihre Regierung verfolge die Lage. »Wir haben keinerlei offizielle Informationen darüber, was Russland plant«, fügte sie hinzu. Zugleich hob die finnische Chefdiplomatin hervor, dass die Russische Föderation ebenfalls der -Konvention zu Seegrenzen beigetreten sei. »Wir erwarten nur, dass Russland die Konvention achtet«, sagte Valtonen.Zuvor hatte die finnische Außenministerin im Onlinedienst X geschrieben: »Es sollte nicht vergessen werden, dass das Stiften von Verwirrung auch hybrider Einfluss ist. Finnland wird sich nicht verwirren lassen.« Finnlands Präsident Alexander Stubb, der den außenpolitischen Kurs des Landes festlegt, , Russland stehe »in der Angelegenheit nicht mit Finnland im Kontakt«.Valtonens Interpretation einer hybriden Konfliktführung Russlands folgte auch ihr litauischer Kollege. »Ein weiterer russischer hybrider Einsatz läuft, dieses Mal wird versucht, Furcht, Unsicherheit und Zweifel hinsichtlich ihrer Intentionen in der Ostsee zu verbreiten«, . Dies sei »eine offensichtliche Eskalation gegen die Nato und die EU und dem muss mit einer angemessen entschlossenen Antwort begegnet werden«.Kremlsprecher Dmitrij Peskow sagte am Mittwoch vor Journalisten, es sei »nichts Politisches« an dem Dokument, »auch wenn die politische Lage sich seit 1985 sehr stark verändert« habe. In jenem Jahr waren die aktuellen Grenzen der russischen Seegebiete festgelegt worden.»Man kann den Grad der Konfrontation sehen, wie er derzeit ist, insbesondere in der Ostseeregion«, fügte der Sprecher von Russlands Staatschef  hinzu. »Dies erfordert, dass die geeigneten Einrichtungen die geeigneten Maßnahmen ergreifen, um unsere Sicherheit sicherzustellen.«Wie die Nachrichtenagentur Reuters berichtet, hat Russland das umstrittene Dokument inzwischen aus einem offiziellen Portal gelöscht. »Der Entwurf ist gelöscht«, hieß es lediglich.Das Verteidigungsministerium in Moskau erklärte, die Neufestlegung der russischen Seegrenzen sei notwendig, weil die gegenwärtigen Koordinaten »nicht vollständig der aktuellen geografischen Lage entsprechen«. Die Änderungen sollen demnach im Januar 2025 in Kraft treten.Bundesverteidigungsminister Boris Pistorius (SPD) bezeichnete die Verwirrung über das Grenzprojekt als Teil der hybriden Kriegsführung des Kreml. »Wie auch immer das jetzt war oder tatsächlich ist, es scheint ein weiteres Beispiel zu sein für die durchaus perfide Art der hybriden Kriegsführung, die Putin betreibt. Verunsicherung, Provokation, Rücknahme, Relativierung, den Spalt dazwischentreiben, Drohen – also immer das ganze Repertoire«, sagte Pistorius bei einem Besuch in Litauen.Schiff der litauischen Küstenwache",
        "ranked": 14,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447610.0563257,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.10",
        "en_title": "Lithuania and Finland require declaration from Russia – planned extension of the sea boundary",
        "en_content": "In view of controversial Russian plans to extend the sea borders in Lithuanian and Finnish waters, the Russian representative has appointed. The Lithuanian Foreign Minister Gabrielius Landsbergis also called for a determined response to the EU.Russia has no more ambassador in Vilnius, after Lithuania in April 2022 had denounced the then ambassador for atrocities of the Russian army in the Ukrainian buta and had reduced diplomatic relations with Russia. According to the document, the sea borders of the western Russian exclave and the eastern Finnish seabus would be postponed.The Finnish Foreign Minister Elina Valtonen said that her government was following the situation. \"We have no official information about what Russia is planning\", she added. At the same time, the Finnish chief diplomat pointed out that the Russian Federation had also joined the maritime convention. \"We only expect Russia to respect the convention,\" said Valtonen. Previously, the Finnish Foreign Minister wrote in the online service X: \"It should not be forgotten that the pen of confusion is also hybrid. Finland will not be confused.\" Finland’s President Alexander Stubb, who sets the country’s foreign policy course, , Russia is “not in contact with Finland”.Valtonen’s interpretation of a hybrid conflict management of Russia also followed her Lithuanian colleague. \"Another Russian hybrid mission is running, this time it is attempting to spread fear, uncertainty and doubts in terms of its intentions in the Baltic Sea,\" \"This is an obvious escalation against the Nato and the EU and must be met with an adequately determined response\". In that year the current borders of the Russian sea areas were established. \"One can see the degree of confrontation as it is currently, especially in the Baltic Sea region\", added the spokesman of Russia's Head of State. “This requires the appropriate facilities to take appropriate measures to ensure our security.” As the news agency Reuters reports, Russia has deleted the controversial document from an official portal. \"The draft is erased\", it was merely said.The Ministry of Defense in Moscow stated that the redefinition of the Russian sea borders was necessary because the current coordinates \"not fully correspond to the current geographic situation\". The amendments should therefore enter into force in January 2025.Federal Defense Minister Boris Pistorius (SPD) described the confusion about the border project as part of the hybrid warfare of the Kremlin. \"As always this was or is, it seems to be another example of the quite perfidal type of hybrid warfare that Putin operates. Insecurity, provocation, withdrawal, relativization, the gap between them, threats – that is, always the whole repertoire”, said Pistorius during a visit to Lithuania.",
        "en_subtitle": "Russia apparently plans to expand its sea areas in Lithuanian and Finnish waters. Vilnius has now appointed the Russian representative. Minister of Defence Pistorius speaks of “hybrid warfare”.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lithuania",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finland",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuanian",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finnish",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vilnius",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defence Pistorius",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuanian",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finnish",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuanian",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gabrielius Landsbergis",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vilnius",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuania",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "April 2022",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 515,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finnish",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 554,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finnish",
                "start_char": 585,
                "end_char": 592,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elina Valtonen",
                "start_char": 610,
                "end_char": 624,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 723,
                "end_char": 729,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finnish",
                "start_char": 777,
                "end_char": 784,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Federation",
                "start_char": 817,
                "end_char": 839,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 897,
                "end_char": 903,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Valtonen",
                "start_char": 937,
                "end_char": 945,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finnish",
                "start_char": 963,
                "end_char": 970,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finland",
                "start_char": 1089,
                "end_char": 1096,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finland",
                "start_char": 1120,
                "end_char": 1127,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexander Stubb",
                "start_char": 1140,
                "end_char": 1155,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1205,
                "end_char": 1211,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Valtonen",
                "start_char": 1245,
                "end_char": 1253,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1306,
                "end_char": 1312,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuanian",
                "start_char": 1331,
                "end_char": 1341,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1362,
                "end_char": 1369,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Baltic Sea",
                "start_char": 1493,
                "end_char": 1507,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nato",
                "start_char": 1553,
                "end_char": 1557,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 1566,
                "end_char": 1568,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "that year",
                "start_char": 1629,
                "end_char": 1638,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1666,
                "end_char": 1673,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Baltic Sea",
                "start_char": 1781,
                "end_char": 1791,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1824,
                "end_char": 1830,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 1841,
                "end_char": 1846,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Reuters",
                "start_char": 1963,
                "end_char": 1970,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1980,
                "end_char": 1986,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of Defense",
                "start_char": 2093,
                "end_char": 2116,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 2120,
                "end_char": 2126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 2163,
                "end_char": 2170,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "January",
                "start_char": 2341,
                "end_char": 2348,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 2362,
                "end_char": 2369,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boris Pistorius",
                "start_char": 2379,
                "end_char": 2394,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "SPD",
                "start_char": 2396,
                "end_char": 2399,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 2487,
                "end_char": 2494,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 2604,
                "end_char": 2609,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pistorius",
                "start_char": 2749,
                "end_char": 2758,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuania",
                "start_char": 2777,
                "end_char": 2786,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Palästina als Staat anerkennen: Der Palästina-Coup von Pedro Sánchez",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 15:36:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/palaestina-als-staat-anerkennen-der-palaestina-coup-von-pedro-sanchez-a-cdf5d7ea-2431-47fb-8bf2-e3883749438e#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Spanien, Irland und Norwegen verkünden beinahe gleichzeitig, Palästina als Staat anzuerkennen. Eingefädelt hat das der spanische Ministerpräsident. Das Timing kurz vor der Europawahl ist kein Zufall.",
        "content": "Spaniens Ministerpräsident Pedro Sánchez: Auch innenpolitische Gründe",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447610.0851424,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.10",
        "en_title": "Recognising Palestine as State: The Palestine Coup of Pedro Sánchez",
        "en_content": "Spain's Prime Minister Pedro Sánchez: Also domestic reasons",
        "en_subtitle": "Spain, Ireland and Norway are almost at the same time proclaiming Palestine as a state. This is the Spanish Prime Minister. The timing just before the European elections is no coincidence.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Sánchez",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Sánchez",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Taiwan: Zehntausende demonstrieren gegen umstrittene Parlamentsreform",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 11:04:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/taiwan-zehntausende-demonstrieren-gegen-umstrittene-parlamentsreform-a-b09db6b1-e7ed-4a09-93ce-777735fd4912#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Zehntausende Demonstranten sind William Lai am Tag nach seinem Amtseid in Taipeh beigesprungen. Sie wollen eine Parlamentsreform seiner chinafreundlichen Gegner verhindern. Diese würde Taiwans Demokratie umbauen.",
        "content": "Protestierende auf der East Qingdao Road vor dem Parlament in Taipeh: Sorge um die Demokratie",
        "ranked": 18,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447610.1032114,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.10",
        "en_title": "Taiwan: Tens of thousands demonstrate against controversial parliamentary reform",
        "en_content": "Protestant on East Qingdao Road in front of Parliament in Taipeh: concern for democracy",
        "en_subtitle": "Tens of thousands of demonstrators joined William Lai on the day after his oath in Taipeh. They want to prevent a parliamentary reform of their China-friendly opponents. This would transform Taiwan's democracy.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tens of thousands",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tens of thousands",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "William Lai",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taipeh",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Protestant",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Qingdao Road",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Taipeh",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Gazastreifen: Güter erreichen Menschen kaum über provisorische Anlegestelle",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 08:04:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/gazastreifen-gueter-erreichen-menschen-kaum-ueber-provisorische-anlegestelle-a-32cbfa79-6a20-4e0e-8b42-4f960842cc53#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Die Situation in Gaza verschlechtert sich, bei der Verteilung der Hilfen gibt es Probleme. Güter kommen über die provisorische Anlegestelle derzeit kaum bei den Menschen an.",
        "content": "Die US-Regierung hat sich gegen Kritik an der schleppenden Verteilung von Hilfsgütern über eine provisorische Anlegestelle des US-Militärs in den umkämpften  verteidigt. »Man darf auch nicht vergessen, dass es sich um ein Kampfgebiet und eine komplexe Operation handelt«, sagte -Sprecher Pat Ryder. Man arbeite etwa daran, alternative Routen für den Transport der Hilfsgüter an Land auszumachen. Ryder betonte, dass das US-Militär an der Verteilung der Lieferungen im Gazastreifen nicht beteiligt sei.Die humanitäre Lage in Gaza verschlechtert sich derzeit massiv. Die -Lager in Rafah laufen offenbar leer, wo rund 400.000 Menschen ausharren. Hier soll die Verteilung der Hilfsgüter derzeit aus Sicherheitsgründen zu gefährlich sein.Abeer Etefa, Sprecher des Uno-Welternährungsprogramms, warnt, man stehe in Gaza mit der Hilfe »nahe am Kollaps«.Uno-Sprecher Stéphane Dujarric zufolge verließen am Samstag 16 Lastwagen den schwimmenden Pier. »Aber elf dieser Lastwagen schafften es nie bis zum Lagerhaus. An verschiedenen Stellen auf dem Weg hatten Menschenmassen die Lastwagen angehalten«, so Dujarric. Diese Lastwagen seien durch Gebiete gefahren, in denen es keine Hilfe gegeben habe. Daher hätten sich die Menschen genommen, was sie konnten. Seit Samstag seien keine neuen Lastwagen mehr auf dem schwimmenden Pier angekommen. Pentagon-Sprecher Ryder sagte ebenfalls, dass einige Lastwagen »abgefangen« worden seien.Das US-Zentralkommando Centcom hatte zuvor mitgeteilt, dass über den provisorischen Hafen bisher 569 Tonnen Hilfsgüter an der Anlegestelle in Gaza angekommen seien. Das entspreche auf Basis früherer Hilfslieferungen in den Küstenstreifen etwa 25 Lastwagenladungen, schrieb die »Times of Israel«.Pentagon-Sprecher Ryder betonte, dass es sich um Hilfsgüter handele, die noch weiterverteilt werden müssten. Auf die Frage, ob davon auch schon Güter an die Menschen im Gazastreifen ausgeliefert worden seien, sagte er: »Mit Stand heute – ich glaube nicht.« Die US-Regierung gehe davon aus, dass die Hilfe in den kommenden Tagen verteilt werde, sofern die Bedingungen es zuließen. Der Transport sei am Dienstag wieder aufgenommen worden.Die provisorische Anlage war Ende vergangener Woche fertiggestellt worden. Frachter bringen dabei Hilfslieferungen von Zypern aus zunächst zu einer schwimmenden Plattform einige Kilometer vor der Küste des Gazastreifens. Die Güter werden dort auf kleinere Schiffe verladen, die näher an die Küste heranfahren können. Diese legen dann mit den Lkw-Ladungen an dem an der Küste befestigten temporären Pier an.Dort werden die Hilfslieferungen von Hilfsorganisationen entgegengenommen und verteilt. Das Pentagon schätzte, dass über den Hafen zunächst etwa 90 Lkw-Ladungen pro Tag in den Gazastreifen gelangen könnten. Zu einem späteren Zeitpunkt erwarte man bis zu 150 Lkw-Ladungen täglich, hieß es vergangene Woche.Lastwagen mit Hilfsgütern in Gaza (Archivfoto)",
        "ranked": 20,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447610.1427872,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.10",
        "en_title": "Gaza Strip: Goods hardly reach people over temporary dock",
        "en_content": "The U.S. government has defended itself against criticism of the dragging distribution of supplies via a provisional dock of the U.S. military in the battles. \"One must also remember that it is a battle area and a complex operation,\" said - spokesman Pat Ryder. For example, one is working on making alternative routes for the transport of the auxiliary goods to land. Ryder stressed that the US military was not involved in the distribution of supplies in the Gaza Strip.The humanitarian situation in Gaza is currently severely deteriorating. The camps in Rafah seem to run empty, where about 400,000 people stand out. But Etefa, spokesman for the Uno World Food Programme, warns that we are standing in Gaza with the help of \"near the collapse\". According to Uno spokesman Stéphane Dujarric, 16 trucks left the floating pier on Saturday. \"But eleven of these trucks never made it to the warehouse. In various places on the way, crowds of people stopped the trucks,\" said Dujarric. These trucks were driven by areas where there was no help. Therefore, people would have taken what they could. No new trucks have arrived on the floating pier since Saturday. Pentagon spokesman Ryder also said that some trucks had been \"absorbed\".The US Central Command Centcom had previously informed that 569 tons of supplies had arrived at the dock in Gaza via the provisional port. Based on previous aid deliveries in the coasts, this corresponds to about 25 truckloads, wrote the \"Times of Israel\".Pentagon spokesman Ryder emphasised that it was a matter of auxiliary goods that would have to be redistributed. On the question of whether goods had already been delivered to the people in the Gaza Strip, he said: \"With a stand today – I don't think so.\" The U.S. government assumes that the aid will be distributed in the coming days, provided the conditions permit. Transport was resumed on Tuesday.The temporary facility was completed at the end of last week. Freighters bring aid deliveries from Cyprus to a floating platform a few kilometers off the coast of the Gaza Strip. The goods will be loaded onto smaller ships that can approach the coast. They then attach with the truck loads to the temporary pier attached to the coast.The auxiliary supplies are received and distributed by aid organisations. The Pentagon estimated that about 90 truckloads per day could reach the Gaza Strip via the port. At a later stage, up to 150 truckloads are expected daily, it was said last week.",
        "en_subtitle": "The situation in Gaza is deteriorating and there are problems in the distribution of aid. Goods are currently barely arriving at people via the temporary dock.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pat Ryder",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ryder",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 557,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 400,000",
                "start_char": 588,
                "end_char": 601,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Etefa",
                "start_char": 624,
                "end_char": 629,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Uno World Food Programme",
                "start_char": 645,
                "end_char": 673,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 705,
                "end_char": 709,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Uno",
                "start_char": 761,
                "end_char": 764,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Stéphane Dujarric",
                "start_char": 775,
                "end_char": 792,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "16",
                "start_char": 794,
                "end_char": 796,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 830,
                "end_char": 838,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "eleven",
                "start_char": 845,
                "end_char": 851,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dujarric",
                "start_char": 973,
                "end_char": 981,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 1148,
                "end_char": 1156,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 1158,
                "end_char": 1166,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ryder",
                "start_char": 1177,
                "end_char": 1182,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The US Central Command Centcom",
                "start_char": 1230,
                "end_char": 1260,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "569 tons",
                "start_char": 1290,
                "end_char": 1298,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1338,
                "end_char": 1342,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 25",
                "start_char": 1437,
                "end_char": 1445,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 1486,
                "end_char": 1494,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ryder",
                "start_char": 1505,
                "end_char": 1510,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 1676,
                "end_char": 1690,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 1715,
                "end_char": 1720,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 1746,
                "end_char": 1750,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming days",
                "start_char": 1806,
                "end_char": 1821,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 1880,
                "end_char": 1887,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of last week",
                "start_char": 1928,
                "end_char": 1948,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cyprus",
                "start_char": 1987,
                "end_char": 1993,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few kilometers",
                "start_char": 2017,
                "end_char": 2033,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 2051,
                "end_char": 2065,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 2300,
                "end_char": 2308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "about 90",
                "start_char": 2324,
                "end_char": 2332,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 2364,
                "end_char": 2378,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "150",
                "start_char": 2417,
                "end_char": 2420,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 2445,
                "end_char": 2450,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "last week",
                "start_char": 2464,
                "end_char": 2473,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "IStGH zu Israel und Hamas: »Die Kritik am Strafgerichtshof ist vor allem politisch motiviert«",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 16:35:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/istgh-zu-israel-und-hamas-die-kritik-am-strafgerichtshof-ist-vor-allem-politisch-motiviert-a-30b8a0b7-8fd2-4ce7-adca-29abc3ad7f96#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Wegen eines möglichen Haftbefehls gegen Netanyahu muss sich der IStGH kritische Fragen gefallen lassen. Auch wird in Zweifel gezogen, ob die Behörde in Den Haag überhaupt zuständig ist. Völkerrechtler Talmon erklärt, was das bedeutet.",
        "content": "Zerstörung in Chan Junis im Süden des Gazastreifens",
        "ranked": 13,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447610.1960332,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.10",
        "en_title": "IStGH on Israel and Hamas: \"The criticism of the Criminal Court is primarily politically motivated\"",
        "en_content": "Destruction in Chan Junis in the South of the Gaza Strip",
        "en_subtitle": "Because of a possible arrest warrant against Netanyahu, the ICC must be pleased with critical questions. It is also in doubt whether the authority in The Hague is responsible at all. International ruler Talmon explains what that means.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ICC",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Hague",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Talmon",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chan Junis",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israel und Palästina: Norwegen wird Palästina als Staat anerkennen",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 08:52:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/israel-und-palaestina-norwegen-wird-palaestina-als-staat-anerkennen-a-146c6e9e-96e3-4b4b-abf6-dd009539e216#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Norwegen macht seine Ankündigung wahr und will offiziell einen Palästinenserstaat anerkennen. Offenbar wollen Irland und Spanien folgen. Israel sieht in dem Schritt eine »Belohnung des Terrorismus«.",
        "content": " wird Palästina als Staat anerkennen. Die Anerkennung werde zum 28. Mai erfolgen, teilte der norwegische Ministerpräsident Jonas Gahr Støre am Mittwochmorgen mit.Auch die Regierung von  will den Schritt am Mittwoch noch verkünden, wie berichtet wird. »Wir glauben, eine Zweistaatenlösung ist im Interesse Israels«, sagte Gahr Støre bei der Pressekonferenz.Die Regierung des EU-Landes Irland hatte vergangene Woche bereits erklärt, dass sie »sicherlich« bis Monatsende einen Palästinenserstaat anerkennen werde. Auch die Regierung in Oslo stellte einen derartigen Schritt im Laufe des Frühlings in Aussicht.Das israelische Außenministerium veröffentlichte eine Videobotschaft im Onlinedienst X, in der es die irische Regierung vor einem solchen Vorgehen warnte. Einen »Palästinenserstaat anzuerkennen, birgt das Risiko, dass Sie sich in einen Spielstein in den Händen des Iran« sowie der radikalislamischen Palästinenserorganisation  verwandeln, hieß es darin. Der Schritt bewirke nichts anderes, »als Extremismus und Instabilität zu nähren«.Der spanische Regierungschef Pedro Sánchez will am Mittwoch nach eigenen Angaben dem Parlament ein Datum für Spaniens Anerkennung eines Palästinenserstaates mitteilen. Im März hatte er in Brüssel mit den Regierungschefs von Irland, Slowenien und Malta eine gemeinsame Erklärung unterzeichnet, in der die vier EU-Länder ihren Willen bekundeten, einen eigenständigen Palästinenserstaat anzuerkennen. Im April reiste Sánchez nach Norwegen und Irland. Die drei Länder versicherten dabei, dass sie sich bei der Anerkennung eng abstimmten. sieht in einem derartigen Schritt eine »Belohnung des Terrorismus«, die eine Verhandlungslösung im Gazakrieg unwahrscheinlicher mache.Auslöser des Kriegs im  war der Großangriff der von der EU und den USA als Terrororganisation eingestuften islamistischen Palästinenserorganisation Hamas auf Israel am 7. Oktober. Die radikalislamischen Kämpfer töteten nach israelischen Angaben mehr als 1170 Menschen. 252 weitere Menschen wurden als Geiseln in den Gazastreifen verschleppt. 124 von ihnen befinden sich immer noch dort, 37 davon sind nach Armeeangaben tot.Als Reaktion geht Israel seither massiv militärisch im Gazastreifen vor. Dabei wurden nach Angaben des von der Hamas kontrollierten Gesundheitsministeriums, die sich nicht unabhängig überprüfen lassen, mehr als 35.600 Menschen getötet.Jonas Gahr Støre, Regierungschef von Norwegen",
        "ranked": 19,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716447610.2202048,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 09:00:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T09.00.10",
        "en_title": "Israel and Palestine: Norway will recognise Palestine as a State",
        "en_content": "will recognise Palestine as a state. The recognition will take place on 28 May, the Norwegian Prime Minister Jonas Gahr Støre told us on Wednesday morning.The government also wants to announce the step on Wednesday, as is reported. \"We believe that a two-state solution is in the interest of Israel,\" said Gahr Støre at the press conference.The government of the EU country of Ireland had already explained last week that it \"safely\" would recognize a Palestinian state by the end of the month. The government in Oslo also took such a step in the course of spring. The Israeli Ministry of Foreign Affairs published a video message in the online service X, in which it warned the Irish Government against such an action. Recognizing a \"Palestinian State\" is the risk that you will turn into a rock in the hands of Iran\" and the radical Islamic Palestinian organization. On Wednesday, the Spanish head of government, Pedro Sánchez, will give Parliament a date for Spain's recognition of a Palestinian state. In March, he signed a joint declaration in Brussels with the heads of government of Ireland, Slovenia and Malta, in which the four EU countries expressed their will to recognise an independent Palestinian state. In April Sánchez travelled to Norway and Ireland. The three countries assured that they agreed closely in recognition. sees in such a step a \"reward of terrorism\" that makes a negotiated solution more unlikely in the Gaza war.Savior of war was the great attack of the Islamist Palestinian organization Hamas, which was classified as a terrorist organization by the EU and the USA, on Israel on 7th. October. According to Israeli data, the radical Islamic fighters killed more than 1170 people. 252 other people were dragged into the Gaza Strip as hostages. 124 of them are still there, 37 of them are dead according to army records. As a reaction, Israel has been massively military in the Gaza Strip. According to the Hamas-controlled Ministry of Health, which cannot be independently checked, more than 35,600 people were killed.Jonas Gahr Støre, Head of Government of Norway",
        "en_subtitle": "Norway is making its announcement and wants to officially recognise a Palestinian state. Apparently, Ireland and Spain want to follow. Israel sees in this step a \"reward of terrorism\".",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "28 May",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norwegian",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jonas Gahr Støre",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 125,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wednesday",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "morning",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wednesday",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gahr Støre",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 384,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last week",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 463,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of the month",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 493,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Oslo",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 517,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "spring",
                "start_char": 557,
                "end_char": 563,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Israeli Ministry of Foreign Affairs",
                "start_char": 565,
                "end_char": 604,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Irish Government",
                "start_char": 675,
                "end_char": 695,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 735,
                "end_char": 746,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 813,
                "end_char": 817,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamic",
                "start_char": 835,
                "end_char": 842,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 843,
                "end_char": 854,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wednesday",
                "start_char": 872,
                "end_char": 881,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 887,
                "end_char": 894,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Sánchez",
                "start_char": 915,
                "end_char": 928,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 940,
                "end_char": 950,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 962,
                "end_char": 967,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 987,
                "end_char": 998,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 1009,
                "end_char": 1014,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 1049,
                "end_char": 1057,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 1090,
                "end_char": 1097,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovenia",
                "start_char": 1099,
                "end_char": 1107,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Malta",
                "start_char": 1112,
                "end_char": 1117,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 1132,
                "end_char": 1136,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 1137,
                "end_char": 1139,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 1199,
                "end_char": 1210,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "April",
                "start_char": 1221,
                "end_char": 1226,
