[
    {
        "title": "Israel-Gaza-Krieg: Frankreich stärkt Internationalem Strafgerichtshof den Rücken",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 21 May 2024 12:35:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/israel-gaza-krieg-frankreich-staerkt-internationalem-strafgerichtshof-den-ruecken-a-4b6c1770-37ac-4f62-b669-deaa10bca9d0#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Der Chefankläger des Internationalen Gerichtshofs hat zeitgleich Haftbefehle für Israels Premier Netanyahu und Hamas-Führer Sinwar beantragt – und erntet dafür scharfe Kritik. Unterstützung kommt nun aus Frankreich.",
        "content": " hat dem Internationalen Strafgerichtshof (IStGH) nach dem Antrag auf Haftbefehle gegen Israels Ministerpräsidenten  und gegen den Anführer der Terrororganisation  im , Yahya Sinwar, den Rücken gestärkt. »Frankreich unterstützt den Internationalen Strafgerichtshof, seine Unabhängigkeit und den Kampf gegen Straflosigkeit in allen Situationen«, teilte das französische Außenministerium in der Nacht zum Dienstag mit.Frankreich habe die von der Hamas verübten antisemitischen Massaker von Anfang an verurteilt, hieß es in Paris. Was  angehe, poche Frankreich seit vielen Monaten auf die strikte Einhaltung des humanitären Völkerrechts und beklage insbesondere die Opfer unter der Zivilbevölkerung im Gazastreifen und den unzureichenden Zugang für Hilfslieferungen. »Frankreich setzt sich für die Suche nach einer dauerhaften politischen Lösung in der Region ein, die als einzige einen Friedenshorizont wiederherstellen und das Leiden sowohl der Israelis als auch der Palästinenser beenden kann«, teilte das Ministerium mit.In Bezug auf Israel werde es nun zunächst Aufgabe der Vorverfahrenskammer des Gerichtshofs sein, die vorgebrachten Beweise zu prüfen und dann über die Ausstellung der Haftbefehle zu entscheiden. Dabei müsse der Grundsatz der Komplementarität und das mögliche Vorgehen israelischer Gerichte berücksichtigt werden, teilte das Pariser Außenministerium mit. Der Grundsatz der Komplementarität besagt, dass der Gerichtshof nur dann strafverfolgend tätig werden kann, wenn Staaten nicht willens oder nicht in der Lage sind, eine bestimmte schwere Straftat ernsthaft zu verfolgen.Der Chefankläger des Internationalen Strafgerichtshofs in Den Haag, Karim Khan, hatte am Montag einen  gegen Israels Regierungschef Netanyahu und Verteidigungsminister Yoav Gallant beantragt. Auch für den Anführer der islamistischen Hamas im Gazastreifen, dessen Stellvertreter sowie gegen den Auslandschef der Hamas wurden Haftbefehle beantragt. Israel und die Hamas reagierten darauf mit Empörung. Beanstandet wird etwa die Parallelität der Anträge: Sowohl Israel als auch die USA und einige europäische Vertreter lesen daraus eine Gleichsetzung zwischen Israel und der Terrororganisation Hamas. »Was auch immer dieser Ankläger andeuten mag, es gibt keine Gleichsetzung – keine – zwischen Israel und der Hamas«, sagte US-Präsident Joe Biden. »Wir werden immer an der Seite Israels stehen, wenn es um Bedrohungen seiner Sicherheit geht.«Internationaler Strafgerichtshof in Den Haag",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289211.746825,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:11",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.11",
        "en_title": "Israel-Gaza war: France strengthens International Criminal Court",
        "en_content": "has strengthened the back of the International Criminal Court (IStGH) following the request for arrest warrants against Israel's Prime Minister and against the leader of the terrorist organization in Yahya Sinwar. “Frankreich supports the International Criminal Court, its independence and the fight against impunity in all situations,” said the French Ministry of Foreign Affairs on Tuesday night.Frankreich condemned the anti-Semitic massacres carried out by Hamas from the outset, it was said in Paris. What has happened to France for many months to insist on strict compliance with international humanitarian law and, in particular, to defend victims under the civilian population in the Gaza Strip and insufficient access to aid supplies. \"France is committed to finding a lasting political solution in the region, which is the only one to restore a peace horizon and to end the suffering of both the Israelis and the Palestinians,\" said the Ministry. With regard to Israel, it will first be the task of the Court of Justice's Prevention Chamber to examine the evidence presented and then to decide on the issue of the arrest warrants. In this context, the principle of complementarity and the possible action of Israeli courts must be taken into account. The principle of complementarity states that the Court can only act in a criminal manner if states are not willing or unable to prosecute a certain serious offence.The chief prosecutor of the International Criminal Court in The Hague, Karim Khan, had requested on Monday an Israeli head of government Netanyahu and Minister of Defence Yoav Gallant. Arrest warrants were also requested for the leader of the Islamist Hamas in the Gaza Strip, its deputy and against Hamas' foreign chief. Israel and Hamas reacted with indignation. For example, the parallelism of the requests is being challenged: both Israel and the United States and some European representatives read a equation between Israel and the Hamas terrorist organization. “Whatever this prosecutor may suggest is no equation – no – between Israel and Hamas”, said US President Joe Biden. \"We will always be at the side of Israel when it comes to threats to its security.\"",
        "en_subtitle": "At the same time, the chief prosecutor of the International Court of Justice has applied for arrest warrants for Israel's Prime Minister Netanyahu and Hamas leader Sinwar – and he reaps sharp criticism. Support now comes from France.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the International Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinwar",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yahya Sinwar",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Frankreich",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the French Ministry of Foreign Affairs",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Frankreich",
                "start_char": 398,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Semitic",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 527,
                "end_char": 533,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "many months",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 549,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 745,
                "end_char": 751,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israelis",
                "start_char": 906,
                "end_char": 914,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 923,
                "end_char": 935,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ministry",
                "start_char": 947,
                "end_char": 955,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 972,
                "end_char": 978,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 988,
                "end_char": 993,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Court of Justice's",
                "start_char": 1009,
                "end_char": 1031,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Prevention Chamber",
                "start_char": 1032,
                "end_char": 1050,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1218,
                "end_char": 1225,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Court",
                "start_char": 1310,
                "end_char": 1315,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 1449,
                "end_char": 1481,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Hague",
                "start_char": 1485,
                "end_char": 1494,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karim Khan",
                "start_char": 1496,
                "end_char": 1506,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 1525,
                "end_char": 1531,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1535,
                "end_char": 1542,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 1562,
                "end_char": 1571,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yoav Gallant",
                "start_char": 1596,
                "end_char": 1608,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamist",
                "start_char": 1668,
                "end_char": 1676,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1677,
                "end_char": 1682,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 1686,
                "end_char": 1700,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1725,
                "end_char": 1730,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1747,
                "end_char": 1753,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1758,
                "end_char": 1763,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1861,
                "end_char": 1867,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 1872,
                "end_char": 1889,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 1899,
                "end_char": 1907,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1948,
                "end_char": 1954,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1963,
                "end_char": 1968,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2061,
                "end_char": 2067,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 2072,
                "end_char": 2077,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 2085,
                "end_char": 2087,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 2098,
                "end_char": 2107,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2143,
                "end_char": 2149,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Spanien bestellt argentinischen Botschafter nach Beleidigungen von Javier Milei ein",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 20 May 2024 19:27:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/spanien-bestellt-argentinischen-botschafter-nach-beleidigungen-von-javier-milei-ein-a-d1570af7-7244-4ee2-afe5-9bf3301031f3#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Die Ausfälle des argentinischen Präsidenten Milei gegen Premier Sánchez und dessen Frau ziehen diplomatische Kreise: Spaniens Außenminister hat den Botschafter Argentiniens einbestellt und droht mit weiteren Schritten.",
        "content": " und  stehen vor einer diplomatischen Krise. Nach den Entgleisungen des argentinischen Präsidenten  gegen Spaniens Regierungschef  und dessen Frau Begoña herrscht Missstimmung zwischen den beiden Ländern.Der spanische Außenminister José Manuel Albares sagte am Montag im staatlichen Fernsehsender RTVE, er habe den argentinischen Botschafter in Madrid persönlich einbestellt. Milei habe nicht nur Sànchez, sondern ganz »Spanien beleidigt«, hieß es in einem Statement der Regierung. Man verlange von Milei eine »öffentliche Entschuldigung«, andernfalls werde man Maßnahmen ergreifen.Zuvor hatte die spanische Regierung bereits ihre Botschafterin aus Argentinien bis auf Weiteres zurückbeordert. Laut RTVE und anderen spanischen Medien erwägt Madrid nun sogar den Abbruch der offiziellen Beziehungen. Ein Regierungssprecher in Buenos Aires schloss eine Entschuldigung zunächst aus und sagte laut Nachrichtenagentur Reuters, Spanien möge sich vielmehr bei Milei entschuldigen.Der Ultraliberale Milei hatte sich am Sonntag zu einer Wahlkampfveranstaltung der spanischen Rechtspopulisten (Vox) zur Europawahl in Madrid aufgehalten. Bei dem Treffen rechtsextremer und rechtspopulistischer Parteien hatte Milei über die Frau des Sozialisten Sánchez hergezogen. Er kritisierte die linke Regierung Spaniens scharf und bezeichnete Sánchez’ Ehefrau Begoña Gómez als »korrupt«.Albares warf Milei am Montag »Einmischung in die inneren Angelegenheiten« Spaniens vor. »Ein ausländisches Staatsoberhaupt besucht nicht in ein Land, um dessen Institutionen zu beleidigen«, sagte der Minister. Am Sonntag hatte Albares von einem »Frontalangriff auf unsere Demokratie, auf unsere Institutionen und auf Spanien« gesprochen.In seiner ersten Reaktion auf den Eklat sagte Sánchez: »Was wir gestern in Madrid erlebt haben, zeigt die Gefahr, die diese rechtsextreme Internationale für Gesellschaften wie die unsere darstellt, in denen die Demokratie auf den Säulen des wirtschaftlichen Fortschritts, der sozialen Gerechtigkeit und des Zusammenlebens beruht.« Auch in den Beziehungen zwischen Regierungen, die ideologisch nicht einer Meinung seien, sei Respekt unverzichtbar.Bei seinem Auftritt in Madrid war Milei wie ein Rockstar gefeiert worden, wie die Zeitung »El Mundo« schrieb. Der Mann, der sich als »Anarchokapitalist« bezeichnet, begeisterte die mehr 10.000 Teilnehmer mit Aussagen wie jener, dass man dem »verdammten und krebsartigen Sozialismus basta« sagen müsse. Sozialismus führe »zu Sklaverei oder Tod«, soziale Gerechtigkeit sei »immer ungerecht«. »Herzlichen Dank, Javier Milei, für den Schrecken, den du den Linken des Westens eingejagt hast«, sagte Vox-Präsident Santiago Abascal bei der Veranstaltung.An dem Treffen nahmen auch hochrangige rechte, rechtspopulistische und nationalkonservative Politiker aus dem Ausland teil, darunter Marine Le Pen von der französischen Partei Rassemblement National, der Portugiese André Ventura, der Chilene José Kast und auch der israelische Minister für soziale Gleichheit, Amichai Chikli.Die italienische Ministerpräsidentin  hatte sich per Video zugeschaltet, Ungarns Regierungschef  hatte eine Botschaft geschickt, in der er die Wahl zum Europäischen Parlament vom 6. bis 9. Juni als »einen großen gemeinsamen Kampf« gegen ein Europa bezeichnete, das »massenhafte illegale Migration« fördere.Argentiniens Staatschef Milei (am 17. Mai in Madrid)Premier Sánchez, Ehefrau Begoña Gomez (im Juli 2023)",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289212.0386086,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.12",
        "en_title": "Spain appoints Argentine ambassadors after insults from Javier Milei",
        "en_content": "and face a diplomatic crisis. Following the revival of the Argentinian President against Spain's head of government and its wife Begoña, there is a misunderstanding between the two countries.On Monday, Spanish Foreign Minister José Manuel Albares said in the state television station RTVE that he personally ordered the Argentinian ambassador in Madrid. Milei not only insulted Sànchez, but also insulted \"Spain\", said it in a statement by the government. Milei asks for a \"public apology\", otherwise it will take action. Before that, the Spanish government had already reordered its ambassador from Argentina until further notice. According to RTVE and other Spanish media, Madrid is now even considering the demolition of official relations. A government spokesperson in Buenos Aires first issued an apology and, according to the news agency Reuters, said that Spain would rather apologise to Milei.The ultra-liberal Milei had stopped on Sunday for a campaign event by the Spanish legal populists (Vox) on the European elections in Madrid. At the meeting of far-right and right-wing populist parties, Milei had drawn up on Sánchez's wife. He criticized the left government of Spain sharply and called Sánchez's wife Begoña Gómez as \"corrupt\".Albares accused Milei on Monday \"interference in internal affairs\" in Spain. \"A foreign head of state does not visit a country to insult its institutions,\" said the minister. On Sunday, Albares had spoken of a \"frontal attack on our democracy, our institutions and Spain\". In his first reaction to the dictator Sánchez said: \"What we experienced yesterday in Madrid shows the danger that this far-right international represents for societies like ours, in which democracy is based on the pillars of economic progress, social justice and coexistence.\" Respect is also indispensable in the relations between governments that are not ideologically of opinion.In his performance in Madrid, Milei was celebrated as a rock star, as the newspaper »El Mundo« wrote. The man, who is called \"anarchocapitalist\", enthralled the more 10,000 participants with statements such as the one that \"damaged and cancerous socialism basta\" must be said. Socialism leads »to slavery or death«, social justice is »always unjust«. \"Thank you, Javier Milei, for the horror you have hunted in the left of the West,\" said Vox President Santiago Abascal at the event. The meeting was attended by high-ranking right-wing, right-wing populist and national-conservative politicians from abroad, including Marine Le Pen from the French Party Rassemblement National, Portugiese André Ventura, Chilene José Kast and also the Israeli Minister for Social Equality, Amichai Chikli.The Italian Prime Minister had turned on a video, Hungary's head of government had sent a message to parliament from June 6. May in Madrid)Premier Sánchez, wife Begoña Gomez (in July 2023)",
        "en_subtitle": "The failures of Argentine President Milei against Premier Sánchez and his wife draw diplomatic circles: Spain's Foreign Minister has appointed the ambassador of Argentina and threatens further steps.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sánchez",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentinian",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Begoña",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "José Manuel Albares",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 246,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentinian",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sànchez",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 456,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 600,
                "end_char": 609,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 660,
                "end_char": 667,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 675,
                "end_char": 681,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos",
                "start_char": 773,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aires",
                "start_char": 780,
                "end_char": 785,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 786,
                "end_char": 791,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Reuters",
                "start_char": 844,
                "end_char": 851,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 863,
                "end_char": 868,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 895,
                "end_char": 900,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 940,
                "end_char": 946,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 975,
                "end_char": 982,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vox",
                "start_char": 1000,
                "end_char": 1003,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 1012,
                "end_char": 1020,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 1034,
                "end_char": 1040,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 1103,
                "end_char": 1108,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sánchez",
                "start_char": 1125,
                "end_char": 1132,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 1178,
                "end_char": 1183,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sánchez",
                "start_char": 1203,
                "end_char": 1210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Begoña Gómez",
                "start_char": 1218,
                "end_char": 1230,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Albares",
                "start_char": 1244,
                "end_char": 1251,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 1260,
                "end_char": 1265,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 1269,
                "end_char": 1275,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 1314,
                "end_char": 1319,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 1422,
                "end_char": 1428,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 1509,
                "end_char": 1514,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1524,
                "end_char": 1529,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sánchez",
                "start_char": 1555,
                "end_char": 1562,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 1590,
                "end_char": 1599,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 1603,
                "end_char": 1609,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 1922,
                "end_char": 1928,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 1930,
                "end_char": 1935,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "»El Mundo«",
                "start_char": 1984,
                "end_char": 1994,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10,000",
                "start_char": 2066,
                "end_char": 2072,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei",
                "start_char": 2263,
                "end_char": 2275,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 2327,
                "end_char": 2331,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vox",
                "start_char": 2339,
                "end_char": 2342,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Santiago Abascal",
                "start_char": 2353,
                "end_char": 2369,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marine Le Pen",
                "start_char": 2518,
                "end_char": 2531,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the French Party Rassemblement National",
                "start_char": 2537,
                "end_char": 2576,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Portugiese",
                "start_char": 2578,
                "end_char": 2588,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chilene José Kast",
                "start_char": 2604,
                "end_char": 2621,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 2635,
                "end_char": 2642,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Social Equality",
                "start_char": 2656,
                "end_char": 2671,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Amichai Chikli",
                "start_char": 2673,
                "end_char": 2687,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 2692,
                "end_char": 2699,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 2738,
                "end_char": 2745,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "June 6",
                "start_char": 2805,
                "end_char": 2811,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "May",
                "start_char": 2813,
                "end_char": 2816,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sánchez",
                "start_char": 2835,
                "end_char": 2842,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Begoña Gomez",
                "start_char": 2849,
                "end_char": 2861,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "July 2023",
                "start_char": 2866,
                "end_char": 2875,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Carlos Lehder, Partner von Pablo Escobar, im Interview: »Tod oder Gefängnis«",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 20 May 2024 16:55:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/carlos-lehder-partner-von-pablo-escobar-im-interview-tod-oder-gefaengnis-a-59d83a9b-c824-49e8-99c4-94dab768a1b3#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Carlos Lehder galt als Freund Pablo Escobars. Nach langer Haft in den USA lebt er heute in Deutschland. Hier spricht er über die Gewalt des berüchtigten Medellín-Kartells und den aktuellen Kokainboom.",
        "content": "Wandgemälde mit Pablo Escobar in Medellín: Der Drogenbaron kam 1993 bei einer Schießerei mit Sicherheitskräften ums Leben",
        "ranked": 20,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289212.0825374,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.12",
        "en_title": "Carlos Lehder, partner of Pablo Escobar, in an interview: »Death or Prison«",
        "en_content": "Wall painting with Pablo Escobar in Medellín: The drug baron died in 1993 in a shooting with security forces",
        "en_subtitle": "Carlos Lehder was considered a friend Pablo Escobars. After long imprisonment in the USA, he lives in Germany today. Here he talks about the violence of the notorious Medellín cartel and the current cocaine boom.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Carlos Lehder",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pablo Escobar",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Carlos Lehder",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pablo Escobars",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Medellín",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pablo Escobar",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Medellín",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1993",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Internationaler Strafgerichtshof: Die Hintergründe zu dem Gericht",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 20 May 2024 18:02:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/internationaler-strafgerichtshof-die-hintergruende-zu-dem-gericht-a-ea13d3e6-116f-48ff-810e-2cad6b2a321c#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Der Chefankläger des Internationalen Strafgerichtshofs hat Haftbefehle gegen Hamas-Führer beantragt – aber auch gegen Israels Premier Netanyahu. Welche Konsequenzen hat das? Die wichtigsten Fragen und Antworten.",
        "content": "Der Chefankläger des Internationalen Strafgerichtshofs hat  und gegen den Anführer der Terrororganisation Hamas im Gazastreifen, Yahya Sinwar, beantragt.Ob die Haftbefehle ausgestellt werden, müssen die Richter noch entscheiden.Der Internationale Strafgerichtshof kann offiziell Einzelpersonen strafrechtlich verfolgen, die für schwerste Straftaten wie Völkermord, Verbrechen gegen die Menschlichkeit, Kriegsverbrechen und Angriffskrieg (»Aggren«) verantworlich gemacht werden.Die Institution soll helfen, das humanitäre Völkerrecht und internationale Strafrecht besser durchzusetzen und erhebliche Lücken in der Strafverfolgung schließen. Doch es gibt auch Länder, die das Gericht nicht anerkennen. Welche sind das? Und was hat das für Folgen? Der Überblick.Der Internationale Strafgerichtshof ist der erste ständige internationale Strafgerichtshof der Welt. Er wurde im Jahr 198 auf einer Staatenkonferenz in Rom gegründet. Man spricht auch vom IStGH oder ICC, kurz für »International Criminal Court«.Nachdem 60 Staaten das  ratifiziert hatten, trat es am 1. Juli 2002 in Kraft. Daraufhin nahm der Gerichtshof im niederländischen Den Haag seine Arbeit auf. »Als Gericht der letzten Instanz soll er die nationalen Gerichte ergänzen, nicht ersetzen«, heißt es .Die Richterinnen und Richter arbeiten zwar mit den Vereinten Nationen (Uno) zusammen, das Gericht ist aber eine unabhängige internationale Organisation.Nein. Staaten steht es frei, dem IStGH beizutreten, einige Länder sind dagegen. Sie würden Eingriffe in die eigene staatliche Souveränität befürchten, Acht Staaten lehnen das Römische Statut gegenwärtig ab: China, der Irak, Israel, Katar, Libyen, Russland, der Sudan und die .Vor dem Internationalen Gerichtshof werden Konflikte zwischen verschiedenen Staaten verhandelt. Vor dem Internationalen Strafgerichtshof wird gegen einzelne Verantwortliche dieser schweren Verbrechen verhandelt und geurteilt.Zur »Situation« in Palästina, wie der Gerichtshof von ihm untersuchte Konflikte nennt, hat ICC-Chefankläger Karim Khan bereits im März 20mittlungen aufgenomn. Mit dem Terrorangriff der Hamas und der Verschleppung von Geiseln am 7. Oktober 2023 – beides aus Sicht des Chefanklägers – und der militärischen Reaktion Israels ist die Untersuchung noch dringlicher geworden.Den Hamas-Führern wirft Khan nun unter anderem »Ausrottung« sowie Mord, Geiselnahme, Vergewaltigungen und Folter als Verbrechen gegen die Menschlichkeit vor. Er forderte die Terrororganisation auf, alle israelischen Geiseln umgehend freizulassen und für die »sichere Rückkehr zu ihren Familien« zu sorgen.Ministerpräsident Netanyahu und Verteidigungsminister Yoav Gallant werden von Khan unter anderem beschuldigt, für das Aushungern von Zivilisten als Methode der Kriegsführung sowie für willkürliche Tötungen und zielgerichtete Angriffe auf Zivilisten verantwortlich zu sein. Khan betonte zwar das Recht Israels, seine Bevölkerung gegen alle Angriffe zu verteidigen. Er erklärte jedoch zugleich, dieses Recht entbinde Israel nicht von der Pflicht, das humanitäre Völkerrecht einzuhalten.Einzelpersonen kann der Gerichtshof verfolgen, wenn ihnen entsprechende Verbrechen vorgeworfen werden, die auf dem Gebiet eines Mitgliedstaates begangen wurden, oder wenn der Beklagte Bürger eines Mitgliedslandes ist.Nun ist Israel zwar kein Vertragsstaat, aber die Palästinenserbehörde hat den ICC im Ja als Rechtsinstanz anerkann. Deshalb sind sowohl bestimmte Israelis als auch Palästinenser belangbar.Inwiefern die Anerkennung Folgen haben kann, war wegen der völkerrechtlich nicht eindeutigen Staatlichkeit Palästinas lange umstritten. Die Vorverfahrenskammer des ICC  2021 aber, das Gericht habe Zuständigkeit für den Gazastreifen und das Westjordanland inklusive Ostjerusalem.Der Strafgerichtshof hat weder eine eigene Polizei, noch Soldaten oder Vollzugsgewalt, also keine exekutiven Befugnisse auf dem Territorium von Staat Doch im Falle einer Vollstreckung ist die Bewegungsfreiheit der Gesuchten stark eingeschränkt. Alle Vertragsstaaten des Gerichts sind dazu verpflichtet, die Gesuchten festzunehmen und dem Gericht zu übergeben, sobald sie sich in ihrem Land befinden.Noch sind keine Haftbefehle ausgestellt. . Ob die beantragten Haftbefehle erlassen werden, müssen die Richter der Vorverfahrenskammer des IStGH entscheiden. Wenn sie die Tatvorwürfe als bestätigt ansehen, kann das Hauptverfahren gegen die Beschuldigten eingeleitet werden.Der ICC in Den Haag, Niederlande: Mit der Verabschiedung des Römischen Statuts im Jahr 1998 wurde erstmals in der Geschichte ein ständiger internationaler Strafgerichtshof ins Leben gerufenGerichtssaal des Internationalen Strafgerichtshofs in Den Haag: Seine Jurisdiktion erstreckt sich zunächst über die Vertragsstaaten des Römischen Statuts, dazu gehören alle Mitgliedstaaten der Europäischen UnionYahya Sinwar: Anführer der Terrororganisation Hamas im GazastreifenBenjamin Netanyahu, Israels Ministerpräsident",
        "ranked": 19,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289212.6667109,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.12",
        "en_title": "International Criminal Court: The background to the court",
        "en_content": "The chief prosecutor of the International Criminal Court has applied for the prosecution of Hamas in the Gaza Strip, Yahya Sinwar.Ob the arrest warrants are issued, the judges still have to decide.The International Criminal Court can officially prosecute individuals who are responsible for the most serious crimes such as genocide, crimes against humanity, war crimes and wars of attacks. But there are also countries that do not recognize the court. What are these? And what's the consequences? The International Criminal Court is the first permanent international Criminal Court in the world. It was founded in 198 at an international conference in Rome. One also speaks of the ICC or ICC, for »International Criminal Court«.After 60 states ratified, it came into force on 1 July 2002. The Court then took up its work in the Netherlands The Hague. \"As a court of last instance, it is said that it should supplement, not replace national courts,\" says .The judges, while working with the United Nations (Uno), the court is an independent international organisation.No. States are free to join the ICC, some countries are opposed. They would fear interventions in their own state sovereignty, and eight states are currently denying the Rome Statute: China, Iraq, Israel, Qatar, Libya, Russia, Sudan and the .Clashes between different states are negotiated before the International Court of Justice. In front of the International Criminal Court, individual persons responsible for these serious crimes are negotiated and judged. For the \"situation\" in Palestine, as the Court of Justice calls conflicts he has examined, ICC chief prosecutor Karim Khan has already received 20 investigations in March. With the terrorist attack of Hamas and the deportation of hostages on the 7th. October 2023 – both from the point of view of the chief prosecutor – and the military reaction of Israel has become even more urgent.The Hamas leaders are now accused of “extermination” as well as murder, hostage, rape and torture as crimes against humanity. He called on the terrorist organization to release all Israeli hostages immediately and to ensure the \"safe return to their families\". Prime Minister Netanyahu and Defence Minister Yoav Gallant are accused by Khan, among other things, of being responsible for the extinction of civilians as a method of warfare, arbitrary killings and targeted attacks on civilians. Khan stressed the right of Israel to defend its people against all attacks. However, at the same time, he stated that this right does not deprive Israel of the duty to comply with international humanitarian law. Individuals may follow the Court if they are accused of corresponding crimes committed in the territory of a Member State, or if the defendant is a citizen of a Member State. That is why both certain Israelis and Palestinians are viable.However the recognition can have consequences was long disputed because of Palestine's unambiguous statehood, which is not clear in international law. But the pre-trial chamber of the ICC 2021, the court has jurisdiction for the Gaza Strip and the West Bank including East Jerusalem.The Criminal Court has neither its own police, soldiers or enforcement, i.e. no executive powers in the territory of the State. All States Parties to the Court of First Instance shall be obliged to arrest the requested persons and to hand them over to the court as soon as they are in their country. . Whether the requested arrest warrants are issued, the judges of the ICC's pre-trial chamber must decide. If they consider the accusations confirmed, the main proceedings against the accused can be initiated.The ICC in The Hague, the Netherlands: With the adoption of the Rome Statute in 1998, a permanent international criminal court was created for the first time in history. Its jurisdiction extends initially to the States Parties to the Rome Statute, including all Member States of the European UnionYahya Sinwar: Leaders of Hamas terrorist organisation in the Gaza StripBenjamin Netanyahu, Israel's Prime Minister",
        "en_subtitle": "The chief prosecutor of the International Criminal Court has requested arrest warrants against Hamas leaders – but also against Israel's prime minister Netanyahu. What consequences does that have? The main questions and answers.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yahya Sinwar",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 529,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 537,
                "end_char": 542,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "international Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 581,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "198",
                "start_char": 614,
                "end_char": 617,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 652,
                "end_char": 656,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ICC",
                "start_char": 681,
                "end_char": 684,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ICC",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 691,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "60",
                "start_char": 734,
                "end_char": 736,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "1 July 2002",
                "start_char": 776,
                "end_char": 787,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Court",
                "start_char": 793,
                "end_char": 798,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Netherlands",
                "start_char": 824,
                "end_char": 839,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Nations",
                "start_char": 986,
                "end_char": 1004,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ICC",
                "start_char": 1099,
                "end_char": 1102,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 1198,
                "end_char": 1203,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Rome Statute:",
                "start_char": 1233,
                "end_char": 1250,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 1251,
                "end_char": 1256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 1258,
                "end_char": 1262,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1264,
                "end_char": 1270,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Qatar",
                "start_char": 1272,
                "end_char": 1277,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libya",
                "start_char": 1279,
                "end_char": 1284,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1286,
                "end_char": 1292,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sudan",
                "start_char": 1294,
                "end_char": 1299,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 1364,
                "end_char": 1398,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 1412,
                "end_char": 1444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 1552,
                "end_char": 1561,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 1566,
                "end_char": 1586,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ICC",
                "start_char": 1620,
                "end_char": 1623,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Karim Khan",
                "start_char": 1641,
                "end_char": 1651,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 1673,
                "end_char": 1675,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 1694,
                "end_char": 1699,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1730,
                "end_char": 1735,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the 7th",
                "start_char": 1771,
                "end_char": 1778,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 2023",
                "start_char": 1780,
                "end_char": 1792,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1878,
                "end_char": 1884,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1917,
                "end_char": 1922,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 2094,
                "end_char": 2101,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 2189,
                "end_char": 2198,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defence",
                "start_char": 2203,
                "end_char": 2210,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yoav Gallant",
                "start_char": 2220,
                "end_char": 2232,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khan",
                "start_char": 2248,
                "end_char": 2252,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khan",
                "start_char": 2405,
                "end_char": 2409,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2432,
                "end_char": 2438,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2551,
                "end_char": 2557,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Court",
                "start_char": 2644,
                "end_char": 2649,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 2733,
                "end_char": 2738,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israelis",
                "start_char": 2817,
                "end_char": 2825,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 2830,
                "end_char": 2842,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 2929,
                "end_char": 2938,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 3079,
                "end_char": 3093,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 3098,
                "end_char": 3111,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 3122,
                "end_char": 3136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Criminal Court",
                "start_char": 3137,
                "end_char": 3155,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 3258,
                "end_char": 3263,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Court of First Instance",
                "start_char": 3287,
                "end_char": 3314,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ICC",
                "start_char": 3507,
                "end_char": 3510,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ICC",
                "start_char": 3650,
                "end_char": 3653,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Hague",
                "start_char": 3657,
                "end_char": 3666,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 3672,
                "end_char": 3683,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Rome Statute",
                "start_char": 3706,
                "end_char": 3722,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "1998",
                "start_char": 3726,
                "end_char": 3730,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 3793,
                "end_char": 3798,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the States Parties to",
                "start_char": 3854,
                "end_char": 3875,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Rome Statute",
                "start_char": 3876,
                "end_char": 3892,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 3915,
                "end_char": 3921,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 3929,
                "end_char": 3937,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 3968,
                "end_char": 3973,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 4004,
                "end_char": 4008,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 4034,
                "end_char": 4040,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Polen: Andrzej Duda kondoliert zum Tod von Ebrahim Raisi und gerät in die Kritik",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 20 May 2024 18:07:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-20",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/polen-praesident-andrzej-duda-kondoliert-zum-tod-von-ebrahim-raisi-und-geraet-in-die-kritik-a-c561925b-438d-47e6-bb93-1cb1d7fc83ba#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Ein Kondolenzschreiben aus Polen nach dem Hubschrauberabsturz in Iran sorgt für Empörung. Auch die Reaktion der EU gefällt nicht jedem. Kremlchef Putin indes würdigt den verunglückten Raisi als wahren Freund Russlands.",
        "content": "Der polnische Präsident steht in der Kritik, nachdem er in einem Kondolenzschreiben zum Tod des iranischen Präsidenten  eine Parallele zum Flugzeugunglück von Smolensk gezogen hat. Er sei tief berührt vom Tod Raisis bei einem Hubschrauberabsturz, schrieb Duda auf der Plattform X.Nur wenige Nationen hätten solche tragischen Seiten in ihren Geschichtsbüchern. »Aber wir , die wir 2010 vom Absturz des polnischen Regierungsflugzeugs bei Smolensk in  betroffen waren, kennen das Gefühl des Schocks und der Leere, das in den Herzen der Menschen und im Staat nach dem plötzlichen Verlust der politischen und gesellschaftlichen Elite, nach dem plötzlichen Verlust von geliebten Menschen und Freunden zurückbleibt.«Beim Absturz der polnischen Regierungsmaschine am 10. April 2010 beim Landeanflug auf das russische Smolensk waren alle 96 Menschen an Bord ums Leben gekommen, darunter auch der damalige Präsident . Sie waren unterwegs zu einer Gedenkfeier für die Opfer der Massaker von Katyn. Dort hatten 1940 Angehörige des sowjetischen Geheimdienstes NKWD Tausende polnische Offiziere ermordet.Viele Polen nahmen Anstoß daran, dass Duda die Trauer nach dem Tod Raisis, der in seiner früheren Funktion als Staatsanwalt im Jahr 1988 für Tausende Verhaftungen und Hinrichtungen politischer Dissidenten verantwortlich war, mit der Trauer um Kaczyński gleichsetzte.»Duda beweint einen Verbrecher und Verbündeten Putins«, kritisierte ein Nutzer und postete dazu ein Bild aus , das öffentliche Hinrichtungen durch Erhängen an Baukränen zeigt.Er verstehe, dass Duda als Staatsoberhaupt sein Beileid ausdrücken müsse, kommentierte Bartosz Wielinski, Chefredakteur der Zeitung »Gazeta Wyborcza«. Der Verweis auf Smolensk sei aber »zutiefst unangemessen«. Andere forderten Duda auf, seinen Beileid-Post zu löschen.Zuvor hatte bereits die  wegen ihrer Reaktion auf den Hubschrauberabsturz in Iran für Irritation gesorgt. Die Brüsseler Behörde hatte auf Bitte Irans ein Satelliten-Ortungssystem aktiviert, das bei der Suche nach dem verschollenen Hubschrauber helfen sollte. Dafür erntete EU-Kommissar , zuständig für Krisenfälle, deutliche Kritik. Ex-Grünenpolitiker , mittlerweile Präsident der Deutsch-Israelischen Gesellschaft, mutmaßte etwa, Hilfe bei der Suche nach dem iranischen Helikopter könnte Unterstützung .Noch weiter ging -Experte . , das Hilfsangebot der EU sei in etwa so, als ob die Alliierten nach dem Attentat auf  dem nationalsozialistischen  Hilfe angeboten hätten.Unmissverständlich war hingegen die Reaktion Moskaus. Kremlchef  würdigte den verunglückten iranischen Präsidenten als einen herausragenden Politiker und wahren Freund Russlands. »Er wurde von seinen Landsleuten zu Recht hochgeachtet und genoss im Ausland großes Ansehen«, hieß es in einem Beileidsschreiben Putins an den iranischen Revolutionsführer .»Als wahrer Freund Russlands leistete er einen unschätzbaren persönlichen Beitrag zur Entwicklung der gutnachbarlichen Beziehungen zwischen unseren Ländern und unternahm große Anstrengungen, um sie auf die Ebene einer strategischen Partnerschaft zu bringen.«Die Beziehungen zwischen  und Moskau sind traditionell eng. Putin sieht Teheran als Schlüsselpartner in seinem Streben nach einer Weltordnung ohne Dominanz der . Er schätzt besonders die iranische Unterstützung beim Angriffskrieg gegen die . Raisi und Putin hatten immer wieder Kontakt miteinander.Die  wertet den Tod Raisis gänzlich anders. Die Präsidentin des oppositionellen Nationalen Widerstandsrats, , sprach von einem »enormen und irreparablen Schlag für den obersten Führer der Mullahs, Ali Khamenei, und das gesamte für seine Exekutionen und Massaker bekannte Regime«. Der Sicherheitsrat hielt eine Schweigeminute im Gedenken an Raisi und seine Begleiter ab. »Die EU drückt ihr aufrichtiges Beileid zum Tod von Präsident Raisi und Außenminister Abdollahian sowie weiteren Mitgliedern ihrer Delegation und der Besatzung bei einem Hubschrauberabsturz aus«, erklärte Ratspräsident . Der EU-Außenbeauftragte sprach von einem »tragischen Hubschrauberunglück«. »Unser Beileid an das iranische Volk zum Tod von Präsident Raisi, Außenminister Amirabdollahian und anderen, die bei dem Hubschrauberabsturz ums Leben gekommen sind.« »Der tragische Tod ist ein großer Verlust für das iranische Volk, und das chinesische Volk hat einen guten Freund verloren.« »Wir teilen die Trauer und den Schmerz des iranischen Brudervolkes.« »Ich bete für die Gnade Gottes für meinen lieben Kollegen und Bruder.«Ebrahim Raisi am Sonntag, wenige Stunden vor dem Absturz",
        "ranked": 18,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1716289212.6830778,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2024-05-21 13:00:12",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-21T13.00.12",
        "en_title": "Poland: Andrzej Duda Condos to the death of Ebrahim Raisi and gets into criticism",
        "en_content": "The Polish President is in criticism after drawing a parallel to the Smolensk aircraft accident in a letter of condolences to the death of the Iranian President. He was deeply touched by the death of Raisis in a helicopter crash, Duda wrote on platform X.Only a few nations would have such tragic pages in their history books. \"But we, who were affected by the collapse of the Polish government aircraft in Smolensk in 2010, know the feeling of shock and emptiness left in the hearts of people and in the state after the sudden loss of political and social elite, after the sudden loss of loved ones and friends.\" April 2010 at the landing trip to the Russian Smolensk all 96 people had died on board, including the then president . They were on the way to a memorial celebration for the victims of the Katyn massacres. There, in 1940, members of the Soviet secret service NKWD had murdered thousands of Polish officers.Many Poles attacked that Duda was responsible for thousands of arrests and executions of political dissidents after the death of Raisis, who, in his former function as a prosecutor in 1988, was equivalent to the mourning of Kaczyński. \"Duda cries a criminal and ally Putin,\" criticized a user and posted an image that shows public executions by hanging on construction cranes. He understands that Duda must express his condolences as Head of State, commented Bartosz Wielinski, editor-in-chief of the newspaper \"Gazeta Wyborcza\". The reference to Smolensk is, however, “indefinitely inappropriate”. Others urged Duda to delete his condolences post. Previously, they had caused irritation because of their reaction to the helicopter crash in Iran. At the request of Iran, the Brussels Authority had activated a satellite tracking system that should help in finding the lost helicopter. For this, the EU Commissioner, responsible for crisis cases, won a clear criticism. Ex-Green politicians, meanwhile President of the German-Israeli Society, suspected that aid in the search for the Iranian helicopter could support .Now go on -expert. The EU's aid offer was roughly as if the Allies had offered after the attack on Nazi aid. Kremlin chief praised the misfortune Iranian president as an outstanding politician and true friend of Russia. \"He was rightly respected by his compatriots and enjoyed great respect abroad,\" said Putin, in a letter of condolences to the Iranian Revolutionary Leader. \"As a true friend of Russia, he made an inestimable personal contribution to the development of good neighbourly relations between our countries and made great efforts to bring them to the level of a strategic partnership. Putin sees Tehran as a key partner in his pursuit of a world order without the dominance of the . He particularly appreciates Iranian support in the war of attack against the . Raisi and Putin have always had contact with each other. The president of the opposition National Resistance Council, spoke of a \"enormous and irreparable blow for the top leader of the Mullahs, Ali Khamenei, and the entire regime known for his executions and massacres\". The Security Council held a minute's silence in the memory of Raisi and his companions. \"The EU expresses her sincere sympathy with the death of President Raisi and Foreign Minister Abdollahian, as well as other members of her delegation and the occupation in a helicopter crash,\" said the President-in-Office of the Council. \"Our condolences to the Iranian people to the death of President Raisi, Foreign Minister Amirabdollahian and others who died in the helicopter crash.\" \"The tragic death is a great loss for the Iranian people, and the Chinese people have lost a good friend.\" \"We share the grief and pain of the Iranian Brotherhood.\" \"I pray for the grace of God for my dear colleague and brother.\"Ebrahim Raisi on Sunday, a few hours before the crash",
        "en_subtitle": "A letter of condolences from Poland after the helicopter crash in Iran provides outrage. The reaction of the EU does not affect everyone. Kremlin chief Putin, however, praises the unhappy Raisi as a true friend of Russia.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrzej Duda Condos",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim Raisi",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Smolensk",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisis",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Duda",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 377,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Smolensk",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2010",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "April 2010",
                "start_char": 614,
                "end_char": 624,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 652,
                "end_char": 659,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Smolensk",
                "start_char": 660,
                "end_char": 668,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "all 96",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 675,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katyn",
                "start_char": 803,
                "end_char": 808,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "1940",
                "start_char": 830,
                "end_char": 834,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Soviet",
                "start_char": 851,
                "end_char": 857,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "NKWD",
                "start_char": 873,
                "end_char": 877,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 891,
                "end_char": 900,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 904,
                "end_char": 910,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poles",
                "start_char": 925,
                "end_char": 930,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Duda",
                "start_char": 945,
                "end_char": 949,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 970,
                "end_char": 979,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisis",
                "start_char": 1049,
                "end_char": 1055,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1988",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1108,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kaczyński",
                "start_char": 1144,
                "end_char": 1153,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Duda",
                "start_char": 1156,
                "end_char": 1160,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 1187,
                "end_char": 1192,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Duda",
                "start_char": 1317,
                "end_char": 1321,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 1362,
                "end_char": 1367,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Bartosz Wielinski",
                "start_char": 1379,
                "end_char": 1396,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gazeta Wyborcza",
                "start_char": 1432,
                "end_char": 1447,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Smolensk",
                "start_char": 1467,
                "end_char": 1475,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Duda",
                "start_char": 1532,
                "end_char": 1536,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1661,
                "end_char": 1665,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1685,
                "end_char": 1689,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Brussels Authority",
                "start_char": 1691,
                "end_char": 1713,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 1819,
                "end_char": 1821,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "German",
                "start_char": 1938,
                "end_char": 1944,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 2003,
                "end_char": 2010,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": ".Now",
                "start_char": 2036,
                "end_char": 2040,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 2060,
                "end_char": 2062,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Allies",
                "start_char": 2097,
                "end_char": 2103,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nazi",
                "start_char": 2136,
                "end_char": 2140,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 2146,
                "end_char": 2153,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 2183,
                "end_char": 2190,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 2249,
                "end_char": 2255,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 2342,
                "end_char": 2347,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 2383,
                "end_char": 2390,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 2434,
                "end_char": 2440,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 2636,
                "end_char": 2641,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 2647,
                "end_char": 2653,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 2762,
                "end_char": 2769,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 2813,
                "end_char": 2818,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 2823,
                "end_char": 2828,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "National Resistance Council",
                "start_char": 2902,
                "end_char": 2929,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mullahs",
                "start_char": 2999,
