[
    {
        "title": "Iran beginnt Großmanöver im Golf von Oman",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:53:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/iran-beginnt-grossmanoever-im-golf-von-oman-a-f64dc960-2d2a-4220-a41b-59f6bf7189f3#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Eine Militärübung in Teilen des Golfs von Oman und des Indischen Ozeans könnte die Spannungen zwischen Israel und Iran verstärken. Die USA bemühen sich um Gespräche, doch Teheran empfängt Russlands Außenminister Lawrow.",
        "content": "Irans Streitkräfte haben an der Südküste ein Großmanöver begonnen. Wie die Regierung mitteilte, nehmen an der Militärübung Truppen der Infanterie, Panzerverbände, Luftabwehrkräfte sowie Marineeinheiten teil. Das Übungsgebiet umfasst die Küstenregion Makran sowie Teile im Golf von Oman und im Indischen Ozean.Bereits im Januar hatten Marineeinheiten der iranischen Revolutionswächter (IRGC) Seemanöver im Persischen Golf abgehalten. In den vergangenen beiden Monaten probte die Flugabwehr zudem ihre Einsatzbereitschaft rund um wichtige Nuklearanlagen.Angesichts der militärischen Spannungen mit Israel war in Iran zuletzt die Sorge vor einem Krieg gewachsen. Israels Regierung drohte wiederholt mit Angriffen auf iranische Nuklearanlagen. Hintergrund sind Befürchtungen, die Islamische Republik könnte nach Atomwaffen streben. Der Konflikt treibt auch die Preise in die Höhe und schürt bei vielen Iranern wirtschaftliche Sorgen.US-Präsident  hatte im Streit über das Atomprogramm Gesprächsbereitschaft signalisiert. Irans Staatsoberhaupt Ajatollah Ali Khamenei lehnte Verhandlungen zunächst ab. Beobachter spekulieren jedoch, ob im Hintergrund bereits Gespräche vorbereitet werden.Am kommenden Dienstag wird der russische Außenminister Sergej Lawrow in Iran erwartet. Es wird vermutet, dass Iran und  die Entwicklungen in  diskutieren werden. Die beiden Länder waren die Hauptverbündeten des gestürzten syrischen Machthabers Baschar al-Assad.Assad war Anfang Dezember von der islamistischen HTS-Miliz und mit ihr verbündeten Gruppierungen gestürzt worden. Die Übergangsregierung unter HTS-Chef Ahmed al-Sharaa gibt sich seitdem gemäßigt.Während des fast 14 Jahre andauernden Bürgerkriegs in Syrien wurde ein Großteil der Infrastruktur zerstört. Auch litt die Wirtschaft des Landes schwer unter internationalen Sanktionen. Die Vereinten Nationen erklärten am Donnerstag, die syrische Wirtschaft werde bei den derzeitigen Wachstumsraten mehr als 50 Jahre brauchen, um auf das Niveau vor Beginn des Bürgerkriegs zu kommen.Manöver südlich der iranischen Küste: Iranische Streitkräfte",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229208.9356172,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "Iran begins big maneuvers in the Gulf of Oman",
        "en_content": "Iran's armed forces started a big maneuver on the south coast. As the government announced, troops from infantry, armored associations, air defenses and naval units participate in the military exercise. The practice area includes the Makran coast region as well as parts in the Gulf of Oman and the Indian Ocean.In January, marine units of the Iranian Revolutionary Guards (IRGC) had held sea maneuvers in the Persian Gulf. In the last two months, the anti-aircraft also tried their willingness to operate around important nuclear installations. Israel's government repeatedly threatened attacks on Iranian nuclear installations. The background is fears that the Islamic Republic could seek nuclear weapons. The conflict also raises prices and raises economic concerns among many Iranians. U.S. President had signaled willingness to talk about the nuclear program in the dispute. Iran's Head of State Ajatollah Ali Khamenei first refused negotiations. However, observers speculate whether discussions are already being prepared in the background. The Russian Foreign Minister Sergej Lawrow will be expected in Iran next Tuesday. It is believed that Iran and developments will be discussed in. The two countries were the main allies of the overthrown Syrian ruler Baschar al-Assad.Assad was crashed in early December by the Islamist HTS militia and its allied groups. The transition government under HTS head Ahmed al-Sharaa has been temperate since then.At about 14 years of civil war in Syria, a large part of the infrastructure has been destroyed. The country's economy also suffered severely from international sanctions. On Thursday, the United Nations declared that the Syrian economy will need more than 50 years at current rates of growth to reach the level before the civil war began.Maneuver south of the Iranian coast: Iranian armed forces",
        "en_subtitle": "A military exercise in parts of the Gulf of Oman and the Indian Ocean could strengthen the tensions between Israel and Iran. The US is trying to talk, but Tehran is receiving Russia's Foreign Minister Lawrow.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Oman",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Oman",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Indian Ocean",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lawrow",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the south coast",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Makran",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Oman",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Indian Ocean",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "January",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Iranian Revolutionary Guards",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "IRGC",
                "start_char": 374,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Persian Gulf",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last two months",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 599,
                "end_char": 606,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Islamic Republic",
                "start_char": 659,
                "end_char": 679,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranians",
                "start_char": 780,
                "end_char": 788,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 790,
                "end_char": 794,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 880,
                "end_char": 884,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 895,
                "end_char": 900,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ajatollah Ali Khamenei",
                "start_char": 901,
                "end_char": 923,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 924,
                "end_char": 929,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1051,
                "end_char": 1058,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergej Lawrow",
                "start_char": 1076,
                "end_char": 1089,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1110,
                "end_char": 1114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next Tuesday",
                "start_char": 1115,
                "end_char": 1127,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1149,
                "end_char": 1153,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1197,
                "end_char": 1200,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syrian",
                "start_char": 1250,
                "end_char": 1256,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Baschar al-Assad",
                "start_char": 1263,
                "end_char": 1279,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Assad",
                "start_char": 1280,
                "end_char": 1285,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "early December",
                "start_char": 1301,
                "end_char": 1315,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Islamist HTS militia",
                "start_char": 1319,
                "end_char": 1343,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "HTS",
                "start_char": 1399,
                "end_char": 1402,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ahmed al-Sharaa",
                "start_char": 1408,
                "end_char": 1423,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 14 years",
                "start_char": 1457,
                "end_char": 1471,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 1488,
                "end_char": 1493,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 1628,
                "end_char": 1636,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Nations",
                "start_char": 1638,
                "end_char": 1656,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Syrian",
                "start_char": 1675,
                "end_char": 1681,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 50 years",
                "start_char": 1700,
                "end_char": 1718,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 1814,
                "end_char": 1821,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 1829,
                "end_char": 1836,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Donald Trump und New York City: Mit Krone auf dem Cover gegen die Maut",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:35:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/donald-trump-und-new-york-city-mit-krone-auf-dem-cover-gegen-die-maut-a-42fdeb4f-1adc-4c58-9d42-c46639f8a16b#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Die Maut in einer Metropole wieder abschaffen und sich zum König stilisieren: Das gelingt Donald Trump in einem Atemzug. Allerdings nicht mit New Yorks Gouverneurin – sie sagt dem US-Präsidenten den Kampf an.",
        "content": "Ein Bild des US-Präsidenten mit Krone, in Anlehnung an ein Time-Magazine-Cover. Darauf der Titel »Lang lebe der König«. Was hat das abstruse, offenbar KI-generierte Motiv mit Verkehrsstau zu tun? Es ist nur eine Folge des Rachefeldzuges, den Donald Trump seit seinem erneuten Amtsantritt führt. Und der traf im jüngsten Fall die Regierung des Bundesstaates New York.Seit Anfang Januar galt in weiten Teilen New York Citys für die allermeisten Autofahrer eine Mautgebühr von neun US-Dollar pro Tag. Es gab Ausnahmeregelungen, etwa für Geringverdienende, aber sogar für eine Fahrt mit einem der ikonischen gelben Taxen wurde ein – wenn auch geringerer – Zuschlag fällig. Die Gebühr sollte den massiven Verkehr in der Millionenmetropole reduzieren, für bessere Luft sorgen und den öffentlichen Nahverkehr stärken.Eigentlich. Denn Trump kam, sah und setzte um, was er im Wahlkampf versprochen hatte: Sein Verkehrsministerium hob die Genehmigung für die wenige Wochen alte Maut wieder auf. New Yorks Gouverneurin will sich solch einen Übergriff nicht gefallen lassen.Dass Trump seinen Schritt mit der eigenen »Krönung« verknüpft und behauptet, Manhattan und ganz New York »gerettet« zu haben, allein das ist schon bemerkenswert. Dass jemand im Weißen Haus dann aber aus einem Beitrag des US-Präsidenten ein Magazin-Cover bastelt und über einen offiziellen Kanal veröffentlicht, sorgt für Fassungslosigkeit – vor allem in New York.Ganz so aufgeheizt, wie beim amerikanischen Unabhängigkeitskrieg im 18. Jahrhundert ist die Stimmung in der Bevölkerung dann aber nicht. Die Maut kostet sie schließlich Geld. Trump, der mehrere Immobilien in New York besitzt, hatte von Anfang an gegen die Maut gewettert. Seine Einmischung in die New Yorker Verkehrspolitik ist nur das jüngste Kapitel in einer ohnehin schon belasteten Beziehung zwischen der Metropole und dem selbsternannten König. Es dürfte nicht das letzte sein.",
        "ranked": 20,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229208.9986954,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.08",
        "en_title": "Donald Trump and New York City: With Krone on the cover against the toll",
        "en_content": "A picture of the US president with crown, based on a time magazine cover. Then the title \"Long live the king\". What's the problem, apparently AI-generated motive to do with traffic jam? It is only a consequence of the revenge campaign that Donald Trump has been leading since his resignation. And in the latest case, he met the government of the state of New York.Since early January, in large parts of New York City, for the vast majority of car drivers, a toll of nine US dollars per day was applicable. There were exceptions, for example for low-earners, but even for a ride with one of the iconic yellow taxes, a – albeit lower – surcharge was due. The fee should reduce massive traffic in the million metropolis, provide better air and strengthen public transport. Because Trump came, saw and killed what he promised in the election campaign: His Ministry of Transport revoked approval for the few weeks old toll. New York's Governor does not want to have such an attack. That Trump is linking his step with his own \"creation\" and asserting that Manhattan and all over New York have \"smelled\" only that is remarkable. The fact that someone in the White House then builds a magazine cover from a post by the US president and publishes it through an official channel ensures unconstitutionality – especially in New York. Century is the mood in the population then not. The toll will cost them money. Trump, who owns several properties in New York, had climbed against the toll from the beginning. His intervention in the New York transport policy is only the most recent chapter in a relationship that is already burdened by the metropolis and the self-appointed king. It shouldn't be the last.",
        "en_subtitle": "Take off the toll in a metropolis and stylise yourself to the king: Donald Trump succeeds in a breath. But not with New York's governor – she says the fight to the US president.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York City:",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Krone",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York's",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "crown",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "early January",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York City",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "nine US dollars",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "million",
                "start_char": 698,
                "end_char": 705,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 778,
                "end_char": 783,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ministry of Transport",
                "start_char": 852,
                "end_char": 873,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the few weeks old",
                "start_char": 895,
                "end_char": 912,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York's",
                "start_char": 919,
                "end_char": 929,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 982,
                "end_char": 987,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manhattan",
                "start_char": 1051,
                "end_char": 1060,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 1074,
                "end_char": 1082,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 1148,
                "end_char": 1163,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 1212,
                "end_char": 1214,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 1314,
                "end_char": 1322,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Century",
                "start_char": 1324,
                "end_char": 1331,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 1403,
                "end_char": 1408,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 1441,
                "end_char": 1449,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 1524,
                "end_char": 1532,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Gazakrieg: Ariel und Kfir Bibas laut Israels Militär »mit bloßen Händen« ermordet",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:02:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/gazakrieg-ariel-und-kfir-bibas-laut-israels-militaer-mit-blossen-haenden-ermordet-a-7f0556f4-6b8d-4ba9-b8bd-4286d0e224a4#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Ariel Bibas war vier Jahre alt, als die Hamas ihn entführt hat, Kfir Bibas wenige Monate. Die Hamas führt einen gegnerischen Luftangriff als Grund für den Tod der Jungen an, Israel widerspricht.",
        "content": "Die Geiseln Ariel und Kfir Bibas sind tot. Am Donnerstag sind die Leichen der Brüder nach  überführt worden. Nach einer Untersuchung der sterblichen Überreste hat das israelische Militär (IDF) nun mitgeteilt: Entgegen den Angaben der Hamas sollen die Kinder nach ihrer Entführung am 7. Oktober 2023 »mit bloßen Händen« ermordet worden sein.»Wir können bestätigen, dass das erst 10 Monate alte Baby Kfir Bibas und sein älterer Bruder Ariel im Alter von vier Jahren von Terroristen brutal ermordet wurden, während sie im  als Geiseln gehalten wurden, spätestens im November 2023«, sagte IDF-Sprecher Daniel Hagari. Die  hatte mitgeteilt, dass Ariel und Kfir durch einen Luftangriff getötet worden seien. Unabhängig überprüfen lassen sich die Angaben beider Seiten nicht.Hagari teilte weiter mit, die Hamas habe weitere »grausame Taten begangen, um diese Gräueltaten zu vertuschen«. Die Einschätzung des israelischen Militärs stützt sich demnach sowohl auf forensische als auch auf nachrichtendienstliche Erkenntnisse. Details zu den Ergebnissen nannte Hagari nicht. Man habe die Erkenntnisse an »unsere Partner in aller Welt« weitergegeben, damit diese sie überprüfen könnten, hieß es. Und: »Die ganze Welt muss genau wissen, wie die Terrororganisation Hamas arbeitet. Ariel und Kfir wurden ermordet, und gestern wurden ihre Leichen in einer zynischen und grausamen Zeremonie in Gaza zurückgegeben.«Die Mutter der Jungen, Shiri Bibas, die als Teil des Abkommens mit ihren Kindern nach Israel zurückgebracht werden sollte, war israelischen Angaben zufolge , die Israel am Donnerstag entgegennahm. Stattdessen habe die Hamas Israel die sterblichen Überreste einer bisher unbekannten Frau überstellt. Übereinstimmenden Medienberichten hat die Terrormiliz angekündigt, , ob es bei der Übergabe von vier toten Geiseln am Donnerstag möglicherweise einen Fehler oder eine Vermischung sterblicher Überreste nach einem israelischen Luftangriff gab.Die Familie Bibas war zum Symbol der Verbrechen der Hamas am 7. Oktober geworden. Das Video von Mutter Shiri, die ihre beiden rothaarigen Kinder in den Armen hält, verzweifelt versucht, sie zu beschützen, während um sie herum Männer auf Arabisch schreien, ging um die Welt. Baby Kfir war bei seiner Entführung neun Monate, sein Bruder Ariel vier Jahre alt.Bilder von Ariel, Shiri und Kfir Bibas auf leeren Stühlen in Jerusalem",
        "ranked": 19,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.0178795,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Gaza War: Ariel and Kfir Bibas, according to Israel's military, murdered »with bare hands«",
        "en_content": "Ariel and Kfir Bibas are dead. On Thursday the corpses of the brothers were transferred. After an investigation of the mortal remains, the Israeli military (IDF) has now informed: Contrary to Hamas' information, the children are to be taken away on 7 after their abduction. October 2023 \"with bare hands\". \"We can confirm that the only 10-month-old baby Kfir Bibas and his older brother Ariel were brutally murdered by terrorists at the age of four, while they were held hostages at the latest in November 2023,\" said IDF spokesman Daniel Hagari. They had informed Ariel and Kfir were killed by an air raid. Regardless, the data from both sides cannot be checked.Hagari continued to report that Hamas has committed further \"grey deeds to cover these atrocities\". The Israeli military assessment is based on both forensic and intelligence. Details of the results did not call Hagari. The findings were passed on to \"our partner in the world\" so that they could check them, it was said. And: \"The whole world must know exactly how Hamas' terrorist organization works. Ariel and Kfir were murdered, and yesterday their corpses were returned to Gaza in a cynical and cruel ceremony.\"The mother of the boys, Shiri Bibas, who was to be returned to Israel as part of the agreement with their children, was according to Israeli information which Israel received on Thursday. Instead, Hamas Israel has transferred the mortal remains of an unknown woman. Convergent media reports have announced the terrorist militia, whether there was a mistake or a mix of mortal remains after an Israeli air raid at the handover of four dead hostages on Thursday.The Bibas family was a symbol of Hamas' crimes on the 7th. October. The video of Mother Shiri, who keeps her two red-haired children in the arms, desperately tries to protect them while around them screaming men in Arabic, went around the world. Baby Kfir was at his kidnapping nine months, his brother Ariel four years old.Pictures by Ariel, Shiri and Kfir Bibas on empty chairs in Jerusalem",
        "en_subtitle": "Ariel Bibas was four years old when Hamas kidnapped him, Kfir Bibas a few months. Hamas is leading an opposing air raid as a reason for the death of the boys, Israel is contradicting.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir Bibas",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ariel Bibas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "four years old",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir Bibas",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few months",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ariel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir Bibas",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "IDF",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 2023",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "10-month-old",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir Bibas",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the age of four",
                "start_char": 433,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "November 2023",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "IDF",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Daniel Hagari",
                "start_char": 532,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel and Kfir",
                "start_char": 565,
                "end_char": 579,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hagari",
                "start_char": 663,
                "end_char": 669,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 695,
                "end_char": 700,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 767,
                "end_char": 774,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hagari",
                "start_char": 875,
                "end_char": 881,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1029,
                "end_char": 1034,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel",
                "start_char": 1066,
                "end_char": 1071,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir",
                "start_char": 1076,
                "end_char": 1080,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 1100,
                "end_char": 1109,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1141,
                "end_char": 1145,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shiri Bibas",
                "start_char": 1203,
                "end_char": 1214,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1242,
                "end_char": 1248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1312,
                "end_char": 1319,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1338,
                "end_char": 1344,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 1357,
                "end_char": 1365,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1376,
                "end_char": 1381,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1382,
                "end_char": 1388,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1572,
                "end_char": 1579,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 1608,
                "end_char": 1612,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 1630,
                "end_char": 1638,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bibas",
                "start_char": 1643,
                "end_char": 1648,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1672,
                "end_char": 1677,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the 7th.",
                "start_char": 1689,
                "end_char": 1697,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "October",
                "start_char": 1698,
                "end_char": 1705,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shiri",
                "start_char": 1727,
                "end_char": 1732,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1748,
                "end_char": 1751,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arabic",
                "start_char": 1854,
                "end_char": 1860,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "Baby Kfir",
                "start_char": 1885,
                "end_char": 1894,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "nine months",
                "start_char": 1917,
                "end_char": 1928,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel",
                "start_char": 1942,
                "end_char": 1947,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "four years old",
                "start_char": 1948,
                "end_char": 1962,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ariel, Shiri",
                "start_char": 1975,
                "end_char": 1987,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kfir Bibas",
                "start_char": 1992,
                "end_char": 2002,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 2022,
                "end_char": 2031,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Waffenstillstand zwischen Israel und Hisbollah: Wahlkampf in der Geisterstadt",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:08:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/waffenstillstand-zwischen-israel-und-hisbollah-wahlkampf-in-der-geisterstadt-a-cc4b0384-42b6-467c-98b6-522855dda90d#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "In den Norden Israels sind bisher nur wenige Bewohner zurückgekehrt, obwohl seit November ein Waffenstillstand mit der libanesischen Schiitenmiliz Hisbollah gilt. Lokalpolitiker kämpfen in den entvölkerten Frontstädten um deren Zukunft.",
        "content": "Einkaufszentrum in Kirjat Schmona: Die Schaufensterpuppen tragen Spinnenweben",
        "ranked": 18,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.0319076,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Armistice between Israel and Hezbollah: campaign in the ghost city",
        "en_content": "Shopping center in Kirjat Schmona: The mannequins carry spider webs",
        "en_subtitle": "Only a few inhabitants have returned to the north of Israel, although since November there has been a ceasefire with the Lebanese Shiite militia Hezbollah. Local politicians are fighting for their future in the depopulated front cities.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Armistice",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "November",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanese",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shiite",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kirjat Schmona",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Syrien: Hoffnung trotz Zerstörung – Lamya Kaddors Eindrücke aus Syrien",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 19:25:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/syrien-hoffnung-trotz-zerstoerung-lamya-kaddors-eindruecke-aus-syrien-a-1e2b8941-6467-4ef0-bd05-4b1bdc4900fd#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Die grüne Bundestagsabgeordnete Lamya Kaddor ist durch Syrien gereist. Hier berichtet sie von Not und Mangel, von nächtlichen Geisterstädten, aber auch von Aufbruchsstimmung. Und sagt, wie Deutschland jetzt helfen muss.",
        "content": "Händler in der zerstörten Stadt Al-Asharah: »Die Syrer sagen, der schlechteste Tag, den wir heute erleben, ist immer noch hundertmal besser als das, was hinter uns liegt«",
        "ranked": 16,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.0515869,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Syria: hope despite destruction – Lamya Kaddor’s impressions from Syria",
        "en_content": "Dealers in the destroyed city of Al-Asharah: \"The Syrians say the worst day we are experiencing today is still a hundred times better than what lies behind us\".",
        "en_subtitle": "The green parliamentarian Lamya Kaddor has traveled through Syria. Here she tells of distress and lack, of nightly ghost towns, but also of a spirit of intrusion. And says how Germany needs to help now.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lamya Kaddor’s",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lamya Kaddor",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "nightly",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Al-Asharah",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syrians",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the worst day",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "hundred",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ukraine-Krieg: Ex-Minister Dominique de Villepin über den notwendigen Umgang mit Donald Trump",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:28:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/ukraine-krieg-ex-minister-dominique-de-villepin-ueber-den-notwendigen-umgang-mit-donald-trump-a-d4b172f9-5ac5-44ed-a39f-58dd6c0450f2#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Frankreichs früherer Außenminister Dominique de Villepin warnt davor, zum Vasallen der USA zu werden. Die Welt stehe an einem Wendepunkt. Was schlägt er vor?",
        "content": "Ex-Diplomat und Politiker Villepin in Paris: »Was wir gerade erleben, ist ein Systemwechsel«",
        "ranked": 17,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.091976,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Ukraine War: Ex-Minister Dominique de Villepin on the necessary handling of Donald Trump",
        "en_content": "Ex diplomat and politician Villepin in Paris: \"What we are experiencing is a system change\"",
        "en_subtitle": "France's former Foreign Minister Dominique de Villepin warns against becoming a vassal in the USA. The world is at a turning point. What does he suggest?",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine War",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dominique de Villepin",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dominique de Villepin",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "China Labor Watch: Trumps US-Hilfskürzungen lähmen Recherchen zu Zwangsarbeit in China",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/china-labor-watch-trumps-us-hilfskuerzungen-laehmen-recherchen-zu-zwangsarbeit-in-china-a-6b911862-71a7-4d7b-8cd9-cbb9eef509df#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Der Aktivist Li Qiang recherchiert mit seiner Organisation China Labor Watch seit 25 Jahren zu Zwangsarbeit in der Volksrepublik. Das Team ist auf US-Hilfsgelder angewiesen – und nun gelähmt. Li sagt: Davon profitiere vor allem Peking.",
        "content": "Präsident Trump (r.) und Berater Musk mit dessen Sohn im Oval Office: »Die USA werden langfristig verlieren«",
        "ranked": 14,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.1061044,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "China Labor Watch: Trump's US shortcuts paralyze forced labour research in China",
        "en_content": "President Trump (r) and consultant Musk with his son in the Oval Office: \"The USA will lose in the long term\"",
        "en_subtitle": "The activist Li Qiang has been researching forced labour in the People's Republic with his organization China Labor Watch for 25 years. The team is dependent on U.S. grants – and now paralyzed. Li says: This is mainly benefiting Beijing.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China Labor Watch",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Li Qiang",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the People's Republic",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China Labor Watch",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "25 years",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Li",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Oval Office",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Sicherheitsgarantien: »Eine Option für die Ukraine ist, sich eine Atombombe zuzulegen«",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 19:53:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/sicherheitsgarantien-eine-option-fuer-die-ukraine-ist-sich-eine-atombombe-zuzulegen-a-d1525abb-a4d4-4d14-98b2-54fbf909a75c#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Vertreter aus den USA und aus Russland haben über ein Kriegsende in der Ukraine gesprochen. Nicht dabei: die Ukraine. Sicherheitsforscherin Florence Gaub analysiert, wie das Land seine Sicherheit gewährleisten könnte.",
        "content": "Nach dem Ende des Kalten Krieges gab die Ukraine ihre nuklearen Waffen ab, im Vertrauen auf Schutzversprechen der USA und Russlands. Fast auf den Tag genau vor drei Jahren überfiel Russland die Ukraine. Nun verhandeln Russland und die USA über ein mögliches Kriegsende in der Ukraine – ohne die Ukraine. Einen Beitritt der Ukraine zur Nato bezeichneten die Amerikaner im Zuge dessen bereits als unrealistisch.In der aktuellen Folge von »8 Milliarden« spricht Host Juan Moreno mit der Militärstrategin Florence Gaub über die brisante Option, dass die Ukraine angesichts fehlender Sicherheitsgarantien durch die USA eine Atombombe entwickeln könnte. Gaub erläutert: »Eine Option für die Ukraine ist, sich eine Atombombe zuzulegen. Sie haben die Ressourcen und die Leute, die recht schnell eine Atombombe bauen könnten.« Das könnte wiederum zu nuklearer Aufrüstung führen. Gaub warnt: »Wenn die Ukraine diesen Weg geht, könnte das einen Dominoeffekt auslösen, bei dem andere Staaten ebenfalls über die Entwicklung eigener Atomwaffen nachdenken.«Hier geht es zur neuen Podcast-Episode.Sie können »Acht Milliarden« in allen Podcast-Apps kostenlos hören und abonnieren. Klicken Sie dafür einfach auf den Link zu ihrer Lieblings-App:Und abonnieren Sie dann den Podcast, um keine Folge zu verpassen. Wenn Sie lieber eine andere Podcast-App nutzen, suchen Sie dort einfach nach »Acht Milliarden«. Den Link zum RSS-Feed finden Sie .Es ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Bitte versuchen Sie es zu einem späteren Zeitpunkt erneut.",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.1209211,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Security guarantees: \"An option for Ukraine is to create a nuclear bomb\"",
        "en_content": "After the end of the Cold War, Ukraine abandoned its nuclear weapons, trusting in US and Russia's defence promises. Almost the day exactly three years ago, Russia surpassed Ukraine. Russia and the US are now negotiating a possible end of war in Ukraine – without Ukraine. The Americans have already described Ukraine's accession to Nato as unrealistic. In the current episode of »8 billion«, Host Juan Moreno talks with the military strategist Florence Gaub about the explosive option that Ukraine could develop a nuclear bomb in the face of missing security guarantees from the US. Gaub explains: \"An option for Ukraine is to create a nuclear bomb. They have the resources and the people who could build a nuclear bomb quite quickly.\" This could, in turn, lead to nuclear upgrade. Gaub warns: \"If Ukraine goes this way, it could trigger a domino effect in which other states also reflect on the development of their own nuclear weapons.\" You can hear and subscribe to \"real billions\" in all Podcast apps for free. Simply click on the link to your favorite app: and then subscribe to the podcast to not miss a episode. If you prefer to use another Podcast app, simply search for \"real billions\". You can find the link to the RSS feed .There has been a mistake. Please try again at a later time.",
        "en_subtitle": "Representatives from the USA and Russia have spoken about a war end in Ukraine. Not here: Ukraine. Security researcher Florence Gaub analyses how the country could guarantee its security.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florence Gaub",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Cold War",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Almost the day exactly three years ago",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Americans",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 309,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nato",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Juan Moreno",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florence Gaub",
                "start_char": 444,
                "end_char": 457,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 490,
                "end_char": 497,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 579,
                "end_char": 581,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaub",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 587,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 613,
                "end_char": 620,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaub",
                "start_char": 782,
                "end_char": 786,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 798,
                "end_char": 805,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Podcast",
                "start_char": 992,
                "end_char": 999,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Podcast",
                "start_char": 1148,
                "end_char": 1155,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "RSS",
                "start_char": 1225,
                "end_char": 1228,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Grafikanalyse: Wie stark – oder schwach – sind Europas Armeen?",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:42:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/grafikanalyse-wie-stark-oder-schwach-sind-europas-armeen-a-7d03942b-8c31-4777-971b-647f27d67a1e#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Europäische Soldaten könnten bei der Sicherung eines Waffenstillstands in der Ukraine helfen. Genug kampfbereite Truppen zu finden, könnte aber schwierig werden.",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 13,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.1358995,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Graphic analysis: How strong – or weak – are Europe's armies?",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "European soldiers could help to secure a ceasefire in Ukraine. Enough to find combat-ready troops, but could be difficult.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ukraine-Krieg: Die drei Rollen des Wolodymyr Selenskyj",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:42:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/ukraine-krieg-die-drei-rollen-des-wolodymyr-selenskyj-a-3d2680c2-83f6-4568-88f3-4571a10d374b#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Wolodymyr Selenskyj hat bislang die Rolle eines ukrainischen Winston Churchill gespielt, siegesgewiss an der Seite des Westens.  Nun zwingt ihn Donald Trump in eine neue Rolle.",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 12,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.1557221,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Ukraine War: The three roles of Wolodymyr Selenskyj",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "Wolodymyr Selenskyj has so far played the role of a Ukrainian Winston Churchill, winning on the side of the West. Now Donald Trump forces him into a new role.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine War",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Wolodymyr Selenskyj",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Winston Churchill",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "USA: Richter bestätigt Freistellungen bei Entwicklungshilfebehörde USAID",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:25:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-21",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/usa-richter-bestaetigt-freistellungen-bei-entwicklungshilfebehoerde-usaid-a-8ab1cd08-0b2e-4f8d-b4c7-ae419436d06f#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Mehr als 2000 Mitarbeiter der Entwicklungshilfebehörde USAID will die Trump-Regierung freistellen. Gewerkschaften hatten dagegen geklagt. Nun mussten sie einen Rückschlag einstecken.",
        "content": "Der Kampf der US-Regierung gegen die  kann weitergehen, zumindest vorerst. Ein Bundesrichter hat am Freitag eine Klage von Gewerkschaftern und Regierungsangestellten gegen die Freistellung von mehr als 2000 Behördenmitarbeitern abgewiesen.Bezirksrichter Carl Nichols sagte in , die Gewerkschaften hätten nicht nachgewiesen, dass ihre Mitarbeiter durch ihre Beurlaubung in Gefahr geraten würden. Daneben gab es auch eine formale Begründung für das Abweisen der Klage. So wies der Vorsitzende Richter weiter darauf hin, dass die Mitarbeiter zunächst ein administratives Streitverfahren durchlaufen müssten, bevor sie vor einem Bundesgericht klagen könnten.US-Präsident  hatte am 20. Januar angeordnet, alle Auslandshilfen für 90 Tage auszusetzen. Die Klage der Gewerkschafter ist eine von mehreren, die wegen der aggressiven Kürzungen eingereicht wurden.Die Entscheidung fällt damit einen Tag, nachdem ein anderer Richter bereits zum zweiten Mal angeordnet hatte, dass sowohl USAID als auch das Außenministerium ihre  wieder aufnehmen müssten.Proteste vor dem Gebäude der US-Entwicklungshilfebehörde USAID",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.169715,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "USA: Judge confirms releases from the USID Development Aid Authority",
        "en_content": "The fight of the US government against it can continue, at least for the time being. On Friday, a federal judge dismissed a lawsuit from trade unionists and government workers against the release of more than 2000 government officials.Curror Carl Nichols said in that the unions had not shown that their employees would be threatened by their leave. In addition, there was also a formal justification for rejecting the action. The Chairman Richter also pointed out that the employees had to conduct an administrative dispute before they could sue a federal court. January ordered to suspend all foreign aid for 90 days. The lawsuit of the trade unionists is one of several who have been filed for aggressive cuts.The decision therefore falls one day after another judge had ordered for the second time that both USAID and the Ministry of Foreign Affairs would have to resume.Protests before the USID Development Aid Agency building",
        "en_subtitle": "More than 2000 employees of the USID Development Aid Authority want to release the Trump administration. Trade unions had complained. Now they had to put in a setback.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the USID Development Aid Authority",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "More than 2000",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the USID Development Aid Authority",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 2000",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Curror Carl Nichols",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Richter",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "January",
                "start_char": 564,
                "end_char": 571,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "90 days",
                "start_char": 611,
                "end_char": 618,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "one day",
                "start_char": 742,
                "end_char": 749,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 790,
                "end_char": 796,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "USAID",
                "start_char": 812,
                "end_char": 817,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Foreign Affairs",
                "start_char": 822,
                "end_char": 853,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the USID Development Aid Agency",
                "start_char": 891,
                "end_char": 922,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Donald Trump: Nachrichtenagentur AP klagt gegen Ausschluss aus Weißem Haus",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:20:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-22",
        "url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/index.rss",
        "news_url": "https://www.spiegel.de/ausland/donald-trump-nachrichtenagentur-ap-klagt-gegen-ausschluss-aus-weissem-haus-a-964e50cf-2d1a-42cf-a6aa-fcef2f731957#ref=rss",
        "subtitle": "Donald Trump will, dass der Golf von Mexiko nur noch »Golf von Amerika« genannt wird. Die Associated Press machte nicht mit und muss draußen bleiben. Dagegen klagt die renommierte Nachrichtenagentur nun.",
        "content": " führt nicht erst seit seinem zweiten Amtsantritt einen Kampf gegen das Establishment Washingtons. Seither hat der -Präsident jedoch wieder die Macht, seine Rachegelüste auch auszuleben. Das erfährt unter anderem die renommierte  derzeit.Die AP bezeichnet den Golf von Mexiko nicht – wie  – als »Golf von Amerika«. Der Präsident hatte die Namensänderung mithilfe eines Dekrets entschieden. Unternehmen wie Google . Die AP nicht, deswegen verweigerten Offizielle des Weißen Hauses den Agenturjournalisten zuletzt den Zugang. Ein Eingriff in die Pressefreiheit – gegen den die AP nun klagt.Die Presse und »alle Menschen in den Vereinigten Staaten« hätten das in der Verfassung festgeschriebene Recht, »ihre eigenen Worte zu wählen und nicht von der Regierung bestraft zu werden«, heißt es unter anderem in der Klageschrift. Der gezielte Angriff auf die redaktionelle Unabhängigkeit berühre den Kern des ersten Verfassungszusatzes. »Das Gericht soll dies sofort korrigieren.«Die AP reichte die Klage bei einem Bundesgericht in Washington ein. Sie zielt auf drei Mitarbeiter des Weißen Hauses ab: Susan Wiles, die Stabschefin von Trump, Taylor Budowich, den stellvertretenden Stabschef, sowie auf die Pressesprecherin des Weißen Hauses, Karoline Leavitt.Leavitt wähnte sich nach Bekanntwerden der Klage auf der ultrakonservativen CPAC-Konferenz im Recht. Das gilt auch für Trump, der ankündigte, die AP so lange aus dem Weißen Haus zu halten, bis sie »Golf von Amerika« schreibe. Unter der Woche unterzeichneten 40 teils auch konservative Medien eine Aufforderung an das Weiße Haus, seine Politik gegenüber der AP zu ändern. Darunter etwa auch der Sender Fox News, der als Trump-nah gilt und eines der Sprachrohre des Präsidenten und seiner Anhänger ist.Pressekonferenz im Weißen Haus: Karoline Leavitt (l.) ist ein Ziel der AP-Klage",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1740229209.2002242,
        "language": "DE",
        "source": "Spiegel",
        "local_time": "2025-02-22 14:00:09",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-22T13.00.09",
        "en_title": "Donald Trump: News Agency AP complains against exclusion from White House",
        "en_content": "does not lead a fight against the Washington establishment only since his second appearance. Since then, however, the President has once again the power to live his vengeance. Among other things, this is what the renowned ones are currently experiencing.The AP does not refer to the Gulf of Mexico – like – as “Golf of America”. The President had decided to change the name by means of a decree. Companies like Google . The AP not, therefore the official of the White House denied the agency journalists last access. An intervention in the freedom of the press – against which the AP now complains.The press and \"all people in the United States\" would have the right in the Constitution to \"elect their own words and not be punished by the government\", says it, inter alia, in the law of law. The targeted attack on editorial independence is at the heart of the first constitutional amendment. \"The court should correct this immediately.\"The AP filed a complaint with a federal court in Washington. She aims at three employees of the White House: Susan Wiles, Trump's Chief of Staff, Taylor Budowich, and the White House Press Officer, Karoline Leavitt. This also applies to Trump, who announced to keep the AP out of the White House until she writes \"Golf of America\". Under the week, 40 conservative media also signed an invitation to the White House to change its policy towards the AP. Among them is the broadcaster Fox News, which is considered to be close to the Trump and is one of the language tubes of the President and his followers.Press conference in the White House: Karoline Leavitt (l.) is a goal of the AP-position",
        "en_subtitle": "Donald Trump wants the Gulf of Mexico to be called \"Golf of America\". The Associated Press didn't go along and have to stay outside. The renowned news agency is now complaining.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Mexico",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Golf of America",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Associated Press",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Mexico",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Google",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 581,
                "end_char": 583,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 627,
                "end_char": 644,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 674,
                "end_char": 686,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 862,
                "end_char": 867,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 942,
                "end_char": 944,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 987,
                "end_char": 997,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 1011,
                "end_char": 1016,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 1030,
                "end_char": 1045,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Susan Wiles",
                "start_char": 1047,
                "end_char": 1058,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 1060,
                "end_char": 1065,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Taylor Budowich",
                "start_char": 1084,
                "end_char": 1099,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 1105,
                "end_char": 1120,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Karoline Leavitt",
                "start_char": 1136,
                "end_char": 1152,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 1175,
                "end_char": 1180,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 1208,
                "end_char": 1210,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 1218,
                "end_char": 1233,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Golf of America",
                "start_char": 1252,
                "end_char": 1267,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the week",
                "start_char": 1276,
                "end_char": 1284,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "40",
                "start_char": 1286,
                "end_char": 1288,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 1337,
                "end_char": 1352,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "start_char": 1386,
                "end_char": 1388,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fox News",
                "start_char": 1420,
                "end_char": 1428,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
