[
    {
        "title": "Tajani, il decreto sul caro bollette in Cdm probabilmente lunedì",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:55:41 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/14/tajani-il-decreto-sul-caro-bollette-in-cdm-probabilmente-lunedi_11fd7376-397b-4c06-8383-583c01ee31a1.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo porterà il ministro Giorgetti. Io sarò in Egitto.",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Lunedì il ministro Giorgetti lo\nporterà, penso, in Consiglio dei ministri\" (il decreto sul caro\nbollette, ndr). \"Io purtroppo sarò in Egitto. Bisogna lavorare\nper tutelare le famiglie perché il prezzo dell'energia non gravi\nsulle imprese e sulle famiglie. I ministri competenti\nstudieranno come intervenire e su quali settori. Nel Consiglio\ndei ministri si vedrà e si deciderà\". L'ha detto il ministro\ndegli Esteri, Antonio\nTajani, a margine dell'Assemblea nazionale degli eletti azzurri\nnegli enti locali,\nin corso a Montecitorio. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 12,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1739624419.2924058,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-15 14:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-15T13.00.19",
        "en_title": "Tajani, the decree on the expensive bills in Cdm probably Monday",
        "en_content": "\"Monday the Minister Giorgetti lo\nwill bring, I think, to the Council of Ministers\" (the decree on the dear\nbills, ndr). \"I will unfortunately be in Egypt. You have to work.\nto protect families because the price of energy is not serious\non enterprises and families. The competent Ministers\nThey will study how to intervene and what sectors. The Council\nof the ministers will see and decide.\" The minister said it\ndi Esteri, Antonio\nTajani, on the edge of the National Assembly of Blue Elects\nin local authorities,\nin Montecitorio.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Minister Giorgetti will bring him. I will be in Egypt.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cdm",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgetti",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgetti lo",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council of Ministers",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ndr",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "di Esteri",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio\nTajani",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Assembly of Blue Elects",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Montecitorio",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 529,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Schlein, tassa sui grandi patrimoni non è tabù, a livello Ue",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:48:01 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/14/schlein-tassa-sui-grandi-patrimoni-non-e-tabu-a-livello-ue_4d6dad46-91d9-4416-9781-40658ee019e7.html",
        "subtitle": "Mi rifaccio alla proposta di Lula",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Il tema non può essere un tabù,\nsulla tassazione dei grandi patrimoni a livello almeno europeo o\ninternazionale\". Lo ha detto la segretaria Pd Elly Schlein a una\ntavola rotonda alla Treccani sul fisco, con il presidente del\nM5s, Giuseppe Conte e il segretario di Si, Nicola Fratoianni,\ndeputato di Avs. \"Mi rifaccio alla proposta di Lula. Ma quella\ndiscussione va fatta a un livello almeno europeo, perché è più\nefficace intervenire su quel livello. Poi siamo aperti a\nragionare e a discutere, lo faremo anche fra noi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 14,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1739624419.306342,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-15 14:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-15T13.00.19",
        "en_title": "Schlein, tax on the big patrimonies is not taboo, at EU level",
        "en_content": "\"The theme cannot be a taboo,\non taxation of large assets at least European or\ninternational.\" That's what the secretary Pd Elly Schlein said.\nround table at Treccani on the fisco, with the president of the\nM5s, Giuseppe Conte and the secretary of Si, Nicola Fratoianni,\nMember of Avs. \"I refer to Lula's proposal. But that's it.\nI would like to thank the rapporteur for his work.\neffective intervention on that level. Then we are open to\nto reason and to discuss, we will also do it among us.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "I refer to Lula's proposal",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd Elly Schlein",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Treccani",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "M5s",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppe Conte",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Si, Nicola Fratoianni",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 269,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Avs",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Quirinale, Mattarella sereno, si rimanda a testo su Russia",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:13:41 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/14/quirinale-mattarella-sereno-si-rimanda-a-testo-su-russia_39671e8a-c3e9-437a-80a1-00f0572ebae7.html",
        "subtitle": "E' quanto filtra dalla Presidenza della Repubblica",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            ++Vedi \"Ecco il passaggio del discorso di Mattarella...\" delle\n16.08++\n   Il Presidente della Repubblica è\nassolutamente sereno e rimanda alla lettura del testo\npronunciato a Marsiglia. È quanto filtra dal Quirinale. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1739624419.334151,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-15 14:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-15T13.00.19",
        "en_title": "Quirinale, Mattarella serene, refer to text on Russia",
        "en_content": "++See \"This is the passage of Mattarella's speech...\"\n16.08++\nThe President of the Republic is\nabsolutely serene and refer to the reading of the text\npronounced in Marseille. It's how much you filter from Quirinale.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "This is what the Presidency of the Republic filters",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "16.08++",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marseille",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quirinale",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "La Russa, inopportune dichiarazioni di Mosca su Mattarella",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:17:52 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/14/la-russa-inopportune-dichiarazioni-di-mosca-su-mattarella_296d075b-acb7-4710-85e7-b48f6dc6b4b8.html",
        "subtitle": "Solidarietà al presidente della Repubblica",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Trovo inopportune e fuori luogo le\ndichiarazioni rilasciate dalla portavoce del ministero degli\nEsteri russo, Maria Zakharova. Al capo dello Stato Sergio\nMattarella, custode dei valori della Repubblica e punto di\nriferimento della nazione, rinnovo la mia stima ed esprimo la\nvicinanza mia personale e del Senato\". A scriverlo sui social è\nil presidente del Senato Ignazio La Russa, \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1739624419.3640985,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-15 14:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-15T13.00.19",
        "en_title": "Russian, inopportune statements of Moscow on Mattarella",
        "en_content": "\"I find inopportune and out of place the\nstatements issued by the Ministry spokesman\nRussian Foreigners, Maria Zakharova. To the head of the Sergio State\nMattarella, guardian of the values of the Republic and point of view\nreference of the nation, I renew my esteem and express the\nmy personal and the Senate.\" To write it on social media is\nthe President of the Senate Ignatius The Russian,\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Solidarity with the President of the Republic",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Solidarity",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ministry",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian Foreigners",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria Zakharova",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Republic",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Senate",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ignatius",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni, attacchi a Mattarella sono un'offesa a tutta la nazione",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:55:26 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/14/meloni-attacchi-a-mattarella-sono-unoffesa-a-tutta-la-nazione_125de89c-55e8-4b5e-8263-bb73d47069a3.html",
        "subtitle": "Piena solidarietà al capo dello Stato da me e dal governo",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Gli insulti della portavoce del\nMinistero degli Esteri russo, che ha definito \"invenzioni\nblasfeme\" le parole del Presidente della Repubblica, Sergio\nMattarella, offendono l'intera Nazione italiana, che il Capo\ndello Stato rappresenta. Esprimo la mia piena solidarietà, così\ncome quella dell'intero Governo, al Presidente Mattarella, che\nda sempre sostiene con fermezza la condanna dell'aggressione\nperpetrata ai danni dell'Ucraina\". Lo afferma in una nota la\npremier Giorgia Meloni. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1739624419.3784075,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-15 14:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-15T13.00.19",
        "en_title": "Meloni, attacks on Mattarella are an offense to the whole nation",
        "en_content": "\"The insults of the spokesman\nRussian Foreign Ministry, which defined \"inventions\nthe words of the President of the Republic, Sergio\nMattarella, offend the entire Italian nation, that the Cape\nof the State represents. I express my full solidarity, so\nlike that of the entire government, the President Mattarella,\nalways firmly supports the condemnation of aggression\nperpetrated against Ukraine.\" It says in a note\npremier Giorgia Meloni.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Full solidarity with the head of the state from me and the government",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian Foreign Ministry",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio\nMattarella",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cape",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 394,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, sul fine vita competenza sia nazionale",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:31:47 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/14/tajani-sul-fine-vita-competenza-sia-nazionale_7a733f1c-39c5-42e8-81a5-c2db24adf6bf.html",
        "subtitle": "'Suicidio assistito non mi convince molto ma no all'accanimento'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Sul fine vita \"la posizione di Forza\nItalia è chiara: non può esserci una competenza regionale, deve\nesserci una competenza nazionale. C'è un dibattito in Parlamento\ne il Parlamento è sovrano, bisogna ben distinguere tra il\nsuicidio assistito e l'accanimento terapeutico. Siamo tutti\ncontrari all'accanimento terapeutico, il suicidio assistito non\nè che mi convinca molto. Sono però assolutamente convinto che\nnessun debba accanirsi e far soffrire di più una persona. Lo\ndico anche per esperienza diretta: quando ho dovuto decidere per\nmia madre, io ho deciso 'no' all'accanimento terapeutico, non\nc'erano più speranze di poterla salvare\". L'ha detto il\nvicepremier e leader di Forza Italia, Antonio Tajani, a margine\ndell'Assemblea nazionale degli eletti azzurri negli enti locali,\nin corso a Montecitorio. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 9,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1739624419.391123,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-15 14:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-15T13.00.19",
        "en_title": "Tajani, on the end of life both national competence",
        "en_content": "On the end of life \"the position of Force\nItaly is clear: there can be no regional competence, it must\nThere is a national competence. There is a debate in Parliament\nand Parliament is sovereign, we must distinguish between\nassisted suicide and treatment. We are all\ncontrary to the therapeutic occurrence, assisted suicide does not\nI'm convinced. But I am absolutely convinced that\nno one should anger and make a person suffer more. I do.\nI also say by direct experience: when I had to decide for\nMy mother, I decided 'no' to the therapeutic event, not\nthere were more hopes of being able to save her.\" He said that.\nVicepremier and leader of Forza Italia, Antonio Tajani, in margin\nof the National Assembly of Blue Elects in Local Authorities,\nin Montecitorio.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Suicide assisted does not convince me very much but not to the occurrence'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Force",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vicepremier",
                "start_char": 618,
                "end_char": 629,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 644,
                "end_char": 656,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 658,
                "end_char": 672,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Assembly of Blue Elects",
                "start_char": 687,
                "end_char": 723,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Local Authorities",
                "start_char": 727,
                "end_char": 744,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Montecitorio",
                "start_char": 749,
                "end_char": 761,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Accordo Intelligence-Paragon per la sospensione di spyware",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:07:59 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/14/accordo-intelligence-paragon-per-la-sospensione-di-spyware_4c9c090e-9e7b-488b-81f7-c198493fcb27.html",
        "subtitle": "Fino alla conclusione delle verifiche di Copasir e Agenzia cyber",
        "content": "Nuovo colpo di scena nella vicenda del software-spia Graphite. A quanto apprende l'ANSA da fonti dell'Intelligence, l'Intelligence italiana e Paragon Solutions - l'azienda produttrice - hanno concordato di sospendere l'operatività del sistema fino alla conclusione della procedura di due diligence condotta dal Copasir e dall'Agenzia nazionale per la cybersicurezza.La novità arriva due giorni dopo che il ministro per i Rapporti con il Parlamento, Luca Ciriani, aveva assicurato - rispondendo al question time della Camera - che \"nessuno ha rescisso in questi giorni alcun contratto nei confronti dell'intelligence. Tutti i sistemi sono stati e sono pienamente operativi contro chi attenta agli interessi e alla sicurezza della Nazione\".Era stato il Guardian, nei giorni scorsi, a scrivere che Paragon aveva rescisso il contratto con l'Italia dopo la notizia che lo spyware era stato utilizzato per sorvegliare il direttore di Fanpage, Francesco Cancellato e l'attivista di Mediterranea saving humans. Ciriani aveva spiegato che le agenzie di intelligence utilizzano il sistema rispettando \"nel modo più rigoroso la Costituzione e le leggi e, in particolare, la legge 3 agosto 2007, n. 124. Questo rigoroso rispetto vale anzitutto verso i soggetti specificamente tutelati da tale legge, in primis i giornalisti. Tutto ciò avviene sotto il controllo, ciascuno per la sua parte, dell'Autorità delegata, del Copasir e della magistratura\". Proprio il Copasir ha avviato un approfondimento sul caso, sentendo il direttore dell'Aise, Giovanni Caravelli. Mercoledì toccherà al direttore dell'Aisi, Bruno Branciforte. Il governo ha poi attivato l'Agenzia per la cybersicurezza nazionale, affinché svolga le verifiche tecniche su quanto riscontrato da Whatsapp che ha trovato 7 utenze italiane (sulle 90 totali) infettate dal virus. E si è mossa anche la procura di Palermo che ha ricevuto l'esposto di Casarini sul suo dispositivo hackerato, con l'ipotesi di reato di \"accesso abusivo a sistema informatico\". Paragon, a quanto emerso, vende Graphite soltanto ad entità governative. C'è stata così - alla luce degli ultimi eventi- un'interlocuzione tra l'intelligence italiana e l'azienda - di proprietà di un fondo americano dopo essere stata fondata in Israele - che ha portato alla decisione di sospendere temporaneamente l'operatività del sistema. Intanto emerge che il nome di David Yambio, attivista sudanese accusatore di Almasri e vittima dello spyware di Paragon, sarebbe agli atti di un'inchiesta della procura di Palermo per favoreggiamento dell'immigrazione clandestina.E' Il Giornale a pubblicare stralci di una comunicazione di polizia all'intelligence datata 6 maggio scorso in cui si informa che \"la procura distrettuale di Palermo ha recentemente iscritto nel registro degli indagati\" Yambio e due connazionali perchè \"indiziati del reato di associazione per delinquere finalizzata al favoreggiamento dell'immigrazione clandestina\". Dunque le utenze del sudanese e di Casarini, è l'ipotesi, sarebbero state controllate nell'ambito di un'indagine della procura siciliana. I due reagiscono. \"Sostengono - afferma Yambio - che lo spyware rilevato sul mio telefono era una 'penetrazione legale' perché ero sotto inchiesta per aver collaborato con Mediterranea. Ma questa cosiddetta indagine non esiste. Nessuna forza dell'ordine, nessuna autorità giudiziaria mi ha mai notificato alcuna indagine. Questa non è altro che una campagna diffamatoria\". Gli fa eco Casarini: \"mai ho ricevuto notizie di indagini per questo tipo di reato dalla procura e mai ne hanno ricevuto altri membri di Mediterranea. Ma sarà facile averne anche le prove: lo chiederò formalmente e per vie legali\".\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1739624419.4156601,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-15 14:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-15T13.00.19",
        "en_title": "Intelligence-Paragon Agreement for Spyware Suspension",
        "en_content": "New twist in the story of the software-spia Graphite. As ANSA learns from sources of Intelligence, Italian Intelligence and Paragon Solutions - the manufacturer - agreed to suspend the operation of the system until the conclusion of the procedure of two diligence conducted by Copasir and the National Agency for Cybersecurity. The novelty arrives two days after the Minister for Relations with Parliament, Luca Ciriani, had assured - answering the question time of the Chamber - that \"no one has rescissoted in these days any contract with the intelligence. All systems have been and are fully operational against those who are attentive to the interests and safety of the nation.\" It was the Guardian, in recent days, to write that Paragon had rescinded the contract with Italy after the news that spyware had been used to supervise the director of Fanpage, Francesco Cancellato and the activist of Mediterranea saving humans. Ciriani had explained that intelligence agencies use the system respecting \"in the strictest way the Constitution and the laws and, in particular, the law 3 August 2007, n. 124. This strict respect applies first of all to subjects specifically protected by that law, especially journalists. All this happens under the control, each for its part, of the delegated Authority, of Copasir and of the judiciary\". Precisely the Copasir has begun a deepening of the case, hearing the director of the Aise, Giovanni Caravelli. Wednesday will be the director of Aisi, Bruno Branciforte. The government then activated the National Cybersecurity Agency, to carry out technical checks on whatsapp's finding 7 Italian users (on the total 90) infected by the virus. And it also moved the Palermo Prosecutor who received Casarini's expost on his hacked device, with the hypothesis of \"unfair access to computer system\". Paragon, as it emerged, sells Graphite only to government entities. There was thus - in the light of the last events - an interlocution between the Italian intelligence and the company - owned by an American fund after being founded in Israel - that led to the decision to temporarily suspend the operation of the system. Meanwhile, it emerges that the name of David Yambio, a Sudanese activist accused of Almasri and victim of Paragon's spyware, would be to the acts of an investigation by the prosecutor of Palermo to support illegal immigration. It is Il Giornale that publishes stralci of a police communication to the intelligence dated 6 May in which it is informed that \"the district attorney of Palermo has recently enrolled in the register of the inquiries\" Yambio and two compatriots because \"inditiated of the crime of association for criminals aimed at promoting illegal immigration\". So the utilities of the Sudanese and Casarini, is the hypothesis, would have been controlled within an investigation of the Sicilian prosecutor. The two react. \"They claim - says Yambio - that the spyware detected on my phone was a 'legal penetration' because I was under investigation for collaborating with Mediterranea. But this so-called investigation does not exist. No law enforcement, no judicial authority has ever notified me of any investigation. This is nothing but a defamatory campaign.\" He echoes Casarini: \"I have received news of investigations for this type of crime from the prosecutor and never received other members of Mediterranea. But it will be easy to have proof of it: I will ask formally and lawfully.\"\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Until the conclusion of the Copasir and Cyber Agency verifications",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Intelligence-Paragon Agreement for Spyware Suspension",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Copasir",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cyber Agency",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANSA",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Intelligence",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian Intelligence",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paragon Solutions",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Copasir",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Agency for",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cybersecurity",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two days",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Minister for Relations",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Luca Ciriani",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "these days",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guardian",
                "start_char": 694,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "recent days",
                "start_char": 707,
                "end_char": 718,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paragon",
                "start_char": 734,
                "end_char": 741,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 774,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fanpage",
                "start_char": 851,
                "end_char": 858,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Francesco Cancellato",
                "start_char": 860,
                "end_char": 880,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mediterranea",
                "start_char": 901,
                "end_char": 913,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ciriani",
                "start_char": 929,
                "end_char": 936,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 1030,
                "end_char": 1042,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "3 August 2007",
                "start_char": 1084,
                "end_char": 1097,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "124",
                "start_char": 1102,
                "end_char": 1105,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1135,
                "end_char": 1140,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Authority",
                "start_char": 1292,
                "end_char": 1301,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Copasir",
                "start_char": 1306,
                "end_char": 1313,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Copasir",
                "start_char": 1351,
                "end_char": 1358,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aise",
                "start_char": 1422,
                "end_char": 1426,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giovanni Caravelli",
                "start_char": 1428,
                "end_char": 1446,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Wednesday",
                "start_char": 1448,
                "end_char": 1457,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aisi",
                "start_char": 1482,
                "end_char": 1486,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bruno Branciforte",
                "start_char": 1488,
                "end_char": 1505,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Cybersecurity Agency",
                "start_char": 1537,
                "end_char": 1570,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "whatsapp",
                "start_char": 1605,
                "end_char": 1613,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 1624,
                "end_char": 1625,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 1626,
                "end_char": 1633,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "90",
                "start_char": 1654,
                "end_char": 1656,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Casarini",
                "start_char": 1735,
                "end_char": 1743,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paragon",
                "start_char": 1834,
                "end_char": 1841,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Graphite",
                "start_char": 1864,
                "end_char": 1872,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 1982,
                "end_char": 1989,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 2033,
                "end_char": 2041,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 2070,
                "end_char": 2076,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "David Yambio",
                "start_char": 2195,
                "end_char": 2207,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sudanese",
                "start_char": 2211,
                "end_char": 2219,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Almasri",
                "start_char": 2240,
                "end_char": 2247,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paragon",
                "start_char": 2262,
                "end_char": 2269,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palermo",
                "start_char": 2343,
                "end_char": 2350,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Il Giornale",
                "start_char": 2389,
                "end_char": 2400,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 May",
                "start_char": 2476,
                "end_char": 2481,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palermo",
                "start_char": 2537,
                "end_char": 2544,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yambio",
                "start_char": 2601,
                "end_char": 2607,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 2612,
                "end_char": 2615,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sudanese",
                "start_char": 2755,
                "end_char": 2763,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Casarini",
                "start_char": 2768,
                "end_char": 2776,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sicilian",
                "start_char": 2855,
                "end_char": 2863,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 2880,
                "end_char": 2883,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yambio",
                "start_char": 2910,
                "end_char": 2916,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mediterranea",
                "start_char": 3040,
                "end_char": 3052,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Casarini",
                "start_char": 3242,
                "end_char": 3250,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mediterranea",
                "start_char": 3371,
                "end_char": 3383,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    }
]
