[
    {
        "title": "Comunali: a San Luca non si voterà, nessun candidato a sindaco",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 11 May 2024 20:29:52 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-11",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/11/comunali-a-san-luca-non-si-votera-nessun-candidato-a-sindaco_e839cb1d-4679-4926-bcad-33de71bc4d5a.html",
        "subtitle": "Il primo cittadino uscente ha deciso di non ripresentarsi",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Non si voterà l'8 e 9 giugno a\nSan Luca per l'elezione del nuovo sindaco e del Consiglio\ncomunale. Non è stata presentata, infatti, alcuna candidatura a\nsindaco ed il Comune, di conseguenza, sarà commissariato.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIl primo cittadino uscente, Bruno Bartolo, in carica dal 2019,\nha deciso di non ripresentare la propria candidatura. Bartolo,\nche era stato eletto dopo un periodo di commissariamento del\nComune per il mancato svolgimento delle elezioni a causa della\nmancanza di candidati a sindaco, spiegherà i motivi della sua\ndecisione il 21 maggio nel corso di un incontro con la\ncittadinanza. Secondo quanto si é appreso, comunque, non c'é\nstata alcuna pressione o alcun condizionamento su Bartolo perché\nnon si ricandidasse. Il disimpegno del sindaco uscente, dunque,\nsarebbe stato determinato esclusivamente da motivazioni\npolitiche.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tA San Luca, comune di poco meno di 3.500 abitanti, c'é sempre\nstata una forte presenza della 'ndrangheta. In passato il centro\ndel Reggino era considerato uno dei vertici del cosiddetto\n\"triangolo dei sequestri\", insieme a Platì e \"Natile\" di Careri.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 12,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544031.7059128,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.31",
        "en_title": "Communali: San Luca will not vote, no candidate for mayor",
        "en_content": "No vote will be taken on 8 and 9 June\nSan Luca for the election of the new mayor and the Council\nMunicipal. No application has been submitted\nmayor and the municipality, consequently, will be commissioned.\n\n\nThe first outgoing citizen, Bruno Bartolo, in office since 2019,\ndecided not to resume its candidacy. Bartolo,\nwhich had been elected after a period of commissioning\nMunicipality for failure to conduct elections due to\nlack of candidates to mayor, will explain the reasons for his\ndecision on 21 May during a meeting with the\ncitizenship. According to what you learned, however, there is no\nwas no pressure or any conditioning on Bartolo because\nHe didn't fall back. The distrust of the outgoing mayor, therefore,\nwould have been determined exclusively by reasons\npolitics.\n\n\nIn San Luca, a town of just under 3,500 inhabitants, there is always\nwas a strong presence of the 'ndrangheta. In the past the center\nof the Reggino was considered one of the leaders of the so-called\n\"Sequest triangle\", along with Plati and \"Natile\" by Careri.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The first outgoing citizen decided not to return",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "San Luca",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "9 June",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "San Luca",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council\nMunicipal",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Bruno Bartolo",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2019",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bartolo",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "21 May",
                "start_char": 501,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bartolo",
                "start_char": 638,
                "end_char": 645,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "San Luca",
                "start_char": 787,
                "end_char": 795,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "just under 3,500",
                "start_char": 807,
                "end_char": 823,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sequest",
                "start_char": 985,
                "end_char": 992,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Plati",
                "start_char": 1015,
                "end_char": 1020,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Natile",
                "start_char": 1026,
                "end_char": 1032,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Careri",
                "start_char": 1037,
                "end_char": 1043,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Vannacci su Nemo, il mondo al contrario sempre più nauseante",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 12:35:17 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/vannacci-su-nemo-il-mondo-al-contrario-sempre-piu-nauseante_4fcae2c1-ea9f-4129-88a5-6c28a3936249.html",
        "subtitle": "Il generale commenta l'artista \"non binary\" che vince Eurovision",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Il Mondo al Contrario è sempre più\nnauseante\". Roberto Vannacci, il generale sospeso dall'Esercito,\ncandidato con la Lega alle Europee, sui social commenta così la\nnotizia della vittoria all'Eurovision Song Contest 2024 di Nemo,\nl'artista che rappresenta la Svizzera ed è la prima persona di\ngenere non binario a vincere la rassegna. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544031.7592707,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.31",
        "en_title": "Vannacci on Nemo, the world on the contrary increasingly nauseating",
        "en_content": "\"The World at Contrary is increasingly\nnauseating.\" Roberto Vannacci, the general suspended by the Army,\ncandidate with the League of Europeans, on social media comments so the\nnews of the victory at the Eurovision Song Contest 2024 Nemo,\nthe artist who represents Switzerland and is the first person of\nnon-track genre to win the review.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The general comments the artist \"non binary\" who wins Eurovision",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vannacci on Nemo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Eurovision",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The World at Contrary",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Vannacci",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Army",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the League of Europeans",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Eurovision Song Contest 2024 Nemo",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Giorgia Meloni: 'Devo tutto a mia madre'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 12:50:53 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/giorgia-meloni-devo-tutto-a-mia-madre_e6bd85a6-1b03-4d2a-832c-40f8f2919c1a.html",
        "subtitle": "La premier si racconta a Leotta nello speciale Mamma Dilettante",
        "content": "\"Io sono cresciuta con una madre che non era così presente e alla fine le devo tutto. La sua era un'assenza calcolata, ha cresciuto le sue figlie dicendo te la devi cavare, la tua libertà è legata alla tua responsabilità\". Lo racconta la premier Giorgia Meloni, ospite del podcast di Diletta Leotta Mamma Dilettante. È la stessa Leotta ad annunciare lo speciale 'Festa della mamma' del podcast con un post a sorpresa su Instagram. Tra gli argomenti toccati durante la puntata, la maternità, la solidarietà tra mamme, il senso di colpa ma anche le chat di classe, le difficoltà nel conciliare le recite di fine anno con il G7.\"La mia era una madre che non ti risolveva i problemi, i problemi te li dovevi risolvere da sola e se io sono la persona che sono... lo devo a lei\", racconta ancora Meloni nel podcast.La premier parla anche della maternità: \"Diventare mamma mi ha dato tantissima stabilità. Sono diventata più pragmatica, più concreta, più attenta alle cose che hanno davvero un senso\". \"La maternità, è vero, tira fuori tutte le tue fragilità ma le mette anche a posto\".    \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 9,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544031.8920143,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.31",
        "en_title": "Giorgia Meloni: \"I owe everything to my mother\"",
        "en_content": "\"I grew up with a mother who was not so present and eventually I owe her everything. His absence was calculated, he raised his daughters, saying you have to take it, your freedom is linked to your responsibility.\" Giorgia Meloni, guest of the podcast by Diletta Leotta Mamma Dilettante. It is the same Leotta to announce the special 'Mother' Festival' of the podcast with a surprise post on Instagram. Among the topics touched during the episode, motherhood, solidarity among mothers, guilt but also class chats, difficulties in reconciling the end-of-year recitals with the G7.\"My was a mother who did not solve the problems, the problems you had to solve them yourself and if I am the person who are... I owe it to her,\" says Meloni in the podcast. The premier also speaks of motherhood: \"To become a mother has given me so much stability. I became more pragmatic, more concrete, more attentive to the things that really make sense.\" \"Maternity, it is true, brings out all your fragility but also puts them in place.\"\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The premier tells Leotta in the special amateur mother",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Leotta",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 228,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Diletta Leotta Mamma Dilettante",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leotta",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Instagram",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 728,
                "end_char": 734,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Garavaglia (Lega), attacchi di Tajani al governo incomprensibili",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 18:43:47 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/garavaglia-lega-attacchi-di-tajani-al-governo-incomprensibili_3f55db08-b1b4-4488-a280-ee1fdce7cf71.html",
        "subtitle": "L'emendamento superbonus è dell'esecutivo non del Mef",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"L'emendamento presentato sul\nsuperbonus è del governo e non del Mef, sorprende che Tajani\nabbia aderito a sua insaputa come già successo per il prelievo\nsugli extraprofitti delle banche. Si chiarisca con la premier\nMeloni e proponga dove reperire le risorse. Questi continui\nattacchi all'esecutivo sono incomprensibili\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo dichiara il senatore della Lega Massimo Garavaglia,\npresidente della commissione Finanze a palazzo Madama. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544032.026252,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:32",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.32",
        "en_title": "Garavaglia (Lega), attacks by Tajani to the incomprehensible government",
        "en_content": "\"The amendment tabled on\nsuperbonus is of the government and not of the Mef, it surprises that Tajani\nhas adhered to its unconscious as already happened for the withdrawal\non the extra profits of the banks. Make it clear with the premier\nMeloni and propose where to find resources. These continue\nattacks on the executive are incomprehensible.\"\n\n\nThe Senator of the League Massimo Garavaglia declares this,\nPresident of the Finance Committee at Madama Palace.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The superbonus amendment is the non-Mef executive",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Garavaglia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mef",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the League",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Massimo Garavaglia",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Finance Committee",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Madama Palace",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Conte, modello sulla separazione delle carriere non va rivisto",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 17:36:59 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/conte-modello-sulla-separazione-delle-carriere-non-va-rivisto_35fb09d4-b138-4a9d-8248-e418ebd2a3bd.html",
        "subtitle": "Governo vuole magistrato requirente assoggettato alla politica",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Sulla separazione delle carriere\nla nostra posizione è molto chiara. Noi non riteniamo che il\nmodello italiano vada rivisto. È un modello che si sta rivelando\nvirtuoso. I passaggi di carriera sono insignificanti\". Lo ha\ndetto il presidente del M5s Giuseppe Conte al congresso\nnazionale dell'Anm a Palermo. Il leader ha aggiunto che \"la\ndirezione\" che sta prendendo il governo è quella  del\n\"magistrato requirente assoggettato al potere politico\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544032.043057,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:32",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.32",
        "en_title": "Conte, model on career separation should not be revised",
        "en_content": "\"On the separation of careers\nour position is very clear. We do not believe that\nItalian model should be revised. It is a model that is revealed\nvirtuous. Career steps are insignificant.\" He did.\nsaid the president of the M5s Giuseppe Conte at the congress\nNational Anm in Palermo. The leader added that \"the\ndirection\" that is taking the government is that of\n\"magistrate requires subject to political power.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Government wants magistrate requiring subject to politics",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Conte",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the M5s Giuseppe Conte",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "congress",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "National Anm",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 269,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palermo",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kerry Kennedy, antisemitismo sta dilagando in America e Europa",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 17:45:46 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/kerry-kennedy-antisemitismo-sta-dilagando-in-america-e-europa_6611778a-4978-4000-9878-facc8a514e91.html",
        "subtitle": "Figlia Bob Kennedy in visita al campo di internamento di Tarsia",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Queste foto, questo museo,\ntestimoniano quello che è stato il dolore di tanti uomini e\ndonne e di tante famiglie distrutte. Un dolore che oggi sta\nriprendendo. L'antisemitismo, infatti, sta nuovamente dilagando\nin America e in Europa e questo mi addolora. La guerra ha\nprodotto atrocità inaudite e oggi assistiamo nuovamente a\nviolazioni dei diritti umani. Sono qui per dire che tutti\ndobbiamo impegnarci per fermare tutto questo\". Lo ha detto Kerry\nKennedy, figlia di Bob Kennedy e presidente onorario del \"Robert\nF. Kennedy Human Rights Italia\", parlando con i giornalisti a\nmargine della visita che ha effettuato nel campo di internamento\nfascista di Ferramonti di Tarsia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Kerry Kennedy ha partecipato alla conclusione del programma\n\"Calabria Terra di pace e fratellanza\" ed ha poi visitato il\nMuseo internazionale della memoria realizzato all'interno del\ncampo. \"Mio padre - ha aggiunto la figlia di Bob Kennedy - disse\nche ciò che serve sempre sono amore e compassione, che poi sono\ni valori che ha sempre perseguito. E queste parole, ancora oggi,\nsono fondamentali. Dobbiamo continuare a perseguire, sempre e\ncomunque, la pace\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544032.062815,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:32",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.32",
        "en_title": "Kerry Kennedy, anti-Semitism is ramping up in America and Europe",
        "en_content": "\"These photos, this museum,\nwitness what was the pain of so many men and\nwomen and many families destroyed. A pain today\nTaking it back. In fact, anti-Semitism is ramping again\nin America and in Europe and this sweetens me. The war has\nproduct unhealthy atrocities and today we see again\nviolations of human rights. I'm here to say everyone\nwe must commit ourselves to stop this.\" That's Kerry.\nKennedy, daughter of Bob Kennedy and honorary president of \"Robert\nF. Kennedy Human Rights Italia\", speaking with journalists to\nmargin of the visit in the field of internment\nFascist of Ferramonti of Tarsia.\n\n\nKerry Kennedy participated in the conclusion of the program\n\"Calabria Terra di pace e fratellanza\" and then visited the\nInternational Museum of Memory\nfield. \"My father - added Bob Kennedy's daughter - said\nthat what is always needed is love and compassion,\nthe values he has always pursued. And these words, even today,\nare fundamental. We must continue to pursue, always and\nHowever, peace.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Daughter Bob Kennedy visiting the Tarsia Internship Camp",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kerry Kennedy",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "America",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Daughter Bob Kennedy",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Tarsia Internship Camp",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "America",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kerry",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kennedy",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bob Kennedy",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Robert\nF. Kennedy",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ferramonti",
                "start_char": 582,
                "end_char": 592,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tarsia",
                "start_char": 596,
                "end_char": 602,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kerry Kennedy",
                "start_char": 606,
                "end_char": 619,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Calabria Terra di",
                "start_char": 667,
                "end_char": 684,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "International Museum of Memory",
                "start_char": 726,
                "end_char": 756,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Bob Kennedy's",
                "start_char": 783,
                "end_char": 796,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 920,
                "end_char": 925,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 1005,
                "end_char": 1038,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni, nella chat di classe commento e partecipo alle votazioni",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 18:46:42 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/meloni-nella-chat-di-classe-commento-e-partecipo-alle-votazioni_cc2dd98d-7e45-4747-bcfb-88beaa756547.html",
        "subtitle": "Non so cosa votino le altre mamme ma ho avuto molta solidarietà",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Giorgia Meloni e la chat dei genitori\ndella classe di sua figlia Ginevra. La premier ha raccontato\nanche questo aspetto della sua vita privata nella puntata del\npodcast di Diletta Leotta, Mamma Dilettante. \"Sono diventata\npresidente del Consiglio quando Ginevra iniziava la prima\nelementare. Sto nella chat, ma non riesco a frequentare quasi\nmai le mamme della classe - spiega -. Nella chat commento, dico\nla mia, voto quando mettono le votazioni, partecipo quando\nposso. Faccio la mamma, insomma\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La Leader di FdI rimarca poi la \"solidarietà\" ricevuta dalle\nmamme delle compagne della figlia. \"È tipica tra le mamme, non è\nneanche una questione di adesione politica. Io non so cosa\nvotino molte delle mamme della classe di Ginevra ma - spiega -\nfanno sempre del loro meglio per darmi una mano. Sanno che alle\nfeste non posso andare e si offrono di portare Ginevra\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544032.1116633,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:32",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.32",
        "en_title": "Meloni, in the chat class comment and participate in the votes",
        "en_content": "Giorgia Meloni and the parents' chat\nof the class of his daughter Geneva. The premier told\nalso this aspect of his private life in the episode of\nDiletta Leotta, amateur mom. \"I've become\nPresident of the Council when Geneva began the first\nElementary. I'm in the chat, but I can't hang out almost\nnever the mothers of the class - he explains -. In the chat comment, I say\nMy vote when they vote, I participate when\nI can. I'm a mom.\n\n\nThe FdI Leader then points out the \"solidarity\" received by the\nmothers of daughter's companions. \"It is typical among mothers, it is not\nIt is not a question of political accession. I don't know what\nvote many of the mothers of the Geneva class but - he explains -\nThey always do their best to help me. They know that\nI can't go and offer you to bring Geneva.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "I don't know what other mothers vote but I've had a lot of solidarity",
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "solidarity",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Geneva",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Diletta Leotta",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Geneva",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Geneva",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 675,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Geneva",
                "start_char": 789,
                "end_char": 795,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 803,
                "end_char": 836,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Eurovision, Vannacci contro Nemo: 'Mondo al contrario sempre più nauseante'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 18:53:45 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/eurovision-vannacci-contro-nemo-mondo-al-contrario-sempre-piu-nauseante_c6f6c950-9f7f-45e1-93e1-cf60ec66dea8.html",
        "subtitle": "Il generale commenta l'artista \"non binary\" che ha vinto",
        "content": "\"Il Mondo al Contrario è sempre più nauseante\". Roberto Vannacci, il generale sospeso dall'Esercito, candidato con la Lega alle Europee, sui social commenta così la notizia della vittoria all'Eurovision Song Contest 2024 di Nemo, l'artista che rappresenta la Svizzera ed è la prima persona di genere non binario a vincere la rassegna.  \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544032.1412585,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:32",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.32",
        "en_title": "Eurovision, Vannacci vs Nemo: 'I'm on the contrary getting more and more nauseating'",
        "en_content": "\"The World at Contrary is increasingly nauseating.\" Roberto Vannacci, the general suspended by the Army, candidate with the League of Europeans, commented on the news of the victory at the Eurovision Song Contest 2024 of Nemo, the artist who represents Switzerland and is the first non-traditional person to win the festival.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The general comments the artist \"non binary\" who won",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Eurovision",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vannacci vs Nemo",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The World at Contrary",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Vannacci",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Army",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the League of Europeans",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Eurovision Song Contest 2024 of",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nemo",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Toti, lunedì Spinelli di nuovo in tribunale a Genova",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 18:39:20 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/12/toti-lunedi-spinelli-di-nuovo-in-tribunale-a-genova_d91cbdb5-2e89-4c01-8b92-4f98bf7b2c84.html",
        "subtitle": "Cozzani verrà invece interrogato a Spezia per l'altra inchiesta",
        "content": "Aldo Spinelli, lo 'zar' del porto di Genova, imprenditore ai domiciliari per corruzione nell'ambito dell'inchiesta sulla Tangentopolina ligure, tornerà domani mattina davanti al gip Paola Faggioni.L'imprenditore avrebbe dovuto esser interrogato dal gip Paola Faggioni sabato ma la cancelleria del giudice ha dimenticato di inviare la pec agli avvocati Vernazza e Gatto e così la giornata tanto attesa è finita in un nulla di fatto. Domani con Aldo Spinelli, interrogatorio di garanzia anche per Francesco Moncada, ormai ex consigliere di amministrazione di Esselunga, indagato per quei 120 mila euro che Esselunga avrebbe pagato per la pubblicità sulla Terrazza Colombo di Genova. Secondo gli inquirenti, si tratterebbe di un \"finanziamento illecito\" alla Lista Toti, in cambio dello sblocco di due pratiche pendenti in regione. Oltre a Moncada sarà interrogato anche il figlio di Aldo Spinelli, Roberto. Infine verrà interrogato l'ex presidente dell'Ente Bacini in porto Vianello che secondo gli inquirenti avrebbe corrotto l'ex presidente dell'authority portuale Signorini per ottenere nuove cariche Martedì invece interrogatorio di garanzia per i due fratelli Testa, Arturo Angelo e Maurizio, ormai ex esponenti di Forza Italia in Lombardia (sono stati sospesi il 7 maggio). I due sono accusati di corruzione elettorale, aggravata dal fine di aver agevolato Cosa Nostra, entrambi sono sottoposti all'obbligo di dimora nel Comune di Boltiere (Bergamo). Alle regionali in Liguria del 20 e 21 settembre 2020, avrebbero promesso posti di lavoro per far convogliare i voti degli elettori, appartenenti alla comunità riesina di Genova e comunque siciliani, verso la lista 'Cambiamo con Toti Presidente' e verso il candidato Stefano Anzalone (che è indagato ma non colpito da 'misure'). Oltre agli interrogatori di garanzia sono previste anche le audizioni come testimone di Ilaria Cavo (che non è indagata), deputata e coordinatrice regionale della Lista Toti. Contemporaneamente domani alla Spezia il gip Mario De Bellis sottoporrà a interrogatorio di garanzia Matteo Cozzani, ex capo di gabinetto di Giovanni Toti ed ex sindaco di Portovenere. Cozzani, figura centrale dell'inchiesta spezzina (le indagini su di lui hanno portato a scoprire il caso Toti) è agli arresti domiciliari anche a Genova per corruzione elettorale aggravata perché commessa al fine di agevolare il clan mafioso dei Cammarata di Riesi e di corruzione per l'esercizio della funzione. Alla Spezia è accusato di corruzione e turbata libertà degli incanti. Già sottoposto a interrogatorio di garanzia a Genova ha prima fatto valere la possibilità di non rispondere poi, con spontanee dichiarazioni, ha negato tutti gli addebiti. Dopo di lui verrà interrogato anche il fratello Filippo, anch'esso indagato. Martedì, sempre davanti al gip della Spezia De Bellis, sarà il turno di Raffaele e Mirko Paletti, gli imprenditori milanesi, arrestati e ai domiciliari, con molti 'appetiti' a Porto Venere e sull'isola della Palmaria. Saverio Cecchi, ormai ex presidente di Confindustria nautica, accusato di corruzione insieme al direttore del Salone Nautico di Genova Alessandro Campagna, sottoposto a interrogatorio di garanzia il 10 maggio aveva chiesto la revoca della misura cautelare dell'interdizione dal ricoprire incarichi in imprese. Il gip deciderà in questi giorni.\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1715544032.1762006,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-12 22:00:32",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-12T22.00.32",
        "en_title": "Toti, Monday Spinelli again in court in Genoa",
        "en_content": "Aldo Spinelli, the 'zar' of the port of Genoa, entrepreneur to domiciliari for corruption in the within of the investigation on the Ligurian Tangentopolina, will return tomorrow morning in front of the gip Paola Faggioni. The entrepreneur should have been questioned by the gip Paola Faggioni Saturday but the chancellor of the judge forgot to send the pect to lawyers Vernazza and Gatto and so the long-awaited day ended in a nothing fact. Tomorrow with Aldo Spinelli, questioning of guarantee also for Francesco Moncada, now former board of directors of Esselunga, investigated for those 120 thousand euros that Esselunga would pay for advertising on the Terrace Colombo of Genoa. According to the polluters, it would be a \"unfair financing\" to the Toti List, in exchange for the unblocking of two practices hanging in the region. In addition to Moncada the son of Aldo Spinelli, Roberto will be questioned. Finally will be questioned the former president of the agency Bacini in port Vianello that according to the inquirents would corrupt the former president of the harbour authority Signorini in order to obtain new charges Tuesday instead questioning of guarantee for the two brothers Testa, Arturo Angelo and Maurizio, now exponents of Forza Italia in Lombardy (they were suspended on May 7). The two are accused of electoral corruption, aggravated by the purpose of facilitating Our Thing, both are subject to the obligation of residence in the Municipality of Boltiere (Bergamo). To the regionals in Liguria of 20 and 21 September 2020, they would have promised jobs to convey the votes of the voters, belonging to the Riesine community of Genoa and however Sicilian, towards the list 'Let's change with Toti President' and towards the candidate Stefano Anzalone (who is investigated but not hit by 'measures'). In addition to the warranty interrogators, the auditions as a witness to Ilaria Cavo (which is not investigated), the deputy and regional coordinator of the Toti List. At the same time tomorrow at La Spezia the gip Mario De Bellis will submit to questioning of guarantee Matteo Cozzani, former chief of cabinet of Giovanni Toti and former mayor of Portovenere. Cozzani, central figure of the spezzina investigation (the investigation on him led to discover the Toti case) is under house arrest also in Genoa for aggravated electoral corruption because committed in order to facilitate the Mafia clan of the Cammarata of Riesi and corruption for the exercise of the function. Alla Spezia is accused of corruption and troubled freedom of the incanti. Already subjected to questioning of guarantee to Genoa has first asserted the possibility not to answer then, with spontaneous declarations, has denied all objections. After him, his brother Philip will also be questioned. Tuesday, always in front of the gip of La Spezia De Bellis, will be the turn of Raffaele and Mirko Paletti, the Milanese entrepreneurs, arrested and the domiciles, with many 'appeti' in Porto Venere and on the island of Palmaria. Saverio Cecchi, now former president of Confindustria nautica, accused of corruption along with the director of the Salone Nautico di Genova Alessandro Campagna, subjected to questioning of guarantee on May 10 had asked the revocation of the precautionary measure of the interdiction from covering assignments in enterprises. The gip will decide these days.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Cozzani will instead be questioned in Spezia for the other investigation",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spinelli",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cozzani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spezia",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Aldo Spinelli",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 'zar'",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ligurian Tangentopolina",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "morning",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paola Faggioni",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vernazza",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gatto",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 387,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aldo Spinelli",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Francesco Moncada",
                "start_char": 504,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esselunga",
                "start_char": 556,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "those 120 thousand euros",
                "start_char": 584,
                "end_char": 608,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esselunga",
                "start_char": 614,
                "end_char": 623,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Terrace Colombo",
                "start_char": 653,
                "end_char": 672,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 676,
                "end_char": 681,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 796,
                "end_char": 799,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moncada",
                "start_char": 848,
                "end_char": 855,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aldo Spinelli",
                "start_char": 867,
                "end_char": 880,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto",
                "start_char": 882,
                "end_char": 889,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vianello",
                "start_char": 987,
                "end_char": 995,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "inquirents",
                "start_char": 1018,
                "end_char": 1028,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Signorini",
                "start_char": 1089,
                "end_char": 1098,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 1130,
                "end_char": 1137,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1179,
                "end_char": 1182,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Testa",
                "start_char": 1192,
                "end_char": 1197,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arturo Angelo",
                "start_char": 1199,
                "end_char": 1212,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maurizio",
                "start_char": 1217,
                "end_char": 1225,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 1244,
                "end_char": 1256,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombardy",
                "start_char": 1260,
                "end_char": 1268,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 7",
                "start_char": 1293,
                "end_char": 1298,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1305,
                "end_char": 1308,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Our Thing",
                "start_char": 1388,
                "end_char": 1397,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Municipality of Boltiere",
                "start_char": 1450,
                "end_char": 1478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Liguria",
                "start_char": 1510,
                "end_char": 1517,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "20 and 21 September 2020",
                "start_char": 1521,
                "end_char": 1545,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riesine",
                "start_char": 1629,
                "end_char": 1636,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 1650,
                "end_char": 1655,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sicilian",
                "start_char": 1668,
                "end_char": 1676,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 1714,
                "end_char": 1718,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Stefano Anzalone",
                "start_char": 1756,
                "end_char": 1772,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilaria Cavo",
                "start_char": 1895,
                "end_char": 1906,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 1979,
                "end_char": 1983,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 2007,
                "end_char": 2015,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Spezia",
                "start_char": 2019,
                "end_char": 2028,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Matteo Cozzani",
                "start_char": 2093,
                "end_char": 2107,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giovanni Toti",
                "start_char": 2136,
                "end_char": 2149,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Portovenere",
                "start_char": 2170,
                "end_char": 2181,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Toti",
                "start_char": 2283,
                "end_char": 2287,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 2324,
                "end_char": 2329,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mafia",
                "start_char": 2411,
                "end_char": 2416,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alla Spezia",
                "start_char": 2497,
                "end_char": 2508,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Genoa",
                "start_char": 2620,
                "end_char": 2625,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 2630,
                "end_char": 2635,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Philip",
                "start_char": 2762,
                "end_char": 2768,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 2794,
                "end_char": 2801,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "De Bellis",
                "start_char": 2843,
                "end_char": 2852,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raffaele",
                "start_char": 2874,
                "end_char": 2882,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mirko Paletti",
                "start_char": 2887,
                "end_char": 2900,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milanese",
                "start_char": 2906,
                "end_char": 2914,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Porto Venere",
                "start_char": 2980,
                "end_char": 2992,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palmaria",
                "start_char": 3014,
                "end_char": 3022,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saverio Cecchi",
                "start_char": 3024,
                "end_char": 3038,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Confindustria",
                "start_char": 3064,
                "end_char": 3077,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Salone Nautico",
                "start_char": 3140,
                "end_char": 3154,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Genova Alessandro Campagna",
                "start_char": 3158,
                "end_char": 3184,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 10",
                "start_char": 3227,
                "end_char": 3233,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "gip",
                "start_char": 3354,
                "end_char": 3357,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "these days",
                "start_char": 3370,
                "end_char": 3380,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    }
]
