[
    {
        "title": "Antimafia ascolterà Emiliano e procuratore Rossi",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:32:26 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/23/antimafia-ascoltera-emiliano-e-procuratore-rossi_ea48cc8e-4a68-4e34-ba43-3f4d9bcdc6e3.html",
        "subtitle": "Ma non ancora decise date per audizione governatore e magistrato",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente della Regione Puglia,\nMichele Emiliano, e il procuratore capo di Bari, Roberto Rossi,\nsaranno ascoltati in commissione parlamentare antimafia, in\nmerito alle recenti vicende e inchieste legate ai rischi di\ninfiltrazioni mafiose nel territorio pugliese e in particolare a\nBari: lo ha deciso l'ufficio di presidenza della commissione, a\nquanto si apprende da fonti, secondo cui le date non sarebbero\nancora state fissate per aspetti di ordine tecnico. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873628.8031836,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:28",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.28",
        "en_title": "Antimafia will listen to Emiliano and prosecutor Rossi",
        "en_content": "The President of the Puglia Region,\nMichele Emiliano, and the attorney head of Bari, Roberto Rossi,\nwill be heard in the parliamentary committee antimafia, in\non recent events and investigations related to risks\nmafia infiltration in Puglia and in particular\nBari: the chairmanship office of the committee decided,\nhow much you learn from sources, according to which dates would not be\nare still set for technical aspects.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "But not yet decided dates for audition governor and magistrate",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Antimafia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Emiliano",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rossi",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Puglia Region",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michele Emiliano",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bari",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Rossi",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Puglia",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bari",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Sondaggi: YouTrend, FdI al 27,8%, salgono Pd e M5s",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:23:16 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/sondaggi-youtrend-fdi-al-278-salgono-pd-e-m5s_50c2ab5f-899b-4005-8f05-7b38a89317bd.html",
        "subtitle": " Il partito di Giorgia Meloni è sostanzialmente stabile ",
        "content": "Se si votasse oggi Fratelli d'Italia sarebbe saldamente il primo partito con il 27,8% dei consensi, secondo l'ultimo sondaggio di Quorum/YouTrend per Sky TG24. Il partito di Giorgia Meloni è sostanzialmente stabile (+0,1%) rispetto a due settimane fa. Crescono in modo significativo Pd (20,5%, +0,7%) e Movimento 5 Stelle (16,5%, +0,5). Più dietro sono in risalita anche Stati Uniti d'Europa (5%), AVS (4,4%) e Azione (3,3%).     Questi i risultati e le variazioni rispetto all'8 aprile: Fratelli d'Italia (27,8%; +0,1%), Partito Democratico (20,5%; +0,7%), Movimento 5 Stelle (16,5%; +0,5%), Forza Italia - Noi Moderati (7,6%; -0,3%), Lega (7,2%; -0,3%), Stati Uniti d'Europa (5,0%; +0,4%), Alleanza Verdi-Sinistra (4,4%, +0,5%); Azione (3,3%; +0,2%), Pace Terra Dignità (1,9%; -0,3%), Libertà (1,6%; +0,0%).     Il Sondaggio svolto con metodologia CAWI tra il 17 e il 19 Aprile 2024 su un campione di 801 intervistati rappresentativi della popolazione maggiorenne residente in Italia, indagate per quote di genere ed età incrociate, stratificate per titolo di studio e ripartizione ISTAT di residenza. Il margine d'errore è del +/- 3,5% con un intervallo di confidenza del 95% .    \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 17,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.582977,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Surveys: YouTrend, FdI at 27.8%, rise Pd and M5s",
        "en_content": "If you voted today, Brothers of Italy would be firmly the first party with 27.8% of consents, according to the latest Quorum/YouTrend survey for Sky TG24. Giorgia Meloni's party is substantially stable (+0.1%) compared to two weeks ago. They grow significantly Pd (20.5%, +0.7%) and Movement 5 Stars (16.5%, +0.5). Further up, the United States of Europe (5%), AVS (4.4%) and Action (3.3%). These are the results and changes compared to 8 April: Brothers of Italy (27.8%; +0.1%), Democratic Party (20.5%; +0.7%), Movement 5 Stars (16.5%; +0.5%), Forza Italia - Noi Moderati (7.6%; -0.3%), League (7.2%; -0.3%), United States of Europe (5.0%; +0.4%), Green- Left Alliance (4.4%, +0.5%); Action (3.3%; +0.2%), Peace Earth Dignity (1.9%; -0.3%), Freedom (1.6%; +0.0%). The Survey carried out with CAWI methodology between 17 and 19 April 2024 on a sample of 801 representative interviewees of the adult population resident in Italy, investigated for gender and cross age quotas, layered by title of study and ISTAT division of residence. The error margin is +/- 3.5% with a 95% confidence interval.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The party of Giorgia Meloni is substantially stable",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "YouTrend",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "27.8%",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "M5s",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brothers of Italy",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "27.8%",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Quorum/YouTrend",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sky",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni's",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two weeks ago",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "20.5%",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.7%",
                "start_char": 272,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Movement 5 Stars",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "16.5%",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States of Europe",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5%",
                "start_char": 356,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "AVS",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4.4%",
                "start_char": 366,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "3.3%",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "8 April",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brothers of Italy",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 463,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "27.8%",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 470,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.1%",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Democratic Party",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "20.5%",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 503,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.7%",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Movement 5 Stars",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 529,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "16.5%",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.5%",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia -",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 560,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "7.6%",
                "start_char": 575,
                "end_char": 579,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "7.2%",
                "start_char": 597,
                "end_char": 601,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "United States of Europe",
                "start_char": 611,
                "end_char": 634,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5.0%",
                "start_char": 636,
                "end_char": 640,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.4%",
                "start_char": 642,
                "end_char": 647,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Left Alliance",
                "start_char": 657,
                "end_char": 670,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4.4%",
                "start_char": 672,
                "end_char": 676,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Action",
                "start_char": 686,
                "end_char": 692,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3.3%",
                "start_char": 694,
                "end_char": 698,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Peace Earth Dignity",
                "start_char": 708,
                "end_char": 727,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1.9%",
                "start_char": 729,
                "end_char": 733,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Freedom",
                "start_char": 743,
                "end_char": 750,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.6%",
                "start_char": 752,
                "end_char": 756,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "+0.0%",
                "start_char": 758,
                "end_char": 763,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "CAWI",
                "start_char": 794,
                "end_char": 798,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "between 17 and 19 April 2024",
                "start_char": 811,
                "end_char": 839,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "801",
                "start_char": 855,
                "end_char": 858,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 923,
                "end_char": 928,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ISTAT",
                "start_char": 1006,
                "end_char": 1011,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3.5%",
                "start_char": 1059,
                "end_char": 1063,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "95%",
                "start_char": 1071,
                "end_char": 1074,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mattarella, i problemi non aspettano i tempi della Ue",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:08:29 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/mattarella-i-problemi-non-aspettano-i-tempi-della-ue_e6882ca2-803b-442f-b76e-ede9d9264501.html",
        "subtitle": "Riformare subito le modalità del processo decisionale",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Tra le riforme essenziali che\naspettano l'Unione europea ci sono certamente \"le modalità del\nprocesso decisionale, perchè i problemi in questo mondo si\npresentano velocemente e richiedono risposte tempestive:\nl'Unione europea non è in questa condizione, non è in condizione\ndi assumere risposte tempestive perchè i problemi non aspettano\"\ni tempi di questa Europa. Lo ha detto il presidente della\nRepubblica, Sergio Mattarella, parlando da Brdo in occasione dei\n20 anni dell'entrata della Slovenia nell'Unione europea. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 18,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.6181607,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Mattarella, problems do not wait for the times of the EU",
        "en_content": "Among the essential reforms that\nwaiting for the European Union there are certainly \"the modalities of\ndecision-making, because the problems in this world are\npresent fast and require prompt responses:\nThe European Union is not in this condition, it is not in condition\nto take prompt answers because problems do not wait\"\nthe times of this Europe. That's what the president said.\nRepublic, Sergio Mattarella, speaking from Brdo on the occasion of\n20 years of Slovenia's entry into the European Union.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Reforming the decision-making procedures immediately",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The European Union",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Mattarella",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brdo",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "20 years",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Slovenia",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 482,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Imbavagliati, a Napoli voci libere dal mondo in guerra",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:03:40 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/imbavagliati-a-napoli-voci-libere-dal-mondo-in-guerra_7884f88d-e078-4455-8fc4-2e0e0d24ef1b.html",
        "subtitle": "ElSayed premio Fonseca, domani al festival focus internazionali",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Voci libere da un mondo tra guerre\ne censure: con la giornalista egiziano-palestinese Youmna\nElSayed, premio Pimentel Fonseca, arrivano a Napoli da Ucraina\nal Medio Oriente, Siria, Repubblica del Congo, Afghanistan, per \n\"Imbavagliati\", fino al 24 aprile, all'Istituto Italiano degli\nStudi Filosofici, nona edizione del Festival Internazionale di\nGiornalismo Civile, ideato e con la direzione artistica di\nDésirée Klain, titolo di quest'anno \"Io ho visto - Strumenti di\npace\". \n   La corrispondente dalla Striscia di Gaza di Al Jazeera\nEnglish, premiata nel nome dell'eroina dei moti del 1799, prima\ndi ricevere il riconoscimento ha voluto recarsi a Piazza Mercato\nche fu il luogo delle esecuzioni dei martiri della Repubblica\nNapoletana. Domani alle 10 i forum 'Guerre Dimenticate' al via\ncon \"Messico, la mattanza dei giornalisti\", partecipa la\ngiornalista messicana Kena A. Megan. Si parlerà del conflitto in\nUcraina nell'incontro 'Cessate il fuoco!', con la testimonianza\ndei giornalisti Zhanna Zukova (Ucraina), Antonio Musella e del\nconsole ucraino a Napoli Maksym Kovalenko. All'incontro 'Giù le\nmani dal Congo' parteciperanno la presidente ivoriana della\nconsulta immigrati e di Articolo21 Campania, Fatou Diako e i\ngiornalisti Enzo Nucci e Antonella Napoli. Concluderà il ciclo\ndi incontri internazionali 'Afghanistan, il paese senza\ndiritti', con interventi dei giornalisti afghani Farzana Jadid,\nNajeeb Farzad, coordina la giornalista Barbara Schiavulli. A\nseguire 'Verità e giustizia' l'omaggio a Mario Paciolla, con i\ngenitori Anna Motta e Giuseppe Paciolla, interverrà il\ngiornalista Guido Piccoli dell'associazione \"CultHurra\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il festival, prodotto da O.R.M.U., è realizzato\ndall'associazione \"Periferie del Mondo - Periferia Immaginaria\"\ncon il patrocinio del Comune di Napoli - che per l'anno 2024\ninoltre promuove e finanzia il Premio Pimentel Fonseca -  in\ncollaborazione con l'Istituto Italiano per gli Studi Filosofici,\nArticolo21, Ordine Nazionale dei Giornalisti, Federazione\nNazionale della Stampa, Sindacato Unitario Giornalisti della\nCampania e il patrocinio di Amnesty International Italia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 16,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.6444194,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Embarrased, in Naples free voices from the world at war",
        "en_content": "Voices free from a world of wars\nand censures: with the Egyptian-Palestinian journalist Youmna\nElSayed, Pimentel Fonseca award, arrive in Naples from Ukraine\nto the Middle East, Syria, Republic of the Congo, Afghanistan, for\n\"Imbavagliati\", until 24 April, at the Italian Institute of\nPhilosophical studies, ninth edition of the International Festival\nCivil Journalism, conceived and artistic direction\nDésirée Klain, title of this year \"I have seen - Instruments of\npeace.\"\nThe correspondent from the Gaza Strip of Al Jazeera\nEnglish, awarded in the name of the heroine of the moths of 1799, first\nto receive the award wanted to go to Piazza Mercato\nwhich was the site of the executions of the martyrs of the Republic\nNeapolitan. Tomorrow at 10 am the forums 'Guerre Forgette' at the start\nwith \"Mexico, the morning of journalists\", participates\nMexican journalist Kena A. Megan. We will talk about the conflict in\nUkraine in the meeting 'Cessate the fire!', with the testimony\njournalists Zhanna Zukova (Ukraine), Antonio Musella and the\nUkrainian consul in Naples Maksym Kovalenko. To the meeting 'More\nhands from the Congo will participate the Ivorian president of\nconsult immigrants and Article21 Campania, Fatou Diako and the\njournalists Enzo Nucci and Antonella Napoli. It will end the cycle\nof international meetings 'Afghanistan, the country without\nrights, with Afghan journalists Farzana Jadid,\nNajeeb Farzad coordinates journalist Barbara Schiavulli. A\nfollow 'Truth and justice' the tribute to Mario Paciolla, with the\nparents Anna Motta and Giuseppe Paciolla, will intervene the\njournalist Guido Piccoli of the association \"CultHurra\".\n\n\nThe festival, produced by O.R.M.U., is realized\nfrom the association \"World suburbs - Imaginary suburbs\"\nwith the patronage of the Municipality of Naples - that for the year 2024\nalso promotes and finances the Pimentel Fonseca Prize - in\ncollaboration with the Italian Institute for Philosophical Studies,\nArticle21, National Order of Journalists, Federation\nNational Press Office, Journalist Union\nCampania and the patronage of Amnesty International Italy.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "ElSayed Fonseca Award, tomorrow at the international focus festival",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ElSayed Fonseca Award",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Egyptian",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Youmna",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ElSayed",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Republic of the",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Congo",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afghanistan",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Imbavagliati",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "24 April",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Institute of\nPhilosophical",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ninth",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Festival",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Civil Journalism",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 368,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Désirée Klain",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "this year",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 436,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 512,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al Jazeera",
                "start_char": 516,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "English",
                "start_char": 527,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "the moths of 1799",
                "start_char": 574,
                "end_char": 591,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 593,
                "end_char": 598,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza Mercato",
                "start_char": 636,
                "end_char": 650,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Republic\nNeapolitan",
                "start_char": 706,
                "end_char": 729,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 731,
                "end_char": 739,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 am the forums '",
                "start_char": 743,
                "end_char": 761,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guerre Forgette'",
                "start_char": 761,
                "end_char": 777,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 797,
                "end_char": 803,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the morning",
                "start_char": 805,
                "end_char": 816,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 847,
                "end_char": 854,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kena A. Megan",
                "start_char": 866,
                "end_char": 879,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 916,
                "end_char": 923,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cessate",
                "start_char": 940,
                "end_char": 947,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zhanna Zukova",
                "start_char": 991,
                "end_char": 1004,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 1006,
                "end_char": 1013,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Musella",
                "start_char": 1016,
                "end_char": 1031,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 1040,
                "end_char": 1049,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 1060,
                "end_char": 1066,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congo",
                "start_char": 1121,
                "end_char": 1126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ivorian",
                "start_char": 1148,
                "end_char": 1155,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Article21 Campania",
                "start_char": 1192,
                "end_char": 1210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fatou Diako",
                "start_char": 1212,
                "end_char": 1223,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Enzo Nucci",
                "start_char": 1244,
                "end_char": 1254,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonella Napoli",
                "start_char": 1259,
                "end_char": 1275,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afghanistan",
                "start_char": 1326,
                "end_char": 1337,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afghan",
                "start_char": 1372,
                "end_char": 1378,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Farzana Jadid",
                "start_char": 1391,
                "end_char": 1404,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Najeeb Farzad",
                "start_char": 1406,
                "end_char": 1419,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Barbara Schiavulli",
                "start_char": 1443,
                "end_char": 1461,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mario Paciolla",
                "start_char": 1507,
                "end_char": 1521,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anna Motta",
                "start_char": 1540,
                "end_char": 1550,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppe Paciolla",
                "start_char": 1555,
                "end_char": 1572,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guido Piccoli",
                "start_char": 1604,
                "end_char": 1617,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "CultHurra",
                "start_char": 1638,
                "end_char": 1647,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "O.R.M.U.",
                "start_char": 1678,
                "end_char": 1686,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the year 2024",
                "start_char": 1817,
                "end_char": 1830,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Institute for Philosophical Studies",
                "start_char": 1909,
                "end_char": 1956,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "National Press Office",
                "start_char": 2011,
                "end_char": 2032,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Journalist Union",
                "start_char": 2034,
                "end_char": 2050,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Campania",
                "start_char": 2051,
                "end_char": 2059,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amnesty International Italy",
                "start_char": 2081,
                "end_char": 2108,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Rossi, 'istruttoria sul caso Scurati, dalla Rai nessuna censura'",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:29:24 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/rossi-istruttoria-sul-caso-scurati-dalla-rai-nessuna-censura_c6c1f5e2-feb3-4836-811b-96973299fa9f.html",
        "subtitle": "\"Palinsesto pluralista, libertà espressiva unica in Italia\"",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"In queste ore in cui si susseguono\nnotizie inverosimili e ricostruzioni surreali, mi trovo\ncostretto ad intervenire per cercare di frenare l'ennesimo\ntentativo di aggressione nei confronti della Rai. È in atto\nun'istruttoria - afferma Rossi in una lunga nota - per\nverificare se ci siano stati errori relativi alla mancata\npartecipazione dello scrittore Scurati alla trasmissione Che\nsarà di Serena Bortone, partecipazione che era prevista nel\ncomunicato stampa ufficiale uscito la sera prima della puntata\nin questione\". Lo dice il direttore generale  di Viale Mazzini\nGiampaolo Rossi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il senso di responsabilità - sottolinea Rossi -\nrichiederebbe di attendere il termine dell'istruttoria prima di\nlasciarsi andare a commenti o conclusioni che rischiano di\nrisultare meri polveroni mediatici, come altre volte in passato.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tMi preme sottolineare che il direttore generale di Corporate non\nha alcuna competenza sugli aspetti editoriali (dentro i quali\nricade anche la scelta degli ospiti nelle trasmissioni). Nello\nstesso tempo, sono obbligato a ricordare che la narrazione di\nuna Rai che censura è del tutto priva di fondamento\".   \n   \"Oggi - spiega Rossi - il palinsesto e la programmazione del\nservizio pubblico dimostrano pluralismo, varietà di punti di\nvista, di visioni e culture, finalizzate a garantire la maggior\neterogeneità di racconti possibile. All'interno di un'offerta\nquotidiana fatta di informazione, intrattenimento, fiction,\ncinema, divulgazione culturale, e di una incredibile ricchezza\ndi conduzioni, artisti e ospiti, la Rai dimostra di avere una\nlibertà espressiva unica in Italia\".   \n   \"Mentre imperversa su giornali e televisioni concorrenti\nl'ennesimo attacco strumentale al servizio pubblico, la Rai -\ninsiste il dg - in tutte le sue strutture sta lavorando alla\nrealizzazione del nuovo piano industriale proprio con\nl'obiettivo di trasformare questa azienda in una moderna digital\nmedia company e di fronteggiare al meglio le grandi sfide a cui\nè chiamata nel prossimo futuro. La stessa approvazione da parte\ndel Cda del bilancio, con un rafforzamento dei fondamentali\neconomici, è la dimostrazione dell'importante lavoro fatto in\nquesti mesi per rimettere la Rai in linea con un percorso di\nsostenibilità economica e finanziaria. Lavoro di cui ovviamente\nnon c'è traccia nel dibattito attorno all'azienda\".   \n   \"La Rai è un patrimonio della nostra Nazione, oltre che un\nhub industriale che sostiene intere filiere produttive italiane,\na partire da quella dell'audiovisivo. Credo sia mio dovere\ndifendere il lavoro quotidiano che viene fatto da migliaia di\nlavoratrici e lavoratori - conclude - per continuare a garantire\nuno dei più grandi servizi pubblici d'Europa\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.6752403,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Rossi, 'instructor on the Scurati case, by Rai no censorship'",
        "en_content": "\"In these hours,\nnews inverosimili and surreal reconstructions, I find myself\nforced to intervene in order to try to restrain the yet another\nattempt to attack the Rai. It is in place\nan instructor - says Rossi in a long note - for\ncheck if there have been errors related to failure\nparticipation of the writer Scurati to the broadcast That\nwill be of Serena Bortone, participation that was previewed in\nofficial press release issued the evening before the bet\nin question.\" The Director General of Viale Mazzini says so\nGiampaolo Rossi.\n\n\n\"The sense of responsibility - says Rossi -\nwould require to wait for the term of the instructor before\nlet go to comments or conclusions that risk\nto be mere medial powders, like other times in the past.\n\n\nI would like to stress that the Director-General of Corporate does not\nhas no competence on the editorial aspects (within which\nis also the choice of guests in broadcasts). The\nat the same time, I am obliged to remember that the narrative of\na Rai that censorship is completely without foundation.\"\n\"Today - says Rossi - the palinsest and the programming of\npublic service demonstrate pluralism, variety of points of\nview, visions and cultures, aimed at guaranteeing the greatest\nheterogeneity of possible stories. Within an offer\ndaily made of information, entertainment, fiction,\ncinema, cultural dissemination, and an incredible wealth\nof conductors, artists and guests, the Rai proves to have a\nfreedom of expression unique in Italy\".\n\"While imperverse in newspapers and competing televisions\nthe new instrumental attack on the public service, the Rai -\ninsists the dg - in all its structures is working on\nrealization of the new industrial plan with\nthe goal of transforming this company into a modern digital\nmedia company and best face the great challenges to which\nis called in the near future. The same approval by\nof the Budget Board, with a strengthening of the fundamentals\neconomics, is the demonstration of the important work done in\nthese months to return the Rai in line with a path of\neconomic and financial sustainability. Work of which of course\nthere is no trace in the debate around the company.\"\n\"The Rai is a heritage of our nation, as well as a\nindustrial hub that supports entire Italian production chains,\nfrom that of audiovisual. I think it's my duty.\ndefend the daily work that is done by thousands of\nworkers and workers - he concludes - to continue to ensure\none of Europe's largest public services.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "\"Palinsesest pluralist, freedom of expression unique in Italy\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Scurati",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai no censorship'",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "these hours",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rossi",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Scurati",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Serena Bortone",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the evening",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Viale Mazzini",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 512,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giampaolo Rossi",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 1047,
                "end_char": 1052,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 1278,
                "end_char": 1283,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1478,
                "end_char": 1483,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Budget Board",
                "start_char": 1874,
                "end_char": 1890,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "these months",
                "start_char": 1995,
                "end_char": 2007,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "\"The Rai",
                "start_char": 2165,
                "end_char": 2173,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 2252,
                "end_char": 2259,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 2365,
                "end_char": 2374,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 2444,
                "end_char": 2450,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il Pd anche al Senato presenta un odg sul diritto di aborto",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:31:44 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/il-pd-anche-al-senato-presenta-un-odg-sul-diritto-di-aborto_7b444e70-1e95-430c-8528-e8ae1bc1782b.html",
        "subtitle": "C'è pure un emendamento soppressivo della norma sui consultori",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Partito democratico ha presentato\nanche al Senato un ordine del giorno al decreto legge Pnrr che\nriguarda il diritto all'aborto e il ruolo dei consultori. Il\ndispositivo ricalca gli impegni del testo già presentato alla\nCamera. L'odg a prima firma Beatrice Lorenzin e Francesco Boccia\npunta a assicurare che non sia minata in alcun modo la piena\nattuazione della legge 194 e non venga ristretto \"il diritto\ndelle donne ad avere accesso ad un'interruzione volontaria di\ngravidanza\". A Senato i Dem hanno depositato anche un\nemendamento soppressivo, sempre al dl Pnrr, della norma\ncontestata sui consultori. Il provvedimento è atteso in Aula a\nPalazzo Madama da domani. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 14,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.7010808,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "The PD also presents an odg on the right of abortion",
        "en_content": "The Democratic Party presented\nalso to the Senate an order of the day to the law decree Pnrr che\nthe right to abortion and the role of counsellors. The\nthe text already submitted to the\nRoom. L'odg a prima firma Beatrice Lorenzin e Francesco Boccia\naims to ensure that it is not minata in any way the full\nImplementation of Law 194 and is not restricted \"the right\nof women having access to a voluntary interruption of\npregnancy.\" In the Senate the Dem also deposited a\nI would like to ask the Commission to take the necessary steps to ensure that the Commission is able to take the necessary measures.\ndisputed on the consultors. The measure is expected in the Chamber\nMadame Palace since tomorrow.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "There is also a suppressive amendment to the Consultative Standard.",
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Democratic Party",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beatrice Lorenzin",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Implementation of Law 194",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 494,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 552,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Chamber\nMadame Palace",
                "start_char": 658,
                "end_char": 683,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 690,
                "end_char": 698,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Fedriga, aumentati di 37 milioni gli investimenti Usa in Fvg",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:11:10 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/fedriga-aumentati-di-37-milioni-gli-investimenti-usa-in-fvg_5564c919-5859-43f5-953b-f235259452ff.html",
        "subtitle": "Durante la missione è stata spiegata la strategicità dell'area",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Abbiamo aumentato di 37 milioni\ndi euro gli investimenti degli Stati Uniti in Friuli Venezia\nGiulia, quindi c'è un maggior interesse deciso degli Usa verso\nil Fvg, credo che sia un percorso che dobbiamo continuare a\ncostruire negli anni\". Lo ha affermato, oggi a Trieste, il\npresidente del Friuli Venezia Giulia, Massimiliano Fedriga, di\nrientro dalla sua missione negli Usa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Non a caso la mia presenza più volte negli Stati Uniti - ha\nspiegato Fedriga, a margine di una cerimonia - ha mirato proprio\na questo. In passato ho visto missioni istituzionali che\ntoccavano un po' alcune parti del mondo traducendosi poi solo in\nvisite di cortesia. Uno deve metterci impegno, sapere che c'è la\ncostanza dei rapporti, continuare a costruire e sviluppare. Mi\nauguro anche che chi verrà dopo di me potrà proseguire un\nrapporto strategico con gli Usa\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Della delegazione della Regione hanno fatto parte anche\nalcune imprese, che, come puntualizzato da Fedriga, \"hanno\ncreato un ottimo interesse anche facendo conoscere una realtà\nche negli Usa non è molto nota. Tutti guardano all'Italia, ma\npoi nel racconto tradizionale ci sono Milano, Roma, Firenze,\nNapoli. Invece è stata spiegata anche dai protagonisti del mondo\ndell'impresa la strategicità del Fvg, anche dal punto di vista\nlogistico. Abbiamo riferito che il nostro mercato è il cuore di\nun'area europea strategica come il Centro sud Europa e questo ha\ncreato molto interesse. Sono convinto che anche da questo\npotranno svilupparsi buone opportunità\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Fedriga ha fatto poi riferimento agli incontri istituzionali\nin Virginia, \"uno dei principali porti della East coast\". \"Dalla\nEast coast penetra tutto il mercato degli Usa - ha concluso -\nquindi ci interessa moltissimo. Poi stiamo lavorando sulla parte\nagricoltura: loro hanno intenzione di sviluppare tutta la parte\nvitivinicola e noi possiamo essere fornitori importanti\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 13,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.7170177,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Original news Fedriga, increased of 37 million US investments in Fvg",
        "en_content": "\"We have increased by 37 million\nof euro the investments of the United States in Friuli Venezia\nGiulia, therefore there is a greater interest of the US towards\nthe Fvg, I think it's a path we have to continue\nbuild over the years.\" Today in Trieste, the\npresident of Friuli Venezia Giulia, Massimiliano Fedriga, di\nreturn from his mission to the U.S.\n\n\n\"Not by chance my presence several times in the United States - it has\nexplained Fedriga, in the margin of a ceremony - it has targeted own\nto this. In the past I have seen institutional missions\nthey touched a little bit some parts of the world translating then only in\ncourtesy visits. One must make us commitment, know that there is\nConsistent relationships, continue to build and develop. ♪\nI also hope that those who will come after me will continue a\nstrategic relationship with the US.\"\n\n\nThe Delegation of the Region also took part\nsome enterprises, which, as pointed out by Fedriga, \"have\ncreated an excellent interest also making known a reality\nthat in the US is not much known. Everyone looks at Italy, but\nthen in the traditional story there are Milan, Rome, Florence,\nNaples. But it was also explained by the protagonists of the world\nof the enterprise the strategicity of the Fvg, also from the point of view\nlogistics. We have reported that our market is the heart of\na strategic European area such as South Europe Centre and this has\ncreated much interest. I am convinced that even from this\nwill develop good opportunities.\"\n\n\nFedriga then referred to institutional meetings\nin Virginia, one of the main East Coast ports. \"From\nEast coast penetrates the entire US market - it has concluded -\nso we care so much. Then we're working on the part\nagriculture: they intend to develop the whole part\nwine and we can be important suppliers.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "During the mission the strategicity of the area has been explained",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Fedriga",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "37 million",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fvg",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "37 million",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friuli Venezia",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giulia",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fvg",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the years",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trieste",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friuli",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezia",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giulia",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Massimiliano Fedriga",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fedriga",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 641,
                "end_char": 644,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "♪",
                "start_char": 746,
                "end_char": 747,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 842,
                "end_char": 844,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Region",
                "start_char": 871,
                "end_char": 877,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fedriga",
                "start_char": 936,
                "end_char": 943,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 1021,
                "end_char": 1023,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1061,
                "end_char": 1066,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 1112,
                "end_char": 1117,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 1119,
                "end_char": 1123,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 1135,
                "end_char": 1141,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fvg",
                "start_char": 1244,
                "end_char": 1247,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 1349,
                "end_char": 1357,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Europe Centre",
                "start_char": 1371,
                "end_char": 1390,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fedriga",
                "start_char": 1498,
                "end_char": 1505,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Virginia",
                "start_char": 1549,
                "end_char": 1557,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 1559,
                "end_char": 1562,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Coast",
                "start_char": 1575,
                "end_char": 1585,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "East coast",
                "start_char": 1599,
                "end_char": 1609,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 1632,
                "end_char": 1634,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Schlein: 'Non ci sarà il mio nome nel simbolo, è una proposta divisiva'",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:09:39 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/schlein-non-ci-sara-il-mio-nome-nel-simbolo-e-una-proposta-divisiva_a9072ebb-ca53-4b6f-bc98-d564a07d5291.html",
        "subtitle": "La segretaria confermata come capolista nelle circoscrizioni Centro e Isole alle elezioni Europee",
        "content": "\"E' stato proposto di inserire il mio nome nel logo, si è aperta una bella discussione, ringrazio chi ha fatto questa proposta, ma penso che il contributo lo possa dare correndo accanto a loro, in questa lista. Una proposta più divisiva che rafforzativa e non ne abbiamo bisogno\". Lo ha detto la segretaria Pd, Elly Schlein, in una diretta Instagram.\"Avremo bisogno di tutto il vostro supporto perché se insieme vinceremo l'alternativa c'è già e c'è da domani. C'è tanta voglia di cambiamento e di accendere una speranza\".approvate all'unanimità dalla direzione di ieri del partito: . Sono quindi    \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.742177,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Schlein: 'There will not be my name in the symbol, it is a divisive proposal'",
        "en_content": "\"It was proposed to put my name in the logo, a nice discussion opened, I thank those who made this proposal, but I think the contribution can make it by running next to them, in this list. A more divisive proposal that strengthens and does not need it.\" The Pd secretary, Elly Schlein, said this in an Instagram live.\"We will need all your support because if together we win the alternative there is already and there is from tomorrow. There is so much desire for change and to turn on a hope.\" unanimously approved by the party's management yesterday: I am.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The secretary confirmed as head of the Central and Islands constituencies in the European elections",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schlein",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Central",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Elly Schlein",
                "start_char": 272,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 542,
                "end_char": 551,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Scurati: Gruber, 'io difendo sempre i valori della Costituzione'",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:05 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/scurati-gruber-io-difendo-sempre-i-valori-della-costituzione_2d7c7827-6bb7-4a49-8059-b79609d7369b.html",
        "subtitle": "A Radio1: \"Non so ancora per chi voto, ma mai per la destra\"",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Se Lucia Annunziata ha fatto bene a\ncandidarsi nel Pd? \"Perché no, aveva detto che non si sarebbe\nmai candidata, poi l'ha fatto e si vede che ritiene questa una\ndecisione saggia e giusta. Sono sicura che prenderà tanti voti\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tCosì a Un Giorno da Pecora, su Rai Radio1, Lilli Gruber,\ngiornalista e conduttrice di Otto e Mezzo, intervistata da Geppi\nCucciari e Giorgio Lauro.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Annunziata ha fatto come lei quando si candidò\nall'Europarlamento. Si è mai pentita di quella scelta? \"Mai. È\nstata un'esperienza interessantissima, dopo quattro anni e mezzo\ndimessa rinunciando anche alla pensione\". Lei per chi voterà\nalle europee? \"Non so ancora per chi voto, non so nemmeno chi è\nil capolista al centro dove sono io\". Comunque sceglierà il\ncentrosinistra? \"Non voterò mai per la destra\". A proposito di\nqueste tematiche, la giornalista ha aggiunto: \"Vedete il\ndibattito, anche sulla vicenda Scurati, non è una questione di\ndestra, sinistra o centro. È una questione di valori\ncostituzionali. Ecco - ha spiegato Gruber a Un Giorno da Pecora\n-, io nel mio programma invito ed accolgo tutti, a prescindere\ndal partito politico, ma nella mia trasmissione difenderò sempre\ni valori della nostra Costituzione. È molto chiaro, io credo\nnella nostra democrazia basata sulla Costituzione\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 12,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.7869596,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Sure. Gruber, 'I always defend the values of the Constitution'",
        "en_content": "If Lucia Annunziata did well\nrunning in the PD? \"Why not, he said that you would not\nnever run, then he did it and you see that he believes this one\nwise and just decision. I'm sure he'll take so many votes.\"\n\n\nSo to One Day from Pecora, on Rai Radio1, Lilli Gruber,\njournalist and conductor of Otto and Mezzo, interviewed by Geppi\nCucciari and Giorgio Lauro.\n\n\nAnnunziata did like her when she ran\nto the European Parliament. Have you ever regretted that choice? \"Never. It is\nwas an interesting experience, after four and a half years\nresigning pension also.\" You will be voting for\nto Europeans? \"I don't know who I vote yet, I don't even know who it is.\nthe leader in the center where I am.\" However he will choose the\nRight? \"I will never vote for the right.\" About\nthese issues, the journalist added: \"See the\nDebates of the European Parliament\nright, left or center. It is a question of values\nconstitutional. Here - Gruber explained to One Day from Pecora\n-, in my program I invite and welcome everyone, regardless\nfrom the political party, but in my transmission I will always defend\nthe values of our Constitution. It's very clear, I think\nin our democracy based on the Constitution.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "A Radio1: \"I still don't know who I vote for, but never for the right\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lucia Annunziata",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pecora",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rai Radio1",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lilli Gruber",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Otto and Mezzo",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Geppi\nCucciari",
                "start_char": 326,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgio Lauro",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Annunziata",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Parliament",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four and a half years",
                "start_char": 515,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 588,
                "end_char": 597,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Debates of the European Parliament",
                "start_char": 816,
                "end_char": 850,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "One Day",
                "start_char": 944,
                "end_char": 951,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pecora",
                "start_char": 957,
                "end_char": 963,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 1111,
                "end_char": 1123,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 1180,
                "end_char": 1192,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Comunali Cagliari, in campo anche Alternativa con Emanuela Corda",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:28:23 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/comunali-cagliari-in-campo-anche-alternativa-con-emanuela-corda_4d294ce9-84d2-4414-b231-9751ef15c299.html",
        "subtitle": "Salgono a 4 gli sfidanti per la carica di sindaco",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Spunta una nuova candidata a\nsindaca di Cagliari. Si tratta dell'ex deputata M5s Emanuela\nCorda, presidente nazionale di Alternativa. Salgono così a 4 i\ncandidati allo scranno più alto del Comune, due donne,\nAlessandra Zedda per il centrodestra e appunto Corda per\nAlternativa, e due uomini, Massimo Zedda per il centrosinistra e\nGiuseppe Farris di una lista civica.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Mercoledì 24 Corda si presenta alla stampa alle 10.30 al\nPalazzo Doglio nella sala Castello. \"Un progetto politico per la\ncittà, nato dal confronto con la cittadinanza e con le diverse\nrealtà della società cagliaritana\", si legge nel comunicato di\nAlternativa che \"si propone di portare avanti un cambiamento\nradicale che ritorni al concetto più puro e profondo della\npolitica come servizio al cittadino e non come mero strumento\nper amministrare il potere. Fuori dalle logiche del bipolarismo\ne del voto utile solo per chi lo chiede\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Alternativa nasce nel 2021 dopo la scelta di Giuseppe Conte\ndi sostenere il governo Draghi. I suoi esponenti, entrati in\nparlamento nel 2018 con il simbolo di M5s, furono espulsi dal\nmovimento. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1713873634.8289113,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-23 14:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-23T14.00.34",
        "en_title": "Comunali Cagliari, also in field Alternativa with Emanuela Corda",
        "en_content": "A new candidate for\nmayor of Cagliari. This is former MP M5s Emanuela\nCorda, national president of Alternativa. That's how they get to 4.\ncandidates for the highest scranno of the Municipality, two women,\nAlessandra Zedda for the center and Corda for\nAlternative, and two men, Massimo Zedda for the centerleft and\nGiuseppe Farris of a civic list.\n\n\nWednesday 24 Corda presents itself to the press at 10.30 am\nDoglio Palace in the Castle Room. \"A political project for\ncity, born from comparison with citizenship and with the different\nreality of the society of Cagliari\", we read in the communiqué of\nAlternative that \" aims to carry out a change\nradical that returns to the purest and deepest concept of\npolicy as a service to the citizen and not as a mere tool\nto administer power. Out of the logic of bipolarism\nand the vote only for those who ask.\"\n\n\nAlternativa was born in 2021 after the choice of Giuseppe Conte\nto support the Draghi government. His exponents, entered into\nparliament in 2018 with the symbol of M5s, were expelled from the\nmovement.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Up to 4 challengers for the office of mayor",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Comunali Cagliari",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alternativa",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Corda",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Up to 4",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cagliari",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "M5s Emanuela",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Corda",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alternativa",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Municipality",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alessandra Zedda",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Corda",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 246,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alternative",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 268,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Massimo Zedda",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppe Farris",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wednesday 24",
                "start_char": 349,
                "end_char": 361,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Corda",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "10.30",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Doglio Palace",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Castle Room",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cagliari",
                "start_char": 561,
                "end_char": 569,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alternativa",
                "start_char": 855,
                "end_char": 866,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 879,
                "end_char": 883,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppe Conte",
                "start_char": 904,
                "end_char": 918,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2018",
                "start_char": 995,
                "end_char": 999,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "M5s",
                "start_char": 1019,
                "end_char": 1022,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Europee: 42 simboli depositati al Viminale, tra doppioni e omonimie",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 23:18:35 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/04/22/europee-42-simboli-depositati-al-viminale-tra-doppioni-e-omonimie_fd9ebbc7-2829-4560-a320-a5555581a343.html",
        "subtitle": "I nomi dei big, i simboli del passato e la galassia dei piccoli ",
