[
    {
        "title": "Mattarella, cercare con ostinazione la soluzione dei due Stati",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 21:02:44 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/23/mattarella-cercare-con-ostinazione-la-soluzione-dei-due-stati_b17da41a-69d8-422c-b23e-e6e2ffec9bfe.html",
        "subtitle": "Accogliendo bin Zayed al Colle, 'rimuovere i sedimenti rancore'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Con ostinazione va ripetuto che il\nperseguimento della prospettiva due popoli-due Stati resta\nl'unica in grado di garantire una pace condivisa e sostenibile\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo ha detto il presidente della Repubblica, Sergio Mattarella,\nnel brindisi in occasione della cena al Quirinale con il\npresidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti,  Mohamed bin Zayed Al\nNahyan, alla sua prima visita di Stato in Italia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Oggi l'impegno non può che essere diretto a evitare una\nripresa dei combattimenti, a tenere aperto il filo dei colloqui\nfaticosamente costruito in questi mesi, a rimuovere i sedimenti\ndi rancore. Il ritorno alle ostilità non è foriero né di\nsicurezza futura per Israele, né, tantomeno, di soluzioni per il\npopolo palestinese, che versa, a Gaza, in condizioni\ndrammatiche\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 17,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.5414422,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Mattarella, to seek with stubbornness the solution of the two States",
        "en_content": "\"With stubbornness it must be repeated that the\nTwo peoples and two States remain\nthe only one able to guarantee a shared and sustainable peace\".\n\n\nThe President of the Republic said so, Sergio Mattarella,\non the occasion of the dinner at the Quirinale with the\nPresident of the United Arab Emirates, Mohamed bin Zayed Al\nNahyan, at his first state visit to Italy.\n\n\n\"Today the commitment can only be directed to avoid a\nresumption of fighting, to keep open the thread of talks\ntiringly constructed in these months, to remove sediments\nof anger. The return to hostilities is not a forum or\nfuture security for Israel, nor, at least, solutions for\nPalestinian people in Gaza, under conditions\ndramatic.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Welcoming bin Zayed to the Colle, 'remove grudge sediment'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "bin Zayed",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colle",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Two",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Mattarella",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quirinale",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed bin Zayed Al\nNahyan",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "these months",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 610,
                "end_char": 616,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 647,
                "end_char": 658,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 673,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mattarella a bin Zayed: 'Cercare con ostinazione la soluzione dei due Stati'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 22:04:19 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/23/mattarella-a-bin-zayed-cercare-con-ostinazione-la-soluzione-dei-due-stati_553dc4a1-09b1-40ef-9d8f-26ce65da84e3.html",
        "subtitle": "Cena al Quirinale con il presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti",
        "content": "\"Con ostinazione va ripetuto che \". Lo ha detto il presidente della Repubblica, Sergio Mattarella, nel brindisi in occasione della cena al Quirinale con il presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti, Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan. \"Oggi l'impegno - ha aggiunto - non può che essere diretto a evitare una ripresa dei combattimenti, a tenere aperto il filo dei colloqui faticosamente costruito in questi mesi, a rimuovere i sedimenti di rancore. Il ritorno alle ostilità non è foriero né di sicurezza futura per Israele, né, tantomeno, di soluzioni per il popolo palestinese, che versa, a Gaza, in condizioni drammatiche\". \"Con grande apprezzamento desidero sottolineare lo straordinario aiuto umanitario degli Emirati Arabi Uniti in favore della popolazione di Gaza. È un impegno - quello per salvare vite umane, prestare soccorso ai feriti - che ci ha visto, ancora una volta, lavorare con orgoglio fianco a fianco\".\"I nostri Paesi condividono - ha detto Mattarella -  accanto a una analoga sensibilità per i temi della pace e della cooperazione, una naturale vocazione agli scambi commerciali e apertura agli investimenti. Sono lieto di constatare che la collaborazione bilaterale negli ultimi anni si è notevolmente intensificata. Sono numerose le imprese italiane che operano negli Emirati Arabi Uniti e con esse è in crescita anche la comunità di italiani che nel Suo Paese vive nell'accogliente realtà emiratina. Lo sviluppo di idee e investimenti in Italia è benvenuto e queste prospettive saranno opportunamente approfondite nel forum imprenditoriale che si svolgerà domani. Accanto ai settori tradizionali, troveranno certamente posto quelli d'avanguardia e maggiormente proiettati al futuro\". \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 18,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.5794966,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Mattarella to bin Zayed: 'Certain the solution of the two States with stubbornness'",
        "en_content": "\"With stubbornness it must be repeated that \". The president of the Republic, Sergio Mattarella, said this in the toast at the Quirinale dinner with the President of the United Arab Emirates, Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan. \"Today the engagement - he added - can only be directed to avoid a resumption of the fights, to keep open the thread of the laboriously constructed talks in these months, to remove the sediments of grudges. The return to hostilities is neither a forum nor a future security for Israel, nor, at least, a solution for the Palestinian people, who pays, in Gaza, in dramatic conditions.\" \"With great appreciation I would like to emphasize the extraordinary humanitarian aid of the United Arab Emirates in favour of the people of Gaza. It is a commitment - that to save human lives, to help the wounded - that has seen us, once again, work proudly side by side\".\"Our countries share - said Mattarella - next to a similar sensitivity to the issues of peace and cooperation, a natural vocation to trade and openness to investments. I am pleased to note that bilateral cooperation in recent years has intensified. There are many Italian companies operating in the United Arab Emirates and with them is also growing the Italian community that in your country lives in the welcoming reality of the Emirates. The development of ideas and investments in Italy is welcome and these prospects will be properly deepened in the entrepreneurial forum that will take place tomorrow. In addition to the traditional sectors, they will certainly find the most advanced and projected ones in the future\".\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Dinner with the President of the United Arab Emirates",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "bin Zayed: '",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sergio Mattarella",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Quirinale dinner",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "these months",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 574,
                "end_char": 578,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 694,
                "end_char": 718,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 746,
                "end_char": 750,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "\"Our",
                "start_char": 878,
                "end_char": 882,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 906,
                "end_char": 916,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent years",
                "start_char": 1097,
                "end_char": 1109,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 1142,
                "end_char": 1149,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 1173,
                "end_char": 1197,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 1232,
                "end_char": 1239,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emirates",
                "start_char": 1309,
                "end_char": 1317,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1363,
                "end_char": 1368,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 1476,
                "end_char": 1484,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mattarella a bin Zayed, amicizia e più intensa collaborazione",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 10:18:39 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/mattarella-a-bin-zayed-amicizia-e-piu-intensa-collaborazione_dc7ee805-f7dc-4510-a576-d61271336144.html",
        "subtitle": "Il Presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti al Quirinale",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Altezza, è un piacere rinnovare il\nbenvenuto a lei e alla delegazione che l'accompagna. E' un onore\nper la Repubblica italiana la sua presenza a Roma. Ed è per me\nun motivo di grande gioia averla al Quirinale ancora questa\nmattina. La ringrazio per il nostro scambio di opinioni iera\nsera durante il pranzo e per quello che abbiamo appena avuto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tAdesso lei incontrerà la Presidente del Consiglio e sarà\nun'occasione di approfondimento ulteriore del significato di\nquesta sua visita di cui la ringrazio. E' la prima visita di\nStato di un Presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti in Italia e le\nsono grato per effettuarla, anche come segno dell'amicizia che\nintercorre tra Emirati Arabi Uniti ed Italia e della volontà di\nintensificare la collaborazione in tanti aspetti. Benvenuto\nAltezza\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   E' il saluto del Presidente della Repubblica Sergio\nMattarella al Presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti, Sheikh\nMohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, al Quirinale. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 14,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.5915077,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Mattarella a bin Zayed, friendship and more intense collaboration",
        "en_content": "\"Altitude, it is a pleasure to renew the\nWelcome to you and the delegation that will accompany you. It's an honor.\nfor the Italian Republic its presence in Rome. And it's for me\na reason for great joy to have it at the Quirinale again\nmorning. Thank you for our exchange of views\nevening during lunch and for what we just had.\n\n\nNow you will meet the President of the Council and will be\nan opportunity to further deepen the meaning of\nThis visit I thank you for. It's the first visit.\nState of a President of the United Arab Emirates in Italy and the\nI am grateful to carry out it, even as a sign of friendship that\nbetween United Arab Emirates and Italy and the will of\nintensify collaboration in many aspects. Welcome\nHeight.\"\n\n\nIs the greeting of the President of the Republic Sergio\nMattarella to the President of the United Arab Emirates, Sheikh\nMohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Quirinale.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The President of the United Arab Emirates at the Quirinale",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Quirinale",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Italian Republic",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quirinale",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 228,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 510,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 625,
                "end_char": 645,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 650,
                "end_char": 655,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio\nMattarella",
                "start_char": 781,
                "end_char": 798,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 819,
                "end_char": 843,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan",
                "start_char": 852,
                "end_char": 879,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quirinale",
                "start_char": 881,
                "end_char": 890,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni riceve bin Zayed, poi il business forum Italia-Emirati",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:08:43 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/meloni-riceve-bin-zayed-poi-il-business-forum-italia-emirati_32fa7bd4-4200-411f-b0e2-aa3a942147a0.html",
        "subtitle": "Dopo l'incontro a Palazzo Chigi i leader al Parco dei Principi",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La premier Giorgia Meloni riceve a\nPalazzo Chigi il presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti Sheikh\nMohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan. Al termine dell'incontro, i due\nleader sono attesi al Parco dei Principi, l'hotel di Roma dove\nsi svolge il Forum imprenditoriale Italia-Emirati Arabi Uniti.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.6584427,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Meloni receives bin Zayed, then the business forum Italy-Emirati",
        "en_content": "Premier Giorgia Meloni receives\nPalace Chigi the President of the United Arab Emirates Sheikh\nMohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan. After the meeting, the two\nleaders are expected at the Parco dei Principi, the hotel in Rome where\nthe Italian-Emirati Arabi Forum takes place.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "After the meeting at Palazzo Chigi the leaders at the Parco dei Principi",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "bin Zayed",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Parco dei Principi",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palace Chigi",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates Sheikh",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Parco dei Principi",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, Le posizioni di Afd sono inconciliabili con le mie",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 11:46:44 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/tajani-le-posizioni-di-afd-sono-inconciliabili-con-le-mie_de1e3a9f-c470-4c52-9a46-96423be44606.html",
        "subtitle": "'Non hanno idee positive sull'Italia e fanno i maestrini'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Io sostengo il Ppe e Cdu-Csu, l'ho\nsempre detto. Afd non è per quanto mi riguarda un nostro\ninterlocutore, lo dico come segretario di Fi e vicepresidente\ndel Ppe, perché ha una visione completamente diversa dalla\nnostra, non è una forza politica che ha idee positive nei\nconfronti dell'Italia, dicono che l'Italia deve uscire\ndall'euro, anche sul debito pubblico, un po' da maestrini e non\nsono d'accordo. Poi rispetto tutti coloro che votano nei diversi\nPaesi per i diversi partiti però per quanto mi riguarda\nposizioni di Afd sono inconciliabili con le mie\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Così il ministro Antonio Tajani sulla reazione di Salvini al\nvoto in Germania. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.6749618,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Tajani, The positions of Afd are unconcilable with my",
        "en_content": "\"I support Ppe and Cdu-Csu, I have\nalways said. Afd is not about ours\nI am speaking as Secretary of Fi and Vice-President\nof the Ppe, because it has a completely different view from\nours is not a political force that has positive ideas in\nagainst Italy, they say that Italy must leave\nfrom the euro, also on the public debt, a bit from masters and not\nI agree. Then I respect all those who vote in the different\nCountries for the different parties, however, regarding me\npositions of Afd are unconcilable with mine.\"\n\n\nSo Minister Antonio Tajani on the reaction of Salvini to\nvote in Germany.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'They have no positive ideas about Italy and do the masters'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ppe",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cdu-Csu",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ppe",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 268,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 565,
                "end_char": 572,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 584,
                "end_char": 591,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni: 'Oltre 40 intese con Emirati, giornata storica'",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:45:55 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/meloni-incontra-bin-zayed_d3c468b4-2992-4f8a-a3ac-5fa699ffda12.html",
        "subtitle": "'Portiamo le relazioni bilaterali a un livello mai sperimentato'",
        "content": "\"È una giornata che considero storica - ha detto  intervenendo al Forum imprenditoriale Italia-Emirati Arabi Uniti -. A volte usiamo questa parola a sproposito, ma questo è uno dei casi in cui non è a sproposito parlare di giornata storica. Questo Business Forum è una tappa fondamentale nel rapporto fra le nostre nazioni, nella prima visita di Stato di un presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti in Italia. Abbiamo deciso di portare la collaborazione bilaterale a un livello mai sperimentato prima. E oggi abbiamo firmato oltre 40 intese bilaterali. La giornata di oggi segna un altro punto di partenza nella nostra cooperazione bilaterale\".La presidente del Consiglio prima del Forum ha incontrato bin Zayed a palazzo Chigi.  \"Saluto con soddisfazione la decisione\" degli Emirati Arabi \"di investire 40 miliardi di dollari\" in Italia, uno dei \"più rilevanti, più imponenti investimenti per la storia della nostra nazione, una straordinaria manifestazione di amicizia nei confronti dell'Italia, del suo sistema produttivo della sua economia\", ha aggiunto Meloni. \"Abbiamo scritto una splendida inedita pagina della nostra storia comune\", assicura.\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.683215,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Meloni: 'Over 40 destinations with Emirates, historical day'",
        "en_content": "\"It is a day I consider historical - he said intervening at the Italian-United Arab Emirates entrepreneurial Forum -. Sometimes we use this word to be unproposed, but this is one of the cases where it is not unproposed to talk about historical day. This Business Forum is a fundamental stage in the relationship between our nations, in the first state visit of a president of the United Arab Emirates in Italy. We decided to bring bilateral collaboration to a level never experienced before. And today we have signed over 40 bilateral agreements. Today's day marks another starting point in our bilateral cooperation.\" The President of the Council before the Forum met bin Zayed at Palazzo Chigi. \"I greet with satisfaction the decision\" of the Arab Emirates \"to invest 40 billion dollars\" in Italy, one of the \"most important, most important investments in the history of our nation, an extraordinary manifestation of friendship towards Italy, its production system of its economy\", added Meloni. \"We wrote a wonderful unpublished page of our common history,\" he says.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'We bring bilateral relations to a level never experienced'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emirates",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "This Business Forum",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 409,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 496,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "40",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 524,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forum",
                "start_char": 659,
                "end_char": 664,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "bin Zayed",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 678,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Chigi",
                "start_char": 682,
                "end_char": 695,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 741,
                "end_char": 758,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "40 billion dollars",
                "start_char": 770,
                "end_char": 788,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 793,
                "end_char": 798,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 800,
                "end_char": 803,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 938,
                "end_char": 943,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 990,
                "end_char": 996,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Gruppo Editoriale San Paolo, don Stimamiglio è il nuovo ceo",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 11:39:38 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/gruppo-editoriale-san-paolo-don-stimamiglio-e-il-nuovo-ceo_d82dc4ad-0ec1-4f29-837b-8146b24fbb49.html",
        "subtitle": "Nominato il CdA del prossimo quadriennio. Don Ponti presidente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Don Stefano Stimamiglio, attuale\ndirettore di Famiglia Cristiana, è il nuovo amministratore\ndelegato del Gruppo Editoriale San Paolo. Lo ha nominato\nl'Assemblea dei soci della società capogruppo, la Editoriale San\nPaolo srl (Esp).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il nuovo Consiglio di amministrazione dell'Esp per il\nprossimo quadriennio è composto da don Roberto Ponti, superiore\ndella Provincia italiana dei Paolini, in qualità di presidente;\ndon Stefano Stimamiglio; don Giuseppe Musardo è direttore\ngenerale e consigliere; don Franco Soliman è consigliere e Cfo;\ndon Antonio Rizzolo, è consigliere di amministrazione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Sono inoltre stati nominati amministratori delle altre\nsocietà del Gruppo: don Antonio Rizzolo di Diffusione San Paolo\n(Disp); don Giuseppe Lacerenza di Periodici San Paolo e St Pauls\nInternational; don Giuseppe Musardo di San Paolo Edizioni e don\nSante Sabatucci di San Paolo Patrimonio. Contestualmente, don\nVincenzo Vitale, attuale direttore di Credere e di Jesus,\ndiventa direttore editoriale del Gruppo. Don Simone Bruno è\ndirettore editoriale di Edizioni San Paolo e viene affiancato da\ndon Antonio Rizzolo come vicedirettore editoriale.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"In questo tempo giubilare desideriamo rafforzare il nostro\nimpegno di comunicatori aprendoci a nuove sfide con la capacità\ndi generare futuro. Intendiamo rafforzare il cammino verso la\ndigitalizzazione con lo spirito innovativo del nostro fondatore\ndon Giacomo Alberione, aiutati dai tanti professionisti laici\nche lavorano con passione nelle nostre testate e nelle nostre\nsocietà\", commenta don Roberto Ponti, che in una nota ringrazia\ndon Antonio Rizzolo \"per l'ottimo lavoro svolto negli ultimi\nquattro anni come Ceo del Gruppo\" e ora impegnato in un compito\nstrategico e di sviluppo come quello dell'area libri. \"Così come\nsono grato a don Sante Sabatucci e a don Paolo Epidotti per la\ndedizione nel loro incarico di amministratori - conclude -.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tRicordo anche con affetto don Carlo Cibien, nostro direttore\neditoriale scomparso a fine gennaio\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 12,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.6965365,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Gruppo Editoriale San Paolo, don Stimamiglio is the new ceo",
        "en_content": "Don Stefano Stimamiglio, current\nDirector of Christian Family, is the new administrator\ndelegate of the Gruppo Editoriale San Paolo. He appointed him.\nthe Shareholders' Meeting of the parent company, the Editorial San\nPaolo srl (Esp).\n\n\nThe new Board of Directors of the Esp for\nnext four years is composed by Don Roberto Ponti, superior\nof the Italian Province of Paolini, as president;\nDon Stefano Etimamiglio; Don Giuseppe Musardo is director\ngeneral and councillor; Don Franco Soliman is councilman and Cfo;\nDon Antonio Rizzolo, is an advisor to administration.\n\n\nOther directors were appointed\nGroup company: Don Antonio Rizzolo di Diffusion San Paolo\n(Disp); Don Giuseppe Lacerenza di Periodici San Paolo e St Pauls\nInternational; Don Giuseppe Musardo di San Paolo Edizioni e don\nSante Sabatucci of St. Paul Heritage. At the same time, don\nVincenzo Vitale, current director of Believe and of Jesus,\nbecomes editorial director of the Group. Don Simone Bruno is\neditorial director of Edizioni San Paolo and is joined by\nDon Antonio Rizzolo as deputy editor.\n\n\n\"In this jubilee time we wish to strengthen our\nCommitment of communicators opening us to new challenges with the ability\nto generate future. We intend to strengthen the path towards\ndigitization with the innovative spirit of our founder\nDon Giacomo Alberione, helped by the many lay professionals\nworking with passion in our heads and in our\ncompany\", comments Don Roberto Ponti, who in a note thanks\nDon Antonio Rizzolo \"for the excellent work done in the last\nfour years as the Group's CEO\" and now engaged in a task\nstrategic and development like that of the book area. \"Thus as\nI am grateful to Fr. Sante Sabatucci and Fr. Paolo Epidotti for the\ndedication in their assignment of directors - he concludes -.\n\n\nI also remember with affection Don Carlo Cibien, our director\npublishing disappeared at the end of January.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Appointed the Board of the next four years. Don Ponti President",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gruppo Editoriale San Paolo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "don Stimamiglio",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Don Ponti",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Don Stefano Stimamiglio",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Christian Family",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gruppo Editoriale San Paolo",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Board of Directors",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "next four years",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Roberto Ponti",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Italian Province of",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paolini",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Stefano Etimamiglio",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Giuseppe Musardo",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 433,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Franco Soliman",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cfo",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Antonio Rizzolo",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Antonio Rizzolo di Diffusion San Paolo",
                "start_char": 614,
                "end_char": 656,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Disp",
                "start_char": 658,
                "end_char": 662,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Giuseppe Lacerenza",
                "start_char": 665,
                "end_char": 687,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "di Periodici",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 700,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "St Pauls",
                "start_char": 713,
                "end_char": 721,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Giuseppe Musardo di San Paolo Edizioni e don\n",
                "start_char": 737,
                "end_char": 786,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sante Sabatucci",
                "start_char": 786,
                "end_char": 801,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "St. Paul Heritage",
                "start_char": 805,
                "end_char": 822,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "don\n",
                "start_char": 842,
                "end_char": 846,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vincenzo Vitale",
                "start_char": 846,
                "end_char": 861,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jesus",
                "start_char": 898,
                "end_char": 903,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Group",
                "start_char": 939,
                "end_char": 944,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Simone Bruno",
                "start_char": 946,
                "end_char": 962,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Edizioni San Paolo",
                "start_char": 988,
                "end_char": 1006,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Antonio Rizzolo",
                "start_char": 1024,
                "end_char": 1043,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Giacomo Alberione",
                "start_char": 1302,
                "end_char": 1323,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Roberto Ponti",
                "start_char": 1426,
                "end_char": 1443,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Antonio Rizzolo",
                "start_char": 1466,
                "end_char": 1485,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "four years",
                "start_char": 1527,
                "end_char": 1537,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Group",
                "start_char": 1545,
                "end_char": 1550,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sante Sabatucci",
                "start_char": 1668,
                "end_char": 1683,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paolo Epidotti",
                "start_char": 1692,
                "end_char": 1706,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Don Carlo Cibien",
                "start_char": 1810,
                "end_char": 1826,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of January",
                "start_char": 1867,
                "end_char": 1885,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni, oltre 40 intese con Emirati, giornata storica",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:25:42 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/meloni-oltre-40-intese-con-emirati-giornata-storica_36cf4259-8666-467a-94e8-010b07160127.html",
        "subtitle": "\"Portiamo le relazioni bilaterali a un livello mai sperimentato\"",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"È una giornata che considero\nstorica. A volte usiamo questa parola a sproposito, ma questo è\nuno dei casi in cui non è a sproposito parlare di giornata\nstorica. Questo Business Forum è una tappa fondamentale nel\nrapporto fra le nostre nazioni, nella prima visita di Stato di\nun presidente degli Emirati Arabi Uniti in Italia. Abbiamo\ndeciso di portare la collaborazione bilaterale a un livello mai\nsperimentato prima. E oggi abbiamo firmato oltre 40 intese\nbilaterali. La giornata di oggi segna un altro punto di partenza\nnella nostra cooperazione bilaterale\". Lo ha detto la premier\nGiorgia Meloni, intervenendo  al Forum imprenditoriale\nItalia-Emirati Arabi Uniti. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.7199285,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Meloni, over 40 destinations with Emirates, historical day",
        "en_content": "\"It's a day I consider\nhistorical. Sometimes we use this word unproposed, but this is\none of the cases in which it is not unproposed to speak of day\nhistorical. This Business Forum is a fundamental stage in\nrelationship between our nations, in the first state visit of\na president of the United Arab Emirates in Italy. We have\ndecided to bring bilateral collaboration to a level never\nexperienced before. And today we have signed over 40 agreements\nbilateral. Today's day marks another starting point\nin our bilateral cooperation.\" The premier said that\nGiorgia Meloni, intervening at the entrepreneurial Forum\nItaly-United Arab Emirates.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "\"We bring bilateral relations to a level never experienced\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "40",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emirates",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "This Business Forum",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "40",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 568,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forum",
                "start_char": 605,
                "end_char": 610,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 611,
                "end_char": 616,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni, dagli Emirati 40 miliardi, investimento imponente",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:19:20 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/meloni-dagli-emirati-40-miliardi-investimento-imponente_b5a025c3-e4b1-42c7-a734-e098b2b7a992.html",
        "subtitle": "Scriviamo splendida inedita pagina della nostra storia comune",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Saluto con soddisfazione la\ndecisione\" degli Emirati Arabi \"di investire 40 miliardi di\ndollari\" in Italia, uno dei \"più rilevanti, più imponenti\ninvestimenti per la storia della nostra nazione, una\nstraordinaria manifestazione di amicizia nei confronti\ndell'Italia, del suo sistema produttivo della sua economia\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tCosì la presidente del Consiglio Giorgia Meloni intervenendo al\nbusiness forum Italia-Emirati Arabi. \"Abbiamo scritto una\nsplendida inedita pagina della nostra storia comune\", assicura.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.7711434,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Meloni, from the Emirates 40 billion, massive investment",
        "en_content": "\"Help with satisfaction the\ndecision\" of the Arab Emirates \"to invest 40 billion\ndollars\" in Italy, one of the \"most relevant, most imposing\ninvestments for the history of our nation, a\nextraordinary manifestation of friendship towards\nof Italy, of its production system of its economy\".\n\n\nThus the President of the Council Giorgia Meloni speaking to the\nbusiness forum Italy-Emirati Arabi. \"We wrote a\nwonderful unpublished page of our common history,\" he assures.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "We write wonderful unpublished page of our common history",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Emirates 40 billion",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "40 billion\ndollars",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il libro Veltroni a scuola fa infuriare la Lega",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:54:31 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/il-libro-veltroni-a-scuola-fa-infuriare-la-lega_3728bd93-6768-4a86-9e92-8539446c1e95.html",
        "subtitle": "Per il deputato del Carroccio Rossano Sasso, dal sindaco Buccinasco e dall'assessore del Pd 'indottrinamento di bambini piccoli'. Salvini: 'Gravissimo'",
        "content": "\"A Buccinasco, in provincia di Milano, il sindaco e l'assessore del PD entrano nelle scuole elementari del paese e regalano un libro di Walter Veltroni (sì, proprio lui) dal titolo 'La più bella del mondo', in cui si parla di bimbi partigiani, bimbi giunti in Italia sui barconi e bimbi che indossano i tacchi. Tutto questo avviene all'insaputa dei genitori, che ovviamente hanno protestato. Ringrazio il consigliere comunale della Lega, Manuel Imberti, per aver denunciato la vicenda, che a mia volta segnalerò al Ministero dell'Istruzione e del Merito con un'interrogazione parlamentare\". Così il deputato della Lega , capogruppo in commissione Scienza, Cultura e Istruzione.\"Ma come si permette il sindaco di arrogarsi il diritto di interferire con la didattica di una scuola pubblica? Il libro del post-comunista Veltroni rientra per caso nel piano dell'offerta formativa della scuola? E i dirigenti scolastici hanno autorizzato il sindaco e l'assessore ad entrare e divulgare il libro? Il Consiglio d'Istituto è stato informato, e soprattutto, i genitori erano al corrente? Urge una legge sul consenso informato che vieti espressamente qualsiasi iniziativa extracurriculare senza il consenso dei genitori. Ma Veltroni ha bisogno di questi mezzucci per divulgare il suo capolavoro in cui si propaganda l'ideologia gender?\", conclude. L'Ufficio scolastico regionale della Lombardia ha avviato una verifica \"sulla correttezza della diffusione del testo 'La più bella del Mondo' in una scuola di Buccinasco\". Lo fa sapere il ministero dell'Istruzione sottolineando che la verifica è scattata \"in seguito alle segnalazioni da parte di alcune famiglie degli alunni\".Sull'episodio è intervenuto anche il leader della Lega, Salvini: \"che un primo cittadino entri nelle scuole per regalare a dei ragazzi di 10 anni (senza il consenso dei genitori) dei libri orientati politicamente che trattano, tra l'altro, temi che non dovrebbero entrare nelle aule scolastiche. Perché sindaco e assessore erano lì? Chi ha finanziato quei libri? Conto che venga fatta presto chiarezza\". \"Credo che l'onorevole leghista Rossano Sasso dovrebbe chiedere scusa al sindaco di Buccinasco Rino Pruiti e a tutta la comunità scolastica della cittadina. E soprattutto dovrebbe leggere il prezioso testo di Walter Veltroni \"La più bella del mondo\" che, come si intuisce, riguarda la nostra Costituzione e non la fantomatica teoria gender\". Così, in una nota, Pierfrancesco Majorino, capogruppo Pd in Consiglio regionale della Lombardia.\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 13,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.7799609,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "The book Veltroni at school makes the League rage",
        "en_content": "\"In Buccinasco, in the province of Milan, the mayor and the Councillor of the PD enter the elementary schools of the country and give a book by Walter Veltroni (yes, just him) entitled 'The most beautiful in the world', in which we talk about partisan children, children arrived in Italy on the bars and children wearing heels. All this happens without the parents, who obviously protested. I thank the Town Council of the League, Manuel Imberti, for having denounced the affair, which in turn I will signal to the Ministry of Education and Merit with a parliamentary question\". So the League Member, leader in Science, Culture and Education Committee. \"But how do the mayor allow himself the right to interfere with the teaching of a public school? The post-communist book Veltroni is part of the school's educational offer plan? And did school executives authorize the mayor and the Councillor to enter and disclose the book? Has the Institute Council been informed, and above all, were parents aware? There is a law on informed consent that expressly prohibits any extracurricular initiative without the consent of parents. But does Veltroni need these half-pieces to spread his masterpiece in which gender ideology is propagated?\", he concludes. The regional school office of Lombardy has started a verification \"on the correctness of the spread of the text 'The most beautiful of the world' in a school of Buccinasco\". The Ministry of Education notes that the verification was taken \"after reports by some families of pupils\". The League leader, Salvini, also intervened on the episode: \"that a first citizen enters schools to give children 10 years old (without the consent of parents) of books oriented politically that treat, among other things, themes that should not enter the classrooms. Why were mayor and city councillor there? Who funded those books? I'm counting on clarity soon.\" \"I believe that Mr Rossano Sasso should apologize to the mayor of Buccinasco Rino Pruiti and to the whole school community of the town. And above all, it should read the precious text of Walter Veltroni \"The most beautiful in the world\" which, as we understand, concerns our Constitution and not the imaginative gender theory\". Thus, in a note, Pierfrancesco Majorino, group leader Pd in Regional Council of Lombardy.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "For the MP of Carroccio Rossano Sasso, the mayor Buccinasco and the Councillor of the Pd 'indoctrination of small children'. Salvini: 'Gravissimo'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Veltroni",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Carroccio Rossano Sasso",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buccinasco",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gravissimo",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Buccinasco",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Councillor of the PD",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Walter Veltroni",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Town Council of the League",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manuel Imberti",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Education",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Merit",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Science, Culture and Education Committee",
                "start_char": 611,
                "end_char": 651,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Veltroni",
                "start_char": 774,
                "end_char": 782,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Institute Council",
                "start_char": 932,
                "end_char": 953,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Veltroni",
                "start_char": 1136,
                "end_char": 1144,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "half",
                "start_char": 1156,
                "end_char": 1160,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lombardy",
                "start_char": 1280,
                "end_char": 1288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buccinasco",
                "start_char": 1411,
                "end_char": 1421,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of Education",
                "start_char": 1424,
                "end_char": 1449,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Salvini",
                "start_char": 1551,
                "end_char": 1558,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1600,
                "end_char": 1605,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10 years old",
                "start_char": 1646,
                "end_char": 1658,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rossano Sasso",
                "start_char": 1915,
                "end_char": 1928,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buccinasco Rino Pruiti",
                "start_char": 1962,
                "end_char": 1984,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Walter Veltroni",
                "start_char": 2083,
                "end_char": 2098,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 2171,
                "end_char": 2183,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pierfrancesco Majorino",
                "start_char": 2241,
                "end_char": 2263,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pd in Regional Council of Lombardy",
                "start_char": 2278,
                "end_char": 2312,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Stasera Montecitorio si illumina con i colori dell'Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:59:11 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2025/02/24/stasera-montecitorio-si-illumina-con-i-colori-dellucraina_f22e45df-6f88-43fa-a305-a1d7e34c4e78.html",
        "subtitle": "Dalle ore 18 alle 7 di domani",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            In occasione della ricorrenza del\nterzo anniversario dell'invasione dell'Ucraina, stasera la\nfacciata di Palazzo Montecitorio viene illuminata con i colori\ndella bandiera dell'Ucraina dalle ore 18 alle 7 di domani,\nmartedì 25. E' quanto si legge in una nota della Camera. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1740409218.7959468,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 16:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T15.00.18",
        "en_title": "Tonight Montecitorio lights up with the colors of Ukraine",
        "en_content": "On the occasion of the event\nthird anniversary of the invasion of Ukraine tonight\nfacade of Palazzo Montecitorio is illuminated with colors\nof the flag of Ukraine from 18 to 7 tomorrow,\nTuesday 25th. That's what you read in a Chamber note.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "From 18 to 7 tomorrow",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tonight",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Montecitorio",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "18 to 7",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palazzo Montecitorio",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "18 to 7 tomorrow",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday 25th",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
