[
    {
        "title": "Colosimo a Emiliano, Antimafia ha modalità giudiziarie",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 14:32:23 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/colosimo-a-emiliano-antimafia-ha-modalita-giudiziarie_95ab670d-4f7b-4beb-bd07-4bbe01569c0b.html",
        "subtitle": "Lettera presidente a governatore:'Non è disponibile a audizione'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Entrambi conosciamo le liturgie\npolitiche e sappiamo che alla Conferenza dei presidenti delle\nRegioni si può mandare un delegato in propria vece. Quindi\nprendo atto che semplicemente lei intende scegliere la data\ndella sua audizione compatibilmente con le sue esigenze\npolitiche. Contrariamente a quanto afferma, lei non è, in\nrealtà, disponibile ad essere audito dalla commissione\nparlamentare antimafia. Infatti, come correttamente lei mi ha\nscritto, la stessa procede alle indagini con gli stessi poteri\ndell'autorità giudiziaria e volendo con le stesse modalità\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tCosì la presidente della commissione antimafia Chiara Colosimo\nin una lettera, visionata dall'ANSA e inviata lo scorso 30\naprile al presidente della Puglia Michele Emiliano, il quale\naveva chiesto uno slittamento per la sua audizione in antimafia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLa data della nuova convocazione di Emiliano sarà decisa oggi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.3487873,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "Colosimo in Emiliano, Antimafia has judicial procedures",
        "en_content": "\"We know the liturgies\nand we know that at the Conference of Presidents\nRegions can send a delegate in their own vex. So...\nI take note that you simply intend to choose the date\nof its compact hearing with its needs\npolitics. Contrary to what he says, she is not, in\nreality, available to be audited by the commission\nparliamentary antimafia. In fact, as correctly she has me\nwritten, the same goes on the investigation with the same powers\nof the judicial authority and wishing in the same way.\"\n\n\nSo the president of the antimafia commission Chiara Colosimo\nin a letter, viewed by the ANS and sent last 30\nApril to the president of Puglia Michele Emiliano, who\nHe asked for a slip for his antimafia hearing.\n\n\nThe date of the new call of Emiliano will be decided today.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Letter president to governor:'It is not available to audition'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Emiliano",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antimafia",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "governor:'It",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Conference of Presidents\nRegions",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chiara Colosimo",
                "start_char": 544,
                "end_char": 559,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANS",
                "start_char": 587,
                "end_char": 590,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last 30\nApril",
                "start_char": 600,
                "end_char": 613,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Puglia",
                "start_char": 634,
                "end_char": 640,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michele Emiliano",
                "start_char": 641,
                "end_char": 657,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emiliano",
                "start_char": 740,
                "end_char": 748,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 765,
                "end_char": 770,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Colosimo a Emiliano: 'Antimafia ha modalità giudiziarie'. Lui: 'Conferenza delle regioni non è liturgia' ",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 15:54:06 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/colosimo-a-emiliano-antimafia-ha-modalita-giudiziarie.-lui-conferenza-delle-regioni-non_62775a5c-5b2b-481e-9f26-a5e01cbd92b8.html",
        "subtitle": "Il 30 aprile la lettera della presidente della commissione antimafia, e la risposta del governatore pugliese",
        "content": "\"Entrambi conosciamo le liturgie politiche e sappiamo che alla Conferenza dei presidenti delle Regioni si può mandare un delegato in propria vece. Quindi prendo atto che semplicemente lei intende scegliere la data della sua audizione compatibilmente con le sue esigenze politiche. Contrariamente a quanto afferma, lei non è, in realtà, disponibile ad essere audito dalla commissione parlamentare antimafia. Infatti, come correttamente lei mi ha scritto, la stessa procede alle indagini con gli stessi poteri dell'autorità giudiziaria e volendo con le stesse modalità\". Così la presidente della commissione antimafia Chiara Colosimo in una lettera, visionata dall'ANSA e inviata lo scorso 30 aprile al presidente della Puglia Michele Emiliano, il quale aveva chiesto uno slittamento per la sua audizione in antimafia. La data della nuova convocazione di Emiliano sarà decisa oggi.\"Il mio diritto di partecipazione alla Conferenza delle regioni che si svolgerà lo stesso 2 maggio non è una 'liturgia politica' ma è un dovere istituzionale, a maggior ragione perché svolgo il ruolo di vice presidente della Conferenza delle regioni, il che vuol dire che in casi di impedimento del presidente Fedriga ho il diritto e dovere addirittura di presiedere tale importante consesso\". Così il presidente della Puglia Michele Emiliano in una lettera di risposta inviata il 30 aprile alla presidente della commissione antimafia, Chiara Colosimo, di cui l'ANSA ha potuto visionare alcuni stralci. Nella lettera Emiliano, rispondendo ancora a Colosimo, ha negato di voler di scegliere la data compatibilmente con le sua esigenze politiche: \"le assicuro che, se questa fosse stata la mia volontà, mi sarei limitato a indicarle una data in cui ero disponibile ad essere audito anziché dirle che sono a disposizione della commissione dal 10 al 30 maggio in ogni momento\", ha scritto.\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 17,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.3621638,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "Colosimo in Emiliano: Antimafia has judicial procedures. He: 'Conference of regions is not liturgy'",
        "en_content": "\"We know political liturgies and we know that at the Conference of Presidents of the Regions a delegate can be sent in his vex. So I take note that you simply intend to choose the date of your audition compatibly with your political needs. Contrary to what he says, you are not actually available to be audited by the parliamentary committee of antimafia. In fact, as you correctly wrote to me, the same goes on investigations with the same powers of the judicial authority and wanting in the same way\". So the president of the anti-Mafia commission Chiara Colosimo in a letter, visioned by the ANSA and sent on 30 April to the president of Puglia Michele Emiliano, who had asked for a slip for his audition in anti-mafia. The date of the new convocation of Emiliano will be decided today.\"My right to participate in the Conference of the Regions that will take place on 2 May is not a 'political liturgy' but it is an institutional duty, more so because I play the role of vice president of the Conference of the Regions, which means that in cases of impediment of President Fedriga I have the right and even duty to preside over this important conviction\". So the president of Puglia Michele Emiliano in a letter of reply sent on April 30 to the president of the anti-Mafia commission, Chiara Colosimo, of which the ANSA could see some stralci. In the letter Emiliano, responding again to Colosimo, he denied wanting to choose the date compatibly with his political needs: \"I assure you that if this was my will, I would be limited to indicating a date when I was available to be audited instead of telling her that I am available to the commission from 10 to 30 May at any time,\" he wrote.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "On 30 April the letter of the president of the anti-Mafia commission, and the response of the Apulian governor",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Antimafia",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "30 April",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Mafia",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Apulian",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Conference of Presidents of the Regions",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Mafia",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chiara Colosimo",
                "start_char": 550,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA",
                "start_char": 595,
                "end_char": 599,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "30 April",
                "start_char": 612,
                "end_char": 620,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Puglia",
                "start_char": 641,
                "end_char": 647,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michele Emiliano",
                "start_char": 648,
                "end_char": 664,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emiliano",
                "start_char": 758,
                "end_char": 766,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 783,
                "end_char": 788,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2 May",
                "start_char": 871,
                "end_char": 876,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Conference of the Regions",
                "start_char": 992,
                "end_char": 1021,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fedriga",
                "start_char": 1076,
                "end_char": 1083,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Puglia",
                "start_char": 1179,
                "end_char": 1185,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "April 30",
                "start_char": 1232,
                "end_char": 1240,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Mafia",
                "start_char": 1265,
                "end_char": 1275,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chiara Colosimo",
                "start_char": 1288,
                "end_char": 1303,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA",
                "start_char": 1318,
                "end_char": 1322,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Emiliano",
                "start_char": 1361,
                "end_char": 1369,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colosimo",
                "start_char": 1391,
                "end_char": 1399,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 to 30",
                "start_char": 1656,
                "end_char": 1664,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Non solo Giorgia, da \"Ultimo\" a \"Pavone\", valanga di detti",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 18:58:54 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/non-solo-giorgia-da-ultimo-a-pavonevalanga-di-detti_d6b42935-d894-420f-b677-2b2382ba2722.html",
        "subtitle": "Si va da Letizia Maria Brichetto Arnaboldi detta Letizia Moratti a Domenico Lucano detto Mimmo",
        "content": " Non c'è solo Giorgia Meloni detta Giorgia. Nelle liste per le europee i \"detti\" sono una valanga. Si va da Letizia Maria Brichetto Arnaboldi detta Letizia Moratti candidata con Forza Italia nel Nord ovest a Domenico Lucano detto Mimmo (Avs), da Alessandro Cecchi Paone detto Cecchi detto Pavone nella lista Stati Uniti d'Europa a Alessio D'Amato detto Damato candidato con Azione fino a Sergio De Caprio detto \"Capitano Ultimo\" detto \"Capitano\" detto \"Ultimo\". Nelle liste di FdI compaiono anche: Stefano Cavedagna detto Cavedania, Piergiacomo Sibiano detto Piga, Salvatore Deidda detto Sasso, Massimiliano Giammusso detto Massi detto Musso e Giuseppa Savarino detta Giusi. In quelle azzurre spiccano: Rossella Chiusaroli detta Ros, Antonio Cenini detto Cenno, Fulvio Martusciello detto Fulvio, Francesca Salatiello detta Fra, Margherita La Rocca Ruvolo detta Rita e Edmondo Tamajo detto Tamaio detto Di Maio detto Edy detto Edi detto Eddy. In Avs Suad Omar Sheikh Esahaq è detta Su, Giuliana Fiertler è detta Firtler. Passando ai candidati di Stati Uniti d'Europa, ci sono: Raffaella Paita detta Lella, Muharem Saljihu detto Marco, Kateryna Shmorhav detta Katya, Giovanni Domenico Caiazza detto Giandomenico Caiazza, Gerardo Stefanelli detto Stefano, Alessandrina Lonardo Mastella detta Sandra Mastella (la moglie di Clemente Mastella, ndr). Azione di Carlo Calenda schiera: Gianni Palazzolo detto Giangiacomo, Mariapia Abbraccio detta Mapy, Alessandro Tommasi detto Sandro, Caterina Avanza detta Caterina detta Cate, Cuno Jakob Tarfusser detto Cuno e Paul Kollensperger detto Paul.Nel M5s la candidata Giusy Esposito diventa anche Giusi, Daniela Gobbo è detta Daniela Varedo. Nel Pd spicca la segretaria, Elena Ethel Schlein detta Elly, ma ci sono anche: Brando Maria Benifei detto Brando detto Bonifei, Marco Pacciotti detto Paciotti detto Marco, Giuseppina Picierno detta Pina, Giuseppe Lupo detto Peppino. Nella lista Libertà di Cateno De Luca spicca la candidatura di Sergio De Caprio detto \"Capitano Ultimo\", detto \"Capitano\", detto \"Ultimo\". Nella Lega compaiono, tra gli altri, Susanna Ceccardi detta Susanna detta Susi, Claudio Borghi detto Borghi Aquilini.   \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 16,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.3825853,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "Not only Giorgia, from \"Ultimo\" to \"Pavone\", avalanche of sayings",
        "en_content": "There is not only Giorgia Meloni called Giorgia. In European lists the \"rights\" are an avalanche. It goes from Letizia Maria Brichetto Arnaboldi called Letizia Moratti candidate with Forza Italia in the North West to Domenico Lucano said Mimmo (Avs), from Alessandro Cecchi Paone said Cecchi Pavone in the list United States of Europe to Alessio D'Amato said Damato candidate with Action up to Sergio De Caprio said \"Capitano Ultimo\" called \"Capitano\" called \"Ultimo\". FdI lists also appear: Stefano Cavedagna called Cavedania, Piergiacomo Sibiano called Piga, Salvatore Deidda said Sasso, Massimiliano Giammusso called Massi called Musso and Giuseppa Savarino called Giusi. In the blue ones stand out: Rossella Chiusaroli called Ros, Antonio Cenini said Cenno, Fulvio Martusciello said Fulvio, Francesca Salatiello called Fra, Margherita La Rocca Ruvolo called Rita and Edmondo Tamajo said Tamaio said Di Maio Edy said Edi said Eddy. In Avs Suad Omar Sheikh Esahaq is called Su, Giuliana Fiertler is called Firtler. Passing to the candidates of the United States of Europe, there are: Raffaella Paita called Lella, Muharem Saljihu said Marco, Kateryna Shmorhav said Katya, Giovanni Domenico Caiazza said Giandomenico Caiazza, Gerardo Stefanelli said Stefano, Alessandrina Lonardo Mastella called Sandra Mastella (the wife of Clemente Mastella, ndr). Action by Carlo Calenda: Gianni Palazzolo said Giangiacomo, Mariapia Abbraccio called Mapy, Alessandro Tommasi called Sandro, Caterina Advanced called Cate, Cuno Jakob Tarfusser said Cuno and Paul Kollensperger said Paul. In M5s the candidate Giusy Esposito also becomes Giusi, Daniela Gobbo is called Daniela Varedo. In the Pd stands the secretary, Elena Ethel Schlein called Elly, but there are also: Brando Maria Benifei said Brando said Bonifei, Marco Pacciotti said Paciotti said Marco, Giuseppina Picierno called Pina, Giuseppe Lupo said Peppino. In the list Freedom of Cateno De Luca stands the candidacy of Sergio De Caprio called \"Capitano Ultimo\", called \"Capitano\", called \"Ultimo\". In the League, Susanna Ceccardi, called Susanna Susi, Claudio Borghi, known as Borghi Aquilini, appeared among others.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "It goes from Letizia Maria Brichetto Arnaboldi called Letizia Moratti to Domenico Lucano said Mimmo",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ultimo",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Letizia Maria Brichetto Arnaboldi",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Letizia Moratti",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Domenico Lucano",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Letizia Maria Brichetto Arnaboldi",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Letizia Moratti",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the North West",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Domenico Lucano",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mimmo (Avs",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alessandro Cecchi Paone",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cecchi Pavone",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alessio D'Amato",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Damato",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio De Caprio",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 410,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Capitano Ultimo",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Capitano",
                "start_char": 442,
                "end_char": 450,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ultimo",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Stefano Cavedagna",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cavedania",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Piergiacomo Sibiano",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piga",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 559,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sasso",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 588,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Massimiliano Giammusso",
                "start_char": 590,
                "end_char": 612,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Massi",
                "start_char": 620,
                "end_char": 625,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Musso",
                "start_char": 633,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppa Savarino",
                "start_char": 643,
                "end_char": 660,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giusi",
                "start_char": 668,
                "end_char": 673,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rossella Chiusaroli",
                "start_char": 703,
                "end_char": 722,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ros",
                "start_char": 730,
                "end_char": 733,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Cenini",
                "start_char": 735,
                "end_char": 749,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cenno",
                "start_char": 755,
                "end_char": 760,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fulvio Martusciello",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 781,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fulvio",
                "start_char": 787,
                "end_char": 793,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Francesca Salatiello",
                "start_char": 795,
                "end_char": 815,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Margherita La",
                "start_char": 828,
                "end_char": 841,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rita and Edmondo Tamajo",
                "start_char": 862,
                "end_char": 885,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tamaio",
                "start_char": 891,
                "end_char": 897,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Di Maio Edy",
                "start_char": 903,
                "end_char": 914,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Edi",
                "start_char": 920,
                "end_char": 923,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eddy",
                "start_char": 929,
                "end_char": 933,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Avs Suad Omar Sheikh Esahaq",
                "start_char": 938,
                "end_char": 965,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Su",
                "start_char": 976,
                "end_char": 978,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuliana Fiertler",
                "start_char": 980,
                "end_char": 997,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Firtler",
                "start_char": 1008,
                "end_char": 1015,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States of Europe",
                "start_char": 1046,
                "end_char": 1073,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raffaella Paita",
                "start_char": 1086,
                "end_char": 1101,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lella",
                "start_char": 1109,
                "end_char": 1114,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Muharem Saljihu",
                "start_char": 1116,
                "end_char": 1131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco",
                "start_char": 1137,
                "end_char": 1142,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kateryna Shmorhav",
                "start_char": 1144,
                "end_char": 1161,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katya",
                "start_char": 1167,
                "end_char": 1172,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giovanni Domenico Caiazza",
                "start_char": 1174,
                "end_char": 1199,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giandomenico Caiazza",
                "start_char": 1205,
                "end_char": 1225,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gerardo Stefanelli",
                "start_char": 1227,
                "end_char": 1245,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stefano",
                "start_char": 1251,
                "end_char": 1258,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alessandrina Lonardo Mastella",
                "start_char": 1260,
                "end_char": 1289,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sandra Mastella",
                "start_char": 1297,
                "end_char": 1312,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Clemente Mastella",
                "start_char": 1326,
                "end_char": 1343,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ndr",
                "start_char": 1345,
                "end_char": 1348,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Calenda",
                "start_char": 1361,
                "end_char": 1374,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gianni Palazzolo",
                "start_char": 1376,
                "end_char": 1392,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giangiacomo",
                "start_char": 1398,
                "end_char": 1409,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mariapia Abbraccio",
                "start_char": 1411,
                "end_char": 1429,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mapy, Alessandro Tommasi",
                "start_char": 1437,
                "end_char": 1461,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sandro, Caterina Advanced",
                "start_char": 1469,
                "end_char": 1494,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cate",
                "start_char": 1502,
                "end_char": 1506,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cuno Jakob Tarfusser",
                "start_char": 1508,
                "end_char": 1528,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cuno",
                "start_char": 1534,
                "end_char": 1538,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paul Kollensperger",
                "start_char": 1543,
                "end_char": 1561,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paul",
                "start_char": 1567,
                "end_char": 1571,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giusy Esposito",
                "start_char": 1594,
                "end_char": 1608,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giusi",
                "start_char": 1622,
                "end_char": 1627,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Daniela Gobbo",
                "start_char": 1629,
                "end_char": 1642,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Daniela Varedo",
                "start_char": 1653,
                "end_char": 1667,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elena Ethel Schlein",
                "start_char": 1701,
                "end_char": 1720,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brando Maria Benifei",
                "start_char": 1754,
                "end_char": 1774,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brando",
                "start_char": 1780,
                "end_char": 1786,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bonifei",
                "start_char": 1792,
                "end_char": 1799,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco Pacciotti",
                "start_char": 1801,
                "end_char": 1816,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paciotti",
                "start_char": 1822,
                "end_char": 1830,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco",
                "start_char": 1836,
                "end_char": 1841,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppina Picierno",
                "start_char": 1843,
                "end_char": 1862,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pina, Giuseppe Lupo",
                "start_char": 1870,
                "end_char": 1889,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Peppino",
                "start_char": 1895,
                "end_char": 1902,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Freedom of Cateno De Luca",
                "start_char": 1916,
                "end_char": 1941,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio De Caprio",
                "start_char": 1966,
                "end_char": 1982,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Capitano Ultimo",
                "start_char": 1991,
                "end_char": 2006,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ultimo",
                "start_char": 2036,
                "end_char": 2042,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Susanna Ceccardi",
                "start_char": 2060,
                "end_char": 2076,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Susanna Susi",
                "start_char": 2085,
                "end_char": 2097,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Claudio Borghi",
                "start_char": 2099,
                "end_char": 2113,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Pizzaballa, 'scongiurare l'intervento a Rafah? Siamo presenti'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 17:26:50 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/pizzaballa-scongiurare-lintervento-a-rafah-siamo-presenti_269bad8c-f0b0-4cd9-ba51-2e4dc5e8c1f4.html",
        "subtitle": "'A Gaza e in Cisgiordania si soffre e si resiste. Serve perdono'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Una pace vera e\nduratura richiederà tempi lunghi, adesso dobbiamo lavorare per\nuna cessazione delle ostilità, un cessate il fuoco come primo\npasso verso altre prospettive di carattere politico che però\nsono tutte da costruire\". Non si sottrae alle domande dei\ngiornalisti, il cardinale Pierbattista Pizzaballa, patriarca\nlatino di Gerusalemme, a Roma per la presa di possesso della sua\nsede cardinalizia, che già aveva dovuto rimandare per la\nchiusura dello spazio aereo causata dall'attacco di risposta\niraniano di due settimane fa, e per una lectio magistralis alla\nPontificia Università Lateranense sul tema, attualissimo e allo\nstesso tempo delicatissimo, \"Caratteri e criteri per una\npastorale della pace\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Così Pizzaballa insiste su tre pilastri, \"perdono, verità e\ngiustizia\", sottolineando la necessità della presa in carico del\n\"dolore\" che però non sfoci solo in \"rancore\" e \"rabbia\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tDirettrici essenziali per i leader religiosi che, come lui,\nstanno tentando il dialogo in ore che non ha esitato a definire\n\"drammatiche\" ma anche di \"speranza\". Stando ben attento però a\nspecificare che la Santa sede o altri come lo stesso\nPatriarcato, in questa fase, \"non devono\" direttamente\n\"mediare\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Si sta parlando, si sta lavorando - spiega -, ma è molto\ndifficile individuare percorsi e prospettive finché c'è il\nconflitto in corso, finché questa situazione non si ferma\"\nservono innanzitutto \"la liberazione degli ostaggi da un lato e\nquella di almeno alcuni prigionieri palestinesi dall'altro e poi\nsi vedrà\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il ruolo della Santa Sede e non solo della Santa Sede -\naggiunge - è quello di creare spazi e contesti di facilitazione,\nnon è il nostro ruolo entrare dentro la mediazione soprattutto\nin realtà così complesse e problematiche però creare i contesti,\nle premesse perché questo possa avvenire\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.4711456,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "Pizzaballa, 'short the intervention to Rafah? We're here.",
        "en_content": "\"A true peace and\nit will take long times, now we have to work for\na cessation of hostilities, a ceasefire as the first\nI should like to thank the rapporteur for his work.\nare all to be built.\" He does not subtract from the questions of\njournalists, Cardinal Pierbattista Pizzaballa, Patriarch\nLatin of Jerusalem, in Rome for the possession of his\ncardinal's seat, which had already had to postpone for the\nclosure of air space caused by the response attack\nIranian two weeks ago, and for a lectio magistralis to\nPontifical Lateran University on the topic, very current and at\nsame delicate time, \"Charters and criteria for a\npastoral care of peace\".\n\n\nSo Pizzaballa insists on three pillars, \"love, truth and\nJustice\", stressing the need for taking into account the\n\"sweet\" but not only in \"rancore\" and \"rabbia\".\n\n\nEssential directors for religious leaders who, like him,\nare trying dialogue in hours that he has not hesitated to define\n\"dramatic\" but also \"hope\". But be careful\nspecify that the Holy See or others as the same\nPatriarchate, at this stage, \"they must not\" directly\n\"mediate.\"\n\n\n\"You are talking, you are working - he explains -, but it is very\ndifficult to identify paths and prospects as long as there is\nongoing conflict, until this situation stops\"\nfirst serve \"the liberation of hostages on one side and\nthat of at least some Palestinian prisoners on the other and then\nWe'll see.\"\n\n\n\"The role of the Holy See and not only of the Holy See -\nadds - is to create spaces and contexts of facilitation,\nis not our role to enter the mediation especially\nin reality so complex and problematic but create contexts,\nthe premises so that this may happen.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'In Gaza and the West Bank we suffer and resist. Need forgiveness.",
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the West Bank",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pierbattista Pizzaballa",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Latin",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 312,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two weeks ago",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pontifical Lateran University",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 542,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Charters",
                "start_char": 598,
                "end_char": 606,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 678,
                "end_char": 683,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Holy See",
                "start_char": 995,
                "end_char": 1007,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Patriarchate",
                "start_char": 1030,
                "end_char": 1042,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1271,
                "end_char": 1276,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 1349,
                "end_char": 1360,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Holy See",
                "start_char": 1420,
                "end_char": 1432,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Holy See -\n",
                "start_char": 1449,
                "end_char": 1464,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Corteo anti Vannacci, scontri con la polizia a Napoli",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 17:39:09 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/corteo-anti-vannacci-scontri-con-la-polizia-a-napoli_de056f31-12be-4113-bb1a-deb708afa4aa.html",
        "subtitle": "Manifestanti poi allontanati, cantano slogan a distanza",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Scontri con le forze dell'ordine in\nassetto antisommossa si sono verificati durante il corteo di una\ntrentina di giovani che protestano per la presenza a Napoli di\nRoberto Vannacci. I manifestanti, che intendevano superare le\ntransenne e il cordone di polizia a protezione dell'area dove\nVannacci presenta il suo libro, hanno lanciato palloncini pieni\nd'acqua e poi colpito gli scudi degli agenti con aste di\nbandiera. La polizia ha quindi risposto con l'utilizzo dei\nmanganelli, ma non sembrano esserci feriti. Dopo i momenti di\nscontro, i manifestanti che protestano contro Vannacci\ncontinuano a fronteggiarsi a distanza con il cordone di polizia\nche chiude loro l'accesso all'area dove il candidato della Lega\npresenterà il suo ultimo libro. Gli attivisti si tengono a\ndistanza dagli agenti, cantando cori e gridando slogan. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.5119193,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "Corteo anti Vannacci, clashes with the police in Naples",
        "en_content": "Danger with law enforcement forces in\nanti-shock trim occurred during the procession of a\nthirty young people protesting for the presence in Naples\nRoberto Vannacci. The protesters, who intended to overcome\ntransenne and the police cord to protect the area where\nVannacci presents his book, they launched full balloons\nof water and then hit the shields of agents with rods of\nflag. The police then responded with the use of\nManganelli, but they don't seem to be hurt. After the moments of\nprotesters protesting against Vannacci\ncontinue facing distance with the police cordon\nwho closes their access to the area where the League candidate\nwill present his last book. Activists are held in\ndistance from the agents, singing choirs and shouting slogans.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Manifestanti then estranged, singing slogans at distance",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Manifestanti",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "thirty",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Vannacci",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vannacci",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manganelli",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vannacci",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Corteo anti-Vannacci a Napoli, scontri con la polizia",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 19:49:24 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/corteo-anti-vannacci-a-napoli-scontri-con-la-polizia_82457d91-779f-4ca2-9d1e-c530b15c4f83.html",
        "subtitle": "Giovani in piazza contestano il generale candidato con la Lega, 'non ti vogliamo'",
        "content": "Scontri con le forze dell'ordine in assetto antisommossa si sono verificati a Napoli durante un corteo di una trentina di giovani che protestano per la presenza a Napoli di Roberto Vannacci, il generale candidato alle europee con la Lega, e impegnato nella presentazione del suo libro 'Il mondo al contrario', in un teatro sul lungomare.I manifestanti, che intendevano dirigersi verso il luogo della presentazione, mostravano uno striscione con la frase 'Vannacci Napoli non ti vuole, fattene una ragione'. Uno di loro reggeva una bandiera palestinese, altri mostravano foto del generale con gli occhi coperti dallo slogan 'cacciamolo'.I manifestanti, hanno provato a superare le transenne e il cordone di polizia a protezione dell'area dove Vannacci stava presentando il suo libro, poi hanno lanciato palloncini pieni d'acqua e poi colpito gli scudi degli agenti con aste di bandiera. La polizia ha quindi risposto con l'utilizzo dei manganelli, ma non sembrano esserci feriti. I due schieramenti al momento si fronteggiano in via Nazario Sauro.   \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 9,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.5492766,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "Anti-Vannacci court in Naples, clashes with police",
        "en_content": "Scontri with the forces of the order in anti-sommossa order occurred in Naples during a procession of thirty young people protesting for the presence in Naples by Roberto Vannacci, the general candidate for Europeans with the League, and engaged in the presentation of his book 'The world on the contrary', in a theater on the seafront. The protesters, who intended to head towards the place of the presentation, showed a banner with the phrase 'Vannacci Naples does not want you, make a reason for it'. One of them held a Palestinian flag, others displayed photos of the general with the eyes covered by the slogan 'cacciamolo'. The protesters tried to overcome the trans-year-olds and the police cord to protect the area where Vannacci was presenting his book, then launched balloons full of water and then hit the shields of the agents with flag rods. The police then responded with the use of manganelli, but there does not seem to be any injuries. The two sides currently face Nazario Sauro street.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Young people in the square contest the general candidate with the League, 'we don't want you'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Anti-Vannacci",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Scontri",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "thirty",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Vannacci",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "'The world on the contrary'",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vannacci Naples",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 504,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 523,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "trans-year-olds",
                "start_char": 667,
                "end_char": 682,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vannacci",
                "start_char": 729,
                "end_char": 737,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 957,
                "end_char": 960,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nazario Sauro",
                "start_char": 982,
                "end_char": 995,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Europee: fra i capilista big, ma anche esordi e ritorni",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 16:52:33 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/europee-fra-i-capilista-big-ma-anche-esordi-e-ritorni_766248b5-b201-4195-b386-4b424f3987a1.html",
        "subtitle": "Tra i leader Giorgia Meloni, Antonio Tajani, Elly Schlein e Carlo Calenda",
        "content": "Big di partito, come la premier Giorgia Meloni per Fdi, il vicepremier Antonio Tajani per Fi, la segretaria del Pd Elly Schlein e quello di Azione, Carlo Calenda.Michele Santoro per la sua lista \"Pace terra e dignità\" e Cateno De Luca per Libertà. E poi qualche esordio in politica e qualche ritorno.Sono queste le scelte delle forze politiche per i capilista alle europee dell'8 e 9 giugno.  capolista Giorgia Meloni ovunque. Silvia Sardone al Nord ovest; Paolo Borchia al Nord est; il generale Roberto Vannacci al Centro e al Sud; Annalisa Tardino nelle Isole.: Antonio Tajani ovunque salvo le Isole dove c'è Caterina Chinnici. Carlo Calenda è capolista ovunque tranne che nel Nord ovest dove c'è Elena Bonetti. Emma Bonino sarà capolista a Nord ovest, Gian Domenico Caiazza al Centro, il segretario del Psi Enzo Maraio al sud. Al Nord est il capolista sarà il leader liberal democratico scozzese Graham Watson, nelle isole la militante radicale Rita Bernardini. Elly Schlein capolista al centro e nelle Isole, Lucia Annunziata al Sud, Stefano Bonaccini al Nord est, Cecilia Strada al Nord ovest.: Maria Angela Danzì al Nord ovest, Sabrina Pignedoli al Nord est, Carolina Morace al Centro, Pasquale Tridico al Sud, Giuseppe Antoci nelle Isole. Ilaria Salis nel Nord ovest, Cristina Guarda nel Nord est, Ignazio Marino al Centro, Domenico Lucano al Sud, Leoluca Orlando nelle Isole. Michele Santoro ovunque. ticket ovunque di Cateno De Luca e Laura Castelli.     \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.5912235,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "European: among the big leaders, but also debuts and returns",
        "en_content": "Big party, such as Premier Giorgia Meloni for Fdi, Vicepremier Antonio Tajani for Fi, the secretary of the Pd Elly Schlein and that of Action, Carlo Calenda. Michele Santoro for his list \"Peace land and dignity\" and Cateno De Luca for Freedom. And then some beginnings in politics and some return. These are the choices of the political forces for the leaders to the Europeans of 8 and 9 June. capolista Giorgia Meloni everywhere. Silvia Sardone to the north west; Paolo Borchia in the North East; General Roberto Vannacci in the Centre and in the South; Annalisa Tardino in the Islands.: Antonio Tajani everywhere except the islands where there is Caterina Chinnici. Carlo Calenda is a leader everywhere except in the North West where Elena Bonetti is. Emma Bonino will be head of the North West, Gian Domenico Caiazza at the Centre, the secretary of the Psi Enzo Maraio to the south. In the North East, the leader will be the Scottish liberal democratic leader Graham Watson, in the islands the radical militant Rita Bernardini. Elly Schlein head of the centre and the islands, Lucia Annunziata in the South, Stefano Bonaccini in the North East, Cecilia Strada in the North West.: Maria Angela Danzì in the North West, Sabrina Pignedoli in the North East, Carolina Morace at the Centre, Pasquale Tridico in the South, Giuseppe Antoci in the Islands. Ilaria Salis in the North West, Cristina Guarda in the North East, Ignazio Marino al Centro, Domenico Lucano al Sud, Leoluca Orlando in the Islands. Michele Santoro everywhere. ticket anywhere in Cateno De Luca and Laura Castelli.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Among the leaders Giorgia Meloni, Antonio Tajani, Elly Schlein and Carlo Calenda",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elly Schlein",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Calenda",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fdi",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Pd Elly Schlein",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Calenda",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michele Santoro",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cateno De Luca for Freedom",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 and 9 June",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Silvia Sardone",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paolo Borchia",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North East",
                "start_char": 482,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Vannacci",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 548,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Annalisa Tardino",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 571,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 589,
                "end_char": 603,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caterina Chinnici",
                "start_char": 649,
                "end_char": 666,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Calenda",
                "start_char": 668,
                "end_char": 681,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North West",
                "start_char": 715,
                "end_char": 729,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elena Bonetti",
                "start_char": 736,
                "end_char": 749,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emma Bonino",
                "start_char": 754,
                "end_char": 765,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North West",
                "start_char": 782,
                "end_char": 796,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gian Domenico",
                "start_char": 798,
                "end_char": 811,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Centre",
                "start_char": 827,
                "end_char": 833,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North East",
                "start_char": 889,
                "end_char": 903,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Scottish",
                "start_char": 928,
                "end_char": 936,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "democratic",
                "start_char": 945,
                "end_char": 955,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Graham Watson",
                "start_char": 963,
                "end_char": 976,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rita Bernardini",
                "start_char": 1014,
                "end_char": 1029,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elly Schlein",
                "start_char": 1031,
                "end_char": 1043,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lucia Annunziata",
                "start_char": 1080,
                "end_char": 1096,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1109,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North East",
                "start_char": 1132,
                "end_char": 1146,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North West",
                "start_char": 1166,
                "end_char": 1180,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria Angela Danzì",
                "start_char": 1183,
                "end_char": 1201,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North West",
                "start_char": 1205,
                "end_char": 1219,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sabrina Pignedoli",
                "start_char": 1221,
                "end_char": 1238,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North East",
                "start_char": 1242,
                "end_char": 1256,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carolina Morace",
                "start_char": 1258,
                "end_char": 1273,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Centre",
                "start_char": 1277,
                "end_char": 1287,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 1313,
                "end_char": 1318,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppe Antoci",
                "start_char": 1320,
                "end_char": 1335,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ilaria Salis",
                "start_char": 1352,
                "end_char": 1364,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North West",
                "start_char": 1368,
                "end_char": 1382,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cristina Guarda",
                "start_char": 1384,
                "end_char": 1399,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North East",
                "start_char": 1403,
                "end_char": 1417,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marino al Centro",
                "start_char": 1427,
                "end_char": 1443,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Domenico Lucano al Sud",
                "start_char": 1445,
                "end_char": 1467,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orlando",
                "start_char": 1477,
                "end_char": 1484,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Michele Santoro",
                "start_char": 1501,
                "end_char": 1516,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cateno De Luca",
                "start_char": 1548,
                "end_char": 1562,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Laura Castelli",
                "start_char": 1567,
                "end_char": 1581,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nella circoscrizione Nord Ovest rigettata la lista di Santoro",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 16:27:50 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/nella-circoscrizione-nord-ovest-rigettata-la-lista-di-santoro_55a57464-9f6a-406a-8086-b5320c14f7d8.html",
        "subtitle": "Nove quelle escluse, anche Forza Nuova, Animalisti e Pirati",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Pace Terra Dignità, la lista di\nMichele Santoro per le prossime elezioni europee, è stata\nesclusa insieme ad altre otto tra quelle depositate nella\ncircoscrizione Nord-Ovest.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La lista, composta da 20 candidati e presentata martedì\nscorso presso la Corte d'Appello di Milano, includeva nomi come\nquello dell'attore Paolo Rossi e dello scrittore moldavo Nicolai\nLilin, con il giornalista al primo posto.  \n   Tra le rigettate ci sono anche quella Forza Nuova capeggiata\nda Roberto Fiore, Pirati (legata al Partito Pirati Europeo),\nItalia dei diritti - De Pierro, Alternativa Popolare con\ncapolista il sindaco di Terni Stefano Bandecchi, quella del\nPartito Animalista - Italexit, Pensioni e lavoro - che si era\npresentata, in polemica, con sole 3 firme a fronte delle 15mila\nminime che servirebbero -, Democrazia sovrana e popolare e\ninfine Parlamentare indipendente di Lamberto Roberti, che si era\npresentata senza firme e senza altri candidati. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.610622,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "In the North West constituency rejected the Santoro list",
        "en_content": "Peace Earth Dignity, the list of\nMichele Santoro for the next European elections, was\nexcluded along with eight other deposited in\nNorthwest constituency.\n\n\nThe list, consisting of 20 candidates and presented on Tuesday\nlast at the Court of Appeal of Milan, included names as\nthe actor Paolo Rossi and the Moldovan writer Nicolai\nLilin, with the reporter first.\nThere's also that Force between the rejects. New hut\nby Roberto Fiore, Pirates (legated to the European Pirate Party),\nItaly of rights - De Pierro, Alternativa Popolare con\nthe mayor of Terni Stefano Bandecchi, that of\nAnimal Party - Italexit, Pensions and Jobs - which you had\npresented, in polemic, with only 3 signatures in front of the 15 thousand\nminimums that would serve -, sovereign and popular democracy\nFinally Speaking independent of Lamberto Roberti, who had\npresented without signatures and without other candidates.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Nine excluded ones, including New Force, Animals and Pirates",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the North West",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santoro",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "New Force",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Michele Santoro",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Northwest",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Court of Appeal of Milan",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paolo Rossi",
                "start_char": 286,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moldovan",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 314,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicolai",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lilin",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Fiore",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Pirate Party",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 481,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Popolare",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 530,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Terni Stefano Bandecchi",
                "start_char": 548,
                "end_char": 571,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Animal Party - Italexit",
                "start_char": 581,
                "end_char": 604,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "only 3",
                "start_char": 668,
                "end_char": 674,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "15 thousand",
                "start_char": 702,
                "end_char": 713,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finally Speaking",
                "start_char": 775,
                "end_char": 791,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lamberto Roberti",
                "start_char": 807,
                "end_char": 823,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Vannacci, contestazioni? Quadro preoccupante ",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 18:39:12 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/vannacci-contestazioni-quadro-preoccupante-_e37efa72-9906-4e00-bf93-ccb3e562ed30.html",
        "subtitle": "'Ma non temo per la mia incolumità, non mi sento accerchiato'",
        "content": " \"Non capisco perché non vengono in sala in pace, io sono per il confronto civile, li ascolterei e mi confronterei con loro. E comunque no, non temo per la mia incolumità e non mi sento accerchiato\". Così il generale Roberto Vannacci commenta la manifestazione inscenata dai centri sociali al suo arrivo a Napoli dove si trova per presentare il suo libro.\"Ringrazio i contestatori, li invito a venire in questa sala a manifestare le loro idee, non mi sono mai sottratto al confronto. Ma questo invito che faccio non ha mai successo. Non mi sento accerchiato ma mi preoccupa il contesto che si è venuto a creare\".  \"Non mi sono mai definito antifascista perché non ritengo utile definirmi tale. Non è richiesto da nessuna norma della Costituzione, da nessuna legge, e il fascismo è finito cento anni fa. Non si può essere anti qualcosa che non esiste più\", ha detto il generale Roberto Vannacci al suo arrivo al teatro \"In Arte Vesuvio\" di Napoli dove è in corso la presentazione del suo libro. \"Cosi come nessuno ritiene di dichiararsi antinapoleonico duecento anni dopo - ha aggiunto - , ritengo strumentale dirsi antifascista rispetto a un periodo storico finito cento anni fa\". \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1714676433.630702,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-02 21:00:33",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-02T21.00.33",
        "en_title": "Vannacci, protests? A worrying picture",
        "en_content": "\"I don't understand why they don't come to the room in peace, I am for civil confrontation, I would listen to them and I would confront them. And no, I'm not afraid of my safety and I don't feel encircled.\" So General Roberto Vannacci commented on the event staged by social centers upon his arrival in Naples where he was to present his book. \"I thank the contestants, I invite them to come to this room to manifest their ideas, I have never subtracted myself to confrontation. But this invitation I make never happened. I don't feel encircled but I'm worried about the context that has come to create.\" \"I've never called myself anti-fascist because I don't think it's useful to define myself as such. It is not required by any norm of the Constitution, by no law, and fascism is finished one hundred years ago. You can't be anti anything that doesn't exist anymore\", said General Roberto Vannacci on his arrival at the theater \"In Arte Vesuvio\" in Naples where the presentation of his book is underway. \"As no one believes to declare antinapoleon two hundred years later - he added -, I think instrumental to say anti-fascist regarding a historical period finished one hundred years ago\".\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'But I'm not afraid of my safety, I don't feel encircled'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vannacci",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Roberto Vannacci",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Constitution",
                "start_char": 742,
                "end_char": 754,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "one hundred years ago",
                "start_char": 791,
                "end_char": 812,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Vannacci",
                "start_char": 883,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "In Arte Vesuvio",
                "start_char": 931,
                "end_char": 946,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Naples",
                "start_char": 951,
                "end_char": 957,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two hundred years later",
                "start_char": 1050,
                "end_char": 1073,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "one hundred years ago",
                "start_char": 1168,
                "end_char": 1189,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Elezioni europee: Nelle liste tanti soprannomi e oltre 20 giornalisti",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 2 May 2024 19:05:50 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/02/elezioni-europee-nelle-liste-tanti-soprannomi-e-oltre-20-giornalisti_32decfa9-334a-4e78-8593-0fb4edca8ba9.html",
        "subtitle": "Anche \"Ultimo e Pavone\". Con FdI la pronipote di Giolitti",
