[
    {
        "title": "Mattarella nomina 25 Cavalieri del Lavoro, anche Marina Berlusconi: \"Lo dedico a mio padre\"",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 16:05:26 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/31/mattarella-nomina-i-cavalieri-lavoro-anche-marina-berlusconi_333cca95-2c3f-4abb-b779-c2e90f2410fd.html",
        "subtitle": "Ci sono anche la stilista Chiara Boni, la produttrice discografica Caterina Caselli, la produttrice cinematografica Raffaella Leone",
        "content": " Il Presidente della Repubblica, Sergio Mattarella, ha firmato, in data 31 maggio, il decreto con il quale, su proposta del Ministro delle Imprese e del Made in Italy, Adolfo Urso, sono stati nominati 25 Cavalieri del Lavoro. Lo si legge in una nota del Quirinale. Nell'elenco ci sono, tra gli altri, la produttrice discografica e la stilista  Dell'elenco fanno parte: Lucia Aleotti; Eufrasio Anghileri; Giovanni Arena; Pietro Beccari; Marina Elvira Berlusconi; Paolo Bertazzoni; Maria Chiara Boni; Giorgio Campagnolo; Carmine Caputo; Caterina Imelde Caselli; Carlo Cimbri; Graziano Giordani; Raffaella Leone; Matteo Bruno Lunelli; Fausto Manzana; Giuseppe Marino; Francesco Giovanni Muntoni; Duilio Paolino; Vito Antonio Primiceri; Fabio Ravanelli; Edoardo Roncadin; Enrico Samer; Antonio Serena Monghini; Giovanni Sgariboldi; Aquilino Carlo Villani. \"Desidero esprimere la mia profonda gratitudine al capo dello Stato Sergio Mattarella e al Consiglio dell'Ordine al Merito del Lavoro per avermi onorata con questo prestigioso riconoscimento. Lo dedico a Silvio Berlusconi, mio padre, che è stato e sempre sarà 'Il Cavaliere'\". Così Marina Berlusconi, presidente di Mondadori e di Fininvest, nominata Cavaliere del lavoro. \"Voglio quindi condividere questo riconoscimento con ciascuna delle persone che lavorano in Mondadori, e, più in generale, con le persone di Mediaset e di tutto il gruppo Fininvest\", aggiunge.\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1717196422.4280484,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 01:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T01.00.22",
        "en_title": "Mattarella appoints 25 Knights of Labour, also Marina Berlusconi: \"I give it to my father\"",
        "en_content": "On 31 May the President of the Republic, Sergio Mattarella, signed the decree with which, on a proposal from the Minister of Enterprises and Made in Italy, Adolfo Urso, 25 Knights of Labour were appointed. You read it in a Quirinale note. The list includes the record producer and the list designer: Lucia Aleotti; Eufrasio Anghileri; Giovanni Arena; Pietro Beccari; Marina Elvira Berlusconi; Paolo Bertazzoni; Maria Chiara Boni; Giorgio Campagnolo; Carmine Caputo; Caterina Imelde Caselli; Carlo Cimbri; Graziano Giordani; Raffaella Leone; Matteo Bruno Lunelli; Fausto Manzana; Giuseppe Marino; Francesco Giovanni Muntoni; Duilio Paolino; Vito Antonio Primiceri; Fabio Ravanelli; Edoardo Roncadin; Enrico Samer; Antonio Serena Monghini; Giovanni Sgariboldi; Aquilino Carlo Villani. \"I wish to express my deep gratitude to the head of the State Sergio Mattarella and to the Council of the Order of Merit of Labour for honoring me with this prestigious award. I give it to Silvio Berlusconi, my father, who has been and will always be 'The Knight'. So Marina Berlusconi, president of Mondadori and Fininvest, appointed Cavaliere del lavoro. \"I want to share this recognition with each of the people working in Mondadori, and more generally with the people of Mediaset and the whole Fininvest group,\" he adds.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "There are also designer Chiara Boni, record producer Caterina Caselli, film producer Raffaella Leone",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mattarella",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "25",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Knights of Labour",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marina Berlusconi",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chiara Boni",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caterina Caselli",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raffaella Leone",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "31 May",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Mattarella",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Minister of Enterprises and Made",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Adolfo Urso",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "25",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Knights of Labour",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Quirinale",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lucia Aleotti",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eufrasio Anghileri",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giovanni Arena",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pietro Beccari",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marina Elvira Berlusconi",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paolo Bertazzoni",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 409,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria Chiara Boni",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgio Campagnolo",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carmine Caputo",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caterina Imelde Caselli",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlo Cimbri",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 503,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Graziano Giordani",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raffaella Leone",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 539,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Matteo Bruno Lunelli",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 561,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fausto Manzana",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 577,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giuseppe Marino",
                "start_char": 579,
                "end_char": 594,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Francesco Giovanni Muntoni",
                "start_char": 596,
                "end_char": 622,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Duilio Paolino",
                "start_char": 624,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vito Antonio Primiceri",
                "start_char": 640,
                "end_char": 662,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fabio Ravanelli",
                "start_char": 664,
                "end_char": 679,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Edoardo Roncadin",
                "start_char": 681,
                "end_char": 697,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Enrico Samer",
                "start_char": 699,
                "end_char": 711,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Serena Monghini",
                "start_char": 713,
                "end_char": 736,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giovanni Sgariboldi",
                "start_char": 738,
                "end_char": 757,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aquilino Carlo Villani",
                "start_char": 759,
                "end_char": 781,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 839,
                "end_char": 844,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Mattarella",
                "start_char": 845,
                "end_char": 862,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council of the Order of Merit of Labour",
                "start_char": 870,
                "end_char": 913,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Silvio Berlusconi",
                "start_char": 972,
                "end_char": 989,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Knight",
                "start_char": 1039,
                "end_char": 1045,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marina Berlusconi",
                "start_char": 1051,
                "end_char": 1068,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mondadori",
                "start_char": 1083,
                "end_char": 1092,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fininvest",
                "start_char": 1097,
                "end_char": 1106,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cavaliere del lavoro",
                "start_char": 1118,
                "end_char": 1138,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mondadori",
                "start_char": 1209,
                "end_char": 1218,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mediaset",
                "start_char": 1258,
                "end_char": 1266,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Domenica corteo di protesta degli antimilitaristi a Cagliari",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 13:42:06 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/politica_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/politica/2024/05/31/domenica-corteo-di-protesta-degli-antimilitaristi-a-cagliari_4e17cd97-aa2f-4880-b2e2-130a850b3c58.html",
        "subtitle": "Nel mirino anche l'aeroporto civile di Elmas , 'è militarizzato'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Anche l'aeroporto civile di\nCagliari è militarizzato. Lo denunciano i militanti di A Foras\nin una conferenza stampa nello scalo di Elmas. Sarà uno dei temi\ndella marcia di protesta di domenica 2 giugno: appuntamento alle\n16 in piazza San Bartolomento. \"Cagliari è una città a misura di\nmilitare. E l'aeroporto non fa eccezione - spiegano gli\nattivisti di A Foras - È utilizzato da molto tempo dai militari,\na cui non basta il vicino aeroporto di Decimomannu. In caso di\nnecessità le forze armate possono adibire l'intero scalo di\nElmas ad uso militare, come è avvenuto la notte del contrattacco\niraniano, con il lancio di centinaia di missili dall'Iran verso\nIsraele\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Una situazione a rischio. \"Un uso promiscuo che in caso di\nguerra rappresenta un grave pericolo per il traffico civile e\nper gli abitanti delle zone vicine - sottolineano gli\nantimilitaristi - Inoltre da più di dieci anni l'aeroporto di\nElmas è utilizzato per spedire carichi di bombe prodotte a\nDomusnovas. Da qui sono partite molte spedizioni dirette in\nArabia Saudita, per venire utilizzate nei bombardamenti contro\nla popolazione civile dello Yemen. Anche durante l'aggressione\ngenocida di Israele contro Gaza, molti carichi di bombe sono\npartiti da Elmas ed esiste il sospetto che alcuni di essi siano\nfiniti in Israele dopo avere fatto scalo in altri paesi per\ndepistare l'opinione pubblica e togliere dall' imbarazzo il\ngoverno italiano\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Per questo A Foras chiede alla Sogaer, società di gestione\ndell'aeroporto, \"di avere delucidazioni in merito alla\ndestinazione finale di tutti i carichi di morte che sono\ntransitati da Elmas\". Cagliari militarizzata, secondo gli\nattivisti del movimento: \"Dalla Sella del Diavolo a Monte\nUrpinu, fino al Poetto, passando dal porto ormai occupato in\npianta stabile da navi da guerra, sono tantissime le caserme,\nresidenze, depositi e installazioni, spesso inutilizzate ma\nancora sottratte all'uso della comunità\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Domenica la protesta, in occasione della festa della\nRepubblica: \"Per manifestare contro l'occupazione militare e in\nsolidarietà con il popolo palestines. Sarà un corteo allegro -\nannuncia a Foras - composito e colorato, di tutte le persone che\nvogliono vivere in un'Isola di pace, finalmente libera dalle\nlogiche di guerra e solidale con tutti i popoli oppressi\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Politica",
        "epoch": 1717196422.5186434,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 01:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T01.00.22",
        "en_title": "Sunday parade of anti-militarist protests in Cagliari",
        "en_content": "Also the civil airport\nCagliari is militarized. A Foras militants denounce it\nat a press conference at Elmas airport. It will be one of the themes\nof the protest march on Sunday 2 June: appointment at\n16 in Piazza San Bartolomento. \"Cagliari is a city to measure\nMilitary. And the airport is no exception - explain the\nA Foras activists - It has long been used by the military,\nto which is not enough the near airport of Decimomannu. In case of\nneed the armed forces can inhibit the entire port of call\nElmas for military use, as happened the night of the counterattack\nIran, with the launch of hundreds of missiles from Iran to\nIsrael.\"\n\n\nA risky situation. \"A promiscuous use that in case of\nwar represents a serious danger to civil traffic and\nfor the inhabitants of the nearby areas - emphasize the\nanti-militarists - Moreover for more than ten years the airport\nElmas is used to ship bomb loads produced at\nDomusnovas. Many direct shipments have started from here\nSaudi Arabia, to be used in bombings against\nthe civilian population of Yemen. Even during the attack\nIsrael’s genocide against Gaza, many bomb loads are\ndeparted from Elmas and there is suspicion that some of them are\nfinished in Israel after making stopovers in other countries for\ndepistare the public opinion and remove from embarrassment the\nItalian government\".\n\n\nFor this reason A Foras asks Sogaer, management company\nof the airport, \"to have clarifications regarding\nfinal destination of all death loads that are\ntransited by Elmas\". Cagliari militarized, according to the\nmovement activists: \"From the Sella del Diavolo to Monte\nUrpinu, to the Poetto, passing from the port now occupied in\nstable plant from warships, there are many barracks,\nresidences, deposits and installations, often unused but\nstill undermined the use of the community.\"\n\n\nSunday the protest, on the occasion of the feast of\nRepublic: \"To manifest against military occupation and in\nsolidarity with the people of Palermo. It will be a cheerful procession -\nannounces to Foras - composite and colorful, of all the people who\nthey want to live in an island of peace, finally free from\nlogic of war and solidarity with all the oppressed peoples.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In the view of Elmas civil airport, 'is militarized'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cagliari",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Elmas",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cagliari",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Foras",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Elmas airport",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday 2 June",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "16",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piazza San Bartolomento",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cagliari",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Foras",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Decimomannu",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elmas",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 508,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the night",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 574,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "hundreds",
                "start_char": 595,
                "end_char": 603,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 621,
                "end_char": 625,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 629,
                "end_char": 635,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than ten years",
                "start_char": 835,
                "end_char": 854,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elmas",
                "start_char": 867,
                "end_char": 872,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 969,
                "end_char": 981,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 1041,
                "end_char": 1046,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1071,
                "end_char": 1077,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1097,
                "end_char": 1101,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elmas",
                "start_char": 1137,
                "end_char": 1142,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1200,
                "end_char": 1206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 1316,
                "end_char": 1323,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Foras",
                "start_char": 1357,
                "end_char": 1362,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sogaer",
                "start_char": 1368,
                "end_char": 1374,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elmas",
                "start_char": 1504,
                "end_char": 1509,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cagliari",
                "start_char": 1512,
                "end_char": 1520,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monte\nUrpinu",
                "start_char": 1602,
                "end_char": 1614,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 1825,
                "end_char": 1831,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palermo",
                "start_char": 1965,
                "end_char": 1972,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Foras",
                "start_char": 2022,
                "end_char": 2027,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    }
]
