[
    {
        "title": "Brasile, la denuncia contro Bolsonaro arriva alla Corte suprema",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:41:37 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/brasile-la-denuncia-contro-bolsonaro-arriva-alla-corte-suprema_589ad00c-6bb8-41c7-ab1a-6eea962ca7a3.html",
        "subtitle": "A decidere il giudice Alexandre de Moraes",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il giudice della Corte suprema\nbrasiliana (Stf), Alexandre de Moraes, ha trasmesso la denuncia\ncontro l'ex presidente Jair Bolsonaro ed altre sette persone per\nil loro coinvolgimento nel presunto golpe di oltre due anni fa,\nalla Prima sezione del massimo organo giuridico verde-oro. Lo\nriporta il sito all news Poder360.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Spetta ora al presidente della Prima sezione della Corte\nsuprema, Cristiano Zanin, ex avvocato difensore del presidente\nLula durante la Lava Jato, la Mani Pulite brasiliana, definire\nuna data per analizzare l'accusa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La decisione arriva lo stesso giorno in cui il procuratore\ngenerale del Brasile, Paulo Gonet, ha respinto le richieste\ndegli avvocati difensori di Bolsonaro e di altri 7 accusati,\nmantenendo la denuncia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Oltre a quella contro Bolsonaro, Moraes ha trasmesso alla\nPrima sezione della Corte suprema anche la denuncia contro\nAlexandre Ramagem, ex-direttore generale dell'Abin (l'agenzia di\nintelligence brasiliana), Almir Garnier, ex-comandante della\nMarina, Anderson Torres, ex-ministro della Giustizia, Augusto\nHeleno, ex-ministro del Gabinetto di Sicurezza istituzionale,\nMauro Cid, ex-aiutante di campo di Bolsonaro, Paulo Sérgio\nNogueira, ex-ministro della Difesa e Braga Netto, ex-ministro\ndella Casa Civile e candidato alla vicepresidenza nel 2022. \n   Con Zanin, gli altri 4 giudici della Prima sezione della\nCorte suprema che dovranno decidere se accettano o no la\ndenuncia, sono lo stesso Moraes, Cármen Lúcia, Luiz Fux e Flávio\nDino. Se la denuncia sarà accettata, gli otto accusati\ndiventeranno imputati in sede penale. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903220.0118754,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.20",
        "en_title": "Brazil, the complaint against Bolsonaro arrives at the Supreme Court",
        "en_content": "The Supreme Court Judge\nBrazilian (Stf), Alexandre de Moraes, has transmitted the complaint\nagainst former president Jair Bolsonaro and seven other people for\ntheir involvement in the supposed coup over two years ago,\nto the first section of the maximum green-gold legal body. I do.\nreport the website to the news Poder360.\n\n\nIt is now up to the President of the First Chamber of the Court\nsupreme, Cristiano Zanin, former defender of the president\nLula during Lava Jato, the Brazilian Pulite Hands, define\na date to analyze the prosecution.\n\n\nThe decision comes the same day when the prosecutor\nGeneral of Brazil, Paulo Gonet, rejected requests\nof the defense attorneys of Bolsonaro and other 7 accused,\nmaintaining the complaint.\n\n\nIn addition to that against Bolsonaro, Moraes sent to\nFirst Chamber of the Supreme Court also the complaint against\nAlexandre Ramagem, former general manager of Abin (the agency of\nBrazilian intelligence), Almir Garnier, former commander of the\nMarina, Anderson Torres, former Minister of Justice, Augustus\nHeleno, former Minister of the Institutional Security Cabinet,\nMauro Cid, former field assistant of Bolsonaro, Paulo Sérgio\nNogueira, former Minister of Defense and Braga Netto, former Minister\nof the Civil House and candidate for vice president in 2022.\nWith Zanin, the other 4 judges of the First Chamber\nThe Court of Justice shall decide whether or not they accept\ncomplaint, are the same Moraes, Cármen Lúcia, Luiz Fux and Flávio\nDino. If the complaint is accepted, the eight accused\nThey'll be charged in the prosecution.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Judge Alexandre de Moraes",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jair Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two years ago",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the First Chamber of the Court",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cristiano Zanin",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lava Jato",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 470,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Brazilian Pulite Hands",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the same day",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 575,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 607,
                "end_char": 613,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paulo Gonet",
                "start_char": 615,
                "end_char": 626,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 674,
                "end_char": 683,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 694,
                "end_char": 695,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 771,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moraes",
                "start_char": 773,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "First Chamber of",
                "start_char": 788,
                "end_char": 804,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 805,
                "end_char": 822,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre Ramagem",
                "start_char": 850,
                "end_char": 867,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abin",
                "start_char": 895,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 915,
                "end_char": 924,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Almir Garnier",
                "start_char": 940,
                "end_char": 953,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marina",
                "start_char": 979,
                "end_char": 985,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anderson Torres",
                "start_char": 987,
                "end_char": 1002,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Justice",
                "start_char": 1023,
                "end_char": 1030,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Augustus\nHeleno",
                "start_char": 1032,
                "end_char": 1047,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Institutional Security Cabinet",
                "start_char": 1068,
                "end_char": 1102,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mauro Cid",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1113,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 1141,
                "end_char": 1150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paulo Sérgio",
                "start_char": 1152,
                "end_char": 1164,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nogueira",
                "start_char": 1165,
                "end_char": 1173,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Braga Netto",
                "start_char": 1206,
                "end_char": 1217,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Civil House",
                "start_char": 1238,
                "end_char": 1253,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2022",
                "start_char": 1290,
                "end_char": 1294,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanin",
                "start_char": 1301,
                "end_char": 1306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 1318,
                "end_char": 1319,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "First Chamber",
                "start_char": 1334,
                "end_char": 1347,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 1348,
                "end_char": 1368,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moraes",
                "start_char": 1433,
                "end_char": 1439,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cármen Lúcia",
                "start_char": 1441,
                "end_char": 1453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Fux",
                "start_char": 1455,
                "end_char": 1463,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Flávio",
                "start_char": 1468,
                "end_char": 1474,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 1515,
                "end_char": 1520,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani arrivato in Canada per il G7 Esteri",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:28:20 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/13/tajani-arrivato-in-canada-per-il-g7-esteri_de191e2f-823f-4bf2-bfb4-0d26f774c73c.html",
        "subtitle": "Atterrato anche Marco Rubio, incontri in Quebec fino al 14 marzo",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro degli\nEsteri Antonio Tajani è atterrato in Canada, dove prenderà parte\nalla riunione dei ministri degli Esteri del G7, la prima sotto\nla presidenza canadese, in programma dal 12 al 14 marzo a\nCharlevoix, in Quebec.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   I ministri discuteranno del conflitto in Ucraina, anche alla\nluce dei recenti colloqui a Gedda. La riunione vedrà poi una\ndiscussione su come rafforzare il formato G7 in occasione dei 50\nanni dalla sua istituzione, e prevede sessioni dedicate a\nIndopacifico, Americhe, Medio Oriente e Africa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel corso della missione, Tajani avrà numerosi incontri\nbilaterali, tra cui quello con il segretario di Stato, Marco\nRubio, l'omologo giapponese Takeshi Iwaya, la ministra canadese\nMélanie Joly e i partner europei. Infine, il vicepremier\nconcluderà il viaggio in Canada con un incontro a Quebec City\ncon un gruppo di imprenditori italiani presenti nel Paese,\ndedicato allo sviluppo delle opportunità di crescita tra Italia\ne Canada.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Anche il Segretario di Stato americano Marco Rubio è arrivato\nin Canada dall'Arabia Saudita. Rubio è il primo alto funzionario\ndell'amministrazione Trump a mettere piede sul suolo canadese,\nnel mezzo delle tensioni tra i due Paesi nordamericani coinvolti\nin una guerra commerciale scatenata dai dazi imposti da Donald\nTrump.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   All'arrivo a Québec, un piccolo tappeto rosso è stato steso\nsulla pista dell'aeroporto prima della sua partenza per\nraggiungere Charlevoix, dove si terrà la ministeriale G7 che\ndiscuterà della proposta di tregua in Ucraina ma anche di Medio\nOriente, Indopacifico e Africa. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903220.3259428,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.20",
        "en_title": "Tajani arrived in Canada for the G7 Esteri",
        "en_content": "The Minister for Foreign Affairs\nEsteri Antonio Tajani landed in Canada, where he will take part\nat the G7 Foreign Ministers meeting, the first under\nthe Canadian Presidency, scheduled from 12 to 14 March to\nCharlevoix, Quebec.\n\n\nThe ministers will discuss the conflict in Ukraine, including\nlight of recent talks in Gedda. The meeting will then see a\ndiscussion on how to strengthen the G7 format on the occasion of the 50\nyears from its institution, and provides sessions dedicated to\nIndopacific, America, Middle East and Africa.\n\n\nDuring the mission, Tajani will have numerous meetings\nbilateral, including the one with the Secretary of State, Marco\nRubio, the Japanese counterpart Takeshi Iwaya, the Canadian ministra\nMélanie Joly and European partners. Finally, the Vice-Premier\nwill conclude your trip to Canada with a meeting in Quebec City\nwith a group of Italian entrepreneurs present in the country,\ndedicated to the development of growth opportunities between Italy\nand Canada.\n\n\nAlso the American Secretary of State Marco Rubio arrived\nCanada from Saudi Arabia. Rubio is the first senior official\nof the Trump administration to set foot on Canadian soil,\nin the midst of tensions between the two North American countries involved\nin a commercial war unleashed by Donald's duties\nTrump.\n\n\nUpon arrival in Quebec, a small red carpet was laid\non the airport track before departure for\nreach Charlevoix, where the Ministerial G7 will be held\nwill discuss the proposal of truce in Ukraine but also of Middle\nEast, Indopathic and Africa.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Also landed Marco Rubio, meetings in Quebec until 14 March",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Marco Rubio",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quebec",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "14 March",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "12 to 14 March",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Charlevoix",
                "start_char": 208,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quebec",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gedda",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "50\nyears",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indopacific, America",
                "start_char": 487,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Middle East",
                "start_char": 509,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Africa",
                "start_char": 525,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 561,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 641,
                "end_char": 646,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco\nRubio",
                "start_char": 648,
                "end_char": 659,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japanese",
                "start_char": 665,
                "end_char": 673,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Takeshi Iwaya",
                "start_char": 686,
                "end_char": 699,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 705,
                "end_char": 713,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mélanie Joly",
                "start_char": 723,
                "end_char": 735,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 740,
                "end_char": 748,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 812,
                "end_char": 818,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quebec City",
                "start_char": 837,
                "end_char": 848,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 865,
                "end_char": 872,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 972,
                "end_char": 977,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 982,
                "end_char": 988,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 1001,
                "end_char": 1009,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 1023,
                "end_char": 1028,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco Rubio",
                "start_char": 1029,
                "end_char": 1040,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 1049,
                "end_char": 1055,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 1061,
                "end_char": 1073,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rubio",
                "start_char": 1075,
                "end_char": 1080,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1088,
                "end_char": 1093,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 1117,
                "end_char": 1122,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 1153,
                "end_char": 1161,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1205,
                "end_char": 1208,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "North American",
                "start_char": 1209,
                "end_char": 1223,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald",
                "start_char": 1276,
                "end_char": 1282,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 1292,
                "end_char": 1297,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Quebec",
                "start_char": 1317,
                "end_char": 1323,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Charlevoix",
                "start_char": 1401,
                "end_char": 1411,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministerial G7",
                "start_char": 1419,
                "end_char": 1437,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 1489,
                "end_char": 1496,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Middle\nEast",
                "start_char": 1509,
                "end_char": 1520,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indopathic",
                "start_char": 1522,
                "end_char": 1532,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Africa",
                "start_char": 1537,
                "end_char": 1543,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Marcia indietro decisiva di Trump sui gas serra",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:53:19 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/12/marcia-indietro-decisiva-di-trump-sui-gas-serra_0711c4c9-1a37-4cb6-8917-dcdc549cb60d.html",
        "subtitle": "L'Epa ritira una serie di norme contro l'inquinamento",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'amministrazione Trump ha\nannunciato una clamorosa marcia indietro sui gas serra, una\nmossa che minaccia di fare a pezzi le fondamenta delle leggi sul\nclima negli Stati Uniti. Lo riporta il New York Times.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'Environmental Protection Agency (Epa) ha, infatti,  ritirato\noggi una sostanziosa serie di norme sull'inquinamento dopo aver\ndichiarato l'intenzione di voler annullare la storica\nconclusione di uno studio del governo americano del 2009 secondo\ncui i gas che riscaldano il pianeta, come l'anidride carbonica,\nrappresentano una minaccia per la salute umana. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 65,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903220.3704457,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.20",
        "en_title": "Trump's decisive back march on greenhouse gases",
        "en_content": "The Trump administration has\nannounced a clamorous march back on greenhouse gases, a\nmove that threatens to tear apart the foundations of laws on\nclimate in the United States. The New York Times.\n\n\nThe Environmental Protection Agency (Epa) has, in fact, withdrawn\ntoday a substantial set of pollution standards after having\ndeclared the intention of wanting to cancel the historian\nconclusion of a study by the American government of 2009 according to\nwhich gases that heat the planet, like carbon dioxide,\nrepresent a threat to human health.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The EPA withdraws a series of rules against pollution",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EPA",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The New York Times",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Environmental Protection Agency",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Epa",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 269,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "2009",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Brasile, Golden Visa agli stranieri che comprano immobili",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:00:45 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/brasile-golden-visa-agli-stranieri-che-comprano-immobili_de09a3f6-85e2-4143-bacf-25522378925e.html",
        "subtitle": "Il governo firma patto con l'Ente degli intermediari immobiliari",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministero del Turismo del\nBrasile ed il Consiglio verde-oro degli intermediari immobiliari\n(Cofeci) hanno firmato un protocollo d'intesa per mettere in\npratica il Golden Visa brasiliano e così attrarre investitori\nstranieri. Lo rende noto il sito della Folha de São Paulo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'accordo è stato siglato al Mipim, evento immobiliare\ninternazionale che si tiene a Cannes, in Francia e due progetti\nsono già stati commercializzati in Francia. Il Golden Visa\nesiste già in diversi paesi, tra cui la Spagna e l'aspettativa è\ndi attrarre 160 milioni di euro (circa un miliardo di reais) in\nBrasile in questo primo anno di implementazione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIl programma consente agli investitori di altri paesi di\nottenere un visto permanente in Brasile dopo l'acquisto di\nimmobili da 158.400 euro (un milione di reais) in su nelle\nregioni del sud, del sudest e del centro ovest, e da almeno\n110.800 euro (700mila reais) nel nord e nel nordest. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903223.5476549,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.23",
        "en_title": "Brazil, Golden Visa to foreigners who buy properties",
        "en_content": "The Ministry of Tourism\nBrazil and the Green Gold Council of real estate intermediaries\n(Cofeci) signed a memorandum of understanding to put in\npractice the Brazilian Golden Visa and so attract investors\nforeigners. It makes known the site of the Folha de São Paulo.\n\n\nThe agreement was signed at Mipim, real estate event\ninternational held in Cannes, France and two projects\nhave already been marketed in France. The Golden Visa\nthere is already in several countries, including Spain and expectation is\nto attract 160 million euros (about one billion reais) in\nBrazil in this first year of implementation.\n\n\nThe program allows investors from other countries\nobtain a permanent visa in Brazil after purchasing\n158,400 euros (one million reais) up in\nregions of the south, southeast and west, and from at least\n110,800 euros (700 thousand reais) in the north and northeast.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The government signs pact with the body of real estate intermediaries",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Golden Visa",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of Tourism",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Green Gold Council",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cofeci",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mipim",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cannes",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Golden Visa",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 479,
                "end_char": 484,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "160 million euros",
                "start_char": 515,
                "end_char": 532,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "about one billion reais",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 557,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 562,
                "end_char": 568,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this first year",
                "start_char": 572,
                "end_char": 587,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 686,
                "end_char": 692,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "158,400 euros",
                "start_char": 710,
                "end_char": 723,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "one million reais",
                "start_char": 725,
                "end_char": 742,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "110,800 euros",
                "start_char": 810,
                "end_char": 823,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "700 thousand reais",
                "start_char": 825,
                "end_char": 843,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "SpaceX rinvia missione per recuperare astronauti su Iss",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:53:23 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/13/spacex-rinvia-missione-per-recuperare-astronauti-su-iss_bb8bb597-3cdb-413d-b815-80418dccddc2.html",
        "subtitle": "Nasa: 'Problemi alla rampa di lancio'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Un problema alla rampa di\nlancio ha costretto SpaceX a rinviare il volo per recuperare e\nsostituire i due astronauti bloccati sulla Stazione spaziale\ninternazionale dopo nove mesi in orbita. Lo ha annunciato la\nNasa: \"La Nasa e SpaceX hanno deciso di ritirare la missione\nCrew-10 dell'agenzia verso la Iss\", si legge in una nota. \"C'è\nstato un problema con il sistema idraulico a terra\", ha riferito\nfunzionario Derrol Nail, aggiungendo che  \"il razzo e la\nnavicella non hanno nessun guasto\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903223.5530698,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.23",
        "en_title": "SpaceX postpones mission to recover astronauts on Iss",
        "en_content": "A problem at the ramp\nlaunch forced SpaceX to postpone the flight to recover and\nreplace the two blocked astronauts on the Space Station\ninternational after nine months in orbit. He announced it\nNasa: \"The Nasa and SpaceX decided to withdraw the mission\nCrew-10 of the agency towards Iss,\" reads in a note. \"There is\nwas a problem with the hydraulic system on the ground,\" he reported\nDerrol Nail official, adding that \"the rocket and the\nship has no fault.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Nasa: 'Problems to the launch ramp'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SpaceX",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iss",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nasa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "SpaceX",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Space Station",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "nine months",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nasa",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nasa",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SpaceX",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iss",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Derrol Nail",
                "start_char": 385,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Intel nomina un nuovo ceo, le azioni balzano dell'11%",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:06:56 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/13/intel-nomina-un-nuovo-ceo-le-azioni-balzano-dell11_cbb4dd06-c487-4810-9d37-814f60f3418a.html",
        "subtitle": "Tan Lip-Bu dovrà risollevare le sorti dell'azienda di microchip",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Intel ha nominato Tan Lip-Bu\nnuovo amministratore delegato a partire dal 18 marzo. Lo\nriportano i media americani. Ex capo di Cadence Design Systems,\nil 65enneTan avrà il difficile compito di risollevare le sorti\ndi un'azienda pioniera nella produzione dei chip ma che ora è in\nforti crisi. Intel, che ha dominato il campo dei semiconduttori\nper decenni, sta lottando con perdite di quote di mercato,\nbattute d'arresto nella produzione e un brusco calo dei suoi\nguadagni. È anche gravata dai debiti e di recente ha dovuto\ntagliare circa 15.000 posti di lavoro. In un'email ai\ndipendenti, Tansi è detto fiducisio di poter cambiare direzione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t \"Questo non significa che sarà facile. Non lo sarà\", ha\nscritto. \"Ma sono convinto che Intel svolga un ruolo essenziale\nnell'ecosistema tecnologico, sia negli Stati Uniti che nel resto\ndel mondo\". Dopo la nomina le azioni dell'azienda sono balzate\ndi oltre l'11% dopo che il titolo era sceso di oltre il 54% \nnegli ultimi 12 mesi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903223.5613475,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.23",
        "en_title": "Intel appoints a new board, shares jump by 11%",
        "en_content": "Intel appointed Tan Lip-Bu\nnew CEO from 18 March. I do.\nAmerican media reports. Former head of Cadence Design Systems,\nthe 65-year-oldTan will have the difficult task of raising the fortunes\nof a pioneer company in chip production but which is now in\nStrong crisis. Intel, who dominated the semiconductor field\nfor decades, he is struggling with market share losses,\nstop jokes in production and a sharp drop in its\nearnings. It is also burdened by debts and recently had\ncut about 15,000 jobs. In an email to\nemployees, Tansi is said confident to be able to change direction.\n\n\n\"That doesn't mean it'll be easy. It won't be,\" he said.\nwritten. \"But I'm convinced that Intel plays an essential role\nin the technological ecosystem, both in the United States and in the rest\nof the world.\" After the appointment the shares of the company have jumped\nby over 11% after the title had dropped by over 54%\nin the last 12 months.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Tan Lip-Bu will have to raise the fortunes of the microchip company",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Intel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "11%",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tan Lip-Bu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Intel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tan Lip-Bu",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "18 March",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cadence Design Systems",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "65-year",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Intel",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "decades",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 15,000",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tansi",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Intel",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 674,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 739,
                "end_char": 756,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 11%",
                "start_char": 851,
                "end_char": 859,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "over 54%",
                "start_char": 891,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the last 12 months",
                "start_char": 903,
                "end_char": 921,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Guyana, intercettata una barca con a bordo 75 venezuelani",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:33:24 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/guyana-intercettata-una-barca-con-a-bordo-75-venezuelani_91c064df-2851-4355-8246-149ec303ed2a.html",
        "subtitle": "Sulla costa dell'Essequibo. Tutti i migranti sono stati espulsi",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La polizia di pattuglia della\nGuyana ha intercettato vicino alla diga di Abram Zuil, lungo la\ncosta dell'Essequibo contesa con Caracas, una barca di 13 metri\nalimentata da due motori fuoribordo Yamaha da 75 cv con a bordo\n75 cittadini venezuelani, 57 uomini, 9 donne ed altrettanti\nbambini.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Secondo le autorità di Georgetown (la capitale della Guyana),\ncome riportato dal sito Caribbean News, durante la loro\ndetenzione iniziata lunedì 10 marzo e durata 24 ore, i 75\nmigranti venezuelani hanno ricevuto \"un trattamento umanitario,\nricevendo cibo e rifugio temporaneo in una struttura locale\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   I 75 migranti sono stati scortati fuori dalla Guyana sino al\nconfine con il Venezuela ieri, 11 marzo, dopo che al gruppo \"è\nstato fornito il carburante e gli altri beni necessari per il\nloro ritorno a casa\", ha precisato in un comunicato la Guardia\ncostiera di Georgetown.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'episodio conferma il flusso crescente di venezuelani verso\ni Paesi vicini a causa della precaria situazione economica e\npolitica nel loro paese. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903223.5752208,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.23",
        "en_title": "Guyana, intercepted a boat with 75 Venezuelans",
        "en_content": "The patrol police of the\nGuyana intercepted near the dam of Abram Zuil, along the\ncoast of the Essequibo disputed with Caracas, a boat of 13 meters\npowered by two Yamaha outboard engines from 75 cv with onboard\n75 Venezuelan citizens, 57 men, 9 women and as many\nChildren.\n\n\nAccording to the authorities of Georgetown (the capital of Guyana),\nas reported by the site Caribbean News, during their\ndetention started on Monday 10 March and lasted 24 hours, i 75\nVenezuelan migrants received \"a humanitarian treatment,\nreceiving food and temporary shelter in a local facility.\"\n\n\nThe 75 migrants were escorted outside Guyana until the\nborder with Venezuela yesterday, March 11, after the group \"is\nprovided the fuel and other goods necessary for\ntheir return home,\" said the Guard in a statement\nGeorgetown Coast.\n\n\nThe episode confirms the growing flow of Venezuelans towards\nthe neighboring countries because of the precarious economic situation and\npolicy in their country.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "On the coast of Essequibo. All migrants have been expelled",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Guyana",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "75",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelans",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Essequibo",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Guyana",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abram Zuil",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Essequibo",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "13 meters",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yamaha",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "75",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "cv",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "75",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "57",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "9",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Georgetown",
                "start_char": 307,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guyana",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caribbean News",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday 10 March",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 hours",
                "start_char": 444,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "75",
                "start_char": 456,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 459,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "75",
                "start_char": 580,
                "end_char": 582,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guyana",
                "start_char": 614,
                "end_char": 620,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 643,
                "end_char": 652,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 653,
                "end_char": 662,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 11",
                "start_char": 664,
                "end_char": 672,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Georgetown Coast",
                "start_char": 792,
                "end_char": 808,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelans",
                "start_char": 853,
                "end_char": 864,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Brasile, leader narcos del Comando Vermelho liberato a Carnevale",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:32:24 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/brasile-leader-narcos-del-comando-vermelho-liberato-a-carnevale_18cfe625-e248-485c-8bf1-ad1b2e89c21f.html",
        "subtitle": "Lopes, condannato a 39 anni, non è più tornato in carcere",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Considerato uno dei leader nello\nstato del Mato Grosso del Comando Vermelho, la seconda maggiore\norganizzazione criminale del Brasile, il trentenne Janderson dos\nSantos Lopes è latitante dopo essere stato liberato durante\nl'ultimo Carnevale. Pur scontando una pena di 39 anni per\nnarcotraffico, Lopes godeva di privilegi in carcere, lasciandolo\ndurante il giorno guidare la sua auto per gestire beni acquisiti\nillegalmente tra cui una compagnia di trasporti, un negozio di\nmateriali da costruzione, immobili e proprietà rurali per\nrientrare in prigione solo di notte, riporta il sito all news\nbrasiliano Metropóles.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'ordine di liberazione è stato firmato dalla giudice Luciana\nBraga Simão Tomazetti ma nonostante la decisione sia stata\nannullata poco dopo, lui aveva già lasciato la prigione di\nPrimavera do Leste, nel Mato Grosso, nel Brasile\ncentro-occidentale. La richiesta di liberazione fatta\ndall'avvocato di Lopes ha sostenuto l'eccesso di tempo\nnell'ultimo processo penale contro di lui, sostenendo che farlo\nuscire per Carnevale non comportava rischi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIn prigione, Lopes ha accumulato un patrimonio milionario,\ninclusa una flotta di camion e rimorchi per la sua impresa, la\nTransportadora Lopes, immobili nelle città di Cuiabá, la\ncapitale del Mato Grosso, di Primavera do Leste e di Poxoréu,\noltre a veicoli di lusso e allevamenti di bestiame. Tra febbraio\n2022 e novembre 2023, le movimentazioni finanziarie legate alle\nattività di Lopes sono arrivate ad oltre 3,8 milioni di euro (24\nmilioni di reais) secondo un rapporto di intelligence del\nConsiglio di controllo delle attività finanziarie del Brasile,\nil Coaf. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903223.6060658,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.23",
        "en_title": "Brazil, leader narcos of the Vermelho Command liberated at Carnival",
        "en_content": "Considered one of the leaders in\nstate of the Mato Grosso of the Vermelho Command, the second major\ncriminal organization of Brazil, the thirty-year-old Janderson dos\nSantos Lopes is stained after being released during\nthe last Carnival. While serving a 39-year sentence for\nnarcotraffic, Lopes enjoyed privileges in prison, leaving him\nduring the day driving his car to manage acquired assets\nillegally including a transport company, a store\nbuilding materials, buildings and rural properties for\nreturn to prison only at night, report the website to news\nBrazilian Metropóles.\n\n\nThe order of liberation was signed by Judge Luciana\nBraga Simão Tomazetti but despite the decision it was\ncanceled shortly after, he had already left prison\nPrimavera do Leste, in Mato Grosso, Brazil\nCentral-Western. The demand for liberation made\nby Lopes' lawyer supported the excess of time\nin the last criminal trial against him, claiming that he will do so\nleaving for Carnival did not involve risks.\n\n\nIn prison, Lopes has accumulated a millionaire heritage,\nincluded a fleet of trucks and trailers for his company, the\nTransportadora Lopes, real estate in the cities of Cuiabá, la\ncapital of Mato Grosso, of Primavera do Leste and Poxoréu,\nbesides luxury vehicles and livestock farms. February\n2022 and November 2023\nLopes activities have reached over 3,8 million euros (24\nmillion reais) according to an intelligence report\nBrazil's Financial Activity Control Council,\nCoaf.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Lopes, sentenced to 39 years, has not returned to prison",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Vermelho Command",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Carnival",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lopes",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "39 years",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Mato Grosso",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Vermelho Command",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "thirty-year-old",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Janderson",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santos Lopes",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "39-year",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lopes",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "only at night",
                "start_char": 515,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian Metropóles",
                "start_char": 557,
                "end_char": 577,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luciana\n",
                "start_char": 625,
                "end_char": 633,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Braga Simão Tomazetti",
                "start_char": 633,
                "end_char": 654,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Primavera",
                "start_char": 738,
                "end_char": 747,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Leste",
                "start_char": 751,
                "end_char": 756,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mato Grosso",
                "start_char": 761,
                "end_char": 772,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 774,
                "end_char": 780,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lopes",
                "start_char": 832,
                "end_char": 837,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carnival",
                "start_char": 955,
                "end_char": 963,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lopes",
                "start_char": 1000,
                "end_char": 1005,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Transportadora Lopes",
                "start_char": 1107,
                "end_char": 1127,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cuiabá",
                "start_char": 1158,
                "end_char": 1164,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mato Grosso",
                "start_char": 1180,
                "end_char": 1191,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Primavera",
                "start_char": 1196,
                "end_char": 1205,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Leste",
                "start_char": 1209,
                "end_char": 1214,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poxoréu",
                "start_char": 1219,
                "end_char": 1226,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "February\n2022",
                "start_char": 1273,
                "end_char": 1286,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "November 2023",
                "start_char": 1291,
                "end_char": 1304,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lopes",
                "start_char": 1305,
                "end_char": 1310,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3,8 million euros",
                "start_char": 1340,
                "end_char": 1357,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "24\nmillion reais",
                "start_char": 1359,
                "end_char": 1375,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 1413,
                "end_char": 1419,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Financial Activity Control Council",
                "start_char": 1422,
                "end_char": 1456,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Coaf",
                "start_char": 1458,
                "end_char": 1462,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Scontri a Buenos Aires, grave un fotografo ferito alla testa",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:45:34 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/scontri-a-buenos-aires-grave-un-fotografo-ferito-alla-testa_0f90f647-3aaa-48a7-b6dd-71f5bb78ba54.html",
        "subtitle": "Battaglia campale nella manifestazione a sostegno dei pensionati",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Decine di feriti, tra cui un\nfotografo in condizioni gravissime, e oltre 150 arresti. E' il\nbilancio ancora provvisorio della battaglia campale che si è\nscatenata nel pomeriggio di mercoledì nel centro di Buenos Aires\nnel contesto di una manifestazione a sostegno dei pensionati e\ncontro i tagli del governo ultraliberista di Javier Milei.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tGli ingredienti per l'accensione della miccia degli incidenti\nc'erano tutti: dalla presenza annunciata di gruppi ultras a\nsostegno dei pensionati agli avvertimenti del governo che non\navrebbe tollerato disordini né la violazione del rigido\nprotocollo anti-proteste e che avrebbe schierato migliaia di\nagenti delle tre forze di sicurezza: polizia, gendarmeria e\nprefettura.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tA fine giornata l'episodio più grave è quello che riguarda il\nfotografo Pablo Grillo, colpito alla testa da un fumogeno\nsparato dalla polizia ad altezza d'uomo e attualmente ricoverato\nin condizioni gravissime. Le immagini di Grillo che si accascia\na terra improvvisamente, colpito da un proiettile mentre cerca\ndi ritrarre l'azione della polizia, e le drammatiche foto del\nragazzo con il cranio fratturato stanno facendo il giro dei\nsocial.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tA fare le spese della repressione delle forze di sicurezza è\nstata anche una pensionata di 80 anni, caduta a terra dopo aver\nricevuto una manganellata e ricoverata con trauma cranico.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tDiversi video sui social testimoniano anche questo momento.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIl ministero della Sicurezza riferisce d'altra parte di 26\nagenti feriti, di cui uno colpito a un braccio da un proiettile\nd'arma da fuoco mentre non è stato stilato invece ancora un\nbilancio dei danni materiali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tAl momento della smobilitazione i segni della battaglia -  con\ndecine di cassonetti in fiamme, una volante distrutta, resti di\nbarricate e migliaia di pietre sull'asfalto - erano evidenti in\ntutto il centro della capitale, dalla piazza del Parlamento,\ndove tutto è iniziato, fino alla Casa Rosada nell'iconica Plaza\nde Mayo, dove è proseguita la caccia degli agenti ai\nmanifestanti. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 56,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903223.6332183,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.23",
        "en_title": "Scontri in Buenos Aires, a photographer injured in the head",
        "en_content": "Tens of wounded, including a\nphotographer in very serious conditions, and over 150 arrests. It's the\nstill provisional balance of the battle of the camp\non Wednesday afternoon in the centre of Buenos Aires\nin the context of a demonstration in support of pensioners and\nagainst the ultra-liberal government cuts of Javier Milei.\n\n\nIngredients for the ignition of the mice of accidents\nthere were all: from the announced presence of ultras a groups\nsupport of pensioners to government warnings which do not\nwould have tolerated disorders or violation of rigidity\nAnti-protection protocol that would have deployed thousands of\nagents of the three security forces: Police, gendarmerie and\nPrefecture.\n\n\nAt the end of the day the most serious episode is what concerns the\nphotographer Pablo Grillo, hit the head by a smoke\nshot by the police at the height of man and currently hospitalized\nin very serious conditions. The images of Grillo that is lit\non the ground suddenly, hit by a bullet while looking\nto portray police action, and dramatic photos of the\nboy with fractured skull are doing round the\nsocial.\n\n\nTo make the expenses of the repression of the security forces is\nwas also an 80-year-old pensioner, who fell to the ground after\nreceived a manganellated and admitted with skull trauma.\n\n\nSeveral social videos also witness this moment.\n\n\nThe Ministry of Security reports on the other hand of 26\nwounded agents, of which one hit an arm by a bullet\nof firearms while it was not drafted instead still a\nbalance of material damage.\n\n\nAt the moment of demobilization the signs of the battle - with\ndozens of barrels in flames, a broken steering wheel, remains of\nbarricades and thousands of stones on asphalt - were evident in\nall the center of the capital, from the square of Parliament,\nwhere everything started, until Casa Rosada in the iconic Plaza\nde Mayo, where the hunt for agents continued\nprotesters.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Country battle in the event in support of pensioners",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Scontri",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tens",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 150",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wednesday afternoon",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei.",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 611,
                "end_char": 620,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 638,
                "end_char": 643,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of the day",
                "start_char": 702,
                "end_char": 720,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pablo Grillo",
                "start_char": 780,
                "end_char": 792,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Grillo",
                "start_char": 927,
                "end_char": 933,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "80-year-old",
                "start_char": 1185,
                "end_char": 1196,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of Security",
                "start_char": 1346,
                "end_char": 1370,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "26",
                "start_char": 1400,
                "end_char": 1402,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 1428,
                "end_char": 1431,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 1601,
                "end_char": 1607,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 1681,
                "end_char": 1690,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 1780,
                "end_char": 1790,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Casa Rosada",
                "start_char": 1824,
                "end_char": 1835,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Plaza\nde Mayo",
                "start_char": 1850,
                "end_char": 1863,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Visita in Messico del Sottosegretario Delmastro",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:14:32 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/visita-in-messico-del-sottosegretario-delmastro_e2736c6b-7b70-4c68-a8d7-ff4a4780df48.html",
        "subtitle": "Missione nel quadro della cooperazione su giustizia e sicurezza",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Sottosegretario alla\nGiustizia, Andrea Delmastro, ha effettuato dal 6 al 9 marzo\nun'articolata visita in Messico. Nel corso della missione, ha\navuto incontri con la Ministra di Gobernación, Rosa Icela\nRodriguez, con il Sottosegretario alla Governance, Arturo Medina\nPadilla, con il Sottosegretario alla Sicurezza, Hector Elizalde,\ncon la Sottosegretaria agli Esteri competente per l'Europa,\nMaria Teresa Mercado, con il Presidente del Tribunale di\nGiustizia di Città del Messico, Rafael Guerra, e con il\nComandante della Guardia Nazionale, Hernan Cortes Hernandez.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tAl termine dell'incontro presso il Ministero della Sicurezza,\nDelmastro ha firmato una dichiarazione d'intenti fra il\nMinistero della Giustizia italiano, il Ministero della Sicurezza\nMessicano e l'Istituto Interregionale delle Nazioni Unite per la\nRicerca sul Crimine e la Giustizia (Unicri) con sede a Roma,\nvolta a rafforzare la collaborazione nel contrasto alla\ncriminalità organizzata, in materia di giustizia penale e\namministrazione penitenziaria, lotta all'estorsione e alla\ncorruzione. La cooperazione si svolgerà sotto l'egida di Unicri\nche ha effettuato a dicembre 2024 una prima missione per\nincontrare le Autorità messicane, insieme ai rappresentanti\ndell'Ambasciata italiana. La missione del Sottosegretario\nDelmastro si è conclusa con una visita al penitenziario federale\nfemminile di Morelos, e con una colazione di lavoro presso\nl'Istituto Mexicano para la Justicia (Imjus), parimenti\ncoinvolto nella lettera di intenti.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"La mia seconda missione in Messico - ha dichiarato il\nSottosegretario - aveva l'obiettivo di concordare con le nuove\nAutorità di governo messicane il percorso per un ulteriore\nrafforzamento della già solida collaborazione fra i due Paesi\nnel settore della giustizia e sicurezza e nel contrasto alla\ncriminalità organizzata, attraverso il sostegno cooperativo\ndelle Nazioni Unite (UNICRI). Nel corso di tutti gli incontri, è\nemerso il forte interesse delle controparti a sviluppare la\ncooperazione e la conoscenza delle metodologie acquisite\ndall'Italia in decenni di contrasto alle mafie. Il Messico è una\ndemocrazia stabile e un partner affidabile, e il Governo\nitaliano è pronto a rafforzare la collaborazione nella sfida\ncomune alla criminalità organizzata\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741903223.661719,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 23:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-13T22.00.23",
        "en_title": "Visit to Mexico by Undersecretary Delmastro",
