[
    {
        "title": "L'appello di Zelensky, 'subito i missili Patriot'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:15:07 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/21/lappello-di-zelensky-subito-i-missili-patriot_e345673c-a00b-477b-8692-5d820749edea.html",
        "subtitle": "Presidente ucraino: 'Non rimangano invece negli stoccaggi'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"I patriot possono essere definiti\nsistemi di difesa aerea solo se funzionano e salvano vite umane\ninvece di restare immobili da qualche parte nelle basi di\nstoccaggio. I patriot devono essere in mano agli ucraini in\nquesto momento. Nei cieli ucraini sono necessari moderni aerei\nda combattimento. I missili russi e i droni iraniani Shahed\ndevono essere sconfitti per fare trionfare in futuro la vita\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tE' l'appello lanciato del presidente ucraino Volodymyr Zelensky\nsu X all'indomani dell'approvazione da parte della Camera Usa\ndegli aiuti militari per 60 miliardi a Kiev. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 48,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790928.856776,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:08",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.08",
        "en_title": "Zelensky's appeal, 'subito i missile Patriot'",
        "en_content": "\" Patriots can be defined\nair defense systems only if they work and save human lives\ninstead of staying still somewhere in the bases\nstorage. Patriots must be in the hands of Ukrainians in\nThis moment. Modern planes are needed in the Ukrainian skies\ncombat. Russian missiles and Iranian drones Shahed\nmust be defeated to make life triumph in the future.\"\n\n\nIt's Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky's launched appeal\non X after approval by the US House\nmilitary aid for 60 billion in Kiev.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Ukrainian President: 'They don't stay in storage.'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Patriot",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Patriots",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainians",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shahed",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the US",
                "start_char": 442,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "60 billion",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 482,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Elezioni alle Maldive, test sulla rivalità tra Cina e India",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:55:27 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/21/elezioni-alle-maldive-test-sulla-rivalita-tra-cina-e-india_e85d0a20-33a6-4f3a-abd9-ed140a9e356f.html",
        "subtitle": "Il presidente è fautore del riavvicinamento a Pechino",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Le Maldive votano oggi per le\nelezioni legislative che si presentano come un test per la\npolitica di riavvicinamento del presidente Mohamed Muizzu alla\nCina, a scapito dell'India, da tempo potenza dominante\nnell'arcipelago turistico dell'Oceano Indiano.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Le isole delle Maldive che si trovano nell'Oceano Indiano,\noccupano una posizione strategica sulle principali rotte\nmarittime internazionali est-ovest, e sono diventate un focolaio\ndi rivalità geopolitica tra India e Cina. Il presidente, 45\nanni, è stato uno dei primi a votare alla Tajuddin School della\ncapitale Malé.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  Da quando Mohamed Muizzu è entrato in carica alla fine del\n2023, i parlamentari hanno bloccato tre delle sue nomine\ngovernative e rifiutato alcune delle sue proposte di bilancio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'attuale parlamento, dominato dal Partito Democratico\nMaldiviano (Mdp) filo-indiano del suo predecessore Ibrahim\nMohamed Solih, ha cercato di contrastare i suoi sforzi per\nriorientare la diplomazia dell'arcipelago. Si prevede che le\ndivisioni all'interno dei principali partiti politici, compreso\nil Congresso nazionale del popolo (Pnc) di Muizzu, impediranno\nai partiti di ottenere una maggioranza netta, dicono gli\nosservatori, e renderanno necessaria la formazione di una\ncoalizione. Si prevede che il rilascio, giovedì, del mentore del\nleader, l'ex presidente Abdulla Yameen, a seguito della revoca\nda parte di un tribunale della sua condanna a 11 anni di carcere\nper corruzione e riciclaggio di denaro, dovrebbe rafforzare\nMuizzu.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'India considera l'arcipelago parte della sua sfera\nd'influenza, ma le Maldive sono cadute nell'orbita della Cina,\nil suo maggiore creditore estero, con l'elezione di Muizzu.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tSempre a marzo, Malé ha firmato un accordo di \"assistenza\nmilitare\" con Pechino che mira a \"rafforzare i legami\nbilaterali\", secondo il ministero della Difesa delle Maldive.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 46,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.5197268,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Maldive Elections, Test on rivalry between China and India",
        "en_content": "Maldives vote today for\nlegislative elections presenting themselves as a test for\nPresident Mohamed Muizzu's approach policy\nChina, at the expense of India, by time dominant power\nin the tourist archipelago of the Indian Ocean.\n\n\nThe Maldives islands in the Indian Ocean,\ntake a strategic position on the main routes\ninternational seafarers east-west, and became a focolaio\nof geopolitical rivalry between India and China. The President, 45\nyears, it was one of the first to vote at the Tajuddin School\ncapital Malé.\n\n\nSince Mohamed Muizzu entered office at the end of the\n2023, the MPs have blocked three of his appointments\nI would like to thank the rapporteur for his work.\n\n\nThe current parliament, dominated by the Democratic Party\nMaldivian (Mdp) pro-Indian of his predecessor Ibrahim\nMohamed Solih, tried to counter his efforts to\nreorient the diplomacy of the archipelago. It is expected that\ndivisions within the main political parties, including\nthe National Congress of the People (Pnc) of Muizzu, will prevent\nto the parties to obtain a clear majority, say the\nobservers, and will make necessary the formation of a\ncoalition. It is expected that the issue, Thursday, of the mentor of the\nleader, former President Abdulla Yameen, following the revocation\nby a court of his sentence to 11 years in prison\nfor corruption and money laundering, should strengthen\nMove.\n\n\nIndia considers the archipelago part of its sphere\nbut the Maldives fell into China's orbit,\nhis major foreign creditor, with the election of Muizzu.\n\n\nAlso in March, Malé signed a \"assistance agreement\"\nmilitary\" with Beijing aiming to \"strengthen ties\nBilateral\", according to the Ministry of Defense of the Maldives.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The president is author of the rapprochement in Beijing",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "India",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Maldives",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed Muizzu",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "India",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Indian Ocean",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maldives",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Indian Ocean",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "India",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "45\nyears",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Tajuddin School",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 502,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Malé",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohamed Muizzu",
                "start_char": 525,
                "end_char": 539,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 573,
                "end_char": 577,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 600,
                "end_char": 605,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Democratic Party",
                "start_char": 716,
                "end_char": 736,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "pro-Indian",
                "start_char": 753,
                "end_char": 763,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ibrahim\nMohamed Solih",
                "start_char": 783,
                "end_char": 804,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Congress of the People (Pnc",
                "start_char": 956,
                "end_char": 996,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Muizzu",
                "start_char": 1001,
                "end_char": 1007,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 1169,
                "end_char": 1177,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abdulla Yameen",
                "start_char": 1225,
                "end_char": 1239,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "11 years",
                "start_char": 1296,
                "end_char": 1304,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "India",
                "start_char": 1378,
                "end_char": 1383,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maldives",
                "start_char": 1437,
                "end_char": 1445,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 1456,
                "end_char": 1461,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Muizzu",
                "start_char": 1520,
                "end_char": 1526,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 1538,
                "end_char": 1543,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Malé",
                "start_char": 1545,
                "end_char": 1549,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 1597,
                "end_char": 1604,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Defense of the Maldives",
                "start_char": 1657,
                "end_char": 1696,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Commento antisemita',chieste dimissioni del capo Polizia Londra",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:21:48 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/21/commento-antisemitachieste-dimissioni-del-capo-polizia-londra_d17deb4a-4d1a-433d-b102-91e9bd26935d.html",
        "subtitle": "Durante corteo. Media, Sunak sconvolto, sindaco chiede fiducia",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            C'è chi adesso chiede le dimissioni\ndel capo della Met Police a Londra, Sir Mark Rowley, sull'onda\ndelle polemiche su come le forze dell'ordine hanno gestito\nrecenti proteste filo-palestinesi dopo che un agente di polizia\nha descritto come \"palesemente ebreo\" un uomo che indossava una\nkippah. Lo scorso venerdì la polizia si è scusata per\nl'episodio, risalente allo scorso 13 aprile. Gideon Falter,\namministratore delegato della 'Campagna contro l'antisemitismo',\nindossava la kippah quando è stato fermato nei pressi di\nAldwych, nel centro di Londra, e minacciato di arresto. La\npolizia ha detto a Falter che la sua presenza stava causando una\n\"violazione dell'ordine pubblico\". Lui ha da parte sua affermato\nche la polizia lo ha trattato come un criminale perché è ebreo e\nha accusato il commissario Sir Mark Rowley di non aver limitato\nle manifestazioni e di aver consentito che \"innumerevoli crimini\ndi odio antisemita\" fossero commessi per le strade di Londra.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In queste ore la polemica si è estesa coinvolgendo il mondo\npolitico, fino al primo ministro Rishi Sunak che, stando ad\nindiscrezioni raccolte da Sky News, si sarebbe detto \"sconvolto\"\ndall'episodio. Mentre il sindaco di Londra, Sadiq Khan, invita\nad avere piena fiducia nel commissario Rowley. \"Tutti devono\nsentirsi sicuri andando in giro a Londra ovunque vogliano. Il\nmodo in cui l'episodio è stato gestito è preoccupante e la\nrisposta originaria dell'agente sbagliata e insensibile\", fa\nsapere un portavoce del sindaco, che tuttavia aggiunge: la\nMetropolitan Police \"ha un compito estremamente difficile,\nsoprattutto quando si tratta di decisioni operative prese\ndurante le manifestazioni. Ma deve avere la fiducia delle\ncomunità che serve\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 43,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.6839983,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "'Anti-Semitic Committee', requests for resignation of Chief Police London",
        "en_content": "There are those who now call for resignation\nof the head of the Met Police in London, Sir Mark Rowley, on the wave\nof the controversies about how law enforcement agencies managed\nrecent pro-Palestinian protests after a police officer\ndescribed as \"poorly Jewish\" a man wearing a\nkippah. Last Friday the police apologized for\nthe episode, dated 13 April. Gideon Falter,\nCEO of the 'Campagna against anti-Semitism',\nwore kippah when he was stopped near\nAldwych, in central London, is threatened with arrest. The\nPolice told Falter that his presence was causing a\n\"violation of public order.\" He said\nthat the police treated him as a criminal because he is Jewish and\naccused Sir Mark Rowley of not limited\nthe demonstrations and have allowed that \"numerable crimes\nof anti-Semitic hatred\" were committed on the streets of London.\n\n\nIn these hours the controversy has spread involving the world\npolitical, up to Prime Minister Rishi Sunak,\nindiscretions collected by Sky News, it would have been said \"unconvolved\"\nfrom the episode. While the mayor of London, Sadiq Khan, invites\nto have full confidence in Commissioner Rowley. \"Everyone must\nfeel confident walking around London wherever they want. The\nhow the episode was managed is worrying and the\noriginal response of the wrong and insensitive agent,\" he says\nknow a mayor's spokesman, who nevertheless adds:\nMetropolitan Police \"has an extremely difficult task,\nespecially when it comes to operational decisions taken\nduring the events. But he must have the confidence of\ncommunity that serves.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In court. Media, Sunak upset, mayor asks confidence",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Anti-Semitic Committee'",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Met Police",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mark Rowley",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "pro-Palestinian",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Last Friday",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "13 April",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gideon Falter",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aldwych",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Falter",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 654,
                "end_char": 660,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mark Rowley",
                "start_char": 677,
                "end_char": 688,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Semitic",
                "start_char": 766,
                "end_char": 778,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 820,
                "end_char": 826,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "these hours",
                "start_char": 833,
                "end_char": 844,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rishi Sunak",
                "start_char": 924,
                "end_char": 935,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sky News",
                "start_char": 964,
                "end_char": 972,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 1049,
                "end_char": 1055,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sadiq Khan",
                "start_char": 1057,
                "end_char": 1067,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rowley",
                "start_char": 1117,
                "end_char": 1123,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 1170,
                "end_char": 1176,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Orban, a un passo dall'invio delle truppe Occidente in Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:14:31 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/21/orban-a-un-passo-dallinvio-delle-truppe-occidente-in-ucraina_f57ac377-91c6-4434-8497-0fe90f5295fa.html",
        "subtitle": "'Bruxelles gioca col fuoco. Ma noi ne resteremo fuori'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Siamo a un passo dall'invio di\ntruppe da parte dell'Occidente in Ucraina\". E' la previsione del\npremier ungherese Vikton Orban pubblicata sul suo account\nFacebook. \"Si tratta di un vortice di guerra che può trascinare\nl'Europa nel baratro. Bruxelles gioca col fuoco - prosegue il\nleader magiaro -. In Europa l'atmosfera è quella della guerra e\nla politica è dominata dalla logica della guerra. Vedo la\npreparazione alla guerra da parte di tutti\". Orban precisa però\nche il suo Paese \"deve restarne fuori. Questa non è la nostra\nguerra. Non la vogliamo e non vogliamo che l'Ungheria torni ad\nessere il giocattolo delle grandi potenze\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 45,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.7151546,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Orban, one step from the sending of Western troops to Ukraine",
        "en_content": "\"We are one step away from sending\ntroops from the West in Ukraine.\" It's prediction of\nHungarian premier Vikton Orban published on his account\nFacebook. \"This is a vortex of war that can drag\nEurope in the barter. Brussels plays with fire - continues\nMage leader -. In Europe the atmosphere is that of war and\npolitics is dominated by the logic of war. I see the\npreparation for war by all.\" Orban points out\nthat his country \"must stay out of it. This is not ours\nWar. We do not want it and we do not want Hungary to return to\nbe the toy of the great powers.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Brussels plays with fire. But we'll stay out of it.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Orban",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungarian",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vikton Orban",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungary",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Bolsonaro chiede applauso per Musk durante manifestazione a Rio",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:30:53 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/04/21/bolsonaro-chiede-applauso-per-musk-durante-manifestazione-a-rio_1528bd5e-a40b-4c5f-b9a3-ea4b44e3c678.html",
        "subtitle": "'Ha avuto il coraggio di mostrare quello che succede in Brasile'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Intervenendo alla\nmanifestazione in difesa della libertà di espressione da lui\nconvocata a Rio de Janeiro, l'ex presidente brasiliano Jair\nBolsonaro ha chiesto ai partecipanti di rivolgere un applauso a\nElon Musk per \"aver avuto il coraggio di mostrare dove sta\nandando la democrazia in Brasile e quanta libertà è già stata\npersa\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il magnate sudafricano recentemente ha aperto uno scontro con\nil giudice della Corte suprema di Brasilia, Alexandre de Moraes,\naccusandolo di voler censurare X, il social di cui è\nproprietario. Il togato a sua volta ha inserito Musk\nnell'inchiesta sulle 'milizie digitali', dal nome dei profili\nvicini a Bolsonaro sospettati di usare il web per proliferare\nnotizie false. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 41,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.7476864,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Bolsonaro asks applause for Musk during event in Rio",
        "en_content": "Intervention at\ndemonstration in defense of freedom of expression from him\nconvened in Rio de Janeiro, former Brazilian president Jair\nBolsonaro asked the participants to apply an applause to\nElon Musk for \"having had the courage to show where he is\ngoing democracy in Brazil and how much freedom has already been\nLost.\"\n\n\nThe South African tycoon recently opened a clash with\nJudge of the Supreme Court of Brasilia, Alexandre de Moraes,\naccusing him of wanting to censor X, the social of\nowner. The togate in turn inserted Musk\nin the survey of 'digital military', by the name of the profiles\nnear Bolsonaro suspected of using the web to proliferate\nfalse news.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'He had the courage to show what happens in Brazil'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Musk",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rio de Janeiro",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jair\nBolsonaro",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elon Musk",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South African",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court of Brasilia",
                "start_char": 386,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 436,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Musk",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 599,
                "end_char": 608,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Netanyahu, aumenteremo a breve la pressione su Hamas",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:55:34 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/21/netanyahu-aumenteremo-a-breve-la-pressione-su-hamas_b543cd3c-9e5f-4309-a827-9727f01b8978.html",
        "subtitle": "'Unico modo per liberare ostaggi,hanno fatto fallire trattative'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Nei prossimi giorni aumenteremo\nla pressione militare e politica su Hamas perché questo è\nl'unico modo per liberare i nostri ostaggi e ottenere la\nvittoria\". Lo ha detto il premier Benyamin Netanyahu in un\nmessaggio alla vigilia della Pasqua ebraica denunciando che\n\"purtroppo, fino ad ora, tutte le proposte per il rilascio dei\nnostri rapiti sono state completamente respinte da Hamas\". A\nquesto proposito ha ricordato \"che Blinken ha detto che l'unico\nostacolo ad un accordo per la liberazione dei sequestrati è\nHamas\". \"In questa notte del Seder pasquale i nostri rapiti\nprigionieri di Hamas sono davanti ai nostri occhi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 47,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.7715907,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Netanyahu, we will soon increase pressure on Hamas",
        "en_content": "\"In the next few days we will increase\nmilitary and political pressure on Hamas because this is\nthe only way to free our hostages and get the\nvictory.\" Premier Benyamin Netanyahu said in one\nmessage on the eve of Jewish Passover denouncing that\n\"unfortunately, until now, all proposals for the release of\nOur abductors were completely rejected by Hamas.\" A\nthis purpose remembered \"that Blinken said that the only\nobstacle to an agreement for the release of the seized is\nHamas. \"On this night of the Easter Seder our kidnapped\nHamas prisoners are in front of our eyes.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'A way to free hostages, they have failed negotiations'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the next few days",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Benyamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 394,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "this night",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 493,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Easter Seder",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 533,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tensioni Algeria-Marocco per magliette a partita di calcio",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:26:06 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/04/21/tensioni-algeria-marocco-per-magliette-a-partita-di-calcio_f7fcedb5-3a75-46db-8f3e-c30105b3a409.html",
        "subtitle": "Squadra marocchina mostra Sahara annesso, 'contro ogni regola'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            In Algeria, dopo l'arrivo in\naeroporto della squadra marocchina del Nahdet Berkane che\nstasera dovrebbe giocare con l'Usm Alger la semifinale della\nCoppa della confederazione africana di calcio (Caf), è scoppiata\nuna feroce polemica a causa delle maglie del club ospite che\nmostravano una mappa del Regno alawita che includeva il conteso\nSahara occidentale. Le autorità doganali le hanno giudicate\nirregolari e ancora non è chiaro se la partita si giocherà o\nmeno. Il ritorno è in programma per il 28 aprile in Marocco.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In un comunicato diramato nella tarda serata di ieri, la Lega\ncalcio algerina ha espresso \"solidarietà e totale sostegno\nall'Usm Alger\" in seguito a quelle che ha definito \"pratiche e\nmetodi antisportivi utilizzati dall'avversario del club prima\ndella semifinale\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il comunicato sottolinea che la Lega \"si dichiara pronta a\nsostenere il club in qualsiasi decisione presa per salvaguardare\ngli interessi della squadra e dell'Algeria, e contro qualsiasi\ntentativo di contravvenire alle regole del Caf e perfino\ndell'Onu, oltre che all' etica sportiva\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La nota conclude sottolineando che \"la Lega afferma il suo\ntotale rifiuto di qualsiasi forma di compromissione della\nsovranità nazionale, qualsiasi sia la sua natura o la sua\nfonte\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La maggior parte dei club calcistici algerini ha espresso\nsostegno alla squadra dell'Usm Alger denunciando \"le pratiche a\ncui il Nahdet Berkane ha tentato di ricorrere all'arrivo\nall'aeroporto internazionale di Algeri, utilizzando slogan\npolitici sulla maglia della squadra per una competizione\ncontinentale ufficiale, in contrasto con i regolamenti della\nConfederazione del Calcio africano e della Fifa\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Sui social algerini, Fouzi Lekjaa, presidente della\nFedercalcio marocchina, presidente del club Nahdet Berkane e\nuomo potente nei corridoi della Caf, è stato accusato di essere\nil mandante della vicenda.  Utenti marocchini commentano che le\nmagliette sono già state indossate in altre competizioni e\ncontestano che vi sia alcun divieto. Gli utenti algerini hanno\ndiffuso immagini delle magliette di Nahdet Berkane in varie\ncompetizioni locali e continentali senza alcuna mappa del\nMarocco, chiedendosi \"perché questa volta sia stata inserita la\nmappa con il territorio conteso, anche se è considerata un logo\npolitico\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il Sahara Occidentale è un'ex colonia spagnola, in parte\nannessa da Rabat nel 1975 dopo la partenza delle forze di\nMadrid, mentre il Fronte Polisario controlla il resto del\nterritorio e chiede l'applicazione del \"diritto\nall'autodeterminazione\", mentre l'Algeria ospita i rifugiati\nsaharawi nei campi di Tindouf, nell'estremo sud-ovest del Paese.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'Onu considera la questione un \"caso di decolonizzazione ancora\naperto\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 42,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.9002118,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Algeria-Morocco tensions for football shirts",
        "en_content": "In Algeria, after arrival in\nNahdet Berkane Moroccan team airport\ntonight should play with the Usm Alger the semifinal of the\nAfrican Football Confederation Cup (Caf), burst\na fierce controversy due to the shirts of the host club\nshowed a map of the Alawite Kingdom which included the dispute\nWestern Sahara. The customs authorities have judged them\nirregular and yet it is not clear whether the game will be played or\nless. The return is scheduled for 28 April in Morocco.\n\n\nIn a statement issued in the late evening of yesterday, the League\nAlgerian football expressed \"solidarity and total support\nto the Usm Alger\" following those which defined \"practices and\nanti-sports methods used by the opponent of the club before\nof the semi-final.\"\n\n\nThe communiqué underlines that the League \"reports ready to\nsupport the club in any decision taken to safeguard\nthe interests of the team and Algeria, and against any\nattempt to contravene the rules of the Caf and even\nof the UN, as well as sports ethics.\"\n\n\nThe note concludes by pointing out that \"the League affirms its\ntotal rejection of any form of compromise\nnational sovereignty, whatever its nature or its\nsource.\"\n\n\nMost Algerian football clubs have expressed\nsupport for the Usm Alger team by denouncing \"the practices to\nwhich Nahdet Berkane tried to resort on arrival\nat Algiers International Airport, using slogans\npoliticians on the team's jersey for a competition\nofficial continental, in contrast with the regulations of the\nConfederation of African and Fifa Football\".\n\n\nOn social Algerians, Fouzi Lekjaa, president of the\nMoroccan Football Club President Nahdet Berkane and\npowerful man in the corridors of the Caf, was accused of being\nthe president of the story. Moroccan users comment that\nT-shirts have already been worn in other competitions and\nThey argue that there is no ban. Algerian users have\ndiffuse images of Nahdet Berkane T-shirts in various\nlocal and continental competitions without any map\nMorocco, asking \"why this time has been inserted\nmap with disputed territory, although it is considered a logo\npolitical\".\n\n\nWestern Sahara is a former Spanish colony, partly\nannexed by Rabat in 1975 after the departure of forces\nMadrid, while the Polisario Front controls the rest of the\nterritory and asks the application of the \"right\nto self-determination\", while Algeria hosts refugees\nsaharawi in the fields of Tindouf, in the extreme south-west of the country.\n\n\nThe UN considers the issue a \"decolonization case still\nopen.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Moroccan team shows Sahara annexed, 'against every rule'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Morocco",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moroccan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sahara",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moroccan",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "African Football Confederation Cup",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Alawite Kingdom",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western Sahara",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "28 April",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Morocco",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the late evening",
                "start_char": 501,
                "end_char": 517,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 530,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algerian",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 551,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 888,
                "end_char": 895,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caf",
                "start_char": 952,
                "end_char": 955,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 972,
                "end_char": 974,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Algerian",
                "start_char": 1176,
                "end_char": 1184,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nahdet Berkane",
                "start_char": 1284,
                "end_char": 1298,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algiers International Airport",
                "start_char": 1329,
                "end_char": 1358,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Confederation of African",
                "start_char": 1487,
                "end_char": 1511,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fifa Football",
                "start_char": 1516,
                "end_char": 1529,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algerians",
                "start_char": 1544,
                "end_char": 1553,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fouzi Lekjaa",
                "start_char": 1555,
                "end_char": 1567,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moroccan Football Club",
                "start_char": 1586,
                "end_char": 1608,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nahdet Berkane",
                "start_char": 1619,
                "end_char": 1633,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caf",
                "start_char": 1675,
                "end_char": 1678,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moroccan",
                "start_char": 1729,
                "end_char": 1737,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algerian",
                "start_char": 1848,
                "end_char": 1856,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nahdet Berkane",
                "start_char": 1886,
                "end_char": 1900,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Morocco",
                "start_char": 1972,
                "end_char": 1979,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western Sahara",
                "start_char": 2097,
                "end_char": 2111,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 2124,
                "end_char": 2131,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rabat",
                "start_char": 2158,
                "end_char": 2163,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1975",
                "start_char": 2167,
                "end_char": 2171,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 2202,
                "end_char": 2208,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Polisario Front",
                "start_char": 2216,
                "end_char": 2235,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 2340,
                "end_char": 2347,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tindouf",
                "start_char": 2389,
                "end_char": 2396,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 2446,
                "end_char": 2448,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Katz a ministri esteri Ue,sanzioni a progetto missili Iran",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:04:19 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/21/katz-a-ministri-esteri-uesanzioni-a-progetto-missili-iran_83c4075f-888c-460e-87fd-c00180ffbb5c.html",
        "subtitle": "'Pericolo per il mondo, fermare Teheran prima che sia tardi'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro degli esteri\nisraeliano Israel Katz ha chiesto ai suoi omologhi della Ue \"di\nimporre sanzioni al progetto missilistico iraniano\". Lo ha\nannunciato lo stesso Katz aggiungendo che \"il progetto mette in\npericolo il mondo. Bisogna fermare l'Iran prima che sia troppo\ntardi\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  Su X Katz ha ricordato che i \"missili iraniani hanno una\ngittata fino a 3mila chilometri\". Al tempo stesso ha dato\nistruzioni alle ambasciate israeliane nella Ue \"di aumentare la\ncampagna contro l'Iran in vista dell'incontro Fac dei ministri\ndegli esteri europei di domani per discutere le sanzioni\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 39,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.9141338,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Katz to foreign ministers EU, missile-designed sanctions Iran",
        "en_content": "The Foreign Minister\nIsrael Israel Israel Katz asked his homologues of the EU \"\nimpose sanctions on the Iranian missile project.\" He did.\nannounced the same Katz adding that \"the project puts in\ndanger the world. We must stop Iran before it is too much\nlate.\"\n\n\nOn X Katz recalled that the \"Iranian missiles have a\nup to 3 thousand kilometers.\" At the same time\ninstructions to Israeli embassies in the EU \"to increase the\ncampaign against Iran in view of the Fac meeting of Ministers\nto discuss the sanctions.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Danger for the world, stop Tehran before it's late'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel Katz",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Katz",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "up to",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 thousand kilometers",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fac",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 463,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Bolsonaro, 'io presidente grazie alla libertà di espressione'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:46:34 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/04/21/bolsonaro-io-presidente-grazie-alla-liberta-di-espressione_0ba0903f-f3f8-4ba1-bf49-75df8d4958cb.html",
        "subtitle": "'Per questo ora vogliono censurare i social'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            In un discorso davanti a\nmigliaia di persone a Rio de Janeiro, l'ex presidente del\nBrasile Jair Bolsonaro ha dichiarato che è stato \"grazie alla\nlibertà di espressione\" che è diventato presidente della\nRepubblica. E che ora sta affrontando la reazione di \"un\nsistema\" che non ha gradito i suoi quattro anni di governo e per\nquesto ha iniziato a \"lavorare contro questa libertà\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Grazie a questo è arrivato alla presidenza della Repubblica\nqualcuno fuori dal sistema\", ha detto mostrando un cellulare\nnella sua mano. \"Senza questo, con la censura, con\ndiscriminazione, hanno riportato sulla scena del crimine il più\ngrande ladro della storia del Brasile\", ha aggiunto riferendosi\nal suo successore, l'attuale presidente Luiz Inacio Lula da\nSilva.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In tono duro, l'ex leader di destra ha poi affermato che i\nsuoi rivali \"vogliono la dittatura, con il controllo dei social\ne la censura di coloro che non sono d'accordo\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 40,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.939484,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Bolsonaro, 'I president thanks to freedom of expression'",
        "en_content": "In a speech in front of\nthousands of people in Rio de Janeiro, the former president of the\nBrazil Jair Bolsonaro said it was \"thanks to the\nfreedom of expression\" which became president of\nRepublic. And now he's facing the reaction of \"a\nsystem\" which did not like its four years of government and\nThis began to \"work against this freedom\".\n\n\n\"Thanks to this he arrived at the presidency of the Republic\nsomeone out of the system\", he said showing a cell phone\nin his hand. \"Without this, with censorship, with\ndiscrimination, reported on the crime scene the most\ngreat thief of the history of Brazil\", he added referring\nto its successor, the current President Luiz Inacio Lula da\nSilva.\n\n\nIn hard tone, the former right-wing leader later stated that the\nhis rivals \"want dictatorship, with the control of social\nand censorship of those who disagree.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'For this time they want to censor social media'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio de Janeiro",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jair Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "four years",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Republic",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 594,
                "end_char": 600,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Inacio",
                "start_char": 662,
                "end_char": 673,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula da\nSilva",
                "start_char": 674,
                "end_char": 687,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ft, Blinken minaccerà sanzioni a Cina per aiuti a Russia",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:17:53 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/21/ft-blinken-minaccera-sanzioni-a-cina-per-aiuti-a-russia_20ebc524-9a44-4190-951f-5fe44d57bf6c.html",
        "subtitle": "Nel mirino istituti finanziari per tecnologia legata a armamenti",
        "content": " Il segretario di stato Antony Blinken ammonirà Pechino, nella sua visita in Cina la prossima settimana, che gli Usa prenderanno misure punitive se non smette di inviare tecnologia legata agli armamenti alla Russia. Lo scrive il Financial Times, evocando sanzioni contro istituti finanziari cinesi e altre entità. Secondo il Ft, Blinken dirà a Pechino che gli Stati Uniti e i loro alleati stanno diventando sempre più impazienti di fronte al rifiuto di Pechino di smettere di fornire a Mosca qualsiasi cosa, dai chip ai motori dei missili da crociera, per aiutarla a ricostruire la sua base industriale. Il segretario di stato americano, secondo il quotidiano finanziario, non ha intenzione di rivelare quali misure prenderanno gli Usa, ma diverse persone a conoscenza del dossier hanno affermato che sta prendendo in considerazione sanzioni contro istituti finanziari cinesi e altre entità. Una fonte ha affermato che il suo messaggio sarà l'avvertimento più chiaro che gli Usa abbiano mai consegnato di persona ai dirigenti cinesi.    \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 44,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790943.981228,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.23",
        "en_title": "Ft, Blinken will threaten sanctions to China to help Russia",
        "en_content": "Secretary of State Antony Blinken will admonish Beijing, in his visit to China next week, that the US will take punitive measures if he does not stop sending technology linked to arms to Russia. The Financial Times writes it, evoking sanctions against Chinese financial institutions and other entities. According to the Ft, Blinken will tell Beijing that the United States and their allies are becoming increasingly impatient in the face of Beijing's refusal to stop providing Moscow anything from chips to cruise missile engines to help her rebuild its industrial base. The American secretary of state, according to the financial newspaper, does not intend to reveal what measures will take the U.S., but several people aware of the dossier said that it is considering sanctions against Chinese financial institutions and other entities. A source said that his message will be the clearest warning that the US has ever delivered in person to Chinese leaders.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In the view of financial institutions for arms-related technology",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antony Blinken",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next week",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Financial Times",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ft, Blinken",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 477,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 575,
                "end_char": 583,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "state",
                "start_char": 597,
                "end_char": 602,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 696,
                "end_char": 700,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 788,
                "end_char": 795,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 908,
                "end_char": 910,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 943,
                "end_char": 950,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Pnv si conferma prima forza in Paese Basco alla pari con Bildu",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:56:14 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/21/pnv-si-conferma-prima-forza-in-paese-basco-alla-pari-con-bildu_d4c18765-7a30-43e6-87dc-c7f2347cebbf.html",
        "subtitle": "Secondo il sondaggio della tv basca EiTB a chiusura delle urne",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Alla chiusura delle urne alle 20:00\nnel Paese Basco, per eleggere i 75 rappresentanti nel\nParlamento, il Partito nazionalista basco (Pnv) mantiene la\nprima posizione per numero di voti e potrà continuare a\ngovernare la regione autonoma, in un pareggio in numero di seggi\ncon EH Bildu, il partito della sinistra indipendentista radicale\nbasca, che ha sfiorato lo storico sorpasso, secondo il sondaggio\ndella Tv pubblica basca  EiTB. I socialisti del Pse si\nconfermano come terza forza,  mantenendo le chiavi per il\ngoverno della regione insiema al Pnv: entrambi determinati a non\nformare alleanze con Bildu per il rifiuto del suo candidato\ngovernatore Pello Otxandiano di definire l'Eta \"terrorista\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 38,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790944.2763972,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:24",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.24",
        "en_title": "Pnv is confirmed first strength in Country Basco au pair with Bildu",
        "en_content": "At the closing of the urns at 20:00\nin the Basque Country, to elect the 75 representatives in\nParliament, the Basque Nationalist Party (Pnv) maintains the\nfirst position by number of votes and may continue to\nrule the autonomous region, in a tie in number of seats\nwith EH Bildu, the party of the radical independent leftist\nBasque, which has touched the historical overtaking, according to the survey\nof the Basque TV EiTB. The Socialists of the Pse\nconfirm as third strength, keeping the keys for\nGovernment of the region joins the Pnv: both determined not to\nform alliances with Bildu for the refusal of his candidate\nGovernor Pello Otxandiano to define the \"terrorist\" Eta.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "According to the poll of the Basque TV EiTB at closing of the urns",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Country Basco",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bildu",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Basque",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "20:00",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Basque Country",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "75",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Basque Nationalist Party",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EH Bildu",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 278,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Basque",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Socialists",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 439,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pnv",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 537,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bildu",
                "start_char": 582,
                "end_char": 587,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pello Otxandiano",
                "start_char": 630,
                "end_char": 646,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Eta",
                "start_char": 673,
                "end_char": 676,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky replica a Mosca, con gli aiuti Usa non sarà Afghanistan",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:55:13 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/21/zelensky-replica-a-mosca-con-gli-aiuti-usa-non-sara-afghanistan_dfadf3bf-eb1a-4299-bd8b-140438a18c04.html",
        "subtitle": "'Gli Stati Uniti resteranno al fianco dell'Ucraina'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Replicando al sarcasmo di Mosca, il\npresidente ucraino, Volodymyr Zelensky, ha detto nel suo\ndiscorso serale che grazie agli aiuti appena votati dagli Stati\nUniti l'Ucraina non diventerà \"un secondo Afghanistan\". \n   \"Questi aiuti rafforzeranno l'Ucraina e manderanno al\nCremlino un potente segnale che non sarà un secondo Afghanistan,\ncome aveva detto la portavoce del ministero degli Esteri russo,\nMaria Zacharova, che aveva evocato al \"clamoroso e umiliante\nfiasco\" degli americani in Vietnam e a Kabul. \"Gli Stati Uniti\nresteranno a fianco dell'Ucraina, proteggeranno gli ucraini e la\ndemocrazia nel mondo\", ha aggiunto Zelensky. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 36,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713790944.3074374,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-22 15:02:24",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-22T15.02.24",
        "en_title": "Zelensky replica in Moscow, with US aid will not be Afghanistan",
        "en_content": "Replicating to the sarcasm of Moscow, the\nUkrainian president, Volodymyr Zelensky, said in his\nevening speech that thanks to the aid just voted by the States\nU.S. Ukraine will not become \"a second Afghanistan\".\n\"These aids will strengthen Ukraine and send to\nKremlin a powerful signal that will not be a second Afghanistan,\nas the spokesman of the Russian Foreign Ministry said,\nMaria Zacharova, who had summoned the \"clamorous and humiliating\nAmericans in Vietnam and Kabul. \"The United States\nwill remain side by side of Ukraine, protect the Ukrainians and protect it\ndemocracy in the world,\" added Zelensky.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'The United States will remain alongside Ukraine'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afghanistan",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S. Ukraine",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Afghanistan",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 246,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Afghanistan",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Foreign Ministry",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Maria Zacharova",
                "start_char": 379,
                "end_char": 394,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Americans",
                "start_char": 444,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vietnam",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kabul",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
