[
    {
        "title": "Lamborghini ha presentato in Messico il Suv ibrido Urus Se",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:30:45 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/14/lamborghini-ha-presentato-in-messico-il-suv-ibrido-urus-se_b721420f-5405-4d83-9a49-d5a31bb321d0.html",
        "subtitle": "Evento di lancio con l'Ambasciatore Modiano e il Ceo Winkelmann",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            In un evento in due fasi\na Città del Messico — una conferenza stampa seguita da un lancio\ndavanti a un pubblico gremito nel quartiere direzionale di Santa\nFe — , Lamborghini ha presentato il modello Urus Se, il primo\nSuv ibrido del marchio, che dall'inizio della sua presenza\ncommerciale nel Paese latinoamericano, quindici anni fa, ha\nvenduto 536 vetture in terra azteca. Il Ceo, Stephan Winkelmann,\nha sottolineato l'importanza del mercato messicano.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Siamo presenti sul mercato da 15 anni e la nostra storia di\nsuccesso è in continua crescita\", ha affermato il dirigente.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"L'anno scorso — ha aggiunto — è stato il migliore per\nLamborghini in Messico, con 82 auto vendute\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tAll'evento, presieduto insieme a Winkelmann da Andrea Baldi, Ceo\ndi Automobili Lamborghini America, ha partecipato l'ambasciatore\nitaliano in Messico, Alessandro Modiano. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957218.237097,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.18",
        "en_title": "Lamborghini presented in Mexico the Hybrid Suv Urus Se",
        "en_content": "In a two-phase event\nin Mexico City — a press conference followed by a launch\nin front of a crowded audience in the directional district of Santa\nFe —, Lamborghini presented the model Urus Se, the first\nHybrid brand suv, than from the beginning of its presence\ncommercial in the Latin American country, fifteen years ago, has\nsold 536 cars on the Aztec land. The Ceo, Stephan Winkelmann,\nstressed the importance of the Mexican market.\n\n\n\"We have been on the market for 15 years and our history\nsuccess is constantly growing,\" said the manager.\n\n\n\"Last year — he added — was the best for\nLamborghini in Mexico, with 82 cars sold.\"\n\n\nTo the event, presided together with Winkelmann by Andrea Baldi, Ceo\nby Automobili Lamborghini America, participated the ambassador\nItalian in Mexico, Alessandro Modiano.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Launch event with the Modian Ambassador and the Winkelmann",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lamborghini",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Modian",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Winkelmann",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico City",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santa\nFe",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lamborghini",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Urus Se",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Latin American",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifteen years ago",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "536",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aztec",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stephan Winkelmann",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "15 years",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Last year",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lamborghini",
                "start_char": 587,
                "end_char": 598,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 602,
                "end_char": 608,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "82",
                "start_char": 615,
                "end_char": 617,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Winkelmann",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 679,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrea Baldi",
                "start_char": 683,
                "end_char": 695,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Automobili Lamborghini America",
                "start_char": 704,
                "end_char": 734,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 764,
                "end_char": 771,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 775,
                "end_char": 781,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alessandro Modiano",
                "start_char": 783,
                "end_char": 801,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Putin, per una tregua necessarie ancora consultazioni con Usa",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:57:06 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/putin-per-una-tregua-necessarie-ancora-consultazioni-con-usa_e18679b3-c8b9-4f2a-a9ab-4036a8892823.html",
        "subtitle": "Anche con telefonata con Trump. Affrontare cause del conflitto",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Alcune questioni devono ancora\nessere affrontate per una tregua in Ucraina e la Russia ha\nancora bisogno di \"consultazioni con gli Usa\", probabilmente con\nuna telefonata tra i presidenti Vladimir Putin e Donald Trump.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo ha detto lo stesso Putin. Una tregua in Ucraina \"dovrebbe\nessere tale da portare ad una pace a lungo termine e affrontare\nle cause di fondo del conflitto\", ha aggiunto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 66,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957218.4607449,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.18",
        "en_title": "Putin, for a necessary truce still consult with Usa",
        "en_content": "Some issues still need to be\nbe faced for a truce in Ukraine and Russia has\nstill need \"consultations with the US\", probably with\na phone call between presidents Vladimir Putin and Donald Trump.\n\n\nPutin himself said that. A truce in Ukraine \"would\nbe such as to lead to long-term peace and face\nthe underlying causes of the conflict,\" he added.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Even with phone call with Trump. Addressing causes of conflict",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa, intesa con Caracas per ripresa espulsioni di venezuelani",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:22:58 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/usa-intesa-con-caracas-per-ripresa-espulsioni-di-venezuelani_7e7b769b-3086-4b74-92d0-9321624fa2e2.html",
        "subtitle": "Musk, 'negli Stati Uniti non ci sono più città santuario'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Il Venezuela ha accettato di\nriprendere i voli per accogliere i suoi cittadini che hanno\nviolato le leggi sull'immigrazione degli Stati Uniti entrando\nillegalmente\". Lo riferisce Richard Grenell, inviato speciale di\nTrump per la risoluzione dei conflitti, sul suo profilo X. Elon\nMusk ha poi risposto a Grenell, sempre su X, che \"negli Stati\nUniti non ci saranno più città santuario. Basta scuse, il\nVenezuela paga. Gli Stati Uniti vincono\". Il magnate sudafricano\nha poi aggiunto che gli Stati Uniti hanno espulso più di 370\n\"criminali illegali in Venezuela, compresi membri della violenta\nbanda del Tren de Aragua\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La scorsa settimana Maduro aveva annunciato la sospensione\ndei voli di rimpatrio, in risposta alla decisione di Trump di\nrevocare una licenza concessa alla compagnia petrolifera Chevron\nper l'estrazione di petrolio in collaborazione con la compagnia\nstatale Petróleos de Venezuela (Pdvsa).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In passato, il governo di Maduro aveva ricevuto quattro voli\ncon venezuelani espulsi, tra cui famiglie, donne e bambini, e\nuno proveniente dalla base di Guantanamo, a Cuba, con presunti\nmembri del Tren de Aragua. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 65,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957218.4712563,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.18",
        "en_title": "Use, intended with Caracas for resumption of Venezuelans",
        "en_content": "\" Venezuela has accepted\nresume flights to welcome its citizens who have\nviolated US immigration laws by entering\nillegally.\" Richard Grenell, special envoy of\nTrump for the resolution of conflicts, on his profile X. Elon\nMusk then responded to Grenell, always on X, that \"in states\nThere will be no more sanctuary cities. No more excuses, the\nVenezuela pays. The United States wins.\" South African tycoon\nadded that the United States expelled more than 370\n\"legal criminals in Venezuela, including members of the violent\nband of the Tren de Aragua.\"\n\n\nLast week Maduro announced the suspension\nof return flights, in response to Trump's decision of\nrevoke a license granted to the Chevron oil company\nfor oil extraction in collaboration with the company\nPetróleos de Venezuela (Pdvsa).\n\n\nIn the past, Maduro's government had received four flights\nwith ejected Venezuelans, including families, women and children, and\none from the base of Guantanamo, in Cuba, with presumed\nmembers of the Tren de Aragua.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Musk, 'in the United States there are no more sanctuary cities'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelans",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Richard Grenell",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "X. Elon\nMusk",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Grenell",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South African",
                "start_char": 385,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 417,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 370",
                "start_char": 444,
                "end_char": 457,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 478,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Tren de Aragua",
                "start_char": 530,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Last week",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maduro",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 569,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 629,
                "end_char": 634,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chevron",
                "start_char": 681,
                "end_char": 688,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Petróleos de Venezuela (Pdvsa",
                "start_char": 754,
                "end_char": 783,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Maduro",
                "start_char": 801,
                "end_char": 807,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 834,
                "end_char": 838,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelans",
                "start_char": 860,
                "end_char": 871,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guantanamo",
                "start_char": 938,
                "end_char": 948,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cuba",
                "start_char": 953,
                "end_char": 957,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Tren de Aragua",
                "start_char": 984,
                "end_char": 1002,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump, da Putin una dichiarazione molto promettente",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:58:20 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/13/trump-da-putin-una-dichiarazione-molto-promettente_02253c39-0baf-49c1-9f07-4ad3016586d4.html",
        "subtitle": "'Mi piacerebbe incontrarlo e parlare'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Vladimir Putin ha rilasciato una\n\"dichiarazione molto promettente\" sulla tregua. Lo ha detto\nDonald Trump, secondo quanto riporta l'agenzia Bloomberg. \"Mi\npiacerebbe incontrare, parlare con Putin\", ha aggiunto Trump.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Discuteremo di cosa sta succedendo tra Ucraina e Russia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tVogliamo che la guerra finisca\", ha spiegato dallo Studio Ovale\ncon il segretario generale della Nato Mark Rutte. Il conflitto\n\"ha anche un costo enorme per gli Stati Uniti e altri paesi\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tCon Rutte, ha aggiunto, \"parleremo anche di commercio\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957218.496095,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.18",
        "en_title": "Trump, from Putin a very promising statement",
        "en_content": "Vladimir Putin issued a\n\"very promising statement\" on the truce. He said that.\nDonald Trump, according to the Bloomberg agency. ♪\nwould like to meet, talk to Putin,\" Trump added.\n\n\n\"We will discuss what is happening between Ukraine and Russia.\n\n\nWe want the war to end,\" explained Studio Ovale\nwith NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte. The conflict\n\"It also has a huge cost for the United States and other countries.\"\n\n\nWith Rutte, he added, \"we will also talk about commerce.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'I would like to meet him and talk'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bloomberg",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 224,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 299,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mark Rutte",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rutte",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Parlamento Ue, 'ricevuta notifica indagine su caso Huawei'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:11:12 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/parlamento-ue-ricevuta-notifica-indagine-su-caso-huawei_ae30e366-d8b8-4bd1-99d0-2650952b301b.html",
        "subtitle": "'Onoreremo la richiesta di cooperazione delle autorità belghe'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Abbiamo ricevuto una richiesta\ndi cooperazione dalle autorità belghe per assistere l'indagine\"\nsul caso dei lobbisti legati a Huawei fermati dalla polizia\nbelga perché sospettati di aver corrotto ex e attuali\neurodeputati, \"che il Parlamento onorerà rapidamente e\npienamente\". Lo fa sapere il servizio stampa dell'Eurocamera,\nrimandando alle stesse autorità federali del Belgio per\nqualsiasi ulteriore informazione. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 75,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.535718,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Parliament EU, 'receipt investigation notice on Huawei'",
        "en_content": "\"We received a request\nof cooperation by the Belgian authorities to assist the investigation\"\non the case of lobbyists linked to Huawei stopped by the police\nBelgian because suspected of having corrupted ex and current\nMEPs, \"which Parliament will honour quickly and\nfully.\" The Eurocamera Press Service lets you know,\nsending the same federal authorities in Belgium for\nany further information.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'We shall honour the request for cooperation by the Belgian authorities'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Huawei",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Belgian",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Belgian",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Huawei",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgian",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Eurocamera Press Service",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgium",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump attacca sul commercio, 'il mondo intero ci deruba'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:11:18 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/13/trump-attacca-sul-commercio-il-mondo-intero-ci-deruba_04a8e403-aa4f-4877-8b0c-89977d03ec4d.html",
        "subtitle": "'Gli Usa non hanno liberi scambi, hanno scambi stupidi'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Gli Stati Uniti non hanno liberi\nscambi\" commerciali, \"hanno scambi stupidi. Il mondo intero ci\nderuba\". Lo afferma Donald Trump sul suo social Truth dopo aver\nminacciato dazi del 200% sui vini europei. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 76,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.600408,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Trump attacks on trade, 'the whole world steals us'",
        "en_content": "\"The United States has no freedom\ntrade, they have stupid exchanges. The whole world\nderuba.\" Donald Trump says on his social truth after having\nthreatened duties of 200% on European wines.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'The U.S. have no free trade, have stupid exchanges'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "200%",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Caracas, elezioni di maggio anche nella Guyana Esequiba",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:09:15 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/caracas-elezioni-di-maggio-anche-nella-guyana-esequiba_aa569814-f9e7-4c34-9260-8d1b951f4acc.html",
        "subtitle": "Ministro Interno conferma voto nel territorio del Paese vicino",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro dell'Interno del\nVenezuela, Diosdado Cabello, ha confermato l'intenzione di\nestendere le elezioni del 25 maggio alla Guyana Esequiba,\nannessa sulla carta dopo un referendum voluto\ndall'amministrazione di Nicolas Maduro. Nel suo programma\nsettimanale in Tv e sui social media \"Con el Mazo Dando\",\nCabello ha respinto la richiesta della Guyana, che si è rivolta\nanche alla Corte di Giustizia Internazionale, affinché il\nVenezuela non tenga elezioni nella regione che ricade sotto il\nsuo controllo, ma appunto, contesa da Caracas.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il 25 maggio ci sarà un governatore della nostra Guayana\nEsequiba, ci saranno deputati alla Assemblea nazionale e\nlegislatori del Consiglio legislativo\", ha affermato Cabello, in\nriferimento al territorio di 149.500 chilometri quadrati (la\nmetà dell'Italia), una zona economica operativa per varie\ncompagnie petrolifere. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 72,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.6122668,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Caracas, May elections also in Guyana Esequiba",
        "en_content": "Minister for the Interior\nVenezuela, Diosdado Cabello, confirmed the intention of\nextend the May 25 elections to Guyana Esequiba,\nattached to the card after a referendum\nby the administration of Nicolas Maduro. In his programme\nweekly in TV and social media \"Con el Mazo Dando\",\nCabello rejected Guyana's request, which turned\nalso to the International Court of Justice, so that the\nVenezuela does not hold elections in the region that falls under\nhis control, but precisely, disputed by Caracas.\n\n\n\"On May 25 there will be a governor of our Guayana\nEsequiba, there will be Members of the National Assembly and\nlegislators of the Legislative Council\", said Cabello, in\nreference to the territory of 149,500 square kilometers (the\nhalf of Italy), an economic zone operating for various\noil companies.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Minister Interior confirms vote in the territory of the neighbouring country",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "May",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guyana Esequiba",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Diosdado Cabello",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 25",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guyana Esequiba",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicolas Maduro",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "weekly",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cabello",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Guyana",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 488,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 25",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guayana\nEsequiba",
                "start_char": 542,
                "end_char": 558,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Assembly",
                "start_char": 585,
                "end_char": 606,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Legislative Council",
                "start_char": 626,
                "end_char": 649,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cabello",
                "start_char": 657,
                "end_char": 664,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "149,500 square kilometers",
                "start_char": 699,
                "end_char": 724,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "half",
                "start_char": 730,
                "end_char": 734,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 738,
                "end_char": 743,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Parigi, determinati a replicare ai dazi Usa",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:11:02 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/parigi-determinati-a-replicare-ai-dazi-usa_3a552e9b-ede0-41e9-8248-bafa16ed8a3a.html",
        "subtitle": "Dopo minaccia di Trump su tariffe a champagne e vini europei",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Francia resta ''determinata a\nreplicare'' ai dazi evocati dal presidente Usa, Donald Trump,\nsullo champagne e i vini europei. ''Non cederemo mai alle\nminacce e proteggeremo sempre le nostre filiere'', avverte il\nministro francese per il Commercio Estero, Laurent saint-Martin,\nin un messaggio pubblicato sul suo profilo X. Il ministro\ndeplora l'''escalation'' di Donald Trump in questa ''guerra\ncommerciale che ha scelto di dichiarare''. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 73,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.6205595,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Paris, determined to replicate US duties",
        "en_content": "France remains ''determined to\nI'll replicate the duties summoned by US President Donald Trump,\non champagne and European wines. \"We will never give in to\nThreats and we will always protect our supply chains, warn the\nFrench Minister for Foreign Trade, Laurent Saint-Martin,\nin a message published on its X profile. The Minister\ndeplores Donald Trump's escalation in this war\ncommercial you chose to declare.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "After Trump's threat on European champagne and wine rates",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Laurent Saint-Martin",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump's",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Von der Leyen, mobilitiamo 4,7 miliardi in Sudafrica",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:11:07 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/von-der-leyen-mobilitiamo-47-miliardi-in-sudafrica_c33595ea-ab70-4f6f-9f6f-ba81fc441003.html",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Oggi annunciamo un pacchetto di\ninvestimenti per mobilitare oltre 4,7 miliardi di euro in\nSudafrica\". Riguarda \"progetti che supportano una giusta\ntransizione energetica. Per la connettività, sia fisica che\ndigitale. E per i vaccini, prodotti in Africa, per l'Africa\". Lo\nannuncia la presidente della Commissione europea Ursula von der\nLeyen all'avvio del Summit Ue-Sudafrica a Cape Town. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 74,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.627042,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Von der Leyen, we mobilize 4.7 billion in South Africa",
        "en_content": "\"Today we announce a package of\ninvestments to mobilize more than 4.7 billion euros in\nSouth Africa.\" It concerns \"projects that support a just\nenergy transition. For connectivity, both physical and\ndigital. And for vaccines, produced in Africa, for Africa.\" I do.\nannounces the President of the European Commission Ursula von der\nLeyen at the start of the Ue-Sudafrica Summit in Cape Town.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Von der",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4.7 billion",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Africa",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 4.7 billion euros",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Africa",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Africa",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Africa",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cape Town",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, 'portiamo il caso Trentini al G7'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:36:26 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/tajani-portiamo-il-caso-trentini-al-g7_18142baa-2d50-484d-ae59-a24e10313339.html",
        "subtitle": "'Chiederemo liberazione immediata di tutti i detenuti politici'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Qui al G7 parleremo\nanche della questione Venezuela. Noi abbiamo alcuni italiani che\nsono detenuti ingiustamente, un giovane anche, Trentini. Da ieri\nsono di nuovo in contatto con la mamma. Chiederemo la\nliberazione immediata di tutti i detenuti politici, di tutti i\ndetenuti ingiustamente e senza motivazione nelle carceri del\nVenezuela\". Lo ha detto il ministro degli Esteri Antonio Tajani\nparlando con i giornalisti al G7 Esteri di Charlevoix. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 70,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.635298,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Tajani, we bring the Trentini case to the G7.",
        "en_content": "\"Here at the G7 we will talk\nalso the question Venezuela. We have some Italians\nThey are unjustly detained, a young man too, Trentini. From yesterday\nI'm back in touch with Mom. We'll ask.\nimmediate release of all political prisoners, of all\nunjustly and without motivation in prisons\nVenezuela.\" The Foreign Minister Antonio Tajani said this\ntalking to journalists at the G7 Esteri Charlevoix.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'We will call for immediate release of all political prisoners'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trentini",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trentini",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Da Usa nuova proposta a Israele e Hamas per cessate fuoco",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:55:03 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/13/da-usa-nuova-proposta-a-israele-e-hamas-per-cessate-fuoco_5b3d506c-f0a5-4413-ae2e-4ab616e9b4f5.html",
        "subtitle": "Axios, estensione fino al 20 aprile e aiuti umanitari a Gaza",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli Stati Uniti hanno presentato\na Israele e Hamas una nuova proposta per estendere il cessate il\nfuoco a Gaza. Lo riporta Axios citando alcune fonti, secondo le\nquali la nuova iniziativa include un cessate il fuoco a Gaza\nfino a dopo il Ramadam e la Pasqua ebraica, che finisce il 20\naprile, oltre alla ripresa degli aiuti umanitari a Gaza. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 69,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.66704,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "From Usa new proposal to Israel and Hamas for ceasefire",
        "en_content": "The United States presented\nto Israel and Hamas a new proposal to extend the ceasefire\nFire in Gaza. Axios reports it citing some sources, according to\nwhich the new initiative includes a ceasefire in Gaza\nuntil after Ramadam and Passover, which ends 20\nApril, in addition to the recovery of humanitarian aid in Gaza.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Axios, extension until 20 April and humanitarian aid in Gaza",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "20 April",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Axios",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ramadam",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "20\nApril",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Argentina, la giustizia ordina la scarcerazione dei manifestanti",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:23:26 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/argentina-la-giustizia-ordina-la-scarcerazione-dei-manifestanti_1dbc7245-2b1f-4b16-bfe7-a2c6c34737e6.html",
        "subtitle": "'In gioco il diritto alla protesta e la libertà di espressione'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La giustizia argentina ha\nordinato \"l'immediata liberazione\" di tutte le 114 persone\n(oltre 150 secondo fonti giornalistiche) arrestate in flagranza\ndi reato durante gli scontri tra manifestanti e polizia davanti\nal parlamento, nel contesto delle mobilitazioni dei pensionati\ncontro i tagli del governo di Javier Milei. Lo riporta Pagina\n12.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Secondo la giudice Karina Andrade \"essendo in gioco il\ndiritto costituzionale fondamentale di manifestare in modo\ndemocratico e quello della libertà di espressione\", fatto salvo\n\"il parere sull'applicazione del diritto sostanziale o sulle\nindagini che la procura può proseguire nell'accertamento\ndell'esistenza di condotte criminose\" resta preclusa\n\"l'applicazione della procedura di flagranza\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La posizione della magistratura stride con quella del\ngoverno. Su X la ministra della Sicurezza nazionale, Patricia\nBullrich, ha infatti dichiarato che \"gli oltre cento arrestati\nrischiano condanne fino a 20 anni di prigione\" grazie \"alla\nnuova legge antimafia\" approvata del governo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   I disordini sono iniziati già prima dell'inizio della\nmanifestazione organizzata dai pensionati a cui hanno aderito le\ntifoserie organizzate di diverse squadre e vari sindacati tra\ncui la Cgt. Secondo il bilancio ufficiale, 26 agenti e 20\nmanifestanti sono rimasti feriti, tra cui il fotografo Pablo\nGrillo, ricoverato in gravissime condizioni dopo essere stato\ncolpito alla testa da un lacrimogeno. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 71,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.6763222,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Argentina, justice orders the scarceness of the protesters",
        "en_content": "Argentine justice has\nordered \"immediate release\" of all 114 people\n(over 150 according to journalistic sources) arrested in scourgence\nof crime during the clashes between protesters and police in front\nto the parliament, in the context of the mobilizations of pensioners\nagainst Javier Milei's government cuts. Page\n12.\n\n\nAccording to Judge Karina Andrade \"being at stake the\nfundamental constitutional right to manifest in a way\ndemocratic and freedom of expression,\"\n\"the opinion on the application of substantial law or on\ninvestigations that the prosecutor may continue in the investigation\nthe existence of criminal conduct\" remains precluded\n\"the application of the scourgency procedure.\"\n\n\nThe position of the judiciary with that of the\nGovernment. On X the National Security Minister, Patricia\nBullrich, in fact said that \"the over one hundred arrested\nrisk convictions up to 20 years of prison\" thanks \"to the\nnew anti-mafia law\" approved by the government.\n\n\nDisorders have begun before the beginning of the\nevent organized by pensioners to whom they joined\norganized typhoseries of different teams and various unions between\nwhich the Cgt. According to the official budget, 26 agents and 20\nprotesters were injured, including photographer Pablo\nGrillo, admitted in very serious condition after being\nhit the head by a tear gas.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'In game the right to protest and freedom of expression'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "114",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 150",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei's",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "12",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karina Andrade",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Patricia\nBullrich",
                "start_char": 794,
                "end_char": 811,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "one hundred",
                "start_char": 841,
                "end_char": 852,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "up to 20 years",
                "start_char": 879,
                "end_char": 893,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cgt",
                "start_char": 1147,
                "end_char": 1150,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "26",
                "start_char": 1186,
                "end_char": 1188,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 1200,
                "end_char": 1202,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pablo\nGrillo",
                "start_char": 1251,
                "end_char": 1263,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il governo Milei contro la scarcerazione dei manifestanti",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:26:20 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/il-governo-milei-contro-la-scarcerazione-dei-manifestanti_3dee9dc8-b14a-4db2-9d3e-08d4a3415397.html",
        "subtitle": "'La giustizia della porta girevole è la causa dell'insicurezza'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il governo argentino ha\ncriticato la decisione della giustizia di ordinare la\nscarcerazione dei manifestanti arrestati durante le violenze\nesplose a margine della protesta organizzata dai pensionati, cui\nhanno aderito sindacati e ultras delle squadre di calcio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"La giudice Karina Giselle Andrade ha ordinato il rilascio\ndei 114 detenuti che, insieme a molti altri, hanno distrutto la\ncittà di Buenos Aires e attaccato le forze di sicurezza ieri\",\nha affermato su X il portavoce presidenziale Manuel Adorni. \"La\ngiustizia della porta girevole è direttamente responsabile\ndell'insicurezza in Argentina. Coloro che si battono per\nl'impunità in ogni sentenza sono complici\", ha aggiunto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Secondo la tesi del magistrato, gli arresti realizzati dalla\npolizia in flagranza di reato sono \"preclusi\" in questo caso in\nquesto caso \"essendo in gioco il diritto costituzionale\nfondamentale di manifestare in modo democratico e quello della\nlibertà di espressione\". Nel corso delle violenze 50 persone\nsono rimaste ferite tra manifestanti, forze di polizia e\ngiornalisti. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 68,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.7004108,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "The Milei government against the scarceness of protesters",
        "en_content": "The Argentine government has\ncriticized the decision of justice to order the\nscarceness of protesters arrested during violence\nexploded in the margin of the protest organized by pensioners, whose\nhave joined unions and ultras of football teams.\n\n\n\" Judge Karina Giselle Andrade ordered the release\nof the 114 prisoners who, together with many others, destroyed the\ncity of Buenos Aires and attacked security forces yesterday\",\nPresidential spokesman Manuel Adorni said on X. \"\nswivel door justice is directly responsible\nof insecurity in Argentina. Those who fight for\nimpunity in every sentence are complicit,\" he added.\n\n\nAccording to the magistrate's thesis, arrests made by\nPolice in scourgency of crime are \"precluded\" in this case in\nthis case \"being at stake constitutional law\nto manifest in a democratic way and that of\nfreedom of expression.\" In the course of violence 50 people\nwounds between protesters, police forces and\njournalists.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'The justice of the revolving door is the cause of insecurity'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karina Giselle Andrade",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "114",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Manuel Adorni",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 463,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "50",
                "start_char": 879,
                "end_char": 881,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Von der Leyen, 'aperti a negoziati con gli Usa sui dazi'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:02:10 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/von-der-leyen-aperti-a-negoziati-con-gli-usa-sui-dazi_a357be4e-69b9-4dba-9b4b-18795951cc2c.html",
        "subtitle": "'Domani il commissario al Commercio sentirà la controparte'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Non ci piacciono i dazi perché\npensiamo siano come delle tasse e che siano negativi per le\nimprese e per i consumatori. Abbiamo sempre detto che\ndifenderemo i nostri interessi. Lo abbiamo detto e dimostrato.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tMa allo stesso tempo voglio anche sottolineare che siamo aperti\nai negoziati. Il commissario al Commercio è in contatto con la\nsua controparte negli Stati Uniti e domani avranno una\ntelefonata proprio su questo tema\". Lo ha detto la presidente\ndella Commissione europea, Ursula von der Leyen, nella\nconferenza stampa al termine del vertice Ue-Sudafrica a Città\ndel Capo. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.7211103,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Von der Leyen, 'open negotiations with the US on duties'",
        "en_content": "\"We do not like duties because\nWe think they're like taxes and they're negative for\ncompanies and consumers. We always said that\nWe will defend our interests. We said it and proved it.\n\n\nBut at the same time I also want to emphasize that we are open\nto the negotiations. The Commissioner for Trade is in contact with\nhis counterpart in the United States and tomorrow will have a\ncall on this theme.\" The President said so.\nby the European Commission, Ursula von der Leyen,\npress conference at the end of the Ue-Sudafrica Summit in City\nChief.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Tomorrow the Commissioner for Trade will feel the counterpart'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Von der",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Brasile, dalla procura via libera al processo contro Bolsonaro",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:28:51 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/brasile-dalla-procura-via-libera-al-processo-contro-bolsonaro_c30d2281-3fe2-4138-a18e-1ce41006e065.html",
        "subtitle": "'La denuncia soddisfa tutti i requisiti'.Ora deciderà il giudice",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La procura generale del Brasile\nsi è espressa a favore dell'avvio del processo penale contro\nl'ex presidente Jair Bolsonaro, accusato insieme ad altre 33\npersone del tentato colpo di stato organizzato per impedire\nl'insediamento di Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva dopo l'elezione\nvinta dal progressista nel 2022. In un parere inviato questa\nmattina alla Corte suprema, la procura ha sostenuto che la\ndenuncia dovrebbe essere accolta perché soddisfa tutti i\nrequisiti. \"Il documento descrive dettagliatamente gli atti\ncriminali e le loro circostanze, spiegando in modo comprensibile\ne individualizzato la presunta condotta criminale adottata da\nciascuno degli imputati\", si legge. Inoltre, aggiunge la\nprocura, \"gli argomenti presentati nelle memorie difensive degli\nindagati non sono sufficienti a ribaltare le accuse e le\nindagini raccolgono elementi sufficienti per imputare gli\nimputati di coinvolgimento nel complotto golpista\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Incassato l'ok della procura ora il giudice titolare del caso\nAlexandre de Moraes presenterà la richiesta di rinvio a giudizio\ndavanti al primo collegio primo collegio della Corte suprema -\ncomposto da cinque degli undici membri della corte - che\ndecideranno a loro volta se processare Bolsonaro e gli altri\nindagati. In questo caso il dibattimento si svolgerebbe davanti\nalla corte in seduta plenaria seguendo le norme del giusto\nprocesso e del diritto alla difesa. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.7677765,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Brazil, from free proxy to trial against Bolsonaro",
        "en_content": "The general prosecutor of Brazil\nhas been expressed in favour of the commencement of the criminal proceedings against\nformer president Jair Bolsonaro, accused together with 33 others\npeople of the attempted coup organized to prevent\nthe settlement of Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva after the election\nwon by the progressive in 2022. In an opinion sent this\nmorning to the Supreme Court, the prosecutor claimed that the\ncomplaint should be welcomed because it meets all\nrequirements. \"The document describes the acts in detail\ncriminals and their circumstances, explaining in a understandable way\nand individualized the alleged criminal conduct adopted by\neach of the defendants,\" we read. In addition, it adds\nproxy, \"the arguments presented in the defensive memories of\ninvestigated are not enough to overturn the accusations and\ninvestigations collect sufficient elements to charge the\ndefendants of involvement in the coup.\n\n\nEngraved the Prosecutor's ok now the court owner of the case\nAlexandre de Moraes will submit a request for referral to judgment\nbefore the first college of the Supreme Court -\ncomposed of five of the eleven members of the court - which\nwill decide in turn whether to process Bolsonaro and others\ninvestigate. In this case the debate would take place before\nto the court in plenary session following the rules of the right\ntrial and right to defence.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'The complaint meets all requirements'. Now the judge will decide",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jair Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "33",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2022",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "this\nmorning",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 985,
                "end_char": 1004,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1063,
                "end_char": 1068,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 1080,
                "end_char": 1097,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "five",
                "start_char": 1112,
                "end_char": 1116,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "eleven",
                "start_char": 1124,
                "end_char": 1130,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 1199,
                "end_char": 1208,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Messico, 'Vogliamo il miglior accordo con gli Usa sui dazi'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:28:23 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/messico-vogliamo-il-miglior-accordo-con-gli-usa-sui-dazi_bd56aa4e-8a96-427c-83cd-08d0b8c2f210.html",
        "subtitle": "Il ministro Ebrard, 'avvieremo consultazioni con l'industria'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Messico sta cercando\nil miglior accordo possibile con gli Stati Uniti per quanto\nriguarda l'attuazione dei dazi voluti dal presidente Donald\nTrump, ha annunciato oggi il ministro dell'Economia del Paese\nlatinoamericano, Marcelo Ebrard.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIn conferenza stampa, il funzionario ha spiegato che\nl'amministrazione della presidente Claudia Sheinbaum sta\nperseguendo questo obiettivo perché il Messico è la nazione più\nintegrata con gli Usa, persino più del Canada.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tEbrard ha definito una \"cattiva idea\" il fatto che il Messico\nnon sia stato escluso dalla tariffa del 25% sulle importazioni\nstatunitensi di acciaio, alluminio e prodotti derivati, in\nvigore da ieri per tutti i Paesi del mondo, ed ha annunciato che\nil governo avvierà un processo di consultazione con i\nrappresentanti dei principali settori interessati, tra cui\nl'industria siderurgica, automobilistica e degli\nelettrodomestici. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.8087454,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Mexico, 'We want the best deal with the US on duties'",
        "en_content": "Mexico is looking\nthe best deal possible with the United States as far as\nthe implementation of the duties requested by President Donald\nTrump, today announced the Minister of Economy of the Country\nLatin American, Marcelo Ebrard.\n\n\nIn the press conference, the official explained that\nthe administration of President Claudia Sheinbaum is\npursuing this goal because Mexico is the nation more\nintegrated with the US, even more than Canada.\n\n\nEbrard defined a \"bad idea\" the fact that Mexico\nhas not been excluded from the tariff of 25% on imports\nU.S. steel, aluminium and derived products, made of\nvigor from yesterday for all countries of the world, and announced that\nthe government will start a consultation process with the\nrepresentatives of the main sectors concerned, including\nthe steel, automotive and steel industry\nappliances.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Minister Ebrard, 'we will have consultations with industry'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ebrard",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald\nTrump",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Minister of Economy of the Country",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Latin American",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marcelo Ebrard",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Claudia Sheinbaum",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 366,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrard",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 609,
                "end_char": 618,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump, 'penso che annetteremo la Groenlandia'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:41:42 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/trump-penso-che-annetteremo-la-groenlandia_4cf18a86-44f4-4922-a40d-1d14f5c27d00.html",
        "subtitle": "'Ne abbiamo bisogno per la sicurezza nazionale'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Donald Trump si è detto sicuro\nche gli Stati Uniti annetteranno la Groenlandia. \"Penso che\naccadrà\", ha detto il presidente americano nello Studio Ovale\ncon Mark Rutte. \"Sono seduto accanto ad un un uomo che potrebbe\nessere determinante\" per l'annessione della Groenlandia, ha\nsottolineato Trump indicando il segretario generale della Nato.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Dobbiamo farlo. Abbiamo davvero bisogno della Groenlandia per\nla sicurezza nazionale\", ha aggiunto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741957222.8146644,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 14:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T13.00.22",
        "en_title": "Trump, 'I think we'll annex Greenland'",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump said it was safe\nthat the United States will annex Greenland. \"I think\nit will happen,\" said the American president in the Oval Studio\nwith Mark Rutte. \"I'm sitting next to a man who might\nto be decisive\" for the annexation of Greenland, has\nunderlined Trump indicating the general secretary of NATO.\n\n\n\"We have to. We really need Greenland for\nnational security,\" he added.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
