[
    {
        "title": "Von der Leyen e Costa, 'per Kiev pace con forti garanzie'",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:47:21 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/14/von-der-leyen-e-costa-per-kiev-pace-con-forti-garanzie_ab2c2d88-ea6e-4126-b92e-c86914e8fd12.html",
        "subtitle": "L'incontro con Zelensky: 'Acceleriamo l'adesione ucraina all'Ue'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"L'Europa è al vostro fianco per\nuna pace giusta e duratura, con forti garanzie di sicurezza.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tContinueremo a fornire un sostegno costante e stabile\nall'Ucraina. E accelereremo i lavori per la vostra adesione\nall'Ue.\" Lo hanno sottolineato Ursula von der Leyen e Antonio\nCosta nell'incontro con il presidente ucraino Volodymyr\nZelensky. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.1933482,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "Von der Leyen and Costa, 'for Kiev peace with strong guarantees'",
        "en_content": "\"Europe is at your side for\na just and lasting peace, with strong security guarantees.\n\n\nWe will continue to provide constant and stable support\nto Ukraine. And we will accelerate the work for your membership\nto the EU.\" They have emphasized Ursula von der Leyen and Antonio\nCosta in the meeting with Ukrainian President Volodymyr\nZelensky.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The meeting with Zelensky: 'Let us accelerate Ukrainian accession to the EU'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Costa",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr\n",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Presidente Messico minaccia causa a Google su 'Golfo d'America'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:20:56 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/13/presidente-messico-minaccia-causa-a-google-su-golfo-damerica_161cc755-7299-45f3-ab40-b93bc02d8d5e.html",
        "subtitle": "Dopo la modifica delle denominazione nella mappe in Usa",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La presidente messicana,\nClaudia Sheinbaum, ha annunciato una possibile causa civile\ncontro Google per aver chiamato il Golfo del Messico \"Golfo\ndell'America\" nelle sue mappe negli Stati Uniti. Sheinbaum ha\ndichiarato di essere rimasta insoddisfatta della risposta di\nGoogle a una lettera che lei ha inviato il 30 gennaio\nall'amministratore delegato dell'azienda, Sundar Pichai, al\nquale ha chiesto di correggere l'area che ora viene chiamata\n\"erroneamente\" Golfo dell'America, poiché il cambio di nome\ndovrebbe applicarsi solo al territorio statunitense. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.2892487,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "President Mexico threatens Google's cause on 'America'",
        "en_content": "The Mexican President,\nClaudia Sheinbaum, announced a possible civil cause\nagainst Google for calling the Gulf of Mexico \"Golph\nin his maps in the United States. Sheinbaum has\nstated that it was unsatisfied with the answer\nGoogle to a letter you sent on 30 January\nto the managing director of the company, Sundar Pichai, to\nwhich asked to correct the area that is now called\n\"erroneously\" Gulf of America, since the name change\nshould apply only to U.S. territory.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "After changing the name in the map in USA",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Google",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "America",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Claudia Sheinbaum",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Google",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Mexico",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Golph",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sheinbaum",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Google",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "30 January",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sundar Pichai",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gulf of America",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Andava in kayak, ingoiato e risputato da una balena in Cile",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:29:18 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/13/andava-in-kayak-ingoiato-e-risputato-da-una-balena-in-cile_1b644471-f24d-48cd-a229-a7ce5ce6aa39.html",
        "subtitle": "L'episodio ripreso in video dal padre del ragazzo",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Remava placidamente\nnelle acque appena mosse dello stretto di Magellano quando è\nstato inghiottito da una gigantesca megattera affiorata\nimprovvisamente con le fauci completamente spalancate.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il giovane 24enne di origine venezuelana, Daniel Simancas,\nnon ha fatto neanche in tempo a rendersi conto di quello che è\nsuccesso ed è riaffiorato a galla solo alcuni secondi dopo\ninsieme alla sua imbarcazione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'episodio, avvenuto nei giorni scorsi nelle acque di fronte\nalla località cilena di Punta Arenas, e stato interamente\nripreso dal padre del ragazzo, e si è e il video è diventato\nvirale rapidamente sui social nelle ultime ore.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel filmato si sente il ragazzo dire spaventato al padre che\npensava ormai di essere stato inghiottito, venendo quindi\nrassicurato dal genitore mentre questi lo lo riportava verso\nriva con la megattera che si aggirava ancora sullo sfondo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In un'intervista televisiva Simancas ha descritto la\nsensazione di trovarsi tre la fauci della balena: \"mi sono\ngirato e ho visto qualcosa tra il bianco e lo scuro e poi ho\nsentito sul volto una cosa dalla consistenza bavosa che si\nchiudeva su di me, pensavo non ci fosse più nulla da fare\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 66,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.8196976,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "He went kayaking, swallowed and remarried by a whale in Chile",
        "en_content": "Remava placid\nin the freshly moved waters of the Strait of Magellano when it is\nwas swallowed by a giant tapered megatter\nsuddenly with the mouths completely wide open.\n\n\nThe young 24-year-old from Venezuela, Daniel Simancas,\nhe did not even in time to realize what he is\nsuccess and only a few seconds after\nalong with his boat.\n\n\nThe episode, occurred in recent days in the waters in front of\nto the Chilean resort of Punta Arenas, and was entirely\nresumed by the boy's father, and you are and the video has become\nQuickly viral on social media in the last hours.\n\n\nIn the video the boy feels scared to the father who\nhe thought he was swallowed up, so coming\nreassured by the parent while they brought him back to\nshore with the megatter that still wandered in the background.\n\n\nIn a television interview Simancas described the\nsensation of finding three whales: \"I am\nturned and I saw something between white and dark and then I\nfelt on the face a thing with a greedy texture\nHe was closing on me, I thought there was nothing left to do.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The episode taken in video by the boy's father",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chile",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Strait of Magellano",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "24-year-old",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Daniel Simancas",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "only a few seconds",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent days",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 368,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chilean",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 409,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Punta Arenas",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last hours",
                "start_char": 550,
                "end_char": 564,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Simancas",
                "start_char": 808,
                "end_char": 816,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 852,
                "end_char": 857,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump crea commissione Maha per far tornare in salute l'America",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:35:06 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/02/13/trump-crea-commissione-maha-per-far-tornare-in-salute-lamerica_b919dc8a-32fb-4125-970e-3c5729c78833.html",
        "subtitle": "Il tema sta particolarmente a cuore a Kennedy Jr",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Donald Trump firmerà un ordine\nesecutivo per creare una commissione Maha, Make America Healthy\nAgain. Lo ha detto la portavoce della Casa Bianca, Karoline\nLeavitt, sottolineando che l'obiettivo della commissione è\nesaminare come rendere di nuovo in salute l'America. Robert F.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tKennedy Jr, confermato dal Senato come ministro della sanità, ha\ndescritto più volte gli Stati Uniti come un paese non in salute.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.8628404,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "Trump creates Maha commission to bring America back to health",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump will sign an order\nExecutive to create a Maha commission, Make America Healthy\nAgain. The White House spokesman Karoline said this.\nLeavitt, stressing that the objective of the committee is\nexamine how to make America healthy again. Robert F.\n\n\nKennedy Jr, confirmed by the Senate as Minister of Health, has\ndescribed several times the United States as a non-healthy country.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The theme is particularly close to Kennedy Jr",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "America",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kennedy Jr",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Karoline",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leavitt",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "America",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Robert F.\n\n\nKennedy Jr",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Minister of Health",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Arrestato un leader politico di opposizione in Venezuela",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:33:53 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/13/arrestato-un-leader-politico-di-opposizione-in-venezuela_2ce4f31f-e078-4e9b-b51d-c7baadca6b12.html",
        "subtitle": "Portato via da casa da uomini incappucciati nella notte",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il giovane leader politico\nvenezuelano di opposizione Luis Somaza, ex consigliere comunale\ndel municipio di Baruta a Caracas, del partito Voluntad Popular,\nè stato portato via da casa sua da agenti del regime chavista\nincappucciati, vestiti di nero e senza documenti ufficiali. Lo\nconfermano i familiari. La sorella dell'esponente politico,\nValeria Somaza, spiega in un video che l'attivista era già stato\nminacciato dal ministro dell'Interno, Diosdado Cabello, e dal\npresidente dell'Assemblea Nazionale, Jorge Rodríguez, due\n\"falchi\" del regime, ma aveva scelto di rimanere in Venezuela.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.877895,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "Arrested a political opposition leader in Venezuela",
        "en_content": "The Young Political Leader\nVenezuelan opposition Luis Somaza, former municipal councilman\nof the municipality of Baruta in Caracas, of the party Voluntad Popular,\nwas taken away from his house by chavista regime agents\nHooded, black clothes and no official documents. I do.\nconfirm the family members. The sister of the political exponent,\nValeria Somaza explains in a video that the activist had already been\nthreatened by Interior Minister, Diosdado Cabello, and\nPresident of the National Assembly, Jorge Rodríguez, two\n\"falks\" of the regime, but he chose to remain in Venezuela.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Taken away from home by hooded men in the night",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the night",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luis Somaza",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Baruta",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Voluntad Popular",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hooded",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Valeria Somaza",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Diosdado Cabello",
                "start_char": 443,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Assembly",
                "start_char": 478,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jorge Rodríguez",
                "start_char": 501,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 571,
                "end_char": 580,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev ammette di aver perso due terzi territorio nel Kursk",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:20:29 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/13/kiev-ammette-di-aver-perso-due-terzi-territorio-nel-kursk_c9399b84-dd6f-4a4b-8aed-0230e12d7d39.html",
        "subtitle": "'Controlliamo 500 kmq'. Finora ne aveva rivendicato 1.400",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Ucraina ha ammesso di detenere a\nmalapena un terzo del territorio nella regione occidentale russa\ndi Kursk che aveva inizialmente catturato durante un'offensiva\nscattata lo scorso agosto. \"Oggi abbiamo la nostra zona di\nsicurezza sul territorio della Federazione Russa, lungo il\nconfine con l'Ucraina, che detiene circa 500 chilometri\nquadrati\", ha scritto sui social media il comandante in capo\ndell'Ucraina Oleksandr Syrsky. In precedenza gli ucraini avevano\nrivendicato di controllare fino a 1.400 chilometri quadrati di\nterritorio. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 65,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.8849194,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "Kiev admits to having lost two thirds territory in Kursk",
        "en_content": "Ukraine has admitted to detention\nbarely one third of the territory in the Russian western region\nof Kursk who had initially captured during an offensive\ntaken last August. \"Today we have our area\nsecurity in the territory of the Russian Federation, along the\nborder with Ukraine, which holds about 500 kilometers\nsquares\", wrote on social media the commander in chief\nof Ukraine Oleksandr Syrsky. Previously the Ukrainians had\nclaimed to control up to 1,400 square kilometers of\nterritory.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'We control 500 square miles'. So far he had claimed 1,400",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two thirds",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kursk",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "500 square miles",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "1,400",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kursk",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "last August",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Federation",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 272,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 500 kilometers",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Oleksandr Syrsky",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainians",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "up to 1,400 square kilometers",
                "start_char": 447,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Colombia, arrestato un negoziatore della guerriglia",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:36:07 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/13/colombia-arrestato-un-negoziatore-della-guerriglia_a9090b98-b0a8-4caa-ba21-d10eada06f42.html",
        "subtitle": "Preoccupazioni per i negoziati di pace",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il guerrigliero delle Farc Andrés\nRojas, alias 'Araña', negoziatore nei colloqui di pace col\ngoverno colombiano, è stato arrestato a Bogotà dopo la chiusura\ndel terzo ciclo di dialoghi. Il fermo di Rojas, a capo dei\nComandi della frontiera, ha generato reazioni sia da parte\ndell'esecutivo che della guerriglia, che hanno messo in luce i\nrischi per i negoziati in corso. L'arresto è avvenuto sulla base\ndi un'allerta rossa dell'Interpol.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La detenzione di Rojas è avvenuta pochi minuti dopo la\nconferenza stampa per comunicare i progressi del terzo round\nnegoziale. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.9200997,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "Colombia, arrested a guerrilla negotiator",
        "en_content": "The Guerrilla of the Farc Andrés\nRojas, alias 'Araña', negotiator in peace talks with\nColombian government, was arrested in Bogota after closing\nof the third cycle of dialogues. Rojas station, head of the\nFrontier controls, generated reactions from both sides\nof the executive that of the guerrilla, which brought to light the\nrisks to ongoing negotiations. The arrest took place on the basis\nof a red alert from Interpol.\n\n\nRojas detention took place a few minutes after\npress conference to communicate the progress of the third round\nnegotiating.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Concerns for the peace negotiations",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Farc Andrés\nRojas",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Araña",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombian",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bogota",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rojas",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Frontier",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Interpol",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rojas",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few minutes",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 529,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Passa alla Camera in Argentina una legge 'anti-Kirchner'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:35:06 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/13/passa-alla-camera-in-argentina-una-legge-anti-kirchner_3f5cf832-bad4-4638-a960-642cb65f8ad2.html",
        "subtitle": "Il governo mira a impedire la candidatura dell'ex presidente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Con 144 voti favorevoli e 89\ncontrari il governo argentino di Javier Milei è riuscito a far\npassare nella notte tra mercoledì e giovedì la cosiddetta legge\nsulla 'fedina pulita', che impedisce la candidatura di persone\ncon una condanna confermata in secondo grado.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In caso di approvazione in seconda lettura anche da parte del\nSenato l'impatto principale del progetto sarà quello di non\nconsentire un'eventuale candidatura dell'ex presidente Cristina\nKirchner - leader dello schieramento peronista e principale\navversario politico di Milei - alle prossime elezioni politiche\ndi medio termine di ottobre.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La corte di Cassazione argentina ha infatti confermato a\nnovembre del 2024 la sentenza di condanna a sei anni di\nreclusione nei confronti di Kirchner per fatti di corruzione\nlegati ad appalti pubblici. Attualmente è possibile candidarsi\nin Argentina in assenza di una conferma della condanna da parte\nanche della Corte Suprema\n  Nel corso del dibattito alla Camera l'opposizione peronista ha\naccusato il governo di voler proscrivere in questo modo la\nleader dell'opposizione. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.9364877,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "Pass to the House in Argentina an anti-Kirchner law",
        "en_content": "With 144 votes in favour and 89\nagainst the Argentine government of Javier Milei managed to make\nspend the night between Wednesday and Thursday the so-called law\non the 'clean faith', which prevents the candidacy of people\nwith a confirmed sentence in second degree.\n\n\nIn case of second reading approval also by\nSenate the main impact of the project will be that of not\nallow for an application by former President Cristina\nKirchner - leader of the peronist and main line\npolitical opponent of Milei - next political elections\nmid-term of October.\n\n\nThe Argentine Court of Cassation confirmed to\nNovember 2024 the sentence of six years' sentence\nimprisonment against Kirchner for corruption\nrelated to public procurement. Currently you can apply\nin Argentina in the absence of a confirmation of the conviction by\nalso the Supreme Court\nIn the course of the debate at the Chamber the Peronist opposition has\naccused the government of wanting to proscribe in this way the\nopposition leader.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The government aims to prevent the candidacy of the former president",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "144",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "89",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the night",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cristina\nKirchner",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei - next",
                "start_char": 494,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "October",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Argentine Court of Cassation",
                "start_char": 550,
                "end_char": 582,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "November 2024",
                "start_char": 596,
                "end_char": 609,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "six years'",
                "start_char": 626,
                "end_char": 636,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kirchner",
                "start_char": 667,
                "end_char": 675,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 749,
                "end_char": 758,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 818,
                "end_char": 835,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chamber",
                "start_char": 871,
                "end_char": 878,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Peronist",
                "start_char": 883,
                "end_char": 891,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, non accetteremo alcun accordo senza di noi",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:19:47 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/13/zelensky-non-accetteremo-alcun-accordo-senza-di-noi_b4ad5830-3ff9-4c77-84f4-dda546a358cd.html",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente ucraino Volodymyr\nZelensky afferma che Kiev non accetterà \"alcun negoziato\nbilaterale sull'Ucraina senza di noi\". Il leader ucraino ha\nparlato durante la visita alla centrale nucleare di\nKhmelnytskyi, come riporta Ukrainska Pravda.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  \"Come paese indipendente, semplicemente non saremo in grado di\naccettare alcun accordo senza di noi. Lo sto dicendo molto\nchiaramente ai nostri partner. Qualsiasi negoziato bilaterale\nsull'Ucraina - non sto parlando di altri argomenti, qui sono\nliberi - non accetteremo alcun negoziato bilaterale sull'Ucraina\nsenza di noi\", ha detto Zelensky. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541618.9590547,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.18",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, we will not accept any agreement without us",
        "en_content": "Ukrainian President Volodymyr\nZelensky claims that Kiev will not accept \"some negotiation\nbilateral about Ukraine without us.\" The Ukrainian leader has\nduring the visit to the nuclear power plant\nKhmelnytskyi, as Ukrainska Pravda reports.\n\n\n\"As an independent country, we simply will not be able to\naccept no agreement without us. I'm saying a lot.\nclearly to our partners. Any bilateral negotiations\nabout Ukraine - I'm not talking about other topics, here I am\nfree - we will not accept any bilateral negotiations on Ukraine\nwithout us,\" said Zelensky.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr\n",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khmelnytskyi",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainska Pravda",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 545,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, 'piano per fermare Putin prima dei colloqui con russi'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:19:52 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/13/zelensky-piano-per-fermare-putin-prima-dei-colloqui-con-russi_208ad4fb-63e7-43e5-845a-1a6159e9692a.html",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            (ANSA-AFP) - KIEV, 13 FEB - \"Gli incontri tra Ucraina e\nAmerica sono la priorità per noi. E solo dopo questi incontri,\ndopo aver sviluppato un piano per fermare Putin, penso che sarà\ngiusto parlare con i russi\", ha detto Zelensky durante una\nvisita alla centrale nucleare di Khmelnytsky nell'Ucraina\noccidentale. Zelensky che questa settimana parteciperà con i\nsuoi collaboratori ad una serie di incontri con funzionari\ndell'amministrazione Donald Trump, si è anche rammaricato che il\npresidente americano abbia parlato per primo con Putin. Il\nleader ucraino, tuttavia, ha affermato di ritenere che la\npriorità di Donald Trump rimanga l'Ucraina, aggiungendo che il\nleader americano gli ha detto che \"voleva parlare con entrambi i\npresidenti contemporaneamente\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Zelensky ha anche affermato che gli europei devono avere un\nposto al \"tavolo dei negoziati\", facendo eco a un appello simile\ndi diversi leader dell'Ue. \"Siamo parte dell'Europa e saremo\nsicuramente membri dell'Unione europea. Per noi è importante. Ci\nhanno aiutato molto\", ha dichiarato. L'Ucraina teme, come gli\neuropei, di essere tenuta fuori dai futuri negoziati tra\nVladimir Putin e Donald Trump, che si terranno nel prossimo\nfuturo. Per tre anni gli Stati Uniti hanno rappresentato il\nprincipale sostegno militare e finanziario di Kiev di fronte\nall'invasione russa. (ANSA-AFP).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541619.0054748,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.19",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, 'plan to stop Putin before talks with Russians'",
        "en_content": "(ANSA-AFP) - KIEV, 13 FEB - \"The meetings between Ukraine and\nAmerica is our priority. And only after these meetings,\nafter developing a plan to stop Putin, I think it will be\njust talk to the Russians,\" said Zelensky during a\nvisit to the Khmelnytsky nuclear power plant in Ukraine\nWestern. Zelensky this week will participate with\nhis staff at a series of meetings with officials\nof the administration Donald Trump, he also regretted that the\nAmerican president spoke first with Putin. The\nUkrainian leader, however, claimed to believe that the\nDonald Trump priority remains Ukraine, adding that the\nAmerican leader told him that \"wanted to speak with both\nPresidents at the same time.\"\n\n\nZelensky also stated that Europeans must have a\nto the \"table of negotiations\", echoing a similar appeal\nof several EU leaders. \"We are part of Europe and we will be\ncertainly members of the European Union. It's important to us. There we go.\nthey helped a lot,\" he said. Ukraine fears, like the\nEuropeans to be held outside the future negotiations between\nVladimir Putin and Donald Trump, who will be held next\nfuture. For three years the United States has represented\nmain military and financial support of Kiev in front of\nto the Russian invasion. (ANSA-AFP).\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "13 FEB",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "America",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khmelnytsky",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "this week",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 475,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 481,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 559,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 577,
                "end_char": 584,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 602,
                "end_char": 610,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 691,
                "end_char": 699,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 717,
                "end_char": 726,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 807,
                "end_char": 809,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 835,
                "end_char": 841,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 878,
                "end_char": 896,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 962,
                "end_char": 969,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 986,
                "end_char": 995,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 1047,
                "end_char": 1061,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 1066,
                "end_char": 1078,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "three years",
                "start_char": 1114,
                "end_char": 1125,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 1126,
                "end_char": 1143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 1199,
                "end_char": 1203,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1223,
                "end_char": 1230,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 1242,
                "end_char": 1250,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Msf, 'aumentano le violenze in un campo profughi nel Darfur'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:19:26 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2025/02/13/msf-aumentano-le-violenze-in-un-campo-profughi-nel-darfur_7ec5bb29-0683-4135-8ba9-c9cf950cd34f.html",
        "subtitle": "Difficoltà a Zamzam per gli scontri tra paramilitari ed esercito",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nel campo profughi sudanese di\nZamzam civili feriti stanno arrivando nell'ospedale gestito da\nMedici senza frontiere (Msf) da martedì, ma il personale non è\nin grado di curarli per la mancanza di \"capacità chirurgiche\":\nlo ha detto l'Ong dopo l'escalation delle violenze nel campo che\nsorge nei pressi della città assediata di Al-Fashir, nel Darfur\nSettentrionale. Raggiungere l'ospedale pienamente equipaggiato\ndella città è diventato quasi impossibile a causa dei\ncombattimenti tra le forze paramilitari e l'esercito, secondo\nMsf.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La guerra civile scoppiata il 15 aprile 2023 ha visto nelle\nultime settimane un intensificarsi degli scontri da parte dei\nparamilitari, che assediano Al-Fashir dallo scorso maggio per\nprendere l'ultima città rimasta sotto il controllo delle forze\narmate nella regione occidentale del Darfur. Msf ha segnalato\nforze paramilitari all'interno del campo di Zamzam, dove è già\nstata dichiarata la carestia e le ostilità contro le milizie\nalleate dell'esercito mettono \"centinaia di migliaia\" di persone\na rischio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Ieri l'ospedale dell'Ong nel campo ha accolto 17 feriti che\nsi sono aggiunti ai 23 pazienti di martedì, mentre Msf ha\nregistrato sette persone morte all'arrivo. Anche l'Unicef ieri\nha lanciato l'allarme sul peggioramento della situazione a\nZamzam, dove \"centinaia di migliaia di bambini sono a rischio\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541619.0181756,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.19",
        "en_title": "Msf, 'increasing violence in a refugee camp in Darfur'",
        "en_content": "In the Sudanese refugee camp\ninjured civilian Zamzam are coming to the hospital run by\nDoctors without frontiers (Msf) from Tuesday, but the staff is not\nable to cure them for the lack of \"surgical capacity\":\nthe Ong said after the escalation of violence in the field that\nis located near the besieged city of Al-Fashir, in Darfur\nNorth. Reach the fully equipped hospital\nof the city became almost impossible because of\nfighting between the paramilitary forces and the army, second\nMsf.\n\n\nCivil war broke out on 15 April 2023 saw in\nlast weeks an intensification of clashes by the\nparamilitari, who besiege Al-Fashir from last May for\ntake the last remaining city under the control of forces\nArmed in the western region of Darfur. Msf reported\nparamilitary forces within the Zamzam camp, where it is already\nthe famine and hostility against militias was declared\narmy allies put \"thousands of thousands\" of people\nAt risk.\n\n\nYesterday the Ong hospital in the camp welcomed 17 wounded who\nadded to 23 patients on Tuesday, while Msf has\nregistered seven dead people on arrival. Even the Unnicef yesterday\nhas launched the alarm on the worsening of the situation to\nZamzam, where thousands of children are at risk.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Difficulty in Zamzam for the clashes between paramilitary and army",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Darfur",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zamzam",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sudanese",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zamzam",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ong",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Fashir",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Darfur",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "15 April 2023",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "last weeks",
                "start_char": 533,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Fashir",
                "start_char": 607,
                "end_char": 616,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "last May",
                "start_char": 622,
                "end_char": 630,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Darfur",
                "start_char": 723,
                "end_char": 729,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zamzam",
                "start_char": 775,
                "end_char": 781,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands of thousands",
                "start_char": 880,
                "end_char": 902,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yesterday",
                "start_char": 925,
                "end_char": 934,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "17",
                "start_char": 973,
                "end_char": 975,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "23",
                "start_char": 997,
                "end_char": 999,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 1012,
                "end_char": 1019,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 1046,
                "end_char": 1051,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Unnicef",
                "start_char": 1085,
                "end_char": 1092,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 1093,
                "end_char": 1102,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zamzam",
                "start_char": 1163,
                "end_char": 1169,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "thousands",
                "start_char": 1177,
                "end_char": 1186,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Iran, '1.000 nuovi stabilimenti atomici se nemico attacca'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:59:09 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/02/13/iran-1.000-nuovi-stabilimenti-atomici-se-nemico-attacca_d709809c-0d97-4eac-ad07-f0ecef148fea.html",
        "subtitle": "Per il Wp Israele potrebbe colpire nei prossimi mesi",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente iraniano, Masoud\nPezeshkian, ha promesso che in caso ci fosse un attacco da parte\ndi \"nemici\" contro gli stabilimenti nucleari di Teheran la\nRepubblica islamica ne costruirebbe mille nuovi. \"Il nemico\nminaccia di colpire il nostro impianto nucleare. Venite e\ncolpitelo, è il cervello dei nostri appassionati esperti che\nl'ha costruito. Se ne colpite 100, i nostri esperti ne\ncostruiranno 1000\", ha detto Pezeshkian, come riferisce Mehr,\nmentre secondo il Washington Post l'intelligence degli Usa\nritiene che Israele potrebbe tentare di colpire gli stabilimenti\nnucleari iraniani nei prossimi mesi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 54,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541619.0481665,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.19",
        "en_title": "Iran, '1,000 new atomic plants if enemy attacks'",
        "en_content": "Iranian President, Masoud\nPezeshkian, you promised if there was an attack on the side.\nof \"enemies\" against the Tehran nuclear plants\nThe Islamic Republic would build a thousand new ones. \"The enemy\nthreatens to hit our nuclear plant. Come and\nhit it, it is the brain of our expert fans who\nHe built it. If you hit 100, our experts will\nwill build 1000\", said Pezeshkian, as Mehr reports,\nwhile according to Washington Post the intelligence of the U.S.\nbelieves that Israel could try to hit the factories\nIran nuclear power stations in the coming months.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "For Wp Israel could hit in the coming months",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1,000",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Wp",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming months",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Masoud\nPezeshkian",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Islamic Republic",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "a thousand",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "100",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "1000",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pezeshkian",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mehr",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington Post",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming months",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Brasile e Russia discutono l'agenda del Brics dei Comuni",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:38:54 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/13/brasile-e-russia-discutono-lagenda-del-brics-dei-comuni_bada5b39-e73e-4b73-9ae0-158953972a94.html",
        "subtitle": "Collaborazione su fertilizzanti e sicurezza alimentare tra temi",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Forum internazionale dei\nComuni del Brics, con al centro temi quali la cooperazione nel\nsettore dei fertilizzanti, con particolare attenzione alle nuove\ntecnologie russe, e i programmi brasiliani su sicurezza e\nsostenibilità alimentare, è stato il principale tema affrontato \nin una riunione tra il ministro dell'Agricoltura e\ndell'Allevamento, Carlos Fávaro, e una delegazione arrivata da\nMosca. Lo riporta una nota del governo brasiliano.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  Nel quadro della sua presidenza del Brics, il Brasile\norganizzerà l'evento prima della riunione dei leader di luglio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 52,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541619.06288,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.19",
        "en_title": "Brazil and Russia discuss the Brics agenda of Municipalities",
        "en_content": "The International Forum\nMunicipalities of Brics, with themes such as cooperation in\nfertilizer sector, with particular attention to the new\nRussian technologies, and Brazilian programs on safety and\nfood sustainability, was the main topic addressed\nat a meeting between the Minister of Agriculture and\nof the Allevamento, Carlos Fávaro, and a delegation arrived from\nMoscow. It's a note from the Brazilian government.\n\n\nAs part of his presidency of the Brics, Brazil\nwill organize the event before the July leaders meeting.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Collaboration on fertilizers and food safety between themes",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brics",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Municipalities",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Allevamento",
                "start_char": 309,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlos Fávaro",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brics",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "July",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Cremlino, 'se europei vogliono ruolo ne parlino con Trump'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:28:30 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/13/cremlino-se-europei-vogliono-ruolo-ne-parlino-con-trump_4d6f50f3-91e0-4660-8c3f-337d3842082c.html",
        "subtitle": "Il nodo non è stato affrontato nel colloquio tra i due leader",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Donald Trump e Vladimir Putin non\nhanno discusso di una partecipazione degli europei alle\ntrattative sull'Ucraina, e se vogliono un ruolo, i Paesi della\nUe farebbero meglio a parlarne con il presidente americano. Lo\nha detto il portavoce del Cremlino, Dmitry Peskov. \"Le questioni\neuropee non sono state in alcun modo affrontate nella\nconversazione di ieri\" e \"gli europei dovranno probabilmente\nparlare con Washington per chiedere un posto\" al tavolo delle\ntrattative, ha affermato Peskov in un'intervista alla\ntelevisione di Stato ripresa dall'agenzia Tass. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 55,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541619.0712595,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.19",
        "en_title": "Kremlin, 'if Europeans want to play with Trump'",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump and Vladimir Putin not\nhave discussed European participation in\nnegotiations on Ukraine, and if they want a role, the countries of\nThey'd better talk to the American president. I do.\nsaid the spokesman of the Kremlin, Dmitry Peskov. \"The issues\nEuropeans have not been faced in any way in\nconversation yesterday\" and \"Europeans will probably have to\ntalk to Washington to ask for a place\" at the table\ntalks, Peskov said in an interview with\nState television resumed by the agency Tass.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The node was not addressed in the interview between the two leaders",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dmitry Peskov",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 267,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peskov",
                "start_char": 422,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 494,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Non sei il presidente, vai via',virale video del piccolo Musk",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:37:36 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/02/13/non-sei-il-presidente-vai-viavirale-video-del-piccolo-musk_c591c8a8-b680-4a25-b1d1-add8b96e1188.html",
        "subtitle": "Nello studio ovale rivolto a Trump, 'chiudi il becco'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            In un video diventato virale\ndella conferenza improvvisata di Elon Musk con Donald Trump\nnello studio ovale si vede il figlio piccolo del tycoon di X,\nquattro anni, che sembra dire a Trump \"chiudi il becco\" e,\nsecondo altri utenti di X, avrebbe detto anche, rivolto al\npresidente americano, 'vai via, non sei il presidente'. L'audio\ne' difficile da decifrare e dunque le frasi del piccolo\npotrebbero essere solo illazioni, ma il video fa discutere.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il bambino fa il verso al padre imitandone i gesti e si mette\nle dita nel naso per poi pulirsele sulla scrivania presidenziale\nResolute donata alla Casa Bianca dalla Regina Vittoria.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  Non è la prima volta che il patron di Space X mette il figlio\npiccolo sotto i riflettori. Attirandosi le critiche della ex\ncompagna Grimes (la cantante canadese Claire Boucher che con il\ntycoon ha avuto due maschietti e una bambina), Musk aveva\nsovraesposto uno dei suoi 12 figli durante una cerimonia per la\nfirma di un ordine esecutivo destinato a rafforzare i poteri del\nDoge. Grimes aveva sostenuto che \"il bambino non doveva essere\nmesso in piazza cosi\" ma che era contenta che \"fosse stato\nalmeno educato\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 53,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739541619.0796409,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-14 15:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-14T14.00.19",
        "en_title": "'You are not the president, go away', viral video of the little Musk",
