[
    {
        "title": "Colombia, ex presidente Pastrana arrestato allo scalo di Luanda",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:09:53 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/colombia-ex-presidente-pastrana-arrestato-allo-scalo-di-luanda_32796a07-8ac0-45d3-b7b8-c5062e794b3f.html",
        "subtitle": "'Mi hanno rinchiuso in una stanzetta e non so perché'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'ex presidente della Colombia\nAndrés Pastrana, che con altri ex presidenti e figure politiche\nha viaggiato in Angola per partecipare a una conferenza\ninternazionale incentrata sulla democrazia, è trattenuto\nall'aeroporto di Luanda, in Angola. Lo rende noto Radio Caracol.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"A quest'ora mi trovo trattenuto all'aeroporto di Luanda dal\ngoverno dell'Angola, che blocca l'ingresso di un gruppo di\npolitici africani invitati dalla Fondazione Brenthurst e\ndall'Internazionale Democratica di Centro (IDC-CDI),\norganizzazione globale che presiedo\", ha denunciato Pastrana\ntramite il suo account ufficiale di X.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Mi hanno rinchiuso in una stanzetta, ma non ho idea del\nperché mi abbiano messo qui. Nessuno mi dice niente, né mi\nspiegano perché non mi lasciano entrare\", ha detto l'ex\npresidente alla rivista colombiana Semana.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Pastrana, che presiede anche l'Internazionale Democratica, ha\nprecisato che \"quando stavo per prendere un volo per Benguela,\nun'altra città dell'Angola, un territorio attiguo, non mi hanno\nlasciato proseguire\", aggiungendo che era \"venuto a una riunione\norganizzata dal Partito Unite per la Libertà e la Dignità che è\ndi opposizione\". Con Pastrana, fermato anche il leader\ndell'opposizione dell'Angola, Venâncio Mondlane, che però è\nstato poi lasciato passare dalle autorità del suo paese. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 80,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982417.8492796,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.17",
        "en_title": "Colombia, former president Pastrana arrested at the port of Luanda",
        "en_content": "Former President of Colombia\nAndrés Pastrana, who with other former presidents and political figures\ntraveled to Angola to attend a conference\ninternational centred on democracy, is held\nLuanda Airport, Angola. It makes Radio Caracol known.\n\n\n\"At this hour I'm held at Luanda airport from\nGovernment of Angola, which blocks the entry of a group of\nAfrican politicians invited by the Brenthurst Foundation and\nby the Centre Democratic International (IDC-CDI),\nglobal organization that I preside,\" said Pastrana\nvia its official X account.\n\n\n\"They locked me in a room, but I have no idea\nbecause they put me here. Nobody tells me anything.\nThey explain why they don't let me in,\" said the ex\nPresident of Colombian Semana magazine.\n\n\nPastrana, who also presides over the Democratic International, has\nspecified that \"when I was about to take a flight to Benguela,\nanother city of Angola, an adjacent territory, do not have me\nallowed to continue, adding that he had \"come to a meeting\norganized by the United Party for Freedom and Dignity which is\nof opposition.\" With Pastrana, the leader also stopped\nof the opposition of Angola, Venâncio Mondlane, which however is\nwas then left to pass by the authorities of his country.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'They locked me in a room and I don't know why'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pastrana",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luanda",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrés Pastrana",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Angola",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luanda Airport",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Angola",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Radio Caracol",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "this hour",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luanda",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Angola",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "African",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Brenthurst Foundation",
                "start_char": 379,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Centre Democratic International",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pastrana",
                "start_char": 501,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombian Semana",
                "start_char": 703,
                "end_char": 719,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pastrana",
                "start_char": 732,
                "end_char": 740,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Democratic International",
                "start_char": 765,
                "end_char": 793,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Benguela",
                "start_char": 852,
                "end_char": 860,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Angola",
                "start_char": 878,
                "end_char": 884,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Party for Freedom and Dignity",
                "start_char": 996,
                "end_char": 1036,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pastrana",
                "start_char": 1067,
                "end_char": 1075,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Angola",
                "start_char": 1122,
                "end_char": 1128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venâncio Mondlane",
                "start_char": 1130,
                "end_char": 1147,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Perù, ex presidente Castillo portato d'urgenza in ospedale",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:40:15 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/peru-ex-presidente-castillo-portato-durgenza-in-ospedale_9ef4c738-6290-43c4-8683-de49e2c4c0ba.html",
        "subtitle": "In sciopero della fame da quattro giorni si è sentito male",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'ex presidente del Perù, Pedro\nCastillo, è stato trasferito d'urgenza all'ospedale II Vitarte\nEssalud per un malore, poco prima della ripresa del processo\ncontro di lui per il tentato colpo di Stato del dicembre 2022.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tCastillo ha iniziato il 10 marzo scorso uno sciopero della fame\nper protestare contro il processo che lo vede imputato ed in cui\nrischia una pena di oltre 30 anni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   All'inizio della sessione odierna, è stato letto in aula un\nrapporto del direttore del carcere di Barbadillo, dove Castillo\nè detenuto da oltre due anni, in cui \"il medico Jhon Lozano\nAzenjo informa che il signor Pedro Castillo sta venendo evacuato\nd'emergenza con la diagnosi di un disturbo del sensorio,\neziologia da determinare\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il parlamentare ed ex ministro del Turismo e del Commercio\nEstero di Castillo, Roberto Sánchez, che lo ha visitato in\nospedale con lui ha detto ai media peruviani che \"a malapena\nascolta e può parlare. Siamo stati con lui, al pronto soccorso\ncon il suo medico curante, con tutti gli esami che hanno fatto\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Ci hanno relazionato su una disidratazione critica e la\npreoccupazione è che avendo anche una gastrite tutto ciò possa\ncomplicare il suo stato di salute. Per questo chiediamo che\nvenga trasferito all'ospedale Rebagliati, poiché lì ci sono\ntutte le misure adeguate per qualsiasi emergenza o rischio per\nla sua salute,\" ha concluso Sánchez. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 78,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982417.8825612,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.17",
        "en_title": "Peru, former President Castillo urgently brought to the hospital",
        "en_content": "Former President of Peru, Pedro\nCastillo, he was transferred urgently to II Vitarte Hospital\nEssalud for a malore, just before the resumption of the process\nagainst him for the attempted coup of December 2022.\n\n\nCastillo started on March 10 last a hunger strike\nto protest against the trial that sees him accused and in which\nrisks a penalty of over 30 years.\n\n\nAt the beginning of today's session, one room was read\nreport of the prison director of Barbadillo, where Castillo\nhas been detained for over two years, in which \"the doctor Jhon Lozano\nAzenjo informs that Mr Pedro Castillo is being evacuated\nemergency with the diagnosis of a sensor disorder,\neziology to be determined\".\n\n\nParliamentary and former Minister for Tourism and Commerce\nEstero di Castillo, Roberto Sánchez, who visited him in\nhospital with him told the Peruvian media that \" barely\nlisten and you can talk. We stayed with him at the E.R.\nwith his doctor, with all the tests they have done.\"\n\n\n\"We were related to a critical dehydration and\nconcern is that having a gastritis all this can\ncomplicate his health. That's why we ask\nis transferred to the hospital Rebagliati, because there are\nall appropriate measures for any emergency or risk for\nhis health,\" concluded Sánchez.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "On hunger strike for four days it has felt badly",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Peru",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Castillo",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "four days",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Peru",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro\nCastillo",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "II",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Essalud",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "December 2022",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Castillo",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 10",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 30 years",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 387,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Barbadillo",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 460,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Castillo",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "over two years",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jhon Lozano",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Azenjo",
                "start_char": 548,
                "end_char": 554,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Castillo",
                "start_char": 571,
                "end_char": 585,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Sánchez",
                "start_char": 765,
                "end_char": 780,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peruvian",
                "start_char": 828,
                "end_char": 836,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "E.R.",
                "start_char": 908,
                "end_char": 912,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rebagliati",
                "start_char": 1135,
                "end_char": 1145,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sánchez",
                "start_char": 1243,
                "end_char": 1250,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Presidente del Portogallo scioglie il Parlamento, voto il 18/5",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:38:20 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/presidente-del-portogallo-scioglie-il-parlamento-voto-il-185_717c103d-cd00-4d3b-9b0e-889cebcea7b6.html",
        "subtitle": "Martedì il governo di Montenegro non ha superato voto fiducia",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente della Repubblica del\nPortogallo, Marcelo Rebelo de Sousa, ha annunciato lo\nscioglimento del Parlamento e ha convocato elezioni anticipate\nper il prossimo 18 maggio. \"Non si può diffidare dal punto di\nvista etico di un primo ministro\", ha detto il presidente nel\nsuo discorso alla nazione di questa sera, \"e i partiti si sono\nmanifestati unanimemente a favore delle elezioni anticipate\". \nLa decisione di Rebelo de Sousa arriva in seguito alla caduta\ndel governo di centrodestra guidato da Luís Montenegro, che\nmartedì non ha superato la prova del voto di fiducia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Le legislative del 18 maggio saranno le terze elezioni\nanticipate in tre anni. Nel 2022 le elezioni furono vinte dal\nPartito socialista di António Costa che ottenne una maggioranza\nassoluta, ma si dimise nel novembre 2023 e i portoghesi\ndovettero tornare alle urne a marzo del 2024. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 79,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982417.8886552,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.17",
        "en_title": "President of Portugal dissolves Parliament, vote on 18/5",
        "en_content": "The President of the Republic of\nPortugal, Marcelo Rebelo de Sousa, announced the\nParliament's dissolution and called for early elections\nfor the next 18 May. \"You cannot distrust from the point of view\nethical view of a prime minister,\" said the President in\nhis speech to the nation tonight, \"and the parties have\nmanifested unanimously in favour of early elections.\"\nThe decision of Rebelo de Sousa comes after the fall\nof the center-right government led by Luís Montenegro, which\nTuesday did not pass the proof of the vote of confidence.\n\n\nThe laws of 18 May will be the third elections\nanticipated in three years. In 2022 the elections were won by\nSocialist Party of António Costa who obtained a majority\nabsolute, but resigned in November 2023 and the Portuguese\nThey had to return to the urns in March 2024.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Tuesday the Government of Montenegro has not exceeded vote confidence",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Portugal",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "18/5",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Montenegro",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Portugal",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marcelo Rebelo de Sousa",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the next 18 May",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rebelo de Sousa",
                "start_char": 386,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luís Montenegro",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "18 May",
                "start_char": 556,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 575,
                "end_char": 580,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three years",
                "start_char": 606,
                "end_char": 617,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2022",
                "start_char": 622,
                "end_char": 626,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Socialist Party of",
                "start_char": 653,
                "end_char": 671,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "António Costa",
                "start_char": 672,
                "end_char": 685,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "November 2023",
                "start_char": 736,
                "end_char": 749,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Portuguese",
                "start_char": 758,
                "end_char": 768,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "March 2024",
                "start_char": 803,
                "end_char": 813,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, 'da Putin manipolazioni sulla proposta di tregua'",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:45:03 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/zelensky-da-putin-manipolazioni-sulla-proposta-di-tregua_38197fe3-f86d-487a-be6e-d48005ba1da8.html",
        "subtitle": "'In realtà si sta preparando a rifiutarla'",
        "content": " \"Il dittatore russo Vladimir Putin vuole respingere la proposta degli Stati Uniti di un cessate il fuoco di 30 giorni con l'Ucraina. Per riuscirci, pone richieste impossibili\". Lo ha denunciato il presidente ucraino Volodymyr Zelensky nel suo discorso serale riportato da Rbc-Ucraina.     \"Abbiamo tutti sentito dalla Russia parole molto prevedibili e una manipolazione da parte di Putin sulla tregua: in realtà sta preparando un rifiuto fin da ora\", ha osservato il capo dello Stato ucraino.     \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 73,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982417.9030108,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.17",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, 'from Putin manipulations on the proposed truce'",
        "en_content": "\"Russian dictator Vladimir Putin wants to reject the United States proposal of a ceasefire of 30 days with Ukraine. To succeed, he puts impossible demands.\" He denounced Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky in his evening speech reported by Rbc-Ukraine. \"We all heard from Russia very predictable words and a manipulation by Putin on the truce: in reality he is preparing a refusal from now on,\" remarked the head of the Ukrainian state.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "\"It's actually getting ready to refuse it.\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 days",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rbc-Ukraine",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "In Gb ergastolo a 18enne che accoltellò a morte una ragazzina",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:57:39 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/in-gb-ergastolo-a-18enne-che-accoltello-a-morte-una-ragazzina_0b76bfeb-3750-47b6-8930-4c387a856407.html",
        "subtitle": "Elianne Andam uccisa nel 2023 per una lite su un orsacchiotto",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Un 18enne, Hassan Sentamu, è stato\ncondannato all'ergastolo, con un minimo di 23 anni da\ntrascorrere dietro le sbarre prima di poter chiedere la libertà\ncondizionata, per aver accoltellato a morte nel settembre 2023\nnel quartiere londinese di Croydon una ragazza di 15 anni,\nElianne Andam, in uno dei tanti casi di violenza giovanile che\nhanno segnato il Regno Unito negli ultimi tempi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La teenager, subito dopo essere scesa da un autobus per\nandare a scuola, era stata aggredita e colpita più volte al\ncollo e al petto dal giovane, allora 17enne. Era stata presa di\nmira perché aveva difeso un'amica da Sentamu durante una lite\nper la fine della relazione tra i due incentrata sulla\nrestituzione di un orsacchiotto di peluche. \"Elianne aveva 15\nanni quando l'hai assassinata. Rimarrà sempre solo 15enne, non\nrealizzerà mai il potenziale della sua vita. Il dolore per la\nsua perdita da parte dei genitori e del fratello minore è\nindescrivibile\", ha dichiarato la giudice Bobbie Cheema-Grubb\ndurante la lettura della sentenza. La grave pena inflitta è\nderivante dai precedenti di Sentamu per i suoi comportamenti\nviolenti nei confronti di altre ragazze. Durante il processo era\nstato respinta la circostanza attenuante presentata dalla difesa\nsecondo cui un disturbo dello spettro autistico aveva fatto\nperdere al giovane il controllo davanti alla sua vittima.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 75,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982417.9170976,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.17",
        "en_title": "In Gb ergastolo to 18 years old who greeted to death a girl",
        "en_content": "An 18-year-old, Hassan Sentimu, was\nsentenced to life, with a minimum of 23 years from\nspend behind bars before you can ask for freedom\nconditioned, for stabbing death in September 2023\nin the London district of Croydon a 15-year-old girl,\nElianne Andam, in one of the many cases of youth violence that\nhave marked the UK in recent times.\n\n\nThe teen, immediately after being dropped from a bus to\nto go to school, had been attacked and hit several times at\nneck and chest by the young man, then 17 years old. She was taken.\nHe targets why he defended a friend from Sentimu during a fight\nfor the end of the relationship between the two focusing on\nreturn of a teddy bear. \"Elianne had 15\nyears when you murdered her. Only 15-year-old will remain.\nHe will never realize the potential of his life. The pain for the\nhis loss from his parents and younger brother is\nindescribable\", said Judge Bobbie Cheema-Grubb\nduring the reading of the sentence. The grave penalty inflicted is\nderived from the previous of Sentimu for his behaviors\nviolent against other girls. During the process it was\nthe attenuating circumstance presented by the defence\nthat an autistic spectrum disorder had made\nlosing control to the young man in front of his victim.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Elianne Andam killed in 2023 for a fight on a teddy bear",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "18 years old",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Elianne Andam",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "18-year-old",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hassan Sentimu",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "23 years",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "September 2023",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Croydon",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "15-year-old",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elianne Andam",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "17 years old",
                "start_char": 495,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sentimu",
                "start_char": 565,
                "end_char": 572,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 632,
                "end_char": 635,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elianne",
                "start_char": 673,
                "end_char": 680,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "15\nyears",
                "start_char": 685,
                "end_char": 693,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "15-year-old",
                "start_char": 722,
                "end_char": 733,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bobbie Cheema-Grubb",
                "start_char": 889,
                "end_char": 908,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sentimu",
                "start_char": 1005,
                "end_char": 1012,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Polemica in Brasile per l'autostrada della Cop30 in Amazzonia",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:43:38 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/polemica-in-brasile-per-lautostrada-della-cop30-in-amazzonia_1255d50f-6b49-4b44-8a5f-3904f5f765ff.html",
        "subtitle": "Autorizzata una bretella di 13 km in mezzo alla foresta protetta",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            E' polemica in Brasile per\nla decisione del governo di Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva di avviare\nla costruzione di un'autostrada di 13 chilometri che attraversa\nla foresta amazzonica con l'obiettivo di migliorare il\ncollegamento con la città di Belém, sede della prossima\nconferenza sul cambiamento climatico Cop30.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il progetto, definito dal governo di Lula come \"un'autostrada\nsostenibile\", ha scatenato accese polemiche con gli\nambientalisti, che denunciano il notevole impatto ambientale\ndell'infrastruttura che attraverserà un'area protetta.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Oltre al valore ambientale, queste terre hanno un significato\nstorico per la popolazione indigena Tupinambá e, di fronte alle\ncritiche degli ambientalisti, il governo Lula afferma adesso che\nnon si tratta di un progetto legato alla Cop anche se prevede di\ncompletarlo appena un mese prima del vertice.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Non si tratta dell'unica contraddizione in cui incorre il\ngoverno progressista di Lula che a livello internazionale ha\nassunto una leadership in materia di lotta al cambiamento\nclimatico. Gli ambientalisti criticano duramente infatti anche\nla sua scelta di avanzare con le esplorazioni petrolifere del\ngigante statale Petrobras alle foci del Rio delle Amazzoni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 77,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982417.925925,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.17",
        "en_title": "Polemica in Brazil for the Cop30 motorway in the Amazon",
        "en_content": "It's controversy in Brazil for\nthe decision of the government of Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva to start\nthe construction of a highway of 13 kilometers that crosses\nthe Amazon forest with the aim of improving the\nconnection with the city of Belém, seat of the next\nClimate change conference Cop30.\n\n\nThe project, defined by the government of Lula as \"a highway\nsustainable,\" he sparked heated controversy with the\nenvironmentalists, who denounce the significant environmental impact\nof the infrastructure that will cross a protected area.\n\n\nIn addition to environmental value, these lands have a meaning\nhistorical for the indigenous population Tupinambá and, in front of\ncriticism of environmentalists, the Lula government now states that\nit is not a project related to the Cop even if it plans to\nto complete it just a month before the summit.\n\n\nThis is not the only contradiction in which the\nProgressive government of Lula which internationally has\nassumed a leadership in the fight against change\nclimate. Environmentalists criticize harshly even\nhis choice to advance with oil explorations of\nPetrobras state giant at the mouths of the Amazon River.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Authorized a 13 km bretella in the middle of the protected forest",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Polemica",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amazon",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "13 km",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Inácio",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula da Silva",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "13 kilometers",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amazon",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Belém",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tupinambá",
                "start_char": 640,
                "end_char": 649,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 703,
                "end_char": 707,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cop",
                "start_char": 770,
                "end_char": 773,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 917,
                "end_char": 921,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Petrobras",
                "start_char": 1094,
                "end_char": 1103,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Polizia Gb amplia indagine sull'ospedale dell'infermiera killer",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:37:53 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/13/polizia-gb-amplia-indagine-sullospedale-dellinfermiera-killer_19b7b107-ad61-42bf-ae2f-21d1a4d32e27.html",
        "subtitle": "Sospetti di omicidio colposo e negligenza grave sui vertici",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La polizia britannica ha allargato\nle indagini sull'ospedale dove lavorava Lucy Letby, la\ncosiddetta infermiera killer al centro di un caso giudiziario\nche ha suscitato shock e polemiche a non finire nel Regno Unito:\nquello della \"strage di neonati\" - come ribattezzata dai media -\nperpetrata dalla donna\naddetta al reparto maternità, che avrebbe fatto morire\ndeliberatamente, secondo le accuse, almeno 7 neonati esposti a\nsovradosaggi fra il 2015 e il 2016 e tentato di ucciderne altri\nper ragioni rimaste in larga parte oscure in sede processuale.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   I vertici sanitari del Countess of Chester Hospital, nel nord\ndell'Inghilterra, erano già finiti sotto indagine nell'ottobre\n2023 per omicidio colposo a livello di organizzazione\nospedaliera, e da oggi lo sono anche per \"omicidio colposo\nderivante da negligenza grave\", come ha detto un portavoce della\npolizia del Cheshire. \"È importante notare che questo non ha\nalcun impatto sulle condanne di Lucy Letby per i molteplici\nreati di omicidio e tentato omicidio\", ha precisato il\nportavoce. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 74,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982417.942658,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.17",
        "en_title": "Police Gb expands investigation into the hospital of the killer nurse",
        "en_content": "The British police have widened\nthe hospital investigation where Lucy Letby worked, the\nso-called killer nurse at the center of a judicial case\nthat aroused shock and controversy not to end in the UK:\nthat of the \"baby massacre\" - as rebated by the media -\nperpetrated by the woman\nwho would have died\ndeliberately, according to the charges, at least 7 infants exposed to\noverdose between 2015 and 2016 and attempted to kill others\nfor reasons which remain largely obscure in the proceedings.\n\n\nThe Health Summits of the Countess of Chester Hospital, in the North\nof England, they were already under investigation in October\n2023 for manslaughter at organization level\nHospital, and from today I am also for \"silent murder\nresulting from serious negligence,\" said a spokesman for\nCheshire police. \"It is important to note that this has not\nno impact on Lucy Letby's convictions for the multiple\nmurder crimes and attempted murder,\" he said.\nspokesman.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Shocked murder suspects and serious negligence on tops",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lucy Letby",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least 7",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "between 2015 and 2016",
                "start_char": 381,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Health Summits",
                "start_char": 495,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Countess",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 529,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chester Hospital",
                "start_char": 533,
                "end_char": 549,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "North",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 563,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "England",
                "start_char": 567,
                "end_char": 574,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "October\n2023",
                "start_char": 617,
                "end_char": 629,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 693,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cheshire",
                "start_char": 780,
                "end_char": 788,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lucy Letby's",
                "start_char": 853,
                "end_char": 865,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Premier Groenlandia a Trump, 'adesso basta'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:55:37 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/13/premier-groenlandia-a-trump-adesso-basta_d47867c6-3aed-4f9a-acf6-22268f232a4c.html",
        "subtitle": "Egede annuncia che riunirà i leader dei partiti",
        "content": " \"Adesso basta\": il primo ministro uscente groenlandese Mute Egede ha annunciato in serata che riunirà i leader dei partiti \"il prima possibile\" in reazione alle parole di Donald Trump che ha ribadito il desiderio di annettere l'isola artica.     \"Questa volta dobbiamo rafforzare il nostro rifiuto delle parole di Trump. Non dobbiamo continuare a mancare di rispetto a noi stessi\", ha scritto su Facebook Egede, che continua a guidare il territorio ad interim in attesa della formazione di un nuovo governo dopo la sua sconfitta alle elezioni legislative di martedì. \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 76,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982418.0007513,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.18",
        "en_title": "Premier Greenland in Trump, 'just enough'",
        "en_content": "\"That's enough now.\" the outgoing Greenland Prime Minister Mute Egede announced in the evening that it will bring together the leaders of the parties \"as soon as possible\" in reaction to the words of Donald Trump who reiterated the desire to annex the Arctic island. \"This time we must strengthen our rejection of Trump's words. We must not continue to disrespect ourselves\", wrote on Facebook Egede, who continues to lead the interim territory waiting for the formation of a new government after his defeat in the legislative elections on Tuesday.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Egede announces that he will bring together party leaders",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mute Egede",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arctic",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Facebook Egede",
                "start_char": 385,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tuesday",
                "start_char": 540,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Brasile, la denuncia contro Bolsonaro arriva alla Corte suprema",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:38:30 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/brasile-la-denuncia-contro-bolsonaro-arriva-alla-corte-suprema_efd27ee2-1dc9-4836-8812-f38109fec291.html",
        "subtitle": "A decidere il giudice Alexandre de Moraes",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il giudice della Corte suprema\nbrasiliana (Stf), Alexandre de Moraes, ha trasmesso la denuncia\ncontro l'ex presidente Jair Bolsonaro ed altre sette persone per\nil loro coinvolgimento nel presunto golpe di oltre due anni fa,\nalla Prima sezione del massimo organo giuridico verde-oro. Lo\nriporta il sito all news Poder360.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Spetta ora al presidente della Prima sezione della Corte\nsuprema, Cristiano Zanin, ex avvocato difensore del presidente\nLula durante la Lava Jato, la Mani Pulite brasiliana, definire\nuna data per analizzare l'accusa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La decisione arriva lo stesso giorno in cui il procuratore\ngenerale del Brasile, Paulo Gonet, ha respinto le richieste\ndegli avvocati difensori di Bolsonaro e di altri 7 accusati,\nmantenendo la denuncia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Oltre a quella contro Bolsonaro, Moraes ha trasmesso alla\nPrima sezione della Corte suprema anche la denuncia contro\nAlexandre Ramagem, ex-direttore generale dell'Abin (l'agenzia di\nintelligence brasiliana), Almir Garnier, ex-comandante della\nMarina, Anderson Torres, ex-ministro della Giustizia, Augusto\nHeleno, ex-ministro del Gabinetto di Sicurezza istituzionale,\nMauro Cid, ex-aiutante di campo di Bolsonaro, Paulo Sérgio\nNogueira, ex-ministro della Difesa e Braga Netto, ex-ministro\ndella Casa Civile e candidato alla vicepresidenza nel 2022. \n   Con Zanin, gli altri 4 giudici della Prima sezione della\nCorte suprema che dovranno decidere se accettano o no la\ndenuncia, sono lo stesso Moraes, Cármen Lúcia, Luiz Fux e Flávio\nDino. Se la denuncia sarà accettata, gli otto accusati\ndiventeranno imputati in sede penale. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 71,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982418.008964,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.18",
        "en_title": "Brazil, the complaint against Bolsonaro arrives at the Supreme Court",
        "en_content": "The Supreme Court Judge\nBrazilian (Stf), Alexandre de Moraes, has transmitted the complaint\nagainst former president Jair Bolsonaro and seven other people for\ntheir involvement in the supposed coup over two years ago,\nto the first section of the maximum green-gold legal body. I do.\nreport the website to the news Poder360.\n\n\nIt is now up to the President of the First Chamber of the Court\nsupreme, Cristiano Zanin, former defender of the president\nLula during Lava Jato, the Brazilian Pulite Hands, define\na date to analyze the prosecution.\n\n\nThe decision comes the same day when the prosecutor\nGeneral of Brazil, Paulo Gonet, rejected requests\nof the defense attorneys of Bolsonaro and other 7 accused,\nmaintaining the complaint.\n\n\nIn addition to that against Bolsonaro, Moraes sent to\nFirst Chamber of the Supreme Court also the complaint against\nAlexandre Ramagem, former general manager of Abin (the agency of\nBrazilian intelligence), Almir Garnier, former commander of the\nMarina, Anderson Torres, former Minister of Justice, Augustus\nHeleno, former Minister of the Institutional Security Cabinet,\nMauro Cid, former field assistant of Bolsonaro, Paulo Sérgio\nNogueira, former Minister of Defense and Braga Netto, former Minister\nof the Civil House and candidate for vice president in 2022.\nWith Zanin, the other 4 judges of the First Chamber\nThe Court of Justice shall decide whether or not they accept\ncomplaint, are the same Moraes, Cármen Lúcia, Luiz Fux and Flávio\nDino. If the complaint is accepted, the eight accused\nThey'll be charged in the prosecution.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Judge Alexandre de Moraes",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jair Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two years ago",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the First Chamber of the Court",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cristiano Zanin",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lava Jato",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 470,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Brazilian Pulite Hands",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the same day",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 575,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 607,
                "end_char": 613,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paulo Gonet",
                "start_char": 615,
                "end_char": 626,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 674,
                "end_char": 683,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 694,
                "end_char": 695,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 771,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moraes",
                "start_char": 773,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "First Chamber of",
                "start_char": 788,
                "end_char": 804,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 805,
                "end_char": 822,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre Ramagem",
                "start_char": 850,
                "end_char": 867,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abin",
                "start_char": 895,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 915,
                "end_char": 924,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Almir Garnier",
                "start_char": 940,
                "end_char": 953,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marina",
                "start_char": 979,
                "end_char": 985,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anderson Torres",
                "start_char": 987,
                "end_char": 1002,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Justice",
                "start_char": 1023,
                "end_char": 1030,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Augustus\nHeleno",
                "start_char": 1032,
                "end_char": 1047,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Institutional Security Cabinet",
                "start_char": 1068,
                "end_char": 1102,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mauro Cid",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1113,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 1141,
                "end_char": 1150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paulo Sérgio",
                "start_char": 1152,
                "end_char": 1164,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nogueira",
                "start_char": 1165,
                "end_char": 1173,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Braga Netto",
                "start_char": 1206,
                "end_char": 1217,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Civil House",
                "start_char": 1238,
                "end_char": 1253,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2022",
                "start_char": 1290,
                "end_char": 1294,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanin",
                "start_char": 1301,
                "end_char": 1306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 1318,
                "end_char": 1319,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "First Chamber",
                "start_char": 1334,
                "end_char": 1347,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 1348,
                "end_char": 1368,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moraes",
                "start_char": 1433,
                "end_char": 1439,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cármen Lúcia",
                "start_char": 1441,
                "end_char": 1453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Fux",
                "start_char": 1455,
                "end_char": 1463,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Flávio",
                "start_char": 1468,
                "end_char": 1474,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 1515,
                "end_char": 1520,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Brasile, la denuncia contro Bolsonaro arriva alla Corte suprema",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:41:37 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/brasile-la-denuncia-contro-bolsonaro-arriva-alla-corte-suprema_589ad00c-6bb8-41c7-ab1a-6eea962ca7a3.html",
        "subtitle": "A decidere il giudice Alexandre de Moraes",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il giudice della Corte suprema\nbrasiliana (Stf), Alexandre de Moraes, ha trasmesso la denuncia\ncontro l'ex presidente Jair Bolsonaro ed altre sette persone per\nil loro coinvolgimento nel presunto golpe di oltre due anni fa,\nalla Prima sezione del massimo organo giuridico verde-oro. Lo\nriporta il sito all news Poder360.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Spetta ora al presidente della Prima sezione della Corte\nsuprema, Cristiano Zanin, ex avvocato difensore del presidente\nLula durante la Lava Jato, la Mani Pulite brasiliana, definire\nuna data per analizzare l'accusa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La decisione arriva lo stesso giorno in cui il procuratore\ngenerale del Brasile, Paulo Gonet, ha respinto le richieste\ndegli avvocati difensori di Bolsonaro e di altri 7 accusati,\nmantenendo la denuncia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Oltre a quella contro Bolsonaro, Moraes ha trasmesso alla\nPrima sezione della Corte suprema anche la denuncia contro\nAlexandre Ramagem, ex-direttore generale dell'Abin (l'agenzia di\nintelligence brasiliana), Almir Garnier, ex-comandante della\nMarina, Anderson Torres, ex-ministro della Giustizia, Augusto\nHeleno, ex-ministro del Gabinetto di Sicurezza istituzionale,\nMauro Cid, ex-aiutante di campo di Bolsonaro, Paulo Sérgio\nNogueira, ex-ministro della Difesa e Braga Netto, ex-ministro\ndella Casa Civile e candidato alla vicepresidenza nel 2022. \n   Con Zanin, gli altri 4 giudici della Prima sezione della\nCorte suprema che dovranno decidere se accettano o no la\ndenuncia, sono lo stesso Moraes, Cármen Lúcia, Luiz Fux e Flávio\nDino. Se la denuncia sarà accettata, gli otto accusati\ndiventeranno imputati in sede penale. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 70,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982418.034219,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.18",
        "en_title": "Brazil, the complaint against Bolsonaro arrives at the Supreme Court",
        "en_content": "The Supreme Court Judge\nBrazilian (Stf), Alexandre de Moraes, has transmitted the complaint\nagainst former president Jair Bolsonaro and seven other people for\ntheir involvement in the supposed coup over two years ago,\nto the first section of the maximum green-gold legal body. I do.\nreport the website to the news Poder360.\n\n\nIt is now up to the President of the First Chamber of the Court\nsupreme, Cristiano Zanin, former defender of the president\nLula during Lava Jato, the Brazilian Pulite Hands, define\na date to analyze the prosecution.\n\n\nThe decision comes the same day when the prosecutor\nGeneral of Brazil, Paulo Gonet, rejected requests\nof the defense attorneys of Bolsonaro and other 7 accused,\nmaintaining the complaint.\n\n\nIn addition to that against Bolsonaro, Moraes sent to\nFirst Chamber of the Supreme Court also the complaint against\nAlexandre Ramagem, former general manager of Abin (the agency of\nBrazilian intelligence), Almir Garnier, former commander of the\nMarina, Anderson Torres, former Minister of Justice, Augustus\nHeleno, former Minister of the Institutional Security Cabinet,\nMauro Cid, former field assistant of Bolsonaro, Paulo Sérgio\nNogueira, former Minister of Defense and Braga Netto, former Minister\nof the Civil House and candidate for vice president in 2022.\nWith Zanin, the other 4 judges of the First Chamber\nThe Court of Justice shall decide whether or not they accept\ncomplaint, are the same Moraes, Cármen Lúcia, Luiz Fux and Flávio\nDino. If the complaint is accepted, the eight accused\nThey'll be charged in the prosecution.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Judge Alexandre de Moraes",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre de Moraes",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jair Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two years ago",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the First Chamber of the Court",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cristiano Zanin",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lava Jato",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 470,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Brazilian Pulite Hands",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the same day",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 575,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 607,
                "end_char": 613,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paulo Gonet",
                "start_char": 615,
                "end_char": 626,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 674,
                "end_char": 683,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 694,
                "end_char": 695,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 771,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moraes",
                "start_char": 773,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "First Chamber of",
                "start_char": 788,
                "end_char": 804,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 805,
                "end_char": 822,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexandre Ramagem",
                "start_char": 850,
                "end_char": 867,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abin",
                "start_char": 895,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 915,
                "end_char": 924,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Almir Garnier",
                "start_char": 940,
                "end_char": 953,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Marina",
                "start_char": 979,
                "end_char": 985,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anderson Torres",
                "start_char": 987,
                "end_char": 1002,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Justice",
                "start_char": 1023,
                "end_char": 1030,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Augustus\nHeleno",
                "start_char": 1032,
                "end_char": 1047,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Institutional Security Cabinet",
                "start_char": 1068,
                "end_char": 1102,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mauro Cid",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1113,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolsonaro",
                "start_char": 1141,
                "end_char": 1150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paulo Sérgio",
                "start_char": 1152,
                "end_char": 1164,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nogueira",
                "start_char": 1165,
                "end_char": 1173,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Braga Netto",
                "start_char": 1206,
                "end_char": 1217,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Civil House",
                "start_char": 1238,
                "end_char": 1253,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2022",
                "start_char": 1290,
                "end_char": 1294,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zanin",
                "start_char": 1301,
                "end_char": 1306,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 1318,
                "end_char": 1319,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "First Chamber",
                "start_char": 1334,
                "end_char": 1347,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 1348,
                "end_char": 1368,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moraes",
                "start_char": 1433,
                "end_char": 1439,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cármen Lúcia",
                "start_char": 1441,
                "end_char": 1453,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Fux",
                "start_char": 1455,
                "end_char": 1463,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Flávio",
                "start_char": 1468,
                "end_char": 1474,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 1515,
                "end_char": 1520,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Intelligence Colombia, appartenenti ai gruppi armati sono 21.500",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:37:25 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-14",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/13/intelligence-colombia-appartenenti-ai-gruppi-armati-sono-21.500_f45fd457-c1c6-40e9-b28a-e47c5fdb8e05.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo rivela un rapporto delle agenzie dell'esercito",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Sono oltre 21.000 gli appartenenti\nai diversi gruppi armati che operano in Colombia come l'Esercito\ndi liberazione nazionale (Eln), i dissidenti delle Farc (Forze\narmate rivoluzionarie) e il Clan del Golfo, la principale\norganizzazione criminale del Paese. Lo riferisce il comandante\nin capo delle Forze Armate, l'ammiraglio Francisco Cubides,\nsulla base dell'ultimo rilevamento effettuato dall'intelligence\ndell'esercito.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Alla fine dell'anno scorso avevamo un gruppo di circa 20.000\nindividui armati e l'ultimo conteggio ci porta a 21.500\", ha\ndetto oggi Cubides in una conferenza stampa a Bogotà.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'ammiraglio ha precisato che le agenzie di intelligence\nconducono uno studio ogni sei mesi per contare il numero di\nmembri nei vari gruppi armati e ha osservato che dopo la\nsmobilitazione delle guerriglie delle Farc nel 2016, \"il numero\ndi combattenti si è notevolmente ridotto mentre sono aumentati i\nmembri dell'Eln e i dissidenti\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 72,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741982418.3924716,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-14 21:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-14T20.00.18",
        "en_title": "Intelligence Colombia, belonging to armed groups are 21,500",
        "en_content": "Over 21,000 members\nto the different armed groups operating in Colombia as the Army\nof national liberation (Eln), the dissidents of the Farc (Forze)\nrevolutionary armies) and the Gulf Clan, the main\ncriminal organization of the country. The commander reports it\nChief of the Armed Forces, Admiral Francisco Cubides,\non the basis of the last survey carried out by the intelligence\nof the army.\n\n\n\"At the end of last year we had a group of about 20,000\narmed individuals and the last count leads us to 21,500\", he has\nsaid today Cubides in a press conference in Bogota.\n\n\nThe admiral specified that intelligence agencies\nconduct a study every six months to count the number of\nmembers in the various armed groups and observed that after\ndemobilization of the Farc guerrillas in 2016, \"the number\nof fighters has greatly reduced while increased the\nmembers of the Eln and the dissidents.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "It reveals a report of military agencies",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Intelligence Colombia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "21,500",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Over 21,000",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Army",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Eln",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Farc",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Forze",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf Clan",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Armed Forces",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Francisco Cubides",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 314,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of last year",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "DATE",
