[
    {
        "title": "Elezioni in Sudafrica, secondo i sondaggi l'Anc è in calo",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 25 May 2024 15:10:59 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-25",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/05/25/elezioni-in-sudafrica-secondo-i-sondaggi-lanc-e-in-calo_861dd69b-c0cb-4fb1-82fb-17603331476d.html",
        "subtitle": "Elettori incerti a 4 giorni dal voto, prevista bassa affluenza",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Sudafrica si recherà\nalle urne tra quattro giorni per votare in una elezione\nnazionale che promette di essere la più combattuta e quella dal\nrisultato più incerto dalla fine dell'apartheid e dall'avvento\ndi Nelson Mandela, 30 anni fa. Un sondaggio della Social\nResearch Foundation (Srf) mostra che il sostegno all'African\nNational Congress (Anc), il partito al potere dall'avvento della\ndemocrazia, è in calo, mentre il maggiore partito di\nopposizione, Democratic Alliance (Da) e il nuovissimo partito\nguidato dal controverso ex presidente del paese Jacob Zuma,\nuMkhonto weSizwe (Mk) appaiono guadagnare punti a livello\nnazionale.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Se il guadagno del Da appare essere a livello nazionale,\nquello del partito 'cult' di Zuma, l'Mk, è concentrato, nei\nsondaggi, nella provincia di origine del leader, il KwaZulu\nNatal dove l'elettorato tende ad allinearsi con un partito\nincentrato sulla difesa dei diritti degli Zulu, etnia a cui\nappartiene anche Zuma, del loro re Misuzulu kaZwlethini e della\nterra considerata parte del regno.  \n   I sondaggi di Srf del 22 maggio davano una presunta affluenza\nalle urne del 60%, all'Anc il 40,8% dei consensi, al Da il 27,2%\ne al nuovissimo Mk il 13,3% dei consensi. Non poco, tenendo\nconto che un elemento chiave del manifesto dell'Mk è\nl'abolizione dello stato di diritto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    In tutto saranno 52 i simboli sulla scheda elettorale, e a\npochi giorni dal voto l'incertezza sui risultati è altissima.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 14,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716674431.1310186,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-26 00:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-26T00.00.31",
        "en_title": "South African elections, according to the polls the Anc is falling",
        "en_content": "South Africa will travel\nin four days to vote in an election\nnational that promises to be the most fought and the one from\nresult more uncertain from the end of apartheid and the advent\nby Nelson Mandela, 30 years ago. A Social Survey\nResearch Foundation (Srf) shows that support for Africa\nNational Congress (Anc), the party in power since the advent of\ndemocracy, is falling, while the major party\nopposition, Democratic Alliance (Da) and the brand new party\nled by the controversial former president of Jacob Zuma,\nuMkhonto weSizwe (Mk) appear to earn points at level\nnational.\n\n\nIf Da's gain appears to be nationally,\nthat of the 'cult' party of Zuma, the Mk, is concentrated, in\npolls, in the province of origin of the leader, the KwaZulu\nNatal where the electorate tends to align with a party\nfocused on the defence of the rights of the Zulu,\nalso belongs to Zuma, of their king Misuzulu kaZwlethini and of\nland considered part of the kingdom.\nThe Srf polls of May 22 gave an alleged turnout\nto the polls of 60%, to the Anc 40.8% of the consents, to the From 27.2%\nand the brand new Mk 13.3% of consents. Not little, holding\naccount that a key element of the Mk poster is\nthe abolition of the rule of law.\n\n\nThere will be 52 symbols on the ballot, and\na few days from the vote the uncertainty about the results is very high.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Uncertain voters 4 days after voting, expected low turnout",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "South African",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anc",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "4 days",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "South Africa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "four days",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nelson Mandela",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "30 years ago",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Social Survey\nResearch Foundation",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Africa",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "National Congress",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anc",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Democratic Alliance",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jacob Zuma",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Da",
                "start_char": 586,
                "end_char": 588,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zuma",
                "start_char": 650,
                "end_char": 654,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mk",
                "start_char": 660,
                "end_char": 662,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Natal",
                "start_char": 744,
                "end_char": 749,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zuma",
                "start_char": 865,
                "end_char": 869,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Misuzulu",
                "start_char": 885,
                "end_char": 893,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 22",
                "start_char": 967,
                "end_char": 973,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "60%",
                "start_char": 1014,
                "end_char": 1017,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Anc",
                "start_char": 1026,
                "end_char": 1029,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "40.8%",
                "start_char": 1030,
                "end_char": 1035,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "27.2%",
                "start_char": 1065,
                "end_char": 1070,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "13.3%",
                "start_char": 1092,
                "end_char": 1097,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Mk",
                "start_char": 1165,
                "end_char": 1167,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "52",
                "start_char": 1228,
                "end_char": 1230,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days",
                "start_char": 1258,
                "end_char": 1268,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Borrell, 'ordinanze della Corte dell'Aja sono vincolanti'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 25 May 2024 14:56:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-25",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/25/borrell-ordinanze-della-corte-dellaja-sono-vincolanti_eec89ea7-bc9d-4659-b20c-302215c2a047.html",
        "subtitle": "'Attuare pianamente quelle che ha comminato a Israele'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Prendiamo atto dell'ordine\ndella Corte Internazionale di Giustizia  a Israele nella causa\nintentata dal Sudafrica di fermare immediatamente l'offensiva\nmilitare nel governatorato di Rafah; mantenere aperto il valico\ndi Rafah per l'assistenza umanitaria; garantire l'accesso a\nqualsiasi organo investigativo incaricato dalle Nazioni Unite\nper indagare sulle accuse di genocidio; presentare alla Corte un\nrapporto su tutte le misure adottate per dare esecuzione alla\npresente ordinanza.\" Lo scrive su X l'Alto Rappresentante Ue per\nla Politica Estera Josep Borrell.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Le ordinanze della Corte internazionale di giustizia sono\nvincolanti per le parti e devono essere pienamente ed\neffettivamente attuate\", sottolinea. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 15,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716674431.436327,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-26 00:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-26T00.00.31",
        "en_title": "Borrell, 'orders of the Court of Hague are binding'",
        "en_content": "\"We acknowledge the order\nof the International Court of Justice in Israel\nintent by South Africa to stop the offensive immediately\nmilitary in the governorship of Rafah; keep the passage open\nby Rafah for humanitarian assistance; guarantee access to\nany investigative body appointed by the United Nations\nto investigate the charges of genocide; submit to the Court a\nreport on all measures taken to implement the\npresent order.\" X writes the High Representative Ue for\nForeign Policy Josep Borrell.\n\n\n\"The Orders of the International Court of Justice are\nbinding on the parties and must be fully and\nactually implemented,\" he points out.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Actuating slowly what he has committed to Israel'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Borrell",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Court of Hague",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the International Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Africa",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Nations",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Court",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Josep Borrell",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 497,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Orders of the International Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, 'nel megastore potrebbero esserci 200 persone'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 25 May 2024 16:29:29 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-25",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/25/zelensky-nel-megastore-potrebbero-esserci-200-persone_5d52bc78-7c6d-4d76-b234-da9f32d4041b.html",
        "subtitle": "'Se avessimo più anti-aerea tali raid sarebbero impossibili'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"La Russia ha inferto un altro duro\ncolpo alla nostra Kharkiv - su un ipermercato edile - sabato,\nproprio a metà giornata. Al momento si sa che nell'ipermercato\npotrebbero trovarsi più di 200 persone\". Lo scrive su Telegram\nVolodymyr Zelensky in merito all'attacco russo che ha colpito un\nmegastore di Kharkiv. \"Se l'Ucraina avesse abbastanza difesa\naerea e moderni aerei da combattimento, tali attacchi russi\nsarebbero semplicemente impossibili. Ed è per questo che ci\nrivolgiamo a tutti i leader, a tutti gli Stati: abbiamo bisogno\ndi un rafforzamento significativo della difesa aerea e di\ncapacità sufficienti per distruggere i russi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716674431.564021,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-26 00:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-26T00.00.31",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, 'in the megastore there could be 200 people'",
        "en_content": "\"Russia has infered another hard\nblow to our Kharkiv - on a building hypermarket - Saturday,\njust half a day. At the moment it is known that in hypermarket\ncould be more than 200 people.\" He writes about Telegram\nVolodymyr Zelensky about the Russian attack that hit a\nKharkiv megastore. \"If Ukraine had enough defense\nair and modern combat planes, such Russian attacks\nwould simply be impossible. And that's why\nWe address all leaders, to all states: we need\na significant strengthening of air defence and\nenough capacity to destroy the Russians.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'If we had more anti-aircraft such raids would be impossible'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "200",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "just half",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 200",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 537,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il presidente boliviano Arce andrà al Forum economico in Russia",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 25 May 2024 15:17:03 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-25",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/25/il-presidente-boliviano-arce-andra-al-forum-economico-in-russia_afd36588-4cd8-4e9b-87d3-3bc1739546db.html",
        "subtitle": "L'evento a San Pietroburgo con la partecipazione di Putin",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente boliviano Luis Arce\nha confermato la sua presenza al Forum economico internazionale\ndi San Pietroburgo, dal 5 all'8 giugno. Si legge in un post sui\nprofili social del ministero degli Esteri russo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il leader boliviano verrà sicuramente e sarà presente nella\nsessione plenaria\", dove sono previsti interventi del presidente\nVladimir Putin e del capo di Stato boliviano. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 13,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716674431.5821283,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-26 00:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-26T00.00.31",
        "en_title": "Bolivian President Arce will go to the Economic Forum in Russia",
        "en_content": "Bolivian President Luis Arce\nconfirmed its presence at the International Economic Forum\nfrom 5 to 8 June. Read in a post about\nsocial profiles of the Russian Foreign Ministry.\n\n\n\"The Bolivian leader will surely come and will be present in\nPlenary Session\", where the President\nVladimir Putin and the Bolivian Head of State.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The event in St. Petersburg with the participation of Putin",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bolivian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arce",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Economic Forum",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "St. Petersburg",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bolivian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luis Arce",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Economic Forum",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "5 to 8 June",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Foreign Ministry",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolivian",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Plenary Session",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolivian",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Lettonia, 'bene Stoltenberg, nessuna restrizione su armi'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 25 May 2024 20:30:32 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-25",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/25/lettonia-bene-stoltenberg-nessuna-restrizione-su-armi_b5dae4f3-6f5e-42b7-b8e9-72db1b297625.html",
        "subtitle": "'Concordiamo che siano usate per attaccare obiettivi in Russia'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"La Lettonia concorda pienamente\ncon il Segretario Generale della Nato sul fatto che il diritto\ndell'Ucraina all'autodifesa includa il diritto di attaccare\noggetti militari legittimi in Russia. Sosteniamo il Segretario\nGenerale Jens Stoltenberg per l'assenza di restrizioni sulle\narmi fornite all'Ucraina\". Lo ha dichiarato la ministra degli\nEsteri di Riga, Baiba Braze, su X. Le sue parole sono state\nrilanciate dalla portavoce della Nato, Farah Dakhlallah. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716674431.5953455,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-26 00:00:31",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-26T00.00.31",
        "en_title": "Latvia, 'good Stoltenberg, no restrictions on weapons'",
        "en_content": "\" Latvia fully agrees\nwith the Secretary General of NATO on the fact that the right\nof Ukraine to self-defense includes the right to attack\nlegitimate military objects in Russia. We support the Secretary\nGeneral Jens Stoltenberg for the absence of restrictions on\nweapons provided to Ukraine.\" The Minister of Foreign Affairs\nExterior of Riga, Baiba Braze, on X. His words were\nraised by NATO spokesman, Farah Dakhlallah.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'We agree that they are used to attack targets in Russia'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Latvia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Latvia",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jens Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 228,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riga",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Baiba Braze",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Farah Dakhlallah",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 420,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    }
]
