[
    {
        "title": "Lula elogia la Spagna per il riconoscimento della Palestina",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 19:57:10 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/23/lula-elogia-la-spagna-per-il-riconoscimento-della-palestina_6940e3f8-bf61-4160-a64b-95128d159dcc.html",
        "subtitle": "Decisione presa insieme anche a Norvegia e Irlanda",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente brasiliano Luiz\nInácio Lula da Silva  ha salutato oggi la decisione di Spagna,\nNorvegia e Irlanda di riconoscere lo Stato di Palestina.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"La decisione congiunta di Spagna, Norvegia e Irlanda di\nriconoscere la Palestina come stato - ha manifestato Lula\nattraverso i suoi social media - è storica per due ragioni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tRende giustizia alla richiesta di un intero popolo, riconosciuto\nda più di 140 paesi che sostengono il suo diritto\nall'autodeterminazione\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Inoltre questa decisione - ha aggiunto - avrà senza dubbio un\neffetto positivo a sostegno degli sforzi per la pace e la\nstabilità nella regione mediorientale\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Secondo il capo dello stato brasiliano che segue da vicino la\nsituazione in Medio Oriente dall'inizio della crisi lo scorso\nottobre, la pace in Medio Oriente \"ci sarà soltanto quando sarà\ngarantita l'esistenza di uno Stato palestinese indipendente\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Lula ha infine ricordato che \"il Brasile è stato uno dei\nprimi paesi dell'America Latina ad assumere questa posizione,\nquando nel 2010 ha riconosciuto lo Stato di Palestina nei\nconfini del 1967, che comprende la Striscia di Gaza e la\nCisgiordania, con Gerusalemme Est come capitale\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487225.1959622,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.25",
        "en_title": "Lula praises Spain for the recognition of Palestine",
        "en_content": "Brazilian President Luiz\nInácio Lula da Silva greeted today the decision of Spain,\nNorway and Ireland recognize the State of Palestine.\n\n\n\"The Joint Decision of Spain, Norway and Ireland\nrecognize Palestine as state - it has manifested Lula\nthrough its social media - it is historical for two reasons.\n\n\nIt makes justice to the request of a whole people, recognized\nfrom more than 140 countries supporting its right\nto self-determination.\"\n\n\nMoreover this decision - it has added - will undoubtedly have a\npositive effect in support of efforts for peace and\nstability in the Middle East region\".\n\n\nAccording to the head of the Brazilian state that closely follows the\nsituation in the Middle East from the beginning of the crisis last\nOctober, peace in the Middle East \"will be there only when it will be\nguaranteed the existence of an independent Palestinian state.\"\n\n\nLula finally remembered that \" Brazil was one of\nfirst Latin American countries to take this position,\nwhen in 2010 he recognized the State of Palestine in\n1967 borders, which includes the Gaza Strip and the\nWest Bank, with East Jerusalem as capital.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Decision taken together with Norway and Ireland",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz\nInácio Lula da Silva",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State of Palestine",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Joint Decision of Spain",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ireland",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 140",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 384,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 571,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 627,
                "end_char": 636,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 681,
                "end_char": 696,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "last\nOctober",
                "start_char": 730,
                "end_char": 742,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 753,
                "end_char": 768,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 848,
                "end_char": 859,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 870,
                "end_char": 874,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 901,
                "end_char": 907,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 912,
                "end_char": 915,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 919,
                "end_char": 924,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Latin American",
                "start_char": 925,
                "end_char": 939,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "2010",
                "start_char": 981,
                "end_char": 985,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State of Palestine",
                "start_char": 1000,
                "end_char": 1022,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1967",
                "start_char": 1026,
                "end_char": 1030,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 1055,
                "end_char": 1069,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West Bank",
                "start_char": 1078,
                "end_char": 1087,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "East Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 1094,
                "end_char": 1108,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 1127,
                "end_char": 1160,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev, abbattuto un aereo d'attacco russo Su-25 nel Donetsk",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 23:50:24 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/22/kiev-abbattuto-un-aereo-dattacco-russo-su-25-nel-donetsk_f866920d-18f2-464e-9e2f-cda52fc1587d.html",
        "subtitle": "'La situazione resta tesa a Pokrovsky, combattimenti in corso'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Lo Stato maggiore delle Forze armate\nucraine ha annunciato che le forze di difesa hanno abbattuto\noggi un aereo d'attacco russo Su-25 in direzione di Pokrovsky,\nnel Donetsk. Lo riferisce Ukrainska Pravda.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"In direzione Pokrovsky, il numero di attacchi è salito a 25.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIn particolare, il nemico sta cercando di penetrare nelle nostre\nformazioni di battaglia con gruppi ed equipaggiamenti d'assalto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLa situazione rimane tesa: sono ancora in corso combattimenti\",\nscrive lo Stato maggiore nel briefing serale aggiungendo che\n\"secondo i dati disponibili, i soldati ucraini hanno distrutto\nun aereo d'attacco russo Su-25\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 47,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.8313675,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Kiev, shot down a Russian attack plane Su-25 in Donetsk",
        "en_content": "The Major State of the Armed Forces\nUkrainian has announced that the defense forces have broken down\ntoday a Russian attack plane Su-25 in direction of Pokrovsky,\nin Donetsk. This is Ukrainska Pravda.\n\n\n\"In the direction of Pokrovsky, the number of attacks has risen to 25.\n\n\nIn particular, the enemy is trying to penetrate our\nBattle formations with assault groups and equipment.\n\n\nThe situation remains tense: they are still in progress,\"\nwrites the major state in the evening briefing adding that\n\"according to the available data, Ukrainian soldiers destroyed\na Russian attack plane Su-25.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'The situation remains tense in Pokrovsky, fighting in progress'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Su-25",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donetsk",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pokrovsky",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Major State",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Armed Forces\nUkrainian",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pokrovsky",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donetsk",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainska Pravda",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pokrovsky",
                "start_char": 224,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "25",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 565,
                "end_char": 572,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Su-25",
                "start_char": 586,
                "end_char": 591,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 599,
                "end_char": 632,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ucraina, Nyt: la Casa Bianca valuta l'uso di armi Usa in Russia",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 11:27:06 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/23/ucraina-nyt-la-casa-bianca-valuta-luso-di-armi-usa-in-russia_cee7c01c-b19c-4853-be2b-a40c49ae8159.html",
        "subtitle": "Pressioni del Dipartimento di Stato per far cadere tabù di Biden",
        "content": "Il divieto imposto all'Ucraina di usare armi americane per colpire in territorio russo inizia a vacillare. Su spinta del Dipartimento di Stato si è infatti avviato un intenso dibattitto all'interno della Casa Bianca sulla possibilità di far cadere il tabù imposto dal presidente Joe Biden fin dall'inizio della guerra.  Lo riporta il New York Times citando alcune fonti, secondo le quali sul divieto il segretario di Stato americano Antony Blinken ha cambiato idea dopo la sua recente visita a Kiev. Gli Stati Uniti stanno anche valutando l'ipotesi si addestrare le truppe ucraine all'interno del Paese in guerra con Mosca, anche se non è chiaro come potrebbero reagire se gli addestratori finissero sotto attacco. \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 46,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.858232,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Ukraine, Nyt: the White House evaluates the use of US weapons in Russia",
        "en_content": "The ban imposed on Ukraine to use American weapons to strike in Russian territory begins to wave. At the push of the State Department, an intense debate began within the White House on the possibility of dropping the tabooo imposed by President Joe Biden from the beginning of the war. This is reported by the New York Times citing some sources, according to which the American Secretary of State Antony Blinken changed his mind after his recent visit to Kiev. The United States is also evaluating the hypothesis to train Ukrainian troops within the country at war with Moscow, although it is unclear how they could react if trainers ended up under attack.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "State Department presses to drop Biden taboos",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nyt",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "State Department",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State Department",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the New York Times",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antony Blinken",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 576,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Messico, in cinque anni emigrazione salita del 57,8%",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 22:32:21 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/22/messico-in-cinque-anni-emigrazione-salita-del-578_980b1623-7c4a-4dbd-bf3a-ff824bf30c2f.html",
        "subtitle": "Secondo l'Indagine nazionale sulle dinamiche demografiche",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Istituto Nazionale di\nStatistica e Geografia (Inegi) ha riferito che tra agosto 2018 e\nsettembre 2023 sono emigrati un milione e 200mila messicani, una\ncifra che rappresenta un aumento del 57,8% (+459mila persone) se\nparagonata alle 760mila persone partite dal Paese nello stesso\nperiodo tra il 2013 e il 2018.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Secondo l'istituto, quasi tutti i messicani che hanno\nlasciato la propria terra in cerca di nuove opportunità hanno\ndeciso di recarsi negli Stati Uniti e due quinti delle persone\nche si sono trasferite lo hanno fatto senza alcun documento per\npoter lavorare o vivere all'estero.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    Nel presentare l'Indagine nazionale sulle dinamiche\ndemografiche 2023, l'Inegi ha precisato che del totale della\npopolazione emigrante stimata per il periodo 2018-2023, l'87,9%\nsi è diretta verso gli Stati Uniti; il 6% verso il Canada e\nl'1,3% verso la Spagna. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 48,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.8632717,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Mexico, in five years uphill migration of 57.8%",
        "en_content": "The National Institute of\nStatistics and Geography (Inegi) reported that between August 2018 and\nSeptember 2023 a million and 200 thousand Mexican emigrated, one\nfigure representing an increase of 57.8% (+459 thousand people) if\ncompared to 760 thousand people from the country in the same\nperiod between 2013 and 2018.\n\n\nAccording to the institute, almost all Mexicans who have\nleft their land in search of new opportunities have\ndecided to go to the United States and two-fifths of people\nthat they moved they did it without any document for\ncan work or live abroad.\n\n\nIn presenting the National Survey on Dynamics\nDemographics 2023, the Inegi has specified that of the total of\nemigration population estimated for the period 2018-2023, 87.9%\nhe headed to the United States; 6% towards Canada and\n1.3% towards Spain.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "According to the National Survey on Demographic Dynamics",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "five years",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "57.8%",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the National Survey on Demographic Dynamics",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The National Institute of\nStatistics and Geography",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Inegi",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "between August 2018",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "September 2023",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "a million and 200 thousand",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "57.8%",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 202,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "thousand",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "760 thousand",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 253,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "between 2013 and 2018",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexicans",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two-fifths",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Survey on Dynamics\nDemographics",
                "start_char": 585,
                "end_char": 629,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2023",
                "start_char": 630,
                "end_char": 634,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Inegi",
                "start_char": 640,
                "end_char": 645,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the period",
                "start_char": 717,
                "end_char": 727,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2018-2023",
                "start_char": 728,
                "end_char": 737,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "87.9%",
                "start_char": 739,
                "end_char": 744,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 758,
                "end_char": 775,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "6%",
                "start_char": 777,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 788,
                "end_char": 794,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.3%",
                "start_char": 799,
                "end_char": 803,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 812,
                "end_char": 817,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Obrador, 'Non vogliamo investimenti a qualsiasi costo'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 22 May 2024 22:12:07 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-22",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/22/obrador-non-vogliamo-investimenti-a-qualsiasi-costo_a157b311-e5d1-40bd-813b-7b2afef4d638.html",
        "subtitle": "Risposta a Blinken su un arbitrato nella Riviera Maya",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il governo messicano non\nvuole portare imprese nel Paese a qualsiasi costo e ancor meno\n\"quelle che vengono a distruggere il nostro territorio\", ha\naffermato il presidente Andrés Manuel Lopez Obrador rispondendo\nal segretario di Stato statunitense, Antony Blinken, che ieri\naveva dichiarato che un eventuale esproprio dei terreni della\nsocietà Vulcan Materials a Playa del Carmen, nella Riviera Maya,\n\"non è un buon modo per attrarre investimenti\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il presidente messicano ha negato che sia in corso\nun'espropriazione, anche se resta in vigore la chiusura della\ncava di calcare e del porto gestito dall'azienda.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Blinken è stato interrogato sulla questione durante\nun'audizione presso la commissione per le relazioni estere del\nSenato degli Stati Uniti, dove ha risposto che la situazione è\nsoggetta a una procedura arbitrale. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 49,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.8690293,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Obrador, 'We do not want investments at any cost'",
        "en_content": "The Mexican Government\nwants to bring business to the country at any cost and even less\n\"those who come to destroy our territory,\" he\nPresident Andrés Manuel Lopez Obrador responding\nto the US Secretary of State, Antony Blinken, who yesterday\nhad declared that a possible expropriation of land of\nVulcan Materials company in Playa del Carmen, on the Riviera Maya,\n\"It's not a good way to attract investments.\"\n\n\nThe Mexican President denied that it is in progress\nan expropriation, even if the closure of the\nlimestone quarry and port managed by the company.\n\n\nBlinken was questioned about the matter during\na hearing from the Committee on External Relations of the\nUnited States Senate, where he replied that the situation is\nsubject to an arbitration procedure.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Reply to Blinken on an arbitration in the Riviera Maya",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Obrador",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riviera",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrés Manuel Lopez Obrador",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antony Blinken",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vulcan Materials company",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Playa del Carmen",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Riviera",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 561,
                "end_char": 568,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Committee on External Relations",
                "start_char": 623,
                "end_char": 658,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 666,
                "end_char": 679,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Gaza, media: 8 morti in raid Israele su campo profughi Nuseirat",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 03:14:33 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/23/gaza-media-8-morti-in-raid-israele-su-campo-profughi-nuseirat_df45d984-5fc9-4ba0-8c56-82cfc60b076a.html",
        "subtitle": "Wafa: colpita una casa, le vittime quasi tutte donne e bambini",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'agenzia di stampa palestinese Wafa\nafferma che otto persone sono morte e diverse altre sono rimaste\nferite in un bombardamento israeliano che stanotte ha colpito\nuna casa del campo profughi di Nuseirat, nel centro della\nStriscia di Gaza.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La maggior parte delle vittime sono donne e bambini,\nspecifica la Wafa. E il bilancio potrebbe aumentare, riferiscono\nfonti mediche locali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Dal 7 ottobre nell'enclave palestinese ci sono stati almeno\n35.709 morti e 79.990 feriti, secondo il Ministero della Sanità\nlocale gestito dal movimento islamista Hamas. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 44,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.9323242,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Gaza, media: 8 deaths in raid Israel on refugee camp Nuseirat",
        "en_content": "Palestinian press agency Wafa\nstates that eight people have died and several others have remained\nwounds in an Israeli bombing that struck tonight\na house of the refugee camp of Nuseirat, in the center of\nGaza Strip.\n\n\nMost victims are women and children,\nspecifies the Wafa. And the budget could increase, report\nlocal medical sources.\n\n\nSince 7 October in the Palestinian enclave there have been at least\n35.709 dead and 79.990 injured, according to the Ministry of Health\nlocal managed by the Islamist movement Hamas.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Wafa: hit a house, victims almost all women and children",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nuseirat",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Wafa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wafa",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "eight",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nuseirat",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wafa",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "7 October",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "35.709",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 413,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "79.990",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Health",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamist",
                "start_char": 496,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 514,
                "end_char": 519,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ucraina, Nyt: la Casa Bianca valuta l'uso di armi Usa in Russia",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 02:05:38 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/23/ucraina-nyt-la-casa-bianca-valuta-luso-di-armi-usa-in-russia_21af1c71-c030-4006-83f5-ff32c19be315.html",
        "subtitle": "Pressioni del Dipartimento di Stato per far cadere tabù di Biden",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il divieto imposto all'Ucraina di\nusare armi americane per colpire in territorio russo inizia a\nvacillare. Su spinta del Dipartimento di Stato si è infatti\navviato un intenso dibattitto all'interno della Casa Bianca\nsulla possibilità di far cadere il tabù imposto dal presidente\nJoe Biden fin dall'inizio della guerra.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Lo riporta il New York Times citando alcune fonti, secondo le\nquali sul divieto il segretario di Stato americano Antony\nBlinken ha cambiato idea dopo la sua recente visita a Kiev. Gli\nStati Uniti stanno anche valutando l'ipotesi si addestrare le\ntruppe ucraine all'interno del Paese in guerra con Mosca, anche\nse non è chiaro come potrebbero reagire se gli addestratori\nfinissero sotto attacco. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 45,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.940942,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Ukraine, Nyt: the White House evaluates the use of US weapons in Russia",
        "en_content": "The ban imposed on Ukraine\nuse American weapons to strike in Russian territory begins\nI'm sorry. On the push of the State Department,\nstarted an intense debate within the White House\non the possibility of dropping the taboo imposed by the President\nJoe Biden from the beginning of the war.\n\n\nThe New York Times cites some sources, according to\nwhich on the ban the American Secretary of State Antony\nBlinken changed his mind after his recent visit to Kiev. The\nUnited States are also evaluating the hypothesis to train\nUkrainian troops within the country at war with Moscow, also\nif it is not clear how they could react if trainers\nThey ended up under attack.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "State Department presses to drop Biden taboos",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nyt",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "State Department",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State Department",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "White House",
                "start_char": 171,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The New York Times",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antony\nBlinken",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 407,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 474,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 567,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ecuador, dichiarato lo stato di emergenza in 7 province",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 06:35:57 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/23/ecuador-dichiarato-lo-stato-di-emergenza-in-7-province_ed5e77c7-b0b7-43be-b713-096793f7be75.html",
        "subtitle": "Prosegue la \"guerra\" del governo contro le gang della droga",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Ecuador ha dichiarato lo stato di\nemergenza in quasi un terzo delle sue province dopo un'ondata di\nviolenza nel contesto della \"guerra\" in corso da parte del\ngoverno contro le bande della droga.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  La misura, che consente lo spiegamento di soldati in strada, è\nstata annunciata per un periodo di 60 giorni in sette delle 24\nprovince del Paese sudamericano, secondo un decreto governativo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tGli stati di Guayas, El Oro, Santa Elena, Manabi, Los Rios,\nSucumbios e Orellana hanno assistito a un recente aumento di\n\"atti di violenza sistematica perpetrati da gruppi di violenza\norganizzata, organizzazioni terroristiche e individui\nbelligeranti non statali\", si legge nel provvedimento.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il presidente Daniel Noboa ha dichiarato lo stato di\nemergenza a gennaio dopo che un pericoloso boss del\nnarcotraffico - Jose Adolfo Macias, alias \"Fito\" - è fuggito dal\ncarcere di massima sicurezza. Mentre i gangster facevano\nesplodere autobombe, rapivano membri della polizia e uccidevano\ndiverse persone in risposta alla repressione promessa da Noboa,\nil presidente ha detto che il Paese è in uno stato di \"conflitto\narmato interno\" e ha ordinato all'esercito di \"neutralizzare\" 22\ngruppi criminali. Lo stato di emergenza è scaduto il mese\nscorso. Human Rights Watch ha esortato Noboa a cancellare lo\nstato di \"conflitto armato interno\" ancora in atto, affermando\nche ciò ha aperto la porta a violazioni dei diritti umani.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Per lungo tempo un rifugio pacifico stretto tra i principali\npaesi esportatori di cocaina - Colombia e Perù -, l'Ecuador ha\nvisto esplodere la violenza negli ultimi anni mentre bande\nrivali legate ai cartelli messicani e colombiani si contendono\nil controllo. Le guerre tra gang si sono svolte in gran parte\nnelle carceri del Paese, dove leader criminali come Fito\nesercitano un controllo immenso. Dal 2021 le battaglie hanno\nprovocato la morte di centinaia di detenuti, i cui corpi sono\nstati spesso ritrovati smembrati, decapitati o inceneriti.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 40,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.9497826,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Ecuador, state of emergency in 7 provinces",
        "en_content": "Ecuador declared the state of\nemergency in almost a third of its provinces after a wave of\nviolence in the context of the ongoing \"war\" by the\ngovernment against drug gangs.\n\n\nThe measure, which allows the explanation of soldiers in the street, is\nwas announced for a period of 60 days in seven of 24\nprovinces of the South American country, according to a government decree.\n\n\nThe states of Guayas, El Oro, Santa Elena, Manabi, Los Rios,\nSucumbios and Orellana have witnessed a recent increase in\n\"acts of systematic violence perpetrated by groups of violence\norganized, terrorist organizations and individuals\nnon-state belligerents,\" reads in the measure.\n\n\nPresident Daniel Noboa declared the state of\nemergency in January after a dangerous boss\nnarcotraffic - Jose Adolfo Macias, alias \"Fito\" - fled from\nmaximum security prison. While gangsters did\nExploding autobombes, kidnapping police members and killing\nseveral people in response to the repression promised by Noboa,\nthe president said that the country is in a state of \"conflict\nand ordered the army to \"neutralize\" 22\ncriminal groups. The state of emergency has expired the month\nLast. Human Rights Watch urged Noboa to cancel\nstate of \"internal armed conflict\" still in place, affirming\nwhich has opened the door to human rights violations.\n\n\nFor a long time a peaceful retreat between the main\ncocaine exporting countries - Colombia and Peru -, Ecuador has\nseen exploding violence in recent years as bands\nrivals tied to Mexican and Colombian cartels compete\ncontrol. The gang wars took place largely\nin the prisons of the country, where criminal leaders such as Fito\nThey exercise immense control. From 2021 the battles have\ncaused the death of hundreds of prisoners, whose bodies are\noften found dismembered, beheaded or incinerated.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The government's \"war\" against drug gangs continues",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "almost a third",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "60 days",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "24",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "South American",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guayas",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "El Oro",
                "start_char": 400,
                "end_char": 406,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santa Elena",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Manabi",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Los Rios",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sucumbios",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Orellana",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Daniel Noboa",
                "start_char": 671,
                "end_char": 683,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "January",
                "start_char": 719,
                "end_char": 726,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jose Adolfo Macias",
                "start_char": 765,
                "end_char": 783,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fito",
                "start_char": 792,
                "end_char": 796,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Noboa",
                "start_char": 972,
                "end_char": 977,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "22",
                "start_char": 1079,
                "end_char": 1081,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "month\nLast",
                "start_char": 1138,
                "end_char": 1148,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Human Rights Watch",
                "start_char": 1150,
                "end_char": 1168,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Noboa",
                "start_char": 1175,
                "end_char": 1180,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 1390,
                "end_char": 1398,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peru",
                "start_char": 1403,
                "end_char": 1407,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 1411,
                "end_char": 1418,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent years",
                "start_char": 1450,
                "end_char": 1462,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 1487,
                "end_char": 1494,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombian",
                "start_char": 1499,
                "end_char": 1508,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fito",
                "start_char": 1629,
                "end_char": 1633,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 1670,
                "end_char": 1674,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "hundreds",
                "start_char": 1712,
                "end_char": 1720,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Show di Milei, la folla canta contro Kirchner e Sanchez",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 03:33:15 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/23/show-di-milei-la-folla-canta-contro-kirchner-e-sanchez_457b3866-1905-4064-a83b-5ad70e871bce.html",
        "subtitle": "Insulti per il premier spagnolo e 'carcere' per l'ex presidente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Uno show organizzato dal\npresidente argentino Javier Milei per la presentazione del suo\nultimo libro ha vissuto il momento più caldo quando le circa\n8.000 persone accorse giovedì sera nel 'Luna Park' di Buenos\nAires hanno inneggiato dapprima al carcere per l'ex presidente\nCristina Kirchner e successivamente intonato canti contro il\npremier spagnolo Pedro Sanchez.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Due momenti che Milei ha accolto sorridendo con evidente\nsoddisfazione e che ha poi commentato con ironia. \"Canterei con\nvoi ma non posso per una questione di rispetto della divisione\ndei poteri\", ha detto il presidente argentino riguardo la\nrichiesta di vedere in prigione la sua principale avversaria\npolitica. \n   E quando i suoi sostenitori hanno intonato un coro di insulti\ncontro il premier spagnolo (\"Sanchez figlio di puttana\"), Milei\nha sorriso e fatto riferimento alle ore extra di lavoro che gli\ncosterà la circostanza alla ministra degli Esteri, Diana\nMondino, già alle prese con la crisi diplomatica con la Spagna\ninnescata da polemiche dichiarazioni del presidente argentino\npronunciate a Madrid.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Come promesso, lo show ha avuto inizio con la performance\nmusicale di Milei che ha cantato accompagnato da una band la\ncanzone 'Panic Show' del gruppo La Renga, diventato ormai un\nvero e proprio inno dei comizi del presidente argentino. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 43,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.9613488,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Show of Milei, the crowd sings against Kirchner and Sanchez",
        "en_content": "A show organized by\nArgentine President Javier Milei for the presentation of his\nlast book lived the hottest moment when about\n8,000 people flocked Thursday evening to the 'Luna Park' in Buenos\nBuenos Aires first launched the prison for former president\nCristina Kirchner and later sings against\nSpanish premier Pedro Sanchez.\n\n\nTwo moments that Milei greeted smiling with obvious\nsatisfaction and then commented with irony. \"I'd bet with\nyou but I cannot for a matter of respect for the division\nof the powers,\" said the Argentine President about\nrequest to see his main opponent in prison\npolitical.\nAnd when his supporters sang a chorus of insults\nagainst the Spanish premier (\"Sanchez son of a bitch\"), Milei\nhas smiled and referred to the extra hours of work that he\nwill cost the circumstance to the Foreign Minister, Diana\nMondino, already struggling with the diplomatic crisis with Spain\ntriggered by polemics statements of the Argentine President\npronounced in Madrid.\n\n\nAs promised, the show began with the performance\nmusic by Milei who sang accompanied by a band\nsong 'Panic Show' by La Renga group, now become a\nA true hymn of the committees of the Argentine President.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Spanish Premier and 'carcere' insults for former president",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kirchner",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanchez",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "8,000",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "evening",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luna Park'",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aires",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cristina Kirchner",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Sanchez",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Two",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 351,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 663,
                "end_char": 670,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanchez",
                "start_char": 681,
                "end_char": 688,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the extra hours",
                "start_char": 740,
                "end_char": 755,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Diana\nMondino",
                "start_char": 824,
                "end_char": 837,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 890,
                "end_char": 895,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 936,
                "end_char": 945,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 970,
                "end_char": 976,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 1038,
                "end_char": 1043,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "'Panic Show'",
                "start_char": 1080,
                "end_char": 1092,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "La Renga",
                "start_char": 1096,
                "end_char": 1104,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 1162,
                "end_char": 1171,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Messico: crolla tendone candidato presidente Maynez, 4 morti",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 06:45:16 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/23/messico-crolla-tendone-candidato-presidente-maynez-4-morti_6415fc5d-ada0-4074-be35-bec02f10e802.html",
        "subtitle": "'Io sto bene, alcuni membri del mio staff tra i 15 feriti'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Quattro persone sono\nmorte e altre 15 sono rimaste ferite nel nord del Messico per il\ncrollo di un tendone che aveva appena ospitato il candidato\npresidenziale Jorge Álvarez Máynez.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Sto bene e sono in contatto con le autorità per seguire\nl'evolversi di quanto accaduto: la cosa più importante in questo\nmomento è prendersi cura delle vittime dell'incidente\", ha\nscritto Maynez sul suo account X. Il crollo è avvenuto in comune\ndi San Pedro Garza, che fa parte dell'area metropolitana del\ncentro industriale di Monterrey, nello stato nordorientale\nmessicano di Nuevo Leon. Maynez ha aggiunto che alcuni membri\ndel suo staff feriti sono ricoverati in ospedale. \"Torno sulla\nscena per sostenere le vittime\", ha detto. Video trasmessi dai\nmedia locali mostrano il momento in cui uno schermo gigante è\ncrollato su Maynez e altri membri del partito di centrosinistra\nMovimiento Ciudadano, che sono riusciti a mettersi al riparo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tAltre immagini pubblicate su X mostrano persone che vengono\ntirate fuori da una pila di strutture in ferro. Da parte sua, il\ngovernatore Samuel García, ha chiarito che la regione sta\nattraversando temporali, forti venti e forti piogge. \"C'è stata\nuna disgrazia. Un forte vento ha fatto crollare un palco durante\nla chiusura della campagna elettorale qui a San Pedro\", ha\nspiegato in un video pubblicato sui suoi social network. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 39,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.9774303,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Mexico: President Maynez candidate collapses, 4 dead",
        "en_content": "Four people are\ndeath and 15 more were wounded in northern Mexico for\ncollapse of a tent that had just hosted the candidate\nPresidential Jorge Álvarez Máynez.\n\n\n\"I am well and I am in contact with the authorities to follow\nthe evolution of what happened: the most important thing in this\nmoment is taking care of the victims of the accident,\" he said.\nwritten Maynez on his X account. The collapse occurred in common\nby San Pedro Garza, which is part of the metropolitan area\nindustrial center of Monterrey, in the northeastern state\nMexican Nuevo Leon. Maynez added that some members\nof his wounded staff are hospitalized. \"Back to the\nscene to support the victims,\" he said. Video transmitted by\nLocal media show the moment a giant screen is\ncollapsed on Maynez and other members of the Central Left Party\nMovimiento Ciudadano, who managed to shelter.\n\n\nOther images published on X show people who come\nGet out of a pile of iron structures. For his part,\nGovernor Samuel García, made it clear that the region is\nthrough storms, strong winds and heavy rains. \"There was\na disgrace. A strong wind knocked down a stage during\nthe closing of the election campaign here in San Pedro\", has\nexplained in a video published on its social networks.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'I'm fine, some of my staff among the 15 wounded'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maynez",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Four",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jorge Álvarez Máynez",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maynez",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "San Pedro Garza",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monterrey",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 541,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maynez",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 560,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Maynez",
                "start_char": 757,
                "end_char": 763,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Central Left Party",
                "start_char": 785,
                "end_char": 807,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Movimiento Ciudadano",
                "start_char": 808,
                "end_char": 828,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Samuel García",
                "start_char": 966,
                "end_char": 979,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "San Pedro",
                "start_char": 1170,
                "end_char": 1179,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas: 'Il video delle soldatesse rapite è stato manipolato' ",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 12:59:27 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/23/hamas-il-video-delle-soldatesse-rapite-e-stato-manipolato-_edfb8381-44c2-42f8-b4b9-a559b9e4220f.html",
        "subtitle": "'Sono state trattate secondo l'etica della nostra resistenza'",
        "content": "Il video che mostra cinque soldatesse israeliane rapite da Hamas il 7 ottobre \"è stato manipolato e l'autenticità di ciò che contiene non può essere confermata\". A sostenerlo è Hamas che in una dichiarazione rilanciata da Al Jazeera ha affermato che \"le donne soldato sono state trattate secondo l'etica della nostra resistenza e non è stato dimostrato alcun maltrattamento nei confronti dei soldati in questa unità\". Secondo il gruppo, la clip fa parte della promozione di Israele di \"narrazioni falsificate\". Nel video, una delle frasi ripetute dai miliziani alle donne è \"cani, vi schiacceremo tutti\" e ancora \"siete belle sioniste\".  \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 38,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.9870481,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Hamas: 'The video of the raped pennies was manipulated'",
        "en_content": "The video showing five Israeli soldiers kidnapped by Hamas on October 7 \"was manipulated and the authenticity of what it contains cannot be confirmed\". To support it is Hamas that in a statement relaunched by Al Jazeera said that \"Women soldier were treated according to the ethics of our resistance and no mistreatment has been demonstrated against the soldiers in this unit\". According to the group, the clip is part of Israel's promotion of \" falsified narrations\". In the video, one of the phrases repeated by the militiamen to women is \"dog, we will crush all\" and still \"beautiful Zionists\".\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'They were treated according to the ethics of our resistance'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "five",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "October 7",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Al Jazeera",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 422,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 486,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zionists",
                "start_char": 587,
                "end_char": 595,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Taiwan dispiega sue forze per 'rispondere' a esercitazioni Cina",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 23 May 2024 03:39:25 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/05/23/taiwan-dispiega-sue-forze-per-rispondere-a-esercitazioni-cina_f95b4bc8-6ea4-48f2-89c4-196e689996aa.html",
        "subtitle": "\"Ci difendiamo\" dalle \"provocazioni irrazionali\" di Pechino",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Abbiamo inviato forze marittime,\naeree e terrestri per rispondere: per difendere la libertà, la\ndemocrazia e la sovranità\" di Taiwan, afferma Taipei dopo che la\nCina ha lanciato stamattina esercitazioni militari intorno\nall'isola. Taiwan ha quindi condannato le manovre di Pechino\ndefinendole \"provocazioni irrazionali\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 42,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716487229.9922194,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-23 20:00:29",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-23T20.00.29",
        "en_title": "Taiwan deploys its forces to 'respond' to exercises China",
        "en_content": "\"We sent maritime forces,\naerial and terrestrial to answer: to defend freedom,\ndemocracy and sovereignty\" of Taiwan, says Taipei after\nChina launched this morning military exercises around\nto the island. Taiwan then condemned Beijing's maneuvers\ncalling them \"irregular temptations.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "\"Let's defend ourselves\" from Beijing's \"irrational provocations\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taipei",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this morning",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 210,
