[
    {
        "title": "Marcia indietro decisiva di Trump sui gas serra",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:53:19 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/12/marcia-indietro-decisiva-di-trump-sui-gas-serra_0711c4c9-1a37-4cb6-8917-dcdc549cb60d.html",
        "subtitle": "L'Epa ritira una serie di norme contro l'inquinamento",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'amministrazione Trump ha\nannunciato una clamorosa marcia indietro sui gas serra, una\nmossa che minaccia di fare a pezzi le fondamenta delle leggi sul\nclima negli Stati Uniti. Lo riporta il New York Times.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'Environmental Protection Agency (Epa) ha, infatti,  ritirato\noggi una sostanziosa serie di norme sull'inquinamento dopo aver\ndichiarato l'intenzione di voler annullare la storica\nconclusione di uno studio del governo americano del 2009 secondo\ncui i gas che riscaldano il pianeta, come l'anidride carbonica,\nrappresentano una minaccia per la salute umana. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820470.9466012,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:10",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.10",
        "en_title": "Trump's decisive back march on greenhouse gases",
        "en_content": "The Trump administration has\nannounced a clamorous march back on greenhouse gases, a\nmove that threatens to tear apart the foundations of laws on\nclimate in the United States. The New York Times.\n\n\nThe Environmental Protection Agency (Epa) has, in fact, withdrawn\ntoday a substantial set of pollution standards after having\ndeclared the intention of wanting to cancel the historian\nconclusion of a study by the American government of 2009 according to\nwhich gases that heat the planet, like carbon dioxide,\nrepresent a threat to human health.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The EPA withdraws a series of rules against pollution",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EPA",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The New York Times",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Environmental Protection Agency",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Epa",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 269,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 411,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "2009",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Vasto attacco di droni russi sulle città ucraine, anche Kiev'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:37:24 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/12/vasto-attacco-di-droni-russi-sulle-citta-ucraine-anche-kiev_7414629f-2d0a-4ea1-9d41-e5b40d28b277.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo riferiscono i sindaci della capitale, di Kharkiv e Sumy",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Russia ha lanciato un attacco di\ndroni su Kiev, Kharkiv e Sumy. Lo riferiscono i rispettivi\nsindaci su Telegram citati dai media ucraini. In precedenza un\nmassiccio attacco di droni era stato lanciato anche contro la\ncittà di Dnipro.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il sindaco della capitale, Vitaly Klichko, ha affermato che\nle difese aeree sono in azione sulla sua città, mentre a Sumy le\nautorità locali hanno annunciato la morte di un uomo di 32 anni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'attacco arriva poche ore dopo l'intesa tra Usa e Ucraina su\nuna proposta di tregua di 30 giorni, che deve essere ora\nsottoposta alla Russia. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.5964737,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "'Vasto attack of Russian drones on Ukrainian cities, also Kiev'",
        "en_content": "Russia launched an attack\ndrones on Kiev, Kharkiv and Sumy. The respective\nmayors on Telegram quoted by Ukrainian media. Previously a\nmassive drone attack had also been launched against\nDnipro city.\n\n\nThe mayor of the capital, Vitaly Klichko, said that\nair defenses are in action on his city, while in Sumy the\nLocal authorities have announced the death of a 32-year-old man.\n\n\nThe attack arrives a few hours after the agreement between Usa and Ukraine on\na 30-day truce proposal, which must now be\nsubmitted to Russia.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The mayors of the capital, of Kharkiv and Sumy",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vasto",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sumy",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sumy",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dnipro",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vitaly Klichko",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sumy",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 306,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "32-year-old",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few hours",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "30-day",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 518,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Groenlandia, massiccio afflusso alle urne per le legislative",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:50:58 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/12/groenlandia-massiccio-afflusso-alle-urne-per-le-legislative_c2972dac-9066-4363-8645-33119eaccade.html",
        "subtitle": "Unico seggio elettorale allestito nella capitale Nuuk",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            (ANSA-AFP) - NUUK (GODTHÅB), 11 MAR - I quasi 60.000\ncittadini groenlandesi hanno votato in massa per le elezioni\nlegislative. Il voto è stato contraddistinto dalle dichiarazioni\ndi Donald Trump, che vuole l'isola artica con insistenza a volte\nminacciosa. La partecipazione al voto, secondo i funzionari\nelettorali, è stata alta nell'unico seggio elettorale di Nuuk,\nla capitale. Inizialmente previsto per le 20, l'orario di\nchiusura dei seggi è stato prolungato di mezz'ora per consentire\na tutti gli elettori in fila di esprimersi. I risultati sono\nattesi nelle prossime ore. (ANSA-AFP).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.644847,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Greenland, massive urn influx for legislation",
        "en_content": "(ANSA-AFP) - NUUK (GODTHÅB), 11 MAR - I almost 60,000\nGreenland citizens voted in mass for elections\nlaw. The vote was marked by the statements\nby Donald Trump, who wants the Arctic island with insistence sometimes\nthreatening. Participation in the vote, according to officials\nElectoral, she was high in the only election seat of Nuuk,\nthe capital. Initially planned for 20, the time of\nclosing of seats has been extended half an hour to allow\nto all voters in line to express themselves. The results are\nexpected in the next few hours. (ANSA-AFP).\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Unique electoral seat set up in the capital Nuuk",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nuuk",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "11",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "almost 60,000",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arctic",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nuuk",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "half an hour",
                "start_char": 423,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the next few hours",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il ministero dell'Istruzione Usa dimezza i suoi dipendenti",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:08:04 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/12/il-ministero-dellistruzione-usa-dimezza-i-suoi-dipendenti_03a59b33-b741-4353-afe1-9a36649205ef.html",
        "subtitle": "'Impegno per efficienza, risorse vadano a studenti e insegnanti'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Dipartimento dell'istruzione\nannuncia il licenziamento della metà del suo personale. \"La\nriduzione riflette l'impegno del Dipartimento dell'Istruzione\nper l'efficienza e per assicurare che le risorse siano dirette\nverso quello che veramente conta: gli studenti, i genitori e gli\ninsegnanti\", ha detto il segretario all'Istruzione Linda\nMcMahon. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.6505966,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "The US Department of Education halved its employees",
        "en_content": "The Department of Education\nannounces the dismissal of half of his staff. \"\nreduction reflects the commitment of the Department of Education\nfor efficiency and to ensure that resources are directed\nto what really matters: students, parents and\nteachers\", said the Secretary of Education Linda\nMcMahon.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Efficiency commitment, resources go to students and teachers'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The US Department of Education",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Department of Education",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "half",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Department of Education",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Education",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Linda\nMcMahon",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Siria, Usa favorevoli ad accordo tra nuovo governo e curdi",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 02:56:05 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/12/siria-usa-favorevoli-ad-accordo-tra-nuovo-governo-e-curdi_40da1477-3e13-424e-b057-ca63af11368a.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo ha detto il segretario di Stato Marco Rubio",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli Stati Unit accolgono con\nfavore un accordo tra il nuovo governo siriano e i curdi per\n\"integrare il nord-est in una Siria unificata\". Lo ha detto il\nsegretario di Stato Marco Rubio: \"Gli Stati Uniti ribadiscono il\nloro sostegno a una transizione politica - ha spiegato in una\ndichiarazione - che dimostri una governance credibile e non\nsettaria come la strada migliore per evitare ulteriori\nconflitti\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 55,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.6966858,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Syria, United States in favor of agreement between new government and Kurds",
        "en_content": "The United States welcomes with\nfavor an agreement between the new Syrian government and Kurds for\n\"integrating north-east into a unified Syria.\" He said that\nSecretary of State Marco Rubio: \"The United States reiterates\ntheir support for a political transition - he explained in a\nstatement - showing a credible governance and not\nsectarian as the best way to avoid further\nconflicts.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Secretary of State Marco Rubio said",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kurds",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco Rubio",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syrian",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kurds",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco Rubio",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Bolivia, lunghe code ai distributori per la mancanza di benzina",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 01:47:24 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/12/bolivia-lunghe-code-ai-distributori-per-la-mancanza-di-benzina_f64ba5f5-be0b-4fa2-8408-0e39a9ebd9a8.html",
        "subtitle": "Il governo non ha abbastanza liquidità in dollari per importarla",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La carenza di carburante sta\ncolpendo da due settimane la popolazione della Bolivia e, negli\nultimi giorni, sono aumentate le file di automobili e camion\nintorno alle stazioni di servizio. A Santa Cruz, la capitale\ndell'omonimo dipartimento nel sud del paese, le proteste per la\nmancanza di carburante hanno paralizzato oggi tre strade,\nsecondo quanto riporta il sito del quotidiano El Deber.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tImpossibile raggiungere da Santa Cruz le città di Yapacaní,\nConcepción e Puerto Suárez a causa di altrettanti blocchi\nstradali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tNon va meglio a La Paz, dove secondo quanto detto ai media\nlocali da Limbert Tancara, leader dell'associazione sindacale\nTransporte Libre, \"sfortunatamente, solo il 60% dei trasporti\npubblici è in servizio nella città di La Paz, mentre il restante\n40% è fermo per mancanza di benzina. Se questo continua, saranno\nil 40% in servizio e il 60% fermo\". In alcune zone della\nBolivia, riporta il sito Urgente.bo, le file oggi sono arrivare\na 2,5 km.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIeri, il ministro degli Idrocarburi della Bolivia, Alejandro\nGallardo, ha ammesso in una conferenza stampa che non può\nimportare la quantità sufficiente di diesel e benzina per\nsoddisfare la domanda locale perché non ha abbastanza liquidità\nin dollari. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 57,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.705564,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Bolivia, long queues to gas stations",
        "en_content": "Fuel shortage is\nstriking the population of Bolivia for two weeks and\nlast days, car and truck files have increased\naround service stations. In Santa Cruz, the capital\nof the homonymous department in the south of the country, the protests for the\nlack of fuel have paralyzed today three roads,\naccording to the site of the daily El Deber.\n\n\nIt is impossible to reach from Santa Cruz the cities of Yapacaní,\nConcepción and Puerto Suárez due to as many blocks\nroad.\n\n\nIt's no better at La Paz, where according to the media\nlocal from Limbert Tancara, leader of the trade union association\nTransport Libre, \"unfortunately, only 60% of transport\npublic is in service in the city of La Paz, while the remaining\n40% is stationary for lack of gasoline. If this continues, they will be\n40% in service and 60% still\". In some areas\nBolivia, reports the Urgente.bo site, the files are coming today\n2.5 km.\n\n\nYesterday, the Minister of Hydrocarbons of Bolivia, Alejandro\nGallardo, admitted in a press conference that cannot\nimport sufficient amount of diesel and petrol for\nsatisfy the local demand because it does not have enough liquidity\nin dollars.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The government has not enough liquidity in dollars to import it",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bolivia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bolivia",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two weeks",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "last days",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santa Cruz",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "El Deber",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Santa Cruz",
                "start_char": 372,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yapacaní",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Concepción",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Puerto Suárez",
                "start_char": 422,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Paz",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Limbert Tancara",
                "start_char": 532,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the trade union association\n",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 587,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Transport Libre",
                "start_char": 587,
                "end_char": 602,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "only 60%",
                "start_char": 620,
                "end_char": 628,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "La Paz",
                "start_char": 678,
                "end_char": 684,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "40%",
                "start_char": 706,
                "end_char": 709,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "40%",
                "start_char": 778,
                "end_char": 781,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "60%",
                "start_char": 797,
                "end_char": 800,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolivia",
                "start_char": 823,
                "end_char": 830,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Urgente.bo",
                "start_char": 844,
                "end_char": 854,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2.5 km",
                "start_char": 888,
                "end_char": 894,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yesterday",
                "start_char": 898,
                "end_char": 907,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolivia",
                "start_char": 941,
                "end_char": 948,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alejandro\nGallardo",
                "start_char": 950,
                "end_char": 968,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Venezuela, Maduro dona 180mila ettari ai Senza terra brasiliani",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 01:09:56 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/12/venezuela-maduro-dona-180mila-ettari-ai-senza-terra-brasiliani_fc3da391-e454-4c86-8d35-d3c0d8cabb4d.html",
        "subtitle": "Il progetto, annunciato a settembre, era di appena 10mila ettari",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Un progetto agricolo tra il\ngoverno di Nicolás Maduro e il Movimento dei Senza Terra del\nBrasile, l'Mst, occuperà 180.000 ettari dello stato di Bolívar,\nnel sud del Venezuela, invece dei 10.000 annunciati lo scorso\nsettembre dallo stesso presidente venezuelano. \"Giovedì (13\nmarzo) procederò a consegnare il 'conuco' (termine spagnolo che\nindica una porzione di terra che gli indios caraibici dedicavano\nal raccolto) più grande del paese, il progetto Patria Grande del\nSud, con 180.000 ettari, al Movimento Senza Terra del Brasile,\nall'Unione Comunale e alle forze contadine del Venezuela\", ha\ndetto Maduro durante il suo programma settimanale \"Con Maduro+\"\ntrasmesso dalla televisione di stato Vtv e diffuso su Youtube.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIl governo di Maduro promuove il conuco, il sistema di\nproduzione per il sostentamento familiare di origine indigena\nche combina vari coltivazioni su piccola scala. L'Mst, fondato\nnel 1984 e che unisce oltre 470.000 famiglie, gestisce 185\ncooperative e produce vari generi alimentari, mentre lotta da\noltre 40 anni per una vasta riforma agraria in Brasile.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIl progetto in Venezuela era stato annunciato lo scorso\nsettembre \"per promuovere il settore produttivo nel paese e\nrafforzare la sovranità alimentare\", è ubicato a La Vergareña,\nnello stato di Bolívar, e \"si sviluppa in collaborazione con i\nmovimenti contadini e indigeni, i 'comuneros' (i membri del\nmovimento sociale Unione Comunale) e gli enti ufficiali\nincaricati\", secondo quanto riferisce la statale Agencia\nVenezolana de Noticias, l'Avn. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.7272713,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Venezuela, Maduro gives 180,000 hectares to the Brazilian landless",
        "en_content": "An agricultural project between\nNicolás Maduro and the Earthless Movement\nBrazil, the Mst, will occupy 180.000 hectares of the state of Bolívar,\nin southern Venezuela, instead of the 10,000 announced last\nSeptember by the same Venezuelan president. \"Thursday (13\nMarch) I will proceed to deliver the 'conuco' (Spanish term that\nindicates a portion of land that the Caribbean Indians dedicated\nto the harvest) the largest of the country, the Great Home project\nSouth, with 180.000 hectares, to the Earthless Movement of Brazil,\nto the Municipal Union and to the peasant forces of Venezuela,\" he\nsaid Maduro during his weekly program \"Con Maduro+\"\nbroadcast by state television Vtv and broadcast on Youtube.\n\n\nThe government of Maduro promotes the conuco, the system of\nproduction for family support of indigenous origin\nthat combines various small-scale crops. The Mst, founded\nin 1984 and that unites more than 470.000 families, manages 185\ncooperatives and produces various food, while fighting from\nover 40 years for an extensive agricultural reform in Brazil.\n\n\nThe project in Venezuela was announced last\nSeptember \"to promote the productive sector in the country and\nstrengthen food sovereignty,\" is located in La Vergareña,\nin the state of Bolívar, and \" develops in collaboration with the\npeasant and indigenous movements, the 'comuneros' (members of the\nSocial movement Municipal Union) and official bodies\ncommissioned\", according to the state Agencia\nVenezolana de Noticias, Havana.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The project, announced in September, was just 10 thousand hectares",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maduro",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "180,000 hectares",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "September",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "10 thousand hectares",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nicolás Maduro",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "180.000 hectares",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolívar",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10,000",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "last\nSeptember",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "13\nMarch",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caribbean Indians",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Great Home",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 451,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "180.000 hectares",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Earthless Movement of Brazil",
                "start_char": 493,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Municipal Union",
                "start_char": 530,
                "end_char": 549,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 579,
                "end_char": 588,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maduro",
                "start_char": 599,
                "end_char": 605,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "weekly",
                "start_char": 617,
                "end_char": 623,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vtv",
                "start_char": 676,
                "end_char": 679,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Youtube",
                "start_char": 697,
                "end_char": 704,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Maduro",
                "start_char": 726,
                "end_char": 732,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mst",
                "start_char": 864,
                "end_char": 867,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1984",
                "start_char": 880,
                "end_char": 884,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 470.000",
                "start_char": 901,
                "end_char": 918,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "185",
                "start_char": 937,
                "end_char": 940,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "cooperatives",
                "start_char": 941,
                "end_char": 953,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "40 years",
                "start_char": 1006,
                "end_char": 1014,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 1055,
                "end_char": 1061,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 1080,
                "end_char": 1089,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last\nSeptember",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1118,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Vergareña",
                "start_char": 1216,
                "end_char": 1228,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolívar",
                "start_char": 1246,
                "end_char": 1253,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Social movement Municipal Union",
                "start_char": 1362,
                "end_char": 1393,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Agencia\nVenezolana de Noticias",
                "start_char": 1453,
                "end_char": 1483,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Havana",
                "start_char": 1485,
                "end_char": 1491,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Siria, Usa favorevoli ad accordo tra nuovo governo e curdi",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 02:56:02 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/12/siria-usa-favorevoli-ad-accordo-tra-nuovo-governo-e-curdi_f910ae8e-4c2b-4343-b3dd-311405ed9eca.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo ha detto il segretario di Stato Marco Rubio",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli Stati Unit accolgono con\nfavore un accordo tra il nuovo governo siriano e i curdi per\n\"integrare il nord-est in una Siria unificata\". Lo ha detto il\nsegretario di Stato Marco Rubio: \"Gli Stati Uniti ribadiscono il\nloro sostegno a una transizione politica - ha spiegato in una\ndichiarazione - che dimostri una governance credibile e non\nsettaria come la strada migliore per evitare ulteriori\nconflitti\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 54,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.734646,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Syria, United States in favor of agreement between new government and Kurds",
        "en_content": "The United States welcomes with\nfavor an agreement between the new Syrian government and Kurds for\n\"integrating north-east into a unified Syria.\" He said that\nSecretary of State Marco Rubio: \"The United States reiterates\ntheir support for a political transition - he explained in a\nstatement - showing a credible governance and not\nsectarian as the best way to avoid further\nconflicts.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Secretary of State Marco Rubio said",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kurds",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco Rubio",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syrian",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kurds",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marco Rubio",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Australia, 'i dazi Usa sono totalmente ingiustificati'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 01:51:59 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/oceania/2025/03/12/australia-i-dazi-usa-sono-totalmente-ingiustificati_fb4ab0b0-69cc-482a-a7a5-42a82e9da40a.html",
        "subtitle": "Premier Anthony Albanese: \"Questo non è un atto amichevole\"",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            (ANSA-AFP) - SIDNEY, 12 MAR - I dazi di Washington su acciaio\ne alluminio sono \"totalmente ingiustificati\". Lo ha affermato il\nprimo ministro australiano Anthony Albanese, dopo che non è\nriuscito a ottenere un'esenzione all'ultimo minuto. \"Questo non\nè un atto amichevole\", ha detto Albanese ai giornalisti dopo che\nla Casa Bianca ha infranto le speranze che l'Australia sarebbe\nstata esclusa dalle imposte generali del 25 per cento su acciaio\ne alluminio. (ANSA-AFP).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 56,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.7584798,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Australia, 'US duties are totally unjustified'",
        "en_content": "(ANSA-AFP) - SIDNEY, 12 MAR - Washington steel duties\nand aluminum are \"totally unjustified\". He said that\nAustralian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese, after\nmanaged to get a last-minute exemption. \"This is not\nis a friendly act\", said Albanese to journalists after\nthe White House has broken the hopes that Australia would be\nwas excluded from general taxes of 25 percent on steel\nand aluminum. (ANSA-AFP).\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Premier Anthony Albanese: \"This is not a friendly act\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Anthony Albanese",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "12",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "MAR - Washington",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Australian",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anthony Albanese",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "last-minute",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Albanese",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 307,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25 percent",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa, entrati in vigore i dazi al 25% su acciaio e alluminio",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 05:23:47 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/12/usa-entrati-in-vigore-i-dazi-al-25-su-acciaio-e-alluminio_83b9b0db-a68c-4302-bab0-c5812c584914.html",
        "subtitle": "Voluti da Donald Trump",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            I dazi doganali del 25% su\nacciaio e alluminio, voluti da Donald Trump, sono entrati in\nvigore segnando una nuova fase nella guerra commerciale tra gli\nStati Uniti e i suoi principali partner commerciali. Il\npresidente americano aveva già tassato le importazioni di\nacciaio e alluminio durante il suo primo mandato (2017-2021), ma\nquesta nuova tassa intende essere \"senza eccezioni e senza\nesenzioni\", ha assicurato Trump durante l'annuncio all'inizio di\nfebbraio. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 51,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.7663562,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "US, 25% duties entered into force on steel and aluminium",
        "en_content": "Customs duties of 25% on\nsteel and aluminum, wanted by Donald Trump, entered into\nvigor marking a new phase in the trade war between\nUnited States and its main trading partners. The\nAmerican President had already taxed imports\nsteel and aluminium during its first term (2017-2021), but\nthis new tax means to be \"without exception and without\nexemptions,\" Trump assured during the announcement at the beginning of\nFebruary.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Wanted by Donald Trump",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Customs",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2017-2021",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "February",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 421,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Elezioni in Groenlandia, vince l'opposizione di centrodestra",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 05:08:04 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/12/elezioni-in-groenlandia-vince-lopposizione-di-centrodestra_c5da07bd-b3e3-4ca7-9a99-839d4918e100.html",
        "subtitle": "Crollo per i partiti del governo uscente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'opposizione di centrodestra ha\nvinto le elezioni legislative in Groenlandia. Lo ha riferito il\ncanale pubblico groenlandese Knr. Il voto  è stato\ncontraddistinto da un'ondata di nazionalismo per chiedere che\nl'isola artica, ambita da Donald Trump, raggiunga rapidamente\nl'indipendenza. Il voto ha premiato il partito democratico,\nformazione \"social-liberale\", con oltre il 30% dei voti. Bene\nanche i nazionalisti di Naleraq con il 23%. Netto calo infine\nper i partiti del governo uscente: gli ambientalisti di sinistra\ndi Inuit Ataqatigiit sono al 21 (-15 % rispetto al 2021) e i\nsocialdemocratici di Siumut al 15% (-14%). \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 52,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.7760742,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Elections in Greenland, wins centerright opposition",
        "en_content": "The center-right opposition has\nwon the legislative elections in Greenland. He reported it\nGreenland public channel Knr. The vote was\nmarked by a wave of nationalism to ask that\nthe Arctic island, sought after by Donald Trump, quickly reach\nindependence. The vote has rewarded the democratic party,\n\"social-liberal\" training, with over 30% of the votes. Good.\nalso the nationalists of Naleraq with 23%. Net decrease finally\nfor outgoing government parties: left environmentalists\nby Inuit Ataqatigiit are at 21 (-15 % compared to 2021) and\nSocial-Democrats of Siumut to 15% (-14%).\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "collapse for outgoing government parties",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greenland",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Knr",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arctic",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the democratic party",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "over 30%",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Naleraq",
                "start_char": 385,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "23%",
                "start_char": 398,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Inuit Ataqatigiit",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "21",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "-15 %",
                "start_char": 512,
                "end_char": 517,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "2021",
                "start_char": 530,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Social-Democrats",
                "start_char": 540,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Siumut",
                "start_char": 560,
                "end_char": 566,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "15%",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Anp condanna Hamas per contatti con Usa su futuro di Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:48:24 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/12/anp-condanna-hamas-per-contatti-con-usa-su-futuro-di-gaza_f300db5b-d4ed-4cef-997d-daa15692b4f9.html",
        "subtitle": "'Gruppo consegni Striscia all'Autorità nazionale palestinese'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Autorità nazionale palestinese\ncondanna Hamas per aver avviato trattative con gli Stati Uniti\nsul futuro di Gaza, affermando che ciò danneggia l'unità\npalestinese e viola la legge contro le comunicazioni con\nsoggetti stranieri.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In una dichiarazione ufficiale rilasciata alla Wafa, il\nportavoce del presidente Abu Mazen, ha affermato che i colloqui\naggirano e \"indeboliscono\" il consenso arabo a favore del piano\negiziano per la  Gaza nel dopoguerra. Il portavoce presidenziale\nha invitato Hamas a porre fine alla divisione intra-palestinese\ne a consegnare la Striscia di Gaza all'Autorità nazionale\npalestinese. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 48,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.7845726,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Anp condemns Hamas for contacts with the US on the future of Gaza",
        "en_content": "The Palestinian National Authority\nHamas condemnation for starting negotiations with the United States\non the future of Gaza, stating that this damages unity\nPalestinian and violates the law against communications with\nforeign subjects.\n\n\nIn an official statement issued to Wafa, the\nPresident Abu Mazen spokesman, said that talks\nbypassing and \"indebted\" Arabic consent for the plan\nEgyptian for Gaza in the post-war period. Presidential spokesman\ninvited Hamas to end the intra-Palestinian division\nand deliver the Gaza Strip to the National Authority\nPalestinian.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Group consegni Striscia all'Palestinian National Authority'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "National Authority'",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Palestinian National Authority",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wafa",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 278,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Abu Mazen",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arabic",
                "start_char": 356,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egyptian",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "intra-Palestinian",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 491,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "National Authority",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Nyt, Musk valuta donazione da 100 milioni a gruppi di Trump",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 01:23:07 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/12/nyt-musk-valuta-donazione-da-100-milioni-a-gruppi-di-trump_159a3b42-4e95-434f-bfcb-58e61175747e.html",
        "subtitle": "Fondi direttamente alle operazioni politiche del presidente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Elon Musk ha segnalato ai\nconsiglieri di Donald Trump di voler donare 100 milioni di\ndollari ai gruppi che controllano le operazioni politiche del\npresidente. Lo riporta il New York Times citando alcune fonti,\nsecondo le quali i fondi di Musk andrebbero al super pac Make\nAmerica Great Again e alla no profit Securing American\nGreatness. Non è comunque escluso che lo staff di Trump possa\ncreare una nuva entità. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.794692,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Nyt, Musk assesses donation from 100 million to Trump groups",
        "en_content": "Elon Musk reported to\nDonald Trump advisers want to donate 100 million\ndollars to groups controlling political operations\nPresident. The New York Times cites some sources,\naccording to which Musk's funds would go to the super pac Make\nAmerica Great Again and the no profit Securing American\nGreatness. However, Trump's staff may not be excluded.\ncreate a new entity.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Funds directly to the president's political operations",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nyt",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Musk",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "100 million",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Elon Musk",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "100 million\ndollars",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "The New York Times",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Musk",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Cina, tutte le misure necessarie dopo gli ultimi dazi Usa",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 08:48:51 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2025/03/12/cina-tutte-le-misure-necessarie-dopo-gli-ultimi-dazi-usa_2e4f8539-c489-4199-9cf8-78c3d2c8c24d.html",
        "subtitle": "Colpito al 25% l'import di acciaio e alluminio negli Stati Uniti",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Cina \"prenderà tutte le misure\nnecessarie a tutela dei suoi interessi e diritti legttimi\" in\nrisposta all'entrata in vigore dei dazi su acciaio e alluminio\nal 25% voluti da Donald Trump.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Se gli Usa insistono nel voler sopprimere la Cina, allora\ndovremo rispondere in modo risoluto\", ha ammonito la portavoce\ndel ministero degli Esteri Mao Ning, nel corso del briefing\nquotidiano. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 47,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.8131578,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "China, all necessary measures after the last US duties",
        "en_content": "China \"will take all measures\nnecessary to protect its interests and legal rights\" in\nresponse to the entry into force of duties on steel and aluminium\n25% wanted by Donald Trump.\n\n\n\"If the US insists on suppressing China, then\nwe will have to respond resolutely,\" the spokesman warned\nof the Ministry of Foreign Affairs Mao Ning, during the briefing\ndaily.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Shot at 25% steel and aluminum import in the United States",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Foreign Affairs",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mao Ning",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Colloquio telefonico tra capi Cia e intelligence russa",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:45:05 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/12/colloquio-telefonico-tra-capi-cia-e-intelligence-russa_bea3f120-6677-4153-b7f3-65f776c5485b.html",
        "subtitle": "Contatti regolari per contribuire a sicurezza internazionale",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il capo della Cia, John Ratcliffe, e\nquello dell'intelligence esterna russa (Svr), Serghei Naryshkin,\nhanno avuto un colloquio telefonico durante il quale hanno\nconcordato di mantenere \"contatti regolari\" tra loro \"allo scopo\ndi contribuire a garantire la stabilità e la sicurezza\ninternazionale, nonché a ridurre lo scontro nei rapporti tra\nMosca e Washington\". Lo riferisce l'Svr in un comunicato ripreso\ndall'agenzia Tass. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 49,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.8190684,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "Telephone Colloquium between CIA leaders and Russian intelligence",
        "en_content": "The head of the CIA, John Ratcliffe, and\nthe Russian outer intelligence (Svr), Serghei Naryshkin,\nthey had a telephone interview during which they had\nagreed to maintain \"regular contacts\" between them \"for the purpose\nto help ensure stability and security\ninternational, as well as reducing the clash in relations between\nMoscow and Washington.\" The Svr reports it in a press release\nfrom the Tass agency.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Regular contacts to contribute to international security",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CIA",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "CIA",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "John Ratcliffe",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Serghei Naryshkin",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 344,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Svr",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Dazi Usa, Ue annuncia una risposta 'forte ma proporzionata'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:05:11 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/12/dazi-usa-ue-annuncia-una-risposta-forte-ma-proporzionata_964afa20-81bf-422a-881b-b10ebdb057ed.html",
        "subtitle": "\"Profondo rammarico per le misure decise da Trump\"",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Commissione europea ha\nannunciato che applicherà dazi doganali \"forti ma proporzionati\"\nsu una serie di prodotti americani a partire dal primo aprile,\nin risposta alle tasse statunitensi del 25% su acciaio e\nalluminio. L'Unione europea \"si rammarica profondamente\" delle\nmisure decise dal presidente Donald Trump, ha affermato in una\nnota la presidente della Commissione Ursula von der Leyen.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 50,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741820473.8435895,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-13 00:01:13",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-12T23.01.13",
        "en_title": "US Dazi, EU announces a 'strong but proportioned' answer",
        "en_content": "The European Commission has\nannounced that it will apply customs duties \"strong but proportioned\"\non a series of American products from April 1,\nin response to US taxes of 25% on steel and\naluminium. The European Union \"is deeply regretted\"\nmeasures decided by President Donald Trump, said in a\nThe President of the Commission Ursula von der Leyen noted.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "\"Repressive background for Trump's measurements\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US Dazi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The European Commission",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "April 1",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "The European Union",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Media, 'Mosca scettica su cessate il fuoco, servono garanzie'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:03:19 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/12/media-mosca-scettica-su-cessate-il-fuoco-servono-garanzie_0baac021-25b8-4c3f-a99e-19ecd62d6171.html",
        "subtitle": "'Putin ora in vantaggio su terreno'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            C'è cautela mista a scetticismo a\nMosca rispetto alla proposta di una tregua di 30 giorni uscita\nieri dai colloqui di Gedda. Fonti russe hanno detto a Reuters,\ncome appare sul sito dell'agenzia, che qualsiasi accordo per\nporre fine alla guerra in Ucraina dovrà tenere conto dei\nprogressi russi e rispondere alle preoccupazioni di Mosca. Una\nfonte russa di alto livello ha dichiarato che Vladimir Putin\navrebbe difficoltà ad accettare l'idea del cessate il fuoco\nsenza discutere i termini e ottenere qualche tipo di garanzia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Putin ha una posizione forte perché la Russia sta avanzando\",\nspiega la fonte russa. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 43,
