[
    {
        "title": "Biden, sostengo le proteste non violente su Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 19 May 2024 19:27:45 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/19/biden-sostengo-le-proteste-non-violente-su-gaza_0f0ceb80-15ff-44b0-86d3-565491a32f21.html",
        "subtitle": "Presidente, 'lavoro per una pace durevole in Medio Oriente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Affrontando il tema delle\nmanifestazioni nei campus americani a favore della Palestina, il\npresidente Usa Joe Biden ha detto di sostenere \"le proteste non\nviolente\" nel suo discorso alla cerimonia di laurea al Morehouse\nCollege di Atlanta. Nel suo intervento, Biden ha detto che sta\nlavorando \"per una pace durevole\" in Medio Oriente e che\n\"l'unica soluzione è quella dei due Stati\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716145230.3413012,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-19 21:00:30",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-19T21.00.30",
        "en_title": "Biden, I support non-violent protests on Gaza",
        "en_content": "Addressing the theme of\ndemonstrations on American campuses in favor of Palestine, the\nUS president Joe Biden said to support \"the protests not\n\"in his speech at the graduation ceremony at Morehouse\nCollege of Atlanta. In his speech, Biden said that he was\nworking \"for lasting peace\" in the Middle East and that\n\"the only solution is that of the two States.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "President, 'work for lasting peace in the Middle East",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Morehouse\nCollege of Atlanta",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the two States",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Biden, sostengo le proteste non violente su Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 19 May 2024 19:27:48 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/19/biden-sostengo-le-proteste-non-violente-su-gaza_8615d5f7-529a-414e-85fe-b296fa75e8f8.html",
        "subtitle": "Presidente, 'lavoro per una pace durevole in Medio Oriente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Affrontando il tema delle\nmanifestazioni nei campus americani a favore della Palestina, il\npresidente Usa Joe Biden ha detto di sostenere \"le proteste non\nviolente\" nel suo discorso alla cerimonia di laurea al Morehouse\nCollege di Atlanta. Nel suo intervento, Biden ha detto che sta\nlavorando \"per una pace durevole\" in Medio Oriente e che\n\"l'unica soluzione è quella dei due Stati\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716145230.4422998,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-19 21:00:30",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-19T21.00.30",
        "en_title": "Biden, I support non-violent protests on Gaza",
        "en_content": "Addressing the theme of\ndemonstrations on American campuses in favor of Palestine, the\nUS president Joe Biden said to support \"the protests not\n\"in his speech at the graduation ceremony at Morehouse\nCollege of Atlanta. In his speech, Biden said that he was\nworking \"for lasting peace\" in the Middle East and that\n\"the only solution is that of the two States.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "President, 'work for lasting peace in the Middle East",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Morehouse\nCollege of Atlanta",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the two States",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Khamenei, speriamo che Raisi torni, non ci saranno vuoti'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 19 May 2024 19:44:34 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/19/khamenei-speriamo-che-raisi-torni-non-ci-saranno-vuoti_15b11eba-4ce8-4974-a065-0895ca803ed2.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo riporta Al Jazeera",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il leader supremo dell'Iran,\nl'Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, ha espresso preoccupazione per\nl'elicottero scomparso in un incontro pubblico. Lo riporta Al\nJazeera. \"Speriamo che Dio riporti l'onorevole presidente e i\nsuoi compagni tra le braccia della nazione - ha detto - Tutti\ndevono pregare per la salute di questo gruppo di dipendenti\npubblici. La nazione iraniana non deve essere preoccupata, non\nci saranno interruzioni nel lavoro del Paese\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716145230.5756586,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-19 21:00:30",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-19T21.00.30",
        "en_title": "'Khamenei, we hope that Raisi will return, there will be no voids'",
        "en_content": "The supreme leader of Iran,\nAyatollah Ali Khamenei, expressed concern for\nthe helicopter disappeared in a public meeting. It's Al.\nJazeera. \"We hope that God will bring the honourable President and the\nhis companions in the arms of the nation - he said - All\nmust pray for the health of this group of employees\npublic. The Iranian nation must not be concerned, not\nthere will be interruptions in the work of the country.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Al Jazeera reports it",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Al Jazeera",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ayatollah Ali Khamenei",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jazeera",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 460,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Israele, no comment su incidente di Raisi, non coinvolti'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 19 May 2024 20:08:42 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/19/israele-no-comment-su-incidente-di-raisi-non-coinvolti_c4e6e5a7-d75d-46bc-a865-a161e28fe80b.html",
        "subtitle": "Ynet, 'nessuna conseguenza su rispettive politiche'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Alti funzionari a Gerusalemme -\nriferiti dal sito di Ynet - non hanno fatto alcun commento\nsull'incidente che coinvolge il presidente iraniano Ebrahim\nRaisi. Ed hanno chiarito ufficiosamente che Israele non ha nulla\na che fare o sia coinvolta nell'incidente, che, secondo i\nrapporti, è stato causato dalle dure condizioni meteorologiche.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  I funzionari hanno aggiunto che l'eventuale morte di Raisi e\ndel suo ministro degli Esteri Hossein Amir Abdullahian \"non\ndovrebbe avere alcuna conseguenza per Israele, né per la\npolitica della Repubblica islamica nei confronti\" di Israele.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716145230.6226718,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-19 21:00:30",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-19T21.00.30",
        "en_title": "'Israel, no comment on Raisi incident, not involved'",
        "en_content": "High officials in Jerusalem -\nreported by the Ynet site - have not made any comments\non the incident involving Iranian President Ebrahim\nRaisi. And they have unofficially clarified that Israel has nothing\nto deal with or is involved in the accident, which, according to the\nreports, it was caused by harsh weather conditions.\n\n\nOfficials added that the possible death of Raisi and\nof his Foreign Minister Hossein Amir Abdullahian \"not\nshould have no consequence for Israel, nor for\npolicy of the Islamic Republic against Israel.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Ynet, 'no consequence on respective policies'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ynet",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Jerusalem",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ynet",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ebrahim\nRaisi",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Raisi",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hossein Amir Abdullahian",
                "start_char": 405,
                "end_char": 429,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 466,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Islamic Republic",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 512,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Taiwan rafforza pattuglie alla vigilia dell'insediamento di Lai",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 19 May 2024 19:35:47 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/05/19/taiwan-rafforza-pattuglie-alla-vigilia-dellinsediamento-di-lai_a4d7882b-118c-4aef-aa48-aa7dbe780c32.html",
        "subtitle": "Nel mirino le isole Kinmen, Matsu e Penghu di fronte alla Cina",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La guardia costiera taiwanese ha\ninviato le sue unità in servizio a \"pattugliare tutte le ore del\ngiorno e della notte\" intorno alle tre principali isole\nperiferiche di Kinmen, Matsu e Penghu, tutte a pochi chilometri\ndalla Cina, ma sotto l'amministrazione di Taipei. La mossa\ndecisa per il fine settimana è la risposta alla maggiore\npresenza di navi cinesi nell'area, anche nelle parti di mare\nbandite alla navigazione, alla vigilia della cerimonia di\ninsediamento di William Lai alla presidenza dell'isola.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nelle 24 ore fino alle 6 locali (mezzanotte in Italia), il\nministero della Difesa di Taipei ha segnalato che ci sono 7\naerei e 7 navi dell'Esercito popolare di liberazione cinese:\nnumeri straordinariamente bassi che alimentano i sospetti su\nquella che potrebbe essere la risposta di domani da parte di\nPechino. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1716145230.6695597,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-19 21:00:30",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-19T21.00.30",
        "en_title": "Taiwan strengthens patrols on the eve of the settlement of Lai",
        "en_content": "Taiwanese Coast Guard has\nsent his units in service to \"pattugliare all hours of\nday and night\" around the three main islands\nKinmen, Matsu and Penghu peripherals, all a few kilometers\nfrom China, but under the administration of Taipei. The move\ndecided for the weekend is the answer to the major\npresence of Chinese ships in the area, even in the sea parts\nbanished to navigation, on the eve of the ceremony\nWilliam Lai's settlement at the presidency of the island.\n\n\nIn 24 hours until 6 locals (mezzanotte in Italy), the\nTaipei Defense Ministry reported there are 7\nplanes and 7 ships of the Chinese People's Liberation Army:\nextraordinarily low numbers that feed suspicions on\nwhat could be tomorrow's response by\nBeijing.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In view of the Kinmen, Matsu and Penghu Islands in front of China",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lai",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kinmen",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Matsu",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Penghu Islands",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taiwanese Coast Guard",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "all hours",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kinmen",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Matsu",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Penghu",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few kilometers",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taipei",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the weekend",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 269,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 309,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "William Lai's",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 hours",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "6",
                "start_char": 487,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "mezzanotte",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taipei Defense Ministry",
                "start_char": 523,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 566,
                "end_char": 567,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 579,
                "end_char": 580,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Chinese People's Liberation Army",
                "start_char": 590,
                "end_char": 626,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 694,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 717,
                "end_char": 724,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    }
]
