[
    {
        "title": "Vertice Ue, 'accelerare per più prontezza nella difesa'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:47:25 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/20/vertice-ue-accelerare-per-piu-prontezza-nella-difesa_e5a1ccdd-6c5f-4473-8feb-ffbccf77b02a.html",
        "subtitle": "Avanti con proposte della Commissione e sulle opzioni per fondi",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Il Consiglio Europeo invita ad\naccelerare i lavori su tutti i fronti per aumentare in modo\ndecisivo la prontezza di difesa dell'Europa entro i prossimi\ncinque anni\". Lo si legge nelle conclusioni del vertice Ue. I\nleader inoltre invitano \"il Consiglio e i colegislatori a\nportare avanti rapidamente i lavori sulle recenti proposte della\nCommissione\" e \"ad avviare con urgenza l'attuazione delle azioni\nindividuate nelle sue conclusioni del 6 marzo 2025 nel campo\ndelle capacità e a proseguire i lavori sulle relative opzioni di\nfinanziamento\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511617.9445307,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.17",
        "en_title": "EU summit, 'accelerating for more readiness in defence'",
        "en_content": "\"The European Council calls on the\naccelerate jobs on all fronts to increase so\nEurope's defence readiness within the coming\nFive years.\" It is read in the conclusions of the EU summit. I\nleaders also call on \"the Council and the co-operators to\nto carry out the work quickly on the recent proposals for\nCommission\" and \"to urgently start the implementation of the measures\nidentified in its conclusions of 6 March 2025 in the field\ncapacity and work on the relative options\nfinancing\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Next with proposals from the Commission and the options for funds",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The European Council",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Five years",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "6 March 2025",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas, 14 membri di una famiglia uccisi in un raid a Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:35:21 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/19/hamas-14-membri-di-una-famiglia-uccisi-in-un-raid-a-gaza_9771ad99-2150-401b-a7b5-9611c5ebb239.html",
        "subtitle": "Protezione Civile: 'Durante una veglia funebre'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Quattordici membri di una\nfamiglia sono rimasti uccisi in un attacco israeliano contro un\nedificio dove si stava svolgendo una veglia funebre, nella città\nsettentrionale di Beit Lahia, a Gaza. Lo riferisce la Protezione\nCivile. I soccorritori hanno identificato 14 membri morti della\nfamiglia Mubarak, ha detto all'Afp Mahmoud Bassal, portavoce\ndella Protezione civile di Hamas, aggiungendo che circa dieci\npersone risultano ancora disperse sotto le macerie. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 72,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.2240798,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Hamas, 14 members of a family killed in a raid in Gaza",
        "en_content": "Fourteen members of a\nfamily were killed in an Israeli attack against a\nbuilding where a funeral vigil was taking place, in the city\nnorthern Beit Lahia, in Gaza. The Protection Reports\nCivil. The rescuers have identified 14 dead members of the\nMubarak family, told Afp Mahmoud Bassal, spokesman\nof the Hamas Civil Protection, adding that about ten\npeople are still dispersed under the rubble.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Civil Protection: 'During a funeral wake'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "14",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Fourteen",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beit Lahia",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "14",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mubarak",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afp Mahmoud Bassal",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Hamas Civil Protection",
                "start_char": 299,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "about ten",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Brasile, la Banca centrale alza i tassi al 14,25%",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:28:08 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/20/brasile-la-banca-centrale-alza-i-tassi-al-1425_a2a4b6aa-b463-4e87-991e-2026448a4dac.html",
        "subtitle": "Aumento di 100 punti base. È il livello più alto dal 2016",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Comitato di politica\nmonetaria della Banca centrale del Brasile, il Copom ha elevato\noggi di di 100 punti base il tasso di interesse di riferimento\n(Selic), passato così dal 13,25% al 14,25% annuo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La decisione, che è stata presa all'unanimità durante il\nsecondo incontro dell'anno della Banca centrale verde-oro, era\nattesa dal mercato e si tratta del quinto aumento consecutivo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Era dal 2016 che il Selic non era così alto e l'ultima volta\nche il Brasile ha raggiunto questo livello, il paese era in\npiena crisi durante il secondo mandato dell'ex presidente Dilma\nRousseff (2011-2016).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il Copom ritiene che questa decisione sia compatibile con la\nstrategia di convergenza dell'inflazione attorno alla meta lungo\nl'orizzonte rilevante. Senza pregiudicare il suo obiettivo\nfondamentale di garantire la stabilità dei prezzi, questa\ndecisione implica anche un'attenuazione delle fluttuazioni del\nlivello di attività economica e la promozione dell'occupazione\npiena\", ha reso noto la Banca centrale in un comunicato,\naggiungendo che la prossima riunione (il 6 ed i 7 maggio\nprossimi) sarà caratterizzata da un nuovo aumento del Selic,\nseppure di \"minore entità\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 68,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.3793015,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Brazil, the Central Bank raises rates to 14,25%",
        "en_content": "The Political Committee\nthe central bank of Brazil, the Copom has elevated\ntoday of 100 basic points the reference interest rate\n(Selic), thus passed from 13.25% to 14.25% annually.\n\n\nThe decision, which was taken unanimously during the\nsecond meeting of the year of the Green Gold Central Bank, was\nexpected from the market and it is the fifth consecutive increase.\n\n\nIt was since 2016 that Selic was not so high and the last time\nthat Brazil has reached this level, the country was in\nfull crisis during the second term of former President Dilma\nRousseff (2011-2016).\n\n\n\"The Copom believes this decision is compatible with the\nConvergence strategy of inflation around the long-term goal\nthe relevant horizon. Without prejudice to its goal\nto ensure price stability, this\nDecision also implies a attenuation of fluctuations in\nlevel of economic activity and promotion of employment\nthe central bank in a statement,\nadding that the next meeting (on 6 and 7 May)\nnext) will be characterized by a new increase of the Selic,\nalthough of \"minor entities\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Increase of 100 base points. It is the highest level since 2016",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Central Bank",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "14,25%",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "100",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2016",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Political Committee",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Copom",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "100",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "13.25%",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "14.25%",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "annually",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the year",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "fifth",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 344,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2016",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Selic",
                "start_char": 392,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 510,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dilma\nRousseff",
                "start_char": 542,
                "end_char": 556,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2011-2016",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 567,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Copom",
                "start_char": 577,
                "end_char": 582,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Convergence",
                "start_char": 629,
                "end_char": 640,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 and 7 May",
                "start_char": 949,
                "end_char": 960,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Selic",
                "start_char": 1015,
                "end_char": 1020,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Bolivia, contadini indigeni consegnano loro richieste al governo",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 19 Mar 2025 23:33:28 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/19/bolivia-contadini-indigeni-consegnano-loro-richieste-al-governo_46fece69-9357-4504-bc4a-62acec2a602f.html",
        "subtitle": "Ponci Rossi, vicini a Morales, chiedono dimissioni di 4 ministri",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Federazione dipartimentale unica\ndei lavoratori contadini \"Túpac Katari\", organizzazione indigena\nvicina all'ex presidente Evo Morales e più nota in Bolivia come\nPonci Rossi (Ponchos Rojos in spagnolo) ha circondato la piazza\nMurillo di La Paz, il centro del potere politico del paese\nandino per consegnare un documento con numerose rivendicazioni\nal governo del presidente, Luis Arce. Lo rende noto il sito del\nquotidiano boliviano El Diario.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Tra le richieste ci sono le dimissioni dei ministri dei\nLavori Pubblici, Edgar Montaño, degli Idrocarburi e\ndell'Energia, Alejandro Gallardo, della Pianificazione dello\nSviluppo, Sergio Cusicanqui, e degli Interni, Eduardo Del\nCastillo, che lo scorso settembre aveva avviato un'inchiesta\ncontro i Ponci Rossi, accusandoli di rivolta armata e\nterrorismo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il leader dei Ponci Rossi, David Mamani, ha chiesto anche le\ndimissioni del direttore della società statale di supporto alla\nproduzione alimentare, l'Emapa e del vice-ministro della Difesa\ndel Consumatore, oltre alla riduzione del 50% degli stipendi dei\ndipendenti pubblici superiori ai 10mila pesos boliviani (1327\neuro), il rifiuto di qualsiasi credito internazionale e la\nsoluzione immediata alla mancanza di combustibili e all'aumento\ndei prezzi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Mamani ha concesso al governo Arce 72 ore per rispondere,\navvertendo che i Ponci Rossi radicalizzeranno le proteste se le\nloro richieste non saranno soddisfatte.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il viceministro della Sicurezza Cittadina, Roberto Ríos, ha\nlamentato che Mamani sia tornato a coordinare le manifestazioni\ndei Ponci Rossi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 70,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.4041598,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Bolivia, indigenous peasants give their demands to the government",
        "en_content": "The unique departmental Federation\nof peasant workers \"Túpac Katari\", indigenous organization\nclose to former president Evo Morales and more known in Bolivia as\nPonci Rossi (Ponchos Rojos in Spanish) surrounded the square\nMurillo of La Paz, the center of political power of the country\nandin to deliver a document with numerous claims\nto the president's government, Luis Arce. It makes known the site of\nBolivian daily El Diario.\n\n\nAmong the requests are the resignation of the ministers of\nPublic works, Edgar Montaño, Idrocarburi and\nof Energy, Alejandro Gallardo, of the Planning of the\nDevelopment, Sergio Cusicanqui, and the Interior, Eduardo Del\nCastillo, who started an investigation last September\nagainst the Red Ponci, accusing them of armed revolt and\nterrorism.\n\n\nThe leader of the Ponci Rossi, David Mamani, also asked the\nresignation of the director of the state company to support the\nfood production, the Emapa and the Deputy Minister of Defense\nof the Consumer, in addition to the reduction of 50% of the salaries of\npublic employees over 10 thousand Bolivian pesos (1327\neuro), refusal of any international credit and\nimmediate solution to the lack of fuels and the increase\nprice.\n\n\nMamani granted the Arce government 72 hours to respond,\nwarning that the Red Ponces will radicalize the protests if the\nthey will not be satisfied.\n\n\nDeputy Minister of Civil Security, Roberto Ríos, ha\ncomplained that Mamani returned to coordinate the events\nof the Red Ponci.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Ponci Rossi, close to Morales, call for resignation of 4 ministers",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bolivia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ponci Rossi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Morales",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Túpac Katari",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Evo Morales",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolivia",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ponci Rossi",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 172,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ponchos Rojos",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 187,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "Murillo",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Paz",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luis Arce",
                "start_char": 366,
                "end_char": 375,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolivian",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "El Diario",
                "start_char": 419,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Edgar Montaño",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 518,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idrocarburi",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Energy",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Alejandro Gallardo",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Planning of the\nDevelopment",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 601,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergio Cusicanqui",
                "start_char": 603,
                "end_char": 620,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 630,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Eduardo Del\nCastillo",
                "start_char": 640,
                "end_char": 660,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "last September",
                "start_char": 691,
                "end_char": 705,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Ponci",
                "start_char": 714,
                "end_char": 727,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ponci Rossi",
                "start_char": 794,
                "end_char": 805,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "David Mamani",
                "start_char": 807,
                "end_char": 819,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emapa",
                "start_char": 921,
                "end_char": 926,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Consumer",
                "start_char": 969,
                "end_char": 977,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "50%",
                "start_char": 1011,
                "end_char": 1014,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "10 thousand Bolivian pesos",
                "start_char": 1056,
                "end_char": 1082,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "1327\neuro",
                "start_char": 1084,
                "end_char": 1093,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mamani",
                "start_char": 1202,
                "end_char": 1208,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arce",
                "start_char": 1221,
                "end_char": 1225,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "72 hours",
                "start_char": 1237,
                "end_char": 1245,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Ponces",
                "start_char": 1271,
                "end_char": 1285,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Civil Security",
                "start_char": 1371,
                "end_char": 1385,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Roberto Ríos",
                "start_char": 1387,
                "end_char": 1399,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mamani",
                "start_char": 1420,
                "end_char": 1426,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Ponci",
                "start_char": 1464,
                "end_char": 1477,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Difesa civile di Gaza, 10 morti in un attacco israeliano",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 04:38:14 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/20/difesa-civile-di-gaza-10-morti-in-un-attacco-israeliano_0aee5810-db80-4159-af15-1f521870c4e9.html",
        "subtitle": "'E decine di feriti'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Protezione civile nella Striscia\ndi Gaza ha segnalato 10 morti e diversi feriti nelle prime ore\ndi giovedì mattina in una serie di attacchi israeliani sul\nterritorio palestinese, dopo la massiccia ripresa dei\nbombardamenti nella notte tra lunedì e martedì.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Almeno 10 civili sono stati uccisi e decine di altri sono\nrimasti feriti in attacchi aerei israeliani che hanno preso di\nmira sei case a est di Khan Younis, nella Striscia di Gaza\nmeridionale, nelle prime ore di giovedì mattina\", ha detto\nall'Afp il portavoce della Protezione civile Mahmoud Bassal.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.4712985,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Gaza Civil Defense, 10 dead in an Israeli attack",
        "en_content": "Civil Protection in the Strip\nof Gaza reported 10 dead and several wounded in the early hours\nThursday morning in a series of Israeli attacks on\nPalestinian territory, after the massive recovery of\nbombing on the night between Monday and Tuesday.\n\n\n\"At least 10 civilians were killed and dozens of others were killed\nwounded in Israeli air attacks that took\ntargets six houses east of Khan Younis, in the Gaza Strip\nsouthern, in the early hours of Thursday morning,\" he said\nto the Afp the spokesman for civil protection Mahmoud Bassal.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'And dozens of wounded'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza Civil Defense",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the early hours",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday morning",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the night",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "between Monday and Tuesday",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "At least 10",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "six",
                "start_char": 366,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khan Younis",
                "start_char": 385,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 405,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the early hours of",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 447,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 448,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "morning",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 464,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afp",
                "start_char": 482,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mahmoud Bassal",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 535,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, discusso del controllo Usa su centrale Zaporizhzhia",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 19 Mar 2025 23:00:10 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-19",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/19/zelensky-discusso-del-controllo-usa-su-centrale-zaporizhzhia_a4ae28cd-8f9c-48b7-bd06-2637dbcdfd21.html",
        "subtitle": "'Nella telefonata nessuna pressione da Trump su concessioni'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente ucraino Volodymyr\nZelensky ha dichiarato di aver discusso con Donald Trump della\npossibilità che gli Stati Uniti controllino solo una centrale\nnucleare ucraina, quella di Zaporizhzhia. \"Abbiamo discusso solo\ndi una centrale elettrica, che si trova sotto occupazione\nrussa\", ha affermato il presidente ucraino durante una\nconferenza stampa dopo la telefonata con il presidente\namericano.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Zelensky ha poi assicurato di non aver sentito \"alcuna\npressione\" da parte di Trump affinché facesse delle concessioni\nper arrivare alla pace. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 71,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.5349534,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, discussed of the US control on central Zaporizhzhia",
        "en_content": "Ukrainian President Volodymyr\nZelensky claimed to have discussed with Donald Trump of the\npossibility that the United States controls only one central\nUkrainian nuclear, that of Zaporizhzhia. \"We discussed only\nof an electric power station, which is under occupation\nRussian\", said Ukrainian President during a\npress conference after call with the president\nAmerican.\n\n\nZelensky then assured not to have heard \"someone\npressure\" by Trump to make concessions\nto reach peace.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'In the phone call no pressure from Trump on concessions'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zaporizhzhia",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr\n",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "only one",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zaporizhzhia",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 432,
                "end_char": 437,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ottawa, '4 canadesi giustiziati in Cina'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 14:34:27 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/20/ottawa-4-canadesi-giustiziati-in-cina_b60e0ba0-864e-442b-879c-b1400f7fafcd.html",
        "subtitle": "Pechino, 'mano dura contro reati di droga'",
        "content": "Quattro cittadini canadesi sono stati giustiziati in Cina nelle ultime settimane, secondo quanto ha annunciato il ministro degli Esteri canadese Mélanie Joly, precisando che Pechino ha ignorato le richieste di clemenza di Ottawa.     \"Condanniamo fermamente le esecuzioni di cittadini canadesi in Cina\", ha detto Joly ai giornalisti a Ottawa. Il ministro ha affermato di non essere in grado di discutere i dettagli del caso a causa delle richieste di riservatezza avanzate dalle famiglie coinvolte.     Pechino ha difeso le esecuzioni in una dichiarazione inviata al quotidiano canadese Globe and Mail, in cui si afferma che i canadesi sono stati condannati per reati legati alla droga.     \"I reati legati alla droga sono crimini gravi, riconosciuti in tutto il mondo come estremamente dannosi per la società\", si legge nella dichiarazione dell'ambasciata inviata al Globe. \"La Cina continua a imporre pene severe per i reati legati alla droga e mantiene un atteggiamento di 'tolleranza zero' a questo riguardo\", si legge inoltre.     Joly ha affermato che lei e l'ex primo ministro Justin Trudeau, che ha lasciato l'incarico all'inizio di questo mese, avevano chiesto clemenza per i quattro.     I rapporti tra Pechino e Ottawa sono tesi dopo l'arresto, nel 2018, da parte delle autorità canadesi di un manager del colosso cinese Huawei e l'incarcerazione, per rappresaglia, di due cittadini canadesi da parte della Cina. Sebbene tutti e tre siano stati rilasciati, le tensioni persistono, con Pechino che critica in particolare Ottawa per essersi allineata alla politica cinese di Washington. Le autorità canadesi, da parte loro, accusano regolarmente la Cina di ingerenza.   \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.5572712,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Ottawa, 4 Canadians executed in China",
        "en_content": "Four Canadian citizens have been executed in China in recent weeks, according to the Canadian Foreign Minister Mélanie Joly, stating that Beijing has ignored Ottawa's clemency demands. \"We firmly condemn the executions of Canadian citizens in China,\" said Joly to journalists in Ottawa. The Minister said he was unable to discuss the details of the case because of the requests for confidentiality advanced by the families involved. Beijing defended the executions in a statement sent to the Canadian newspaper Globe and Mail, where it is claimed that Canadians were convicted of drug-related crimes. \"The drug-related crimes are serious crimes, recognized worldwide as extremely harmful to society,\" reads in the statement of the embassy sent to the Globe. \"China continues to impose severe penalties for drug-related crimes and maintains a 'zero tolerance' attitude in this regard,\" it also reads. Joly said that you and former Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, who left office earlier this month, had asked for mercy for the four. The relations between Beijing and Ottawa are thesis after the arrest, in 2018, by the Canadian authorities of a manager of the Chinese giant Huawei and the incarceration of two Canadian citizens by China. Although all three were released, tensions persist, with Beijing criticizing Ottawa in particular for aligning with Washington's Chinese policy. The Canadian authorities, on their part, regularly accuse China of ingestion.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Beijing, 'hard hand against drug offenses'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ottawa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadians",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Four",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent weeks",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mélanie Joly",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ottawa",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joly",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ottawa",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 433,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Globe and Mail",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadians",
                "start_char": 552,
                "end_char": 561,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Globe",
                "start_char": 751,
                "end_char": 756,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 759,
                "end_char": 764,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "zero",
                "start_char": 843,
                "end_char": 847,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joly",
                "start_char": 900,
                "end_char": 904,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Justin Trudeau",
                "start_char": 945,
                "end_char": 959,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "earlier this month",
                "start_char": 977,
                "end_char": 995,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 1025,
                "end_char": 1029,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 1053,
                "end_char": 1060,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ottawa",
                "start_char": 1065,
                "end_char": 1071,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2018",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1108,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 1117,
                "end_char": 1125,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 1158,
                "end_char": 1165,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Huawei",
                "start_char": 1172,
                "end_char": 1178,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1204,
                "end_char": 1207,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 1208,
                "end_char": 1216,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 1229,
                "end_char": 1234,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 1249,
                "end_char": 1254,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 1293,
                "end_char": 1300,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ottawa",
                "start_char": 1313,
                "end_char": 1319,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 1352,
                "end_char": 1362,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 1365,
                "end_char": 1372,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 1385,
                "end_char": 1393,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 1439,
                "end_char": 1444,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Houthi, 'missile ipersonico verso l'aeroporto di Tel Aviv'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:18:29 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/20/houthi-missile-ipersonico-verso-laeroporto-di-tel-aviv_b983b797-225f-4571-8940-7fb3ecbd87cc.html",
        "subtitle": "Un altro avrebbe colpito la portaerei Usa Truman nel Mar Rosso",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli Houthi affermano di aver\nattaccato l'aeroporto Ben Gurion di Tel Aviv con un missile\nipersonico poco dopo che Israele ha fatto sapere di avere\nrespinto un missile lanciato dallo Yemen. Lo riporta la Tass\ncitando il portavoce militare del movimento, Yahya Sarea. \"Le\ntruppe missilistiche delle forze armate yemenite hanno condotto\nun'operazione militare e hanno attaccato l'aeroporto Ben Gurion\nnel quartiere occupato di Jaffa con l'uso di un missile\nbalistico ipersonico Palestine-2\", ha dichiarato al canale\ntelevisivo Al Masirah controllato dagli Houthi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Sarea ha anche segnalato un nuovo attacco alla portaerei\nstatunitense  Harry Truman nel Mar Rosso con missili e droni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Le forze armate yemenite hanno intensificato gli attacchi al\nnemico nel Mar Rosso, inclusa la portaerei USS Harry Truman nel\nMar Rosso e le sue navi di scorta. L'operazione è stata condotta\nda truppe missilistiche, forze navali e aviotrasportate con\nl'uso di missili balistici e droni\", ha detto al canale\ntelevisivo Al Masirah.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    Secondo il portavoce degli Houthi, \"l'operazione ha\nraggiunto con successo il suo obiettivo\". Circostanza al momento\nnon confermata nè smentita dal  Comando centrale degli Stati\nUniti. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.6084683,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Houthi, 'individual missile to Tel Aviv airport'",
        "en_content": "The Houthi claim to have\nattack Ben Gurion airport in Tel Aviv with a missile\nipersonian shortly after Israel has announced that they have\nrejected a missile launched by Yemen. The Tass\nciting the military spokesman of the movement, Yahya Sarea. \"\nmissile troops of Yemeni armed forces led\na military operation and attacked Ben Gurion airport\nin the busy district of Jaffa with the use of a missile\nPalestinian-2, said to the canal\nTV Al Masirah controlled by the Houthi.\n\n\nSarea also reported a new attack on the aircraft carrier\nAmerican Harry Truman in the Red Sea with missiles and drones.\n\n\n\"The Yemeni armed forces have intensified attacks on\nenemy in the Red Sea, including USS carrier Harry Truman in\nRed Sea and its escort ships. The operation was conducted\nby missile troops, naval and airborne forces with\nthe use of ballistic and drone missiles,\" he told the channel\nTV Al Masirah.\n\n\nAccording to the Houthi spokesman, \"the operation has\nsuccessfully achieved its goal.\" Circus at the moment\nnot confirmed nor denied by the Central Command of the States\nUnited.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Another would hit the US Truman carrier in the Red Sea",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tel Aviv",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ben Gurion",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tel Aviv",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yahya Sarea",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemeni",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ben Gurion",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jaffa",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al Masirah",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 470,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sarea",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 539,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Harry Truman",
                "start_char": 540,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 556,
                "end_char": 567,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemeni",
                "start_char": 601,
                "end_char": 607,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 658,
                "end_char": 669,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "USS",
                "start_char": 681,
                "end_char": 684,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Harry Truman",
                "start_char": 693,
                "end_char": 705,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Red Sea",
                "start_char": 709,
                "end_char": 716,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 913,
                "end_char": 919,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Central Command",
                "start_char": 1032,
                "end_char": 1051,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Sheinbaum, 'il coordinamento con gli Usa sta funzionando'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:09:40 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/20/sheinbaum-il-coordinamento-con-gli-usa-sta-funzionando_29d4879e-37ad-4b43-ac7b-7f1f4c5224e1.html",
        "subtitle": "La presidente messicana cita gli accordi raggiunti tra i 2 paesi",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Dopo il sequestro di un\ncarico di armi da parte della polizia di frontiera degli Stati\nUniti che era diretto in Messico, la presidente del paese\nlatinoamericano, Claudia Sheinbaum, ha sottolineato che gli\naccordi raggiunti tra i due paesi ai tavoli di negoziazione per\nevitare le minacce tariffarie del presidente Donald Trump stanno\nfunzionando. Lo riporta il sito di El País.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Dopo avere celebrato il sequestro, avvenuto l'altroieri sul\nponte che collega le città di Del Río, in Texas, e Ciudad Acuña,\nin Messico, Sheinbaum ha detto nella sua conferenza stampa\nodierna che \"in effetti si vede che il coordinamento sta\nfunzionando\", aggiungendo che \"noi continuiamo con l'Operazione\nFrontiera per evitare in primis che arrivi fentanyl negli Stati\nUniti e loro ci stanno aiutando ad evitare che arrivino armi\ndagli Usa in Messico\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Come noi stiamo aiutando affinché non arrivino fentanyl e\naltre droghe, particolarmente sintetiche, negli Usa, noi\nchiediamo al Governo degli Stati Uniti di aiutarci affinché non\narrivino armi in Messico. Questo è stato l'accordo\", ha\nprecisato Sheinbaum. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 69,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.6490986,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Sheinbaum, 'coordination with the US is working'",
        "en_content": "After the seizure of a\nloaded with weapons by the border police of the States\nUnited who was headed to Mexico, the president of the country\nLatin American, Claudia Sheinbaum, has emphasized that the\nagreements reached between the two countries at the negotiating tables for\navoid the tariff threats of President Donald Trump are\nWorking. El País' website.\n\n\nAfter celebrating the kidnapping, the otherman took place on the\nbridge connecting the cities of Del Río, Texas, and Ciudad Acuña,\nin Mexico, Sheinbaum said in his press conference\ntoday that \"in fact we see that coordination is\nworking, adding that \"we continue with Operation\nFrontier to avoid first arrivals fentanyl in states\nUnited and they're helping us avoid weapons coming\nfrom the USA to Mexico.\"\n\n\n\"As we are helping so that fentanyl and\nother drugs, especially synthetic, in the US, we\nwe ask the Government of the United States to help us so that we do not\nweapons come to Mexico. That was the deal,\" he said.\nspecified Sheinbaum.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Mexican President cites the agreements reached between the two countries",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sheinbaum",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Latin American",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Claudia Sheinbaum",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "El País'",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Del Río",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Texas",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ciudad Acuña",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 498,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sheinbaum",
                "start_char": 500,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 544,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Operation\nFrontier",
                "start_char": 626,
                "end_char": 644,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 654,
                "end_char": 659,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "United",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 694,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 748,
                "end_char": 751,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 755,
                "end_char": 761,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 848,
                "end_char": 850,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Government of the United States",
                "start_char": 862,
                "end_char": 897,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 943,
                "end_char": 949,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sheinbaum",
                "start_char": 990,
                "end_char": 999,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il Messico entra nella top 10 dei Paesi più felici del mondo",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:07:20 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/20/il-messico-entra-nella-top-10-dei-paesi-piu-felici-del-mondo_0c216587-2000-4899-a41b-578cf643a3d3.html",
        "subtitle": "Sale di 15 posizioni nel World Happiness Report dell'Onu",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Messico si è\nclassificato quest'anno tra i dieci Paesi più felici del\npianeta, secondo il World Happiness Report 2025, coordinato\ndall'Università di Oxford, Gallup e il Sustainable Development\nSolutions Network delle Nazioni Unite.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIn base ai risultati del rapporto, diffuso nell'ambito della\nGiornata Internazionale della Felicità, il Paese latinoamericano\nè salito di 15 posizioni rispetto alla misurazione presentata lo\nscorso anno, collocandosi al 10° posto nella classifica che\nanalizza le informazioni disponibili per 147 nazioni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tAspetti come la forza del supporto sociale e la struttura\nfamiliare sono stati fondamentali in questa ripresa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tI Paesi nordici restano in cima alla lista, con la Finlandia al\nprimo posto per l'ottavo anno consecutivo. All'altro estremo\ndella classifica, l'Afghanistan ripete l'ultima posizione,\nconfermando il suo status di Paese meno felice al mondo. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.654699,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Mexico enters the top 10 of the happiest countries in the world",
        "en_content": "Mexico is\nranked this year among the ten happiest countries of the\nplanet, according to the World Happiness Report 2025, coordinated\nfrom the University of Oxford, Gallup and Sustainable Development\nUnited Nations Solutions Network.\n\n\nBased on the results of the report, available in the\nInternational Day of Happiness, the Latin American Country\nup to 15 positions compared to the measurement presented\nlast year, placing at the 10th place in the ranking that\nanalyzes the information available for 147 nations.\n\n\nAspects like the strength of social support and structure\nfamily were fundamental in this revival.\n\n\nNordic countries remain at the top of the list, with Finland at\nfirst place for the eighth consecutive year. To the other extreme\nof the ranking, Afghanistan repeats the last position,\nconfirming his status as a less happy country in the world.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Salt of 15 positions in the World Happiness Report of the UN",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the World Happiness Report",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "UN",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this year",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "ten",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the World Happiness Report",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the University of Oxford",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallup",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sustainable Development",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "United Nations Solutions Network",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Latin American",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "last year",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 413,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "10th",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "147",
                "start_char": 500,
                "end_char": 503,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nordic",
                "start_char": 616,
                "end_char": 622,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finland",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 676,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 680,
                "end_char": 685,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the eighth consecutive year",
                "start_char": 696,
                "end_char": 723,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afghanistan",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 773,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Caracas, Maduro ordina l'aumento dei voli di rimpatrio dagli Usa",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 20 Mar 2025 06:59:57 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/20/caracas-maduro-ordina-laumento-dei-voli-di-rimpatrio-dagli-usa_1dfefef7-ac82-45c1-8353-dfc53dc03a64.html",
        "subtitle": "Il presidente del Venezuela, 'domani arrivano 306 migranti'",
        "content": "     Il presidente del Venezuela, Nicolás Maduro, ha ordinato di incrementare i voli di rimpatrio dei migranti venezuelani espulsi dagli Stati Uniti, annunciando che domani arriverà in Venezuela un altro aereo con 306 migranti. Lo rende noto il sito venezuelano Alberto News.    \"Ho ordinato di incrementare tutte le azioni diplomatiche per riportare in patria i venezuelani e le venezuelane dagli Stati Uniti. Domani arrivano 306 migranti via Messico e ho dato l'ordine all'inviato speciale per i negoziati di pace con gli Stati Uniti, Jorge Rodríguez (il presidente del Parlamento), di incrementare tutte le azioni per garantire i voli di ritorno dagli Stati Uniti a tutti i migranti detenuti per dare loro rispetto, dignità, sostegno e farli tornare nella loro patria e alla loro famiglia\", ha dichiarato Maduro durante un evento a Caracas.    Maduro ha aggiunto che \"Jorge Rodríguez deve garantirmi il ritorno dei voli con i venezuelani e le venezuelane dagli Stati Uniti, mentre stiamo coordinando in tempo reale con la vicepresidente (Delcy Rodríguez, sorella di Jorge e ministra degli Idrocarburi) il salvataggio dei sequestrati nei campi di concentramento in El Salvador\".    Il Venezuela ha avvertito che non si fermerà fino a quando non avrà salvato quelli che considera \"sequestrati\" in El Salvador, dove gli Stati Uniti hanno inviato più 228 migranti accusati di essere membri della organizzazione criminale transnazionale Tren de Aragua, nata in Venezuela nel 2014 nel carcere di Tocorón    \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1742511626.6727407,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-21 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-20T23.00.26",
        "en_title": "Caracas, Maduro orders the increase of return flights from the US",
        "en_content": "Venezuelan president, Nicolás Maduro, has ordered to increase the repatriation flights of Venezuelan migrants expelled from the United States, announcing that tomorrow another plane with 306 migrants will arrive in Venezuela. It makes known the Venezuelan website Alberto News. \"I ordered to increase all diplomatic actions to bring back home Venezuelans and Venezuelans from the United States. Tomorrow 306 migrants arrived via Mexico and I gave orders to the special envoy for peace negotiations with the United States, Jorge Rodríguez (the President of Parliament), to increase all actions to ensure return flights from the United States to all migrants held to give them respect, dignity, support and bring them back to their homeland and their family,\" Maduro said during an event in Caracas. Maduro added that \"Jorge Rodríguez must guarantee me the return of flights with Venezuelans and Venezuelans from the United States, while we are coordinating in real time with the vice president (Delcy Rodríguez, sister of Jorge and ministra degli Idrocarburi) the rescue of the seized in concentration camps in El Salvador\". Venezuela has warned that it will not stop until he has saved those he considers \"sequested\" in El Salvador, where the United States has sent more than 228 migrants accused of being members of the transnational criminal organization Tren de Aragua, born in Venezuela in 2014 in the Tocorón prison\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The president of Venezuela, 'today 306 migrants arrive'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maduro",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "306",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicolás Maduro",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "306",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 190,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alberto News",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelans",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelans",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "306",
                "start_char": 404,
                "end_char": 407,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 435,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jorge Rodríguez",
