[
    {
        "title": "Vietnam condanna a morte manager per frode da 25 miliardi ",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:47:48 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-11",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/11/vietnam-condanna-a-morte-manager-per-frode-da-25-miliardi_60b01419-646f-4567-b935-f1dfca7a0d30.html",
        "subtitle": "La miliardaria aveva truffato fondi alla Saigon Commercial Bank ",
        "content": "Un tribunale vietnamita ha condannato a morte la dirigente di un colosso immobiliare per un caso di frode da 25 miliardi di euro, il più grande scandalo finanziario del Paese. Il processo a Truong My Lan è il più spettacolare svoltosi in Vietnam. Le azioni di Truong My Lan, presidente del promotore immobiliare Van Thinh Phat, accusata di aver truffato fondi dalla Saigon Commercial Bank (SCB) per un decennio, \"hanno eroso la fiducia della gente nella leadership del Partito (comunista) e dello Stato\", ha dichiarato la giuria, secondo quanto riportato dai media statali, durante il processo tenutosi a Ho Chi Minh City (sud).\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.302161,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Vietnam condemns death managers for fraud from 25 billion",
        "en_content": "A Vietnamese court sentenced the leader of a real estate colossus to death for a 25 billion euro fraud case, the country's largest financial scandal. The Truong My Lan trial is the most spectacular in Vietnam. The actions of Truong My Lan, president of the real estate promoter Van Thinh Phat, accused of having scammed funds from the Saigon Commercial Bank (SCB) for a decade, \"have eroded the trust of people in the leadership of the Party (communist) and the State\", declared the jury, according to the state media, during the trial held in Ho Chi Minh City (sud).\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Vietnam",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "death",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "NOUN"
            },
            {
                "word": "managers",
                "meaning": "dobj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "fraud",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vietnam",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "25 billion",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vietnamese",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "25 billion euro",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lan",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vietnam",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Truong My Lan",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Van Thinh Phat",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Saigon Commercial Bank",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "SCB",
                "start_char": 359,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a decade",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Party",
                "start_char": 436,
                "end_char": 441,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 462,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ho Chi Minh City",
                "start_char": 544,
                "end_char": 560,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Von der Leyen, 'Italia? Ora nessuno è solo sui migranti'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:03:01 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/10/von-der-leyen-italia-ora-nessuno-e-solo-sui-migranti_a48b1623-d687-46a5-8bd5-1f8083c64b21.html",
        "subtitle": "'Per questo abbiamo introdotto la solidarietà obbligatoria'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Con il patto sulla migrazione\nnessun Paese sarà lasciato da solo, per questo abbiamo\nintrodotto un meccanismo di solidarietà obbligatoria: l'Europa\nmigliore è l'Europa che si muove unita\". Lo ha detto la\npresidente della Commissione Europea Ursula von der Leyen al\nParlamento Europeo dopo l'approvazione del Patto sulla\nmigrazione e l'asilo, rispondendo a una domanda se il Patto\npotrà aiutare in concreto Paesi come Italia, Spagna, Grecia e\nMalta. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 75,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.3698885,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Von der Leyen, Italy? Now no one is only on migrants.",
        "en_content": "\"With the migration pact\nno country will be left alone, so we have\nintroduced a compulsory solidarity mechanism: Europe\nThe best is Europe that moves together.\" He said that\nPresident of the European Commission Ursula von der Leyen al\nEuropean Parliament after approval of the Covenant on\nmigration and asylum, answering a question if the Covenant\ncan help in concrete countries such as Italy, Spain, Greece and\nMalta.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Von",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "der",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "meaning": "ROOT",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "meaning": "appos",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "AUX"
            },
            {
                "word": "migrants",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Von der",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "von der",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen al\n",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European Parliament",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Covenant",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Covenant",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greece",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 407,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Malta",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Milei contro la stampa, 'è corrotta e prostituita alla politica'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:32:30 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/04/10/milei-contro-la-stampa-e-corrotta-e-prostituita-alla-politica_e53c8bd1-aead-467d-9e16-1bb5bf2c8ac2.html",
        "subtitle": "Il presidente rivendica il suo diritto a criticare I giornalisti",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente dell'Argentina,\nJavier Milei, ha ingaggiato una battaglia durissima contro la\nstampa rivendicando il suo diritto e la sua libertà di\nrispondere con invettive, insulti e diffamazione ai giornalisti\nche osano mettere in discussione le sue politiche.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In un post pubblicato su X, il leader ultraliberista respinge\n\"la presunta superiorità\" del giornalismo che \"alla pari di\ntutte le cose legate alla politica\" considera \"corrotto e\nprostituito\" e rivendica la \"libertà di espressione per tutti,\nnon solo per alcuni\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Milei risponde in questo modo all'ondata di critiche che si è\nriversata nelle ultime ore su di lui dopo che ha auspicato il\nfallimento di una testata spesso critica nei suoi confronti e\ndopo aver accusato una giornalista di voler distruggere il\ngoverno con le sue domande. \"Non rimarremo zitti di fronte alle\nmenzogne, alle calunnie, alle ingiurie (dei giornalisti). Li\nfaremo scendere dalla torre d'avorio dove credono di stare,\nperché libertà d'espressione significa che nessuno può impedirci\ndi parlare, nemmeno i sacri giornalisti\", ha scritto Milei a\nconclusione del post. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 69,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.4238157,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Milei against the press, 'is corrupt and prostituted to politics'",
        "en_content": "President of Argentina,\nJavier Milei, has engaged a very hard battle against\npress claiming his right and freedom\nrespond with invectives, insults and defamation to journalists\nthat they dare question his policies.\n\n\nIn a post published on X, the ultra-liberal leader rejects\n\"the presumed superiority\" of journalism that \"to the same\nall things related to politics\" considers \"corrupt and\nprostitute\" and claims the \"freedom of expression for all,\nnot just for some.\"\n\n\nMilei responds in this way to the wave of criticism that has been\npoured in the last hours on him after he wished the\nfailure of a often critical test against him and\nafter accused a journalist of wanting to destroy the\ngovernment with his questions. \"We will not remain silent in front of\nlies, slanders, unjust ( journalists). Li\nWe'll get off the ivory tower where they think they're,\nbecause freedom of expression means that no one can prevent us\nto speak, not even the holy journalists,\" Milei wrote\nconclusion of the post.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "AUX"
            },
            {
                "word": "press",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "politics",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last hours",
                "start_char": 547,
                "end_char": 561,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Li",
                "start_char": 800,
                "end_char": 802,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the ivory tower",
                "start_char": 817,
                "end_char": 832,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, su Patto migranti ruolo importante dell'Italia e del Ppe",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:33:38 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/10/tajani-su-patto-migranti-ruolo-importante-dellitalia-e-del-ppe_8ff7d468-9ff7-4d75-89e5-c6e2732cfa2b.html",
        "subtitle": "'Era il miglior compromesso possibile, si supera Dublino'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Il via libera del Parlamento europeo\nal patto sui migranti e sull'asilo è un passo importante. Così\nsi supera la stagione di Dublino. Era il migliore compromesso\npossibile. L' Europa torna protagonista per affrontare\nl'immigrazione legale e tornare ad avere una visione complessiva\ndel fenomeno. L'Italia ha avuto un ruolo importante come lo ha\navuto la nostra famiglia politica, quella popolare\". Lo afferma\nil vicepremier e ministro degli Esteri, Antonio Tajani,\nlasciando l'assemblea nazionale di Cifa Italia. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 68,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.455301,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Tajani, on Patto migrants important role of Italy and Ppe",
        "en_content": "\"The free way of the European Parliament\nthe pact on migrants and asylum is an important step. So\nover the Dublin season. It was the best compromise\npossible. Europe is the protagonist to face\nlegal immigration and return to having an overall view\nof the phenomenon. Italy has played an important role as it has\nhad our political family, the popular one.\" It says\nDeputy Premier and Foreign Minister, Antonio Tajani,\nleaving the national assembly of Cifa Italia.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "meaning": "ROOT",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Patto",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "NOUN"
            },
            {
                "word": "migrants",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "role",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ppe",
                "meaning": "conj",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Patto",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ppe",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the European Parliament",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Dublin season",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 272,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 415,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cifa Italia",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Biden, sistema di difesa antimissile con Giappone e Australia",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:37:22 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/10/biden-sistema-di-difesa-antimissile-con-giappone-e-australia_a1a8edff-4ebf-4975-a598-268d3f1f11a6.html",
        "subtitle": "'Il più grande rafforzamento della cooperazione dagli anni '60'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Per la prima volta Usa,\nGiappone e Australia creeranno un sistema di difesa anti-missile\ncomune\". Lo ha annunciato il presidente americano Joe Biden in\nuna conferenza stampa alla Casa Bianca con il premier giapponese\nFumio Kishida sottolineando che gli accordi siglati oggi sono\n\"il più grande rafforzamento della cooperazione militare dagli\nanni '60\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.4890814,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Biden, antimissile defense system with Japan and Australia",
        "en_content": "\"For the first time Usa,\nJapan and Australia will create an anti-missile defense system\ncommon.\" American President Joe Biden announced it\na press conference at the White House with the Japanese premier\nFumio Kishida underlines that the agreements signed today are\n\"the greatest strengthening of military cooperation by\n60s.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "meaning": "ROOT",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "defense",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "NOUN"
            },
            {
                "word": "system",
                "meaning": "appos",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "meaning": "conj",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 125,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Japanese",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fumio Kishida",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "60s",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "L'Osa condanna il blitz dell'Ecuador nell'ambasciata messicana",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:24:24 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/04/10/losa-condanna-il-blitz-dellecuador-nellambasciata-messicana_037348e9-185a-4215-9632-a99f7202a5c9.html",
        "subtitle": "Governo di Quito isolato nella riunione del Consiglio permanente",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Consiglio permanente\ndell'Organizzazione degli stati americani (Osa), riunito per il\n2/o giorno in seduta straordinaria, ha approvato oggi una\nrisoluzione di condanna per \"l'intrusione nell'ambasciata del\nMessico in Ecuador\" e per \"gli atti di violenza contro\nincolumità e dignità dei diplomatici della missione\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La risoluzione è stata approvata a inizio seduta, prima che\ndegli interventi dei rappresentanti del Paesi membri che, ad\neccezione del delegato dell'Ecuador, il vice ministro degli\nEsteri Alejandro Davalos, hanno criticato e condannato in varia\nmisura il blitz delle forze di sicurezza per prelevare l'ex vice\npresidente ecuadoriano, Jorge Glas.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nella risoluzione si riafferma inoltre \"l'obbligo di tutti\ngli Stati di garantire il rispetto dei privilegi e delle\nimmunità delle missioni diplomatiche e del principio di\ninviolabilità\" ai sensi della Convenzione di Vienna.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   E si esorta infine \"Ecuador e Messico ad avviare un dialogo e\nad adottare misure immediate, in conformità con il diritto\ninternazionale, per risolvere la grave questione in modo\ncostruttivo\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Chiudendo il dibattito, il segretario generale dell'Osa, Luis\nAlmagro, ha sottolineato che i fatti di Quito hanno costituito\n\"un vulnus fondamentale del diritto internazionale americano,\nuniversale e consuetudinario\", e auspicato che per l'apertura di\nun dialogo fra Ecuador e Messico, la situazione creata dal blitz\npossa \"essere corretta\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 71,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.5010886,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "The Osa condemns Ecuador's blitz in the Mexican Embassy",
        "en_content": "The Permanent Council\nof the Organization of American States (Osa), meeting for\n2/day in extraordinary session, today approved a\ncondemnation resolution for \"intrusion in the embassy of the\nMexico in Ecuador\" and \"the acts of violence against\nincolumity and dignity of the diplomats of the mission\".\n\n\nThe resolution was adopted at the beginning of the sitting before\nthe participation of representatives of the Member States,\nthe exception of the delegate of Ecuador, the deputy minister of\nForeigners Alejandro Davalos, have criticized and condemned in various\nmeasure the blitz of security forces to withdraw the former vice\nEcuadorian president, Jorge Glas.\n\n\nThe resolution also reaffirms \"the obligation of all\nStates to ensure compliance with privileges and\nImmunity of diplomatic missions and the principle of\ninviolability\" under the Vienna Convention.\n\n\nAnd he urges \"Ecuador and Mexico to start a dialogue and\nto take immediate measures, in accordance with the right\ninternational, to resolve the grave issue in a way\nconstructive.\"\n\n\nClosing the debate, the Secretary-General of the Osa, Luis\nAlmagro, it has emphasized that the facts of Quito have constituted\n\"a fundamental vulnus of American international law,\nuniversal and customary\", and hoped that for the opening of\na dialogue between Ecuador and Mexico, the situation created by the blitz\ncan be correct.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Osa",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "meaning": "poss",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "blitz",
                "meaning": "dobj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Embassy",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Permanent Council",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Organization of American States (Osa",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2/day",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Member States",
                "start_char": 408,
                "end_char": 425,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Foreigners Alejandro Davalos",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuadorian",
                "start_char": 628,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jorge Glas",
                "start_char": 650,
                "end_char": 660,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 717,
                "end_char": 723,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Vienna Convention",
                "start_char": 839,
                "end_char": 860,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 878,
                "end_char": 885,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 890,
                "end_char": 896,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luis\nAlmagro",
                "start_char": 1100,
                "end_char": 1112,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Quito",
                "start_char": 1150,
                "end_char": 1155,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 1198,
                "end_char": 1206,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 1305,
                "end_char": 1312,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 1317,
                "end_char": 1323,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mosca, non invitati in Svizzera, in ogni caso rifiuteremmo",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:23:51 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/10/mosca-non-invitati-in-svizzera-in-ogni-caso-rifiuteremmo_66539371-c6ff-4b04-b803-860577ad8877.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo ha dichiarato l'ambasciata russa a Berna",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Svizzera non ha invitato la Russia\nalla conferenza per la pace in Ucraina, e qualora dovesse\narrivare un invito Mosca lo rifiuterà. Lo ha affermato\nl'ambasciata russa in Svizzera, secondo quanto riportato dalla\nTass. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 72,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.5109348,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Moscow, not invited in Switzerland, anyway we would refuse",
        "en_content": "Switzerland has not invited Russia\nat the conference for peace in Ukraine, and if it were to\na Moscow invitation will refuse it. He said\nthe Russian embassy in Switzerland, according to the\nTass.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, 'Mosca assente in Svizzera? Non vuole la pace'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:13 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/10/tajani-mosca-assente-in-svizzera-non-vuole-la-pace_9f6c79e1-4b9d-4535-921a-f3263e8fe16e.html",
        "subtitle": "'La Russia si mette dalla parte sbagliata'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"L'assenza della Russia alla\nConferenza di pace in Svizzera sull'Ucraina non è un buon\nsegnale: vuol dire che non vuole la pace. Si mette dalla parte\nsbagliata, quella in cui è il più forte che soffoca il più\ndebole, che non può essere la regola\". Lo afferma il vicepremier\ne ministro degli Esteri, Antonio Tajani, arrivando all'assemblea\nnazionale di Cifa Italia. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 74,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.5372279,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Tajani, 'Moscow absent in Switzerland? He doesn't want peace.",
        "en_content": "\"The absence of Russia to\nPeace conference in Switzerland on Ukraine is not a good\nsignal: means he doesn't want peace. Put it on the side\nthe one in which is the strongest that suffocates the most\nweak, which cannot be the rule.\" The vicepremier says\nand Minister of Foreign Affairs, Antonio Tajani, arriving at the assembly\nnational of Cifa Italy.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "meaning": "ROOT",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "NOUN"
            },
            {
                "word": "absent",
                "meaning": "appos",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "peace",
                "meaning": "dobj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Switzerland",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cifa Italy",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, uccisi 3 figli di Haniyeh, tutti operativi di Hamas",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:29:34 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/10/israele-uccisi-3-figli-di-haniyeh-tutti-operativi-di-hamas_0028f854-1c80-4170-95dd-67b88d4e99e1.html",
        "subtitle": "'Uno era un comandante di cellula delle Brigate Qassam'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Idf ha confermato di aver\nucciso i 3 figli del leader di Hamas Ismail Haniyeh a Gaza. Lo\nha detto il portavoce dell'esercito spiegando che tutti e 3\n\"erano operativi militari\" di Hamas\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Amir Haniyeh - ha aggiunto -era un comandante di cellula\ndelle Brigate Qassam, ala militare di Hamas; Mohammad Haniyeh\nera un operativo militare di Hamas come Hazem Haniyeh\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 70,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.5424178,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Israel, killed 3 sons of Haniyeh, all operative of Hamas",
        "en_content": "The Idf has confirmed that\nkilled the 3 sons of the leader of Hamas Ismail Haniyeh in Gaza. I do.\nsaid the spokesman of the army explaining that all 3\n\"They were military operatives\" of Hamas.\n\n\n\"Amir Haniyeh - he added - was a cell commander\nof the Qassam Brigades, military wing of Hamas; Mohammad Haniyeh\nwas a military operative of Hamas like Hazem Haniyeh.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "sons",
                "meaning": "dobj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "operative",
                "meaning": "ccomp",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ismail Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Amir Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Qassam Brigades",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohammad Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 341,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hazem Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "FdI ha votato sì a gran parte del Patto Ue sui migranti",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:20:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/10/fdi-ha-votato-si-a-gran-parte-del-patto-ue-sui-migranti_1d3ab7c5-69f3-4db6-9e70-548020f5d1a1.html",
        "subtitle": "Contrari solo al testo sostenuto dal Pd. Ma Ecr si è spaccata",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Fratelli d'Italia all'Eurocamera\nha votato a favore in sette votazioni su dieci sui testi del\nPatto di migrazione esprimendosi in maniera contraria solo sul\nregolamento sull'asilo e la migrazione - l'unico appoggiato dal\nPd - che prevede la solidarietà obbligatoria dei Paesi membri.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tHa votato, invece, sì ai due testi considerati più in bilico nel\npacchetto: quello sulle procedure di asilo accelerate e quello\nsulla gestione delle crisi migratorie. Su entrambi i testi la\nmaggioranza del gruppo Ecr, di cui Fdi fa parte, ha votato\ncontro. Sul testo sulla gestione delle crisi, inoltre, 2\neurodeputati si sono astenuti: Berlato e Fiocchi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 73,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.567883,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "FdI voted most of the EU Pact on migrants",
        "en_content": "Brothers of Italy to the Eurocamera\nvoted in favour of seven out of ten votes on the texts of the\nMigration pact expressing itself against only the\nRegulation on asylum and migration - the only one supported by\nPd - which provides for the compulsory solidarity of the Member States.\n\n\nHe voted, instead, yes to the two texts considered more biblical in\npackage: that on accelerated asylum procedures and that\non the management of migration crises. On both texts\nmajority of the group Ecr, of which Fdi is a member, voted\nagainst. On the text on crisis management, 2\nEuro MPs abstained: Berlato and Fiocchi.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "FdI",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pact",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "migrants",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the EU Pact",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brothers of Italy",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Eurocamera",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "ten",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Migration",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Member States",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecr",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 487,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fdi",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 564,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Euro",
                "start_char": 566,
                "end_char": 570,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Fiocchi",
                "start_char": 598,
                "end_char": 605,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Biden, 'la nostra alleanza è difensiva, non minaccia nessuno'",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:55:48 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/10/biden-la-nostra-alleanza-e-difensiva-non-minaccia-nessuno_77c4736a-14cf-490c-b957-b6c3d2a7daec.html",
        "subtitle": "Intesa con Tokyo-Canberra 'per riportare stabilità nell'area'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'alleanza con il Giappone e\nl'Australia è \"puramente difensiva e serve a riportare la\nstabilità nell'Indopacifico\". Lo ha detto Joe Biden in una\nconferenza stampa con il premier giapponese Fumio Kishida\nsottolineando che il patto \"non è una minaccia a nessun Paese\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 65,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.586478,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Biden, our alliance is defensive, no threat to anyone.",
        "en_content": "The alliance with Japan and\nAustralia is \"purely defensive and serves to restore\nstability in the Indopathic.\" Joe Biden said in one\npress conference with Japanese Premier Fumio Kishida\nstressing that the pact \"is not a threat to any country\".\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "AUX"
            },
            {
                "word": "alliance",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "AUX"
            },
            {
                "word": "threat",
                "meaning": "attr",
                "pos": "AUX"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indopathic",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japanese",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fumio Kishida",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa, imminente l'attacco a Israele dall'Iran o gruppi vicini",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 11 Apr 2024 10:53:46 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-11",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/10/usa-imminente-lattacco-a-israele-dalliran-o-gruppi-vicini_29777691-823f-426f-8fb8-81c742d7271c.html",
        "subtitle": "Bloomberg cita fonti americane: 'Possibile nei prossimi giorni'",
        "content": "Gli Stati Uniti e i loro alleati ritengono che un attacco con missili o droni da parte dell'Iran o da gruppi filo-iraniani a Israele sia 'imminente'. Lo riporta l'agenzia Bloomberg citando alcune fonti, secondo le quali il potenziale attacco - possibilmente usando missili ad alta precisione - potrebbe avvenire nei prossimi giorni. I target israeliani che potrebbero essere colpiti sono militari o governativi.   \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.6012058,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Use, imminent attack on Israel from Iran or neighboring groups",
        "en_content": "The United States and their allies believe that an attack with missiles or drones by Iran or pro-Iranian groups in Israel is 'imminent'. The Bloomberg agency reports it citing some sources, according to which the potential attack - possibly using high-precision missiles - could take place in the coming days. The Israeli targets that might be affected are military or governmental.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "attack",
                "meaning": "appos",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "neighboring",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "NOUN"
            },
            {
                "word": "groups",
                "meaning": "conj",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "pro-Iranian",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bloomberg",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the coming days",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Proteste contro Milei, scontri e arresti a Buenos Aires",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:16:59 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/04/10/proteste-contro-milei-scontri-e-arresti-a-buenos-aires_31178a98-bf81-4475-805e-e348c5e51439.html",
        "subtitle": "Almeno 11 persone detenute e cinque ricoverate",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Una nuova giornata di\nproteste contro la politica economica  del governo\nultraliberista di Javier Milei è culminata oggi in una serie di\nscontri e incidenti tra manifestanti e polizia nel centro di\nBuenos Aires.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il bilancio, affermano le autorità, è di 11 persone\narrestate, mentre le organizzazioni sociali (Polo Obrero e\nUnione dei Lavoratori dell'Economia Popolare) denunciano anche\nvari feriti per l'uso di proiettili di gomma da parte delle\nforze dell'ordine, intervenute anche con camion idranti.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Fonti del Polo Obrero hanno riferito all'ANSA di almeno\ncinque manifestanti ricoverati in ospedale mentre tra le vittime\nfigura anche un giornalista dell'emittente Cronica Tv, colpito\nal volto da un proiettile di gomma sparato dalla polizia. \n   Gli scontri hanno preso il via dopo che i manifestanti hanno\ncercato di interrompere il transito nella principale arteria del\ncentro, la Avenida 9 di Luglio con la polizia che ha applicato\nil nuovo protocollo anti-picchetti.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La protesta era stata indetta dalle organizzazioni sociali\ncontro \"la politica di aggiustamenti, licenziamenti e\nprivatizzazioni\" del governo. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.6230373,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Protected against Milei, clashes and arrests in Buenos Aires",
        "en_content": "A new day of\nprotests against government economic policy\nJavier Milei's ultra-liberist culminated today in a series of\nclashes and incidents between protesters and police in the center of\nBuenos Aires.\n\n\nThe budget, says the authorities, is 11 people\narrested, while social organizations (Polo Obrero and\nUnion of People's Economy Workers) also denounce\nvarious injured for the use of rubber bullets by the\nlaw enforcement, even with water trucks.\n\n\nSources of the Obrero Pole reported to the NSA at least\nfive protesters hospitalized while among the victims\nfigure also a journalist of the broadcaster Cronica Tv, hit\nface from a rubber bullet shot by the police.\nThe clashes took their way after the protesters\ntried to stop transit in the main artery of\ncenter, the Avenida 9 of July with the police that applied\nthe new anti-picking protocol.\n\n\nThe protest was called by social organizations\nagainst \"the policy of adjustments, dismissals and\nprivatization\" of the government.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "clashes",
                "meaning": "conj",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "arrests",
                "meaning": "conj",
                "pos": "NOUN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos",
                "meaning": "compound",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aires",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei's",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "11",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polo Obrero",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Union of People's Economy Workers",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Obrero Pole",
                "start_char": 461,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "NSA",
                "start_char": 493,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "five",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 510,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cronica Tv",
                "start_char": 603,
                "end_char": 613,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "9 of July",
                "start_char": 777,
                "end_char": 786,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Biden, Hamas si deve muovere sulla proposta di tregua",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:17:19 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/10/biden-hamas-si-deve-muovere-sulla-proposta-di-tregua_290513b1-f794-4517-babe-bf7e02e7c9e1.html",
        "subtitle": "'Nei colloqui con Netanyahu sono stato molto diretto e franco'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Hamas \"deve muoversi\" sulla\nproposta di cessate il fuoco: lo ha detto Joe Biden nella\nconferenza stampa congiunta col premier giapponese Fumio Kishida\nalla Casa Bianca.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Sono stato molto diretto e franco nei colloqui con\nNetanyahu, ora vedremo cosa fa in termini di rispetto degli\nimpegni presi\", ha aggiunto Biden.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il presidente Usa ha poi ricordato che le priorità sono\nl'aumento degli aiuti umanitari, ridurre il numero delle vittime\ncivili e la liberazione degli ostaggi nel contesto di un accordo\nper il cessate il fuoco di sei settimane. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847634.6327243,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:34",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Biden, Hamas must move on the proposal for a truce",
        "en_content": "Hamas \"must move\" on\nproposal for ceasefire: Joe Biden said in\nJapanese press conference Fumio Kishida\nThe White House.\n\n\n\"I was very direct and frank in talks with\nNetanyahu, now we'll see what he does in terms of respect for\nBiden added.\n\n\nThe US President then recalled that priorities are\nincreasing humanitarian aid, reducing the number of victims\nCivilians and the liberation of hostages in the context of an agreement\nfor the ceasefire of six weeks.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "proposal",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "truce",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japanese",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fumio Kishida",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The White House",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "six weeks",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Haaretz, tre figli di Haniyeh uccisi in un raid a Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 16:53:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/10/haaretz-tre-figli-di-haniyeh-uccisi-in-un-raid-a-gaza_f9ba2126-6d1d-421e-a57c-8ed587c1605e.html",
        "subtitle": "Sarebbero coinvolti anche i nipoti del capo di Hamas all'estero",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Rapporti da Gaza hanno segnalato\nche tre figli del leader di Hamas all'estero Ismail Haniyeh sono\nstati uccisi in un attacco israeliano a Gaza. Lo ha riferito\nHaaretz. Secondo altri media si tratta di un attacco su un'auto\nche avrebbe coinvolto anche i nipoti del capo di Hamas. Non si\nhanno al momento altre conferme. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 87,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847638.926838,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:38",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Haaretz, three sons of Haniyeh killed in a raid in Gaza",
        "en_content": "Reports from Gaza reported\nthat three children of the leader of Hamas abroad Ismail Haniyeh are\nwere killed in an Israeli attack in Gaza. He reported it.\nHaaretz. According to other media it is an attack on a car\nwho would also involve the grandchildren of Hamas' boss. You don't\nhave at the moment other confirmations.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Haaretz",
                "meaning": "ROOT",
                "pos": "PROPN"
            },
            {
                "word": "sons",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "raid",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ismail Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 77,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haaretz",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Haniyeh conferma ad al Jazeera la morte di 3 figli a Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:15:05 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/10/haniyeh-conferma-ad-al-jazeera-la-morte-di-3-figli-a-gaza_6b264fe7-3644-4fa0-b6e2-bc6631ddff5d.html",
        "subtitle": "Colpiti anche alcuni nipoti del leader di Hamas. 'Sono martiri'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il leader di Hamas Ismail Haniyeh\nha confermato, in un'intervista ad al Jazeera, l'uccisione di\ntre suoi figli in un attacco israeliano a Gaza, che ha\nidentificato in Hazem, Amir e Mohammad. Haniyeh ha aggiunto che\nsono stati colpiti anche alcuni suoi nipoti nello stesso\nattacco. \"Attraverso il sangue dei martiri e il dolore dei\nferiti - ha detto, secondo la stessa fonte - creiamo speranza,\nfuturo, l'indipendenza e la libertà per il nostro popolo e la\nnostra nazione\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 86,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1712847638.934763,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-11 17:00:38",
        "filename": "ner_conc_en_2024-04-11T17.00.33E1712854833.475293.json",
        "en_title": "Haniyeh confirms to the Jazeera the death of 3 children in Gaza",
        "en_content": "The leader of Hamas Ismail Haniyeh\nconfirmed, in an interview with the Jazeera, the killing of\nthree of his sons in an Israeli attack in Gaza, which he has\nIdentified in Hazem, Amir and Mohammad. Haniyeh added that\nsome of his grandchildren were also hit\nattack. \"Through the blood of martyrs and the pain of\nwounded - said, according to the same source - we create hope,\nfuture, independence and freedom for our people and\nour nation.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "concepts": [
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "meaning": "nsubj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jazeera",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "death",
                "meaning": "dobj",
                "pos": "VERB"
            },
            {
                "word": "children",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "meaning": "pobj",
                "pos": "ADP"
            }
        ],
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jazeera",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ismail Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jazeera",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 100,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hazem",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Amir",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mohammad",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "In Messico abitanti Ocosingo arrestano sindaco, ripari le buche",
        "date_raw": "Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:29:09 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-10",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
