[
    {
        "title": "Gb, Trump ha creato opportunità ma servono garanzie a Kiev",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:51:55 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/24/gb-trump-ha-creato-opportunita-ma-servono-garanzie-a-kiev_c828fa9f-b46c-4c37-8685-c9696d2b834c.html",
        "subtitle": "Starmer, 'Ucraina deve avere un posto ai colloqui di pace'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente americano Donald\nTrump ha \"cambiato il dibattito globale\" nelle ultime settimane\ne ha \"creato un'opportunità\" per la pace in Ucraina ma servono\ngaranzie di sicurezza a Kiev. Lo ha detto il premier britannico\nKeir Starmer in videocollegamento coi leader europei e\ninternazionali riuniti a Kiev per il terzo anniversario\ndall'inizio del conflitto con la Russia. \"Se vogliamo che la\npace duri, l'Ucraina deve avere un posto al tavolo delle\ntrattative - ha sottolineato Starmer - e un accordo deve basarsi\nsu un'Ucraina sovrana, sostenuta da forti garanzie di\nsicurezza\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402018.2545671,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.18",
        "en_title": "Gb, Trump has created opportunities but serve guarantees in Kiev",
        "en_content": "American President Donald\nTrump has \"changed global debate\" in recent weeks\nand has \"created an opportunity\" for peace in Ukraine but serve\nsecurity guarantees in Kiev. The British Prime Minister said so.\nKeir Starmer in video connection with European leaders and\ninternational meeting in Kiev for the third anniversary\nfrom the beginning of the conflict with Russia. \"If we want the\nhard peace, Ukraine must have a place at the table of\nnegotiations - it has emphasized Starmer - and an agreement must be based\non a sovereign Ukraine, supported by strong guarantees of\nsecurity.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Starmer, 'Ukraine must have a seat in peace talks'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald\nTrump",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent weeks",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Keir Starmer",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 251,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 289,
                "end_char": 293,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 527,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Adolescente indiana violentata per 5 anni da decine di uomini",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:26:02 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-24",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2025/02/23/adolescente-indiana-violentata-per-5-anni-da-decine-di-uomini_575675c7-be21-480e-8dbe-934ae8fb388f.html",
        "subtitle": "Cnn: 'Gli abusi sono iniziati quando aveva 13 anni da parte del suo vicino di casa' ",
        "content": " L'orribile vicenda, descritta nei dettagli in alcuni documenti esaminati dalla Cnn,ed è emersa dopo che la vittima ha parlato con un consulente in visita al suo college, raccontando nei dettagli gli anni di abusi subiti. Gli stupri sono iniziati 5 anni fa quando la giovane aveva appena 13 anni: figlia di poveri lavoratori provenienti da una delle comunità più emarginate dell'India, sarebbe stata vittima di abusi sessuali da parte di uno dei suoi vicini nel villaggio in cui viveva. , e  e ragazzi nei successivi cinque anni. In totale sono stati a, la cui identità non è stata rivelata, in base alle leggi dello Stato che ne protegge l'incolumità. Altri due uomini ricercati in relazione al caso sono fuggiti dal Paese, ha detto alla Cnn il vice ispettore generale della polizia del Kerala, Ajeetha Begum. Tra gli accusati ci sono i suoi compagni di scuola, parenti, vicini di casa: uomini provenienti da ogni angolo della sua vita, da minorenni a quarantenni, secondo i documenti sul caso e le interviste con la polizia locale. \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402020.12658,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.20",
        "en_title": "Indian teenager raped for 5 years by dozens of men",
        "en_content": "The horrible story, described in detail in some documents examined by Cnn, and emerged after the victim spoke with a consultant visiting his college, telling in detail the years of abuse suffered. The rapes began 5 years ago when the young man was only 13 years old: daughter of poor workers from one of the most marginalized communities in India, she would have been victim of sexual abuse by one of her neighbors in the village she lived in. , and boys over the next five years. In total they were a, whose identity was not revealed, according to the laws of the State that protects its safety. Two more men wanted in relation to the case fled the country, told Cnn the Deputy General Inspector of the Police of Kerala, Ajeetha Begum. Among the accused are his schoolmates, relatives, neighbors: men from every corner of his life, from underage to forty years, according to the case documents and interviews with the local police.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Cnn: 'The abuse began when he was 13 years old by his neighbor'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Indian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 years",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "13 years old",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the years",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "5 years ago",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "only 13 years old",
                "start_char": 248,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "India",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the next five years",
                "start_char": 460,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 565,
                "end_char": 570,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Two",
                "start_char": 597,
                "end_char": 600,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 664,
                "end_char": 667,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "General Inspector",
                "start_char": 679,
                "end_char": 696,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kerala",
                "start_char": 714,
                "end_char": 720,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ajeetha Begum",
                "start_char": 722,
                "end_char": 735,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "forty years",
                "start_char": 850,
                "end_char": 861,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Melania torna alla Casa Bianca, mancava da un mese",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:00:54 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/02/23/melania-torna-alla-casa-bianca-mancava-da-un-mese_be300d9f-5208-4ebc-9af5-58fd6c0dad57.html",
        "subtitle": "Per la cena annuale con i governatori del Paese",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Dopo un'assenza di quattro settimane\nda Washington, la first lady Melania Trump è tornata alla Casa\nBianca ieri per la cena annuale e il ricevimento con i\ngovernatori della nazione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Ha lavorato duramente per assicurarsi che tutto fosse bello.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tEd è molto brava in questo\", ha detto il presidente Donald\nTrump, scrive la Cnn, in un breve discorso ai governatori nella\nEast Room illuminata da candele, con la moglie seduta lì vicino\na un tavolo pieno di vasi traboccanti di ortensie bianche e\ntulipani. Anche se è sempre più probabile che Melania potrebbe\nessere coinvolta nell'organizzazione interna della Casa Bianca,\nche a breve dovrebbe aprire ai tour dei visitatori, la first\nlady non ha avuto molto interesse a essere presente.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Da quando suo marito ha prestato giuramento il 20 gennaio,\nnon ha trascorso molto tempo alla Casa Bianca, secondo fonti a\nconoscenza diretta della sua agenda. Melania, viene fatto\nnotare, è stata una presenza attiva durante i primi giorni del\nsecondo mandato del presidente, ma dopo aver raggiunto il marito\nper un viaggio il 24 gennaio nella Carolina del Nord e in\nCalifornia devastate da calamità naturali, non è più tornata a\nWashington fino a ieri. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 68,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402020.198651,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.20",
        "en_title": "Melania returned to the White House for a month",
        "en_content": "After a four-week absence\nfrom Washington, the first lady Melania Trump has returned to the House\nWhite yesterday for the annual dinner and reception with the\nGovernors of the nation.\n\n\n\"He worked hard to make sure everything was beautiful.\n\n\nAnd she's very good at this,\" said President Donald.\nTrump, writes Cnn, in a short speech to governors in\nEast Room lit by candles, with his wife sitting nearby\nat a table full of overflowing vases of white and\ntulips. Although it is increasingly likely that Melania could\nbeing involved in the internal organization of the White House,\nthat shortly should open to visitors tours, the first\nLady had no interest in being present.\n\n\nSince her husband swore on January 20,\ndid not spend much time at the White House, according to sources to\ndirect knowledge of his agenda. Melania, is done\nnotice, it was an active presence during the first days of\nsecond term of the president, but after reaching the husband\nfor a trip on 24 January in North Carolina and\nCalifornia devastated by natural disasters, has not returned to\nWashington until yesterday.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "For annual dinner with country governors",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "annual",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "four-week",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Melania Trump",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "annual",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald",
                "start_char": 288,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 313,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "East Room",
                "start_char": 349,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Melania",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 578,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 628,
                "end_char": 633,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "January 20",
                "start_char": 702,
                "end_char": 712,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 741,
                "end_char": 756,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the first days",
                "start_char": 872,
                "end_char": 886,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 890,
                "end_char": 896,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "24 January",
                "start_char": 965,
                "end_char": 975,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "North Carolina",
                "start_char": 979,
                "end_char": 993,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "California",
                "start_char": 998,
                "end_char": 1008,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 1062,
                "end_char": 1072,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 1079,
                "end_char": 1088,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Femen a seno nudo a Berlino per protestare contro la Russia e l'Afd",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:27:39 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/2025/02/23/femen-a-seno-nudo-a-berlino-per-protestare-contro-la-russia-e-lafd_dedb049d-68fc-4d9a-8122-5c491f329ae6.html",
        "subtitle": "Attivista travestita da Hitler portata via dalla sicurezza ",
        "content": "Un'attivista del gruppo femminista FEMEN protesta contro la Russia e il partito dell'Alternativa per la Germania (AfD), il giorno in cui la Germania tiene le elezioni federali davanti all'edificio del Reichstag a Berlino. Il gruppo accusa il partito tedesco di destra AfD di avere legami con la Russia.Una protesta simile si è svolta questa mattina davanti all'ambasciata tedesca a Kiev, in Ucraina.\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 66,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.3347933,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Breastfemen naked in Berlin to protest against Russia and the Afd",
        "en_content": "An activist of the feminist group FEMEN protests against Russia and the Alternative party for Germany (AfD), the day Germany holds federal elections in front of the Reichstag building in Berlin. The group accuses the right-wing German party AfD of having ties with Russia. A similar protest took place this morning in front of the German embassy in Kiev, Ukraine.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Attivista disguised by Hitler taken away from security",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Berlin",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Attivista",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hitler",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "FEMEN",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Alternative party",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "AfD",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 124,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reichstag",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 174,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Berlin",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "German",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "AfD",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this morning",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 314,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "German",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 349,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 355,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev, nei territori occupati 350 miliardi in risorse naturali",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:43:00 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/kiev-nei-territori-occupati-350-miliardi-in-risorse-naturali_3ef28195-982d-4a01-875a-f5310dbe81af.html",
        "subtitle": "Tra cui il titanio",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            (ANSA-AFP) - KIEV, 23 FEB - L'Ucraina stima di avere risorse\nnaturali \"essenziali\" per un valore di 350 miliardi di dollari,\ntra cui il titanio, nel territorio occupato dalla Russia. Lo ha\naffermato il vice primo ministro ucraino Yulia Svyrydenko.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Abbiamo informazioni secondo cui, sfortunatamente, nel\nterritorio temporaneamente occupato si trovano materiali\nessenziali per un valore di circa 350 miliardi di dollari\", ha\ndetto in una conferenza stampa a Kiev, nel contesto delle\ntensioni con gli Stati Uniti in merito a un accordo proposto sui\nminerali ucraini. (ANSA-AFP).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 65,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.3791695,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Kiev, in the occupied territories 350 billion in natural resources",
        "en_content": "(ANSA-AFP) - KIEV, 23 FEB - Ukraine estimates to have resources\nnatural \"essential\" for a value of 350 billion dollars,\nincluding titanium, in the territory occupied by Russia. He did.\nDeputy Prime Minister Yulia Svyrydenko said.\n\n\n\"We have information that, unfortunately, in\ntemporarily occupied territory are found materials\nessential for a value of approximately 350 billion dollars\", he has\nsaid in a press conference in Kiev, in the context of\ntensions with the United States on a proposed agreement on\nUkrainian minerals. (ANSA-AFP).\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "including titanium",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "350 billion",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "23",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "350 billion dollars",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yulia Svyrydenko",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "approximately 350 billion dollars",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 430,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 509,
                "end_char": 518,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 530,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev, 'lavoriamo ad alternative a Starlink di Musk, esistono'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:06:15 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/kiev-lavoriamo-ad-alternative-a-starlink-di-musk-esistono_9428104e-20c7-4c45-b0b8-39bc79feaaeb.html",
        "subtitle": "Nel contesto delle tensioni con Trump e Musk",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Ucraina sta lavorando a una\n\"alternativa\" ai sistemi di telecomunicazioni Starlink,\nfondamentali per il suo esercito, in un contesto di forti\ntensioni con il presidente americano e il suo alleato\nmiliardario Elon Musk, proprietario del gruppo che li produce.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo afferma il ministro della Difesa ucraino. \"Stiamo già\nlavorando su questo. Le alternative esistono\", ha detto il\nministro Rustem Umerov in una conferenza stampa a Kiev. \"Una\nsoluzione esiste già\", ha aggiunto, promettendo di rivelarne\npresto i dettagli. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.3853767,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Kiev, 'we work at alternatives to Musk Starlink, exist'",
        "en_content": "Ukraine is working on a\n\"alternative\" to Starlink telecommunications systems,\nfundamental for his army, in a context of strong\ntensions with the American president and his ally\nbillionaire Elon Musk, owner of the group that produces them.\n\n\nThe Ukrainian Defence Minister says so. \"We are already\nworking on this. There are alternatives,\" he said.\nMinister Rustem Umerov at a press conference in Kiev. \"A\nsolution already exists\", he added, promising to reveal\nsoon the details.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In the context of tensions with Trump and Musk",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Musk Starlink",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump and Musk",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starlink",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elon Musk",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rustem Umerov",
                "start_char": 357,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mosca, nuovi colloqui Usa-Russia la settimana prossima",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:11:57 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/mosca-nuovi-colloqui-usa-russia-la-settimana-prossima_4a794fe8-23af-4934-b112-bb08b59013f9.html",
        "subtitle": "Al livello di direttori politici",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il prossimo round dei colloqui\nUsa-Russia si svolgerà alla fine della settimana prossima. Lo ha\nriferito un alto funzionario russo, specificando che i colloqui\nsaranno a livello di direttori politici. Lo riporta la Tass.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.3923433,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Moscow, new US-Russia talks next week",
        "en_content": "Next round of talks\nUSA-Russia will take place at the end of next week. He did.\nreported a high Russian official, specifying that talks\nwill be at the level of political directors. Tass.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "At the level of political directors",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next week",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of next week",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Von der Leyen, 'il sostegno all'Ucraina è incrollabile'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:44:46 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/von-der-leyen-il-sostegno-allucraina-e-incrollabile_a95e95f2-ab7e-4160-bda0-92d9976904b9.html",
        "subtitle": "La presidente: 'Buoni colloqui telefonici con Macron e Starmer'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Questo fine settimana ho avuto\nbuoni scambi telefonici con\nEmmanuel Macron e Keir Starmer. Abbiamo discusso del nostro\nincrollabile sostegno all'Ucraina, dal punto di vista\nfinanziario e militare. Abbiamo condiviso gli aggiornamenti sui\nnostri contatti con i partner statunitensi e discusso i piani\nper la difesa e la sicurezza del nostro continente\". Lo scrive,\nsu X, la presidente della Commissione Ue Ursula von der Leyen.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.4023027,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Von der Leyen, 'support to Ukraine is unshakeable'",
        "en_content": "\"This weekend I had\ngood telephone exchanges with\nEmmanuel Macron and Keir Starmer. We discussed our\nunwavering support for Ukraine, from the point of view\nfinancial and military. We shared updates on\nour contacts with US partners and discussed plans\nfor the defence and security of our continent.\" He writes it,\non X, the President of the Commission Ue Ursula von der Leyen.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The President: 'Good phone interviews with Macron and Starmer'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Von der",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "This weekend",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emmanuel Macron",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Keir Starmer",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ue Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 368,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, 'pronto a dimettermi se aderiremo alla Nato'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:16:43 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/zelensky-pronto-a-dimettermi-se-aderiremo-alla-nato_225bea72-b3bd-45a0-a5c4-192d69a48163.html",
        "subtitle": "Presidente a forum 'Ucraina: Anno 2025'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Volodymyr Zelensky si è detto pronto\na dimettersi \"immediatamente\" in cambio dell'adesione\ndell'Ucraina alla Nato. Il presidente ucraino sta rispondendo ad\nalcune domande alla conclusione del forum 'Ucraina: Anno 2025'.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tInterpellato su quali garanzie di sicurezza chieda a Trump, ha\ndetto: \"Se serve che lasci questa sedia, sono pronto a farlo e\nposso anche scambiare la mia posizione con l'adesione\ndell'Ucraina alla Nato\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Zelensky ha poi aggiunto: \"Sarei felice di rinunciare alla\npresidenza se fosse per la pace dell'Ucraina\". Sottolineando di\nessere concentrato sulla sicurezza dell'Ucraina ora, e non tra\n20 anni, e di non avere come obiettivo quello di restare\npresidente per un decennio. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.4085886,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, 'read to resign if we join NATO'",
        "en_content": "Volodymyr Zelensky said hello\nto resign \"immediately\" in exchange for membership\nof Ukraine to NATO. The Ukrainian President is answering\nsome questions at the end of the forum 'Ukraine: Year 2025.\n\n\nAsked about what security guarantees he asks Trump, he has\nsaid: \"If you need me to leave this chair, I'm ready to do it and\nI can also exchange my position with membership\nof Ukraine to NATO.\"\n\n\nZelensky added: \"I'd be happy to give up\nif it were for the peace of Ukraine.\" Emphasis of\nbe focused on the security of Ukraine now, and not between\n20 years, and not having as a goal to remain\nPresident for a decade.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "President of forum 'Ukraine: Year 2025",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Year 2025",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Year 2025",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 196,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 387,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 465,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 524,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "20 years",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 554,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "a decade",
                "start_char": 605,
                "end_char": 613,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Colombia, governo Petro retrocede su politica di 'pace totale'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:14:21 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/23/colombia-governo-petro-retrocede-su-politica-di-pace-totale_dceeeb5d-2d53-466f-ba5b-012972b82558.html",
        "subtitle": "Il nuovo ministro della Difesa, 'ha sortito l'effetto contrario'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nel contesto di una grave\nescalation della violenza delle guerriglie in tutta la Colombia,\nil governo di Gustavo Petro ammette adesso che uno dei\nprincipali punti del suo programma politico, il progetto di\n'pace totale', ha sortito fino ad oggi l'effetto contrario.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Lo afferma in un'intervista rilasciata al quotidiano 'El\nTiempo' e pubblicata oggi, il nuovo ministro della Difesa, l'ex\ngenerale Pedro Sánchez. \"All'epoca in cui venne elaborata la\nstrategia della politica di pace totale, i rischi connessi\nvennero presentati al Presidente che ritenne corretto\nintraprendere comunque questa strada (...) La conclusione oggi è\nche ciò che ci si aspettava non è stato raggiunto e invece\ndiavere la pace succede il contrario (...)  è evidente che il\ncancro (della guerriglia) è cresciuto\", ha affermato Sánchez.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il nuovo titolare della Difesa ha quindi esortato le\nguerriglie a deporre le armi al di là dei meccanismi stabiliti\ndal processo di pace.  \"Per smobilitare non è necessario un\naccordo di pace\", ha detto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'ultimo rilevamento sulla situazione dell'ordine pubblico e\ndella violenza in Colombia effettuata dall'ufficio del Garante\ndei cittadini (Defensor del Pueblo) esibisce la 'fotografia di\nun Paese in guerra'. Secondo le cifre dell'ombudsman colombiano,\nil recente sciopero armato dichiarato nel Chocó dalla guerriglia\ndell'Eln ha provocato più di 3.500 sfollati che si sommano ai\n51.000 per le violenze scatenate dalla guerriglie nella regione\ndel Catatumbo, nel dipartimento del Norte de Santander, dove si\ncontano anche 63 morti e 9 dispersi tra i dissidenti che hanno\naderito agli accordi di pace. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.4148393,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Colombia, Petro government retrocede on 'total peace' policy",
        "en_content": "In the context of a grave\nescalation of guerrilla violence throughout Colombia,\nGustavo Petro's government now admits that one of\nmain points of its political programme, the project\n'total mouth', has so far produced the opposite effect.\n\n\nHe says it in an interview with the newspaper 'El\nTiempo' and published today, the new defense minister, the former\nGeneral Pedro Sánchez. \"At the time when the\nstrategy of total peace policy, the associated risks\nwere presented to the President that he believed correct\nthe conclusion today is\nthat what was expected was not achieved and instead\nto have peace is the opposite (...) it is evident that the\ncancer (of guerrilla) has grown,\" said Sánchez.\n\n\nThe new owner of Defense then exhorted the\nIt is a matter for the Commission to take the necessary steps to ensure that the Commission is not able to take the necessary steps.\nfrom the peace process. \"To demobilize it is not necessary a\npeace agreement,\" he said.\n\n\nThe last survey on the situation of the public order and\nviolence in Colombia carried out by the Garante's office\nof the citizens (Defensor del Pueblo) exhibits the 'photography of\na country in war. According to the figures of Colombian ombudsman,\nthe recent armed strike declared in the Chocó from the guerrilla\nof the Eln has provoked more than 3,500 displaced people who sum up to\n51,000 for the violence of guerrillas in the region\nof Catatumbo, in the department of Norte de Santander, where\nThere are also 63 dead and 9 missing among the dissidents who have\nadhere to the peace agreements.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The new defense minister, 'has created the opposite effect'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gustavo Petro's",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "El\nTiempo'",
                "start_char": 287,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Sánchez",
                "start_char": 364,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 526,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sánchez",
                "start_char": 685,
                "end_char": 692,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 713,
                "end_char": 720,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 772,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 820,
                "end_char": 830,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 1031,
                "end_char": 1039,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Garante",
                "start_char": 1059,
                "end_char": 1066,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "del Pueblo",
                "start_char": 1102,
                "end_char": 1112,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombian",
                "start_char": 1189,
                "end_char": 1198,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chocó",
                "start_char": 1250,
                "end_char": 1255,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eln",
                "start_char": 1282,
                "end_char": 1285,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 3,500",
                "start_char": 1299,
                "end_char": 1314,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "51,000",
                "start_char": 1346,
                "end_char": 1352,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Catatumbo",
                "start_char": 1401,
                "end_char": 1410,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norte de Santander",
                "start_char": 1433,
                "end_char": 1451,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "63",
                "start_char": 1474,
                "end_char": 1476,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "9",
                "start_char": 1486,
                "end_char": 1487,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Inviato Trump, accordo sui minerali con Kiev in settimana",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:20:37 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/02/23/inviato-trump-accordo-sui-minerali-con-kiev-in-settimana_629921b5-4b26-4ee2-a29d-9967568de5a1.html",
        "subtitle": "Witkoff: 'Guerra Ucraina è stata provocata, deve finire'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'inviato di Donald Trump per il\nMedio Oriente, Steve Witkoff, si attende che l'accordo sui\nminerali con l'Ucraina sia firmato in settimana. Lo afferma lo\nstesso Witkoff in un'intervista alla Cnn.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La guerra è stata \"provocata. Questo non significa\nnecessariamente che è stata provocata dalla Russia. Allora\nc'erano conversazioni sulla possibilità che l'Ucraina entrasse\nnella Nato. Questo è divenuto una minaccia per i russi\", ha\nproseguito Witkoff. \"La guerra, a prescindere da chi l'ha\niniziata, deve finire. Il presidente vuole essere un\npacificatore\", ha aggiunto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.435714,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Posted Trump, deal on minerals with Kiev in week",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump's envoy for\nMiddle East, Steve Witkoff, expects the agreement on\nminerals with Ukraine are signed in the week. He says it\nWitkoff himself in an interview with Cnn.\n\n\nThe war was \"provoked. This does not mean\nnecessarily that it was provoked by Russia. Then\nThere were conversations about the possibility that Ukraine would enter\nBorn. This has become a threat to the Russians,\" he said.\ncontinued Witkoff. \"The war, no matter who has it\nStarted, it has to end. The president wants to be a\nPeacekeeper,\" he added.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Witkoff: 'Guerra Ukraine has been provoked, must finish'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Witkoff",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guerra Ukraine",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump's",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Middle East",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Steve Witkoff",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the week",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Witkoff",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Witkoff",
                "start_char": 410,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peacekeeper",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, mi aspetto da Trump garanzie di sicurezza",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:24:10 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/zelensky-mi-aspetto-da-trump-garanzie-di-sicurezza_263068ca-776a-40ac-89b1-2fc3e86ca646.html",
        "subtitle": "'E comprensione reciproca, purtroppo non è ancora venuto a Kiev'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Volodymyr Zelensky, nel corso di una\nconferenza stampa, ha detto di essere \"grato\" per il supporto\ndelle amministrazioni Biden e Trump, ma ha aggiunto di\naspettarsi \"comprensione\" dall'attuale presidente americano e\ngaranzie di sicurezza. \"Voglio che ci sia comprensione reciproca\ncon Trump\", ha aggiunto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Zelensky ha spiegato di aver invitato Trump in Ucraina, ma ha\naggiunto che \"purtroppo non ci siamo ancora riusciti\". \"Forse\nverrà o forse andrò io a Washington e sarà molto utile\", ha\nspiegato. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 57,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.454235,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, I expect from Trump security guarantees",
        "en_content": "Volodymyr Zelensky, during a\npress conference, said to be \"free\" for support\nof the Biden and Trump administrations, but he added of\nexpect \"understanding\" from the current American president and\nsecurity guarantees. \"I want mutual understanding\nwith Trump,\" he added.\n\n\nZelensky explained that he invited Trump to Ukraine, but he\nadded that \"unfortunately we have not yet succeeded\". \"Maybe\nwill come or maybe I will go to Washington and will be very useful,\" he said.\nExplained.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'It is mutual understanding, unfortunately he has not yet come to Kiev'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 271,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Inviato Trump, accordo sui minerali con Kiev in settimana",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:20:35 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/inviato-trump-accordo-sui-minerali-con-kiev-in-settimana_202a0b2b-26da-4480-8876-6a11cf8274c5.html",
        "subtitle": "Witkoff: 'Guerra Ucraina è stata provocata, deve finire'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'inviato di Donald Trump per il\nMedio Oriente, Steve Witkoff, si attende che l'accordo sui\nminerali con l'Ucraina sia firmato in settimana. Lo afferma lo\nstesso Witkoff in un'intervista alla Cnn.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La guerra è stata \"provocata. Questo non significa\nnecessariamente che è stata provocata dalla Russia. Allora\nc'erano conversazioni sulla possibilità che l'Ucraina entrasse\nnella Nato. Questo è divenuto una minaccia per i russi\", ha\nproseguito Witkoff. \"La guerra, a prescindere da chi l'ha\niniziata, deve finire. Il presidente vuole essere un\npacificatore\", ha aggiunto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.4650285,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Posted Trump, deal on minerals with Kiev in week",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump's envoy for\nMiddle East, Steve Witkoff, expects the agreement on\nminerals with Ukraine are signed in the week. He says it\nWitkoff himself in an interview with Cnn.\n\n\nThe war was \"provoked. This does not mean\nnecessarily that it was provoked by Russia. Then\nThere were conversations about the possibility that Ukraine would enter\nBorn. This has become a threat to the Russians,\" he said.\ncontinued Witkoff. \"The war, no matter who has it\nStarted, it has to end. The president wants to be a\nPeacekeeper,\" he added.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Witkoff: 'Guerra Ukraine has been provoked, must finish'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Witkoff",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guerra Ukraine",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump's",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Middle East",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Steve Witkoff",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the week",
                "start_char": 114,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Witkoff",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 175,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Witkoff",
                "start_char": 410,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peacekeeper",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Fonti, 'il 6 marzo vertice Ue straordinario sull'Ucraina'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 17:55:50 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/fonti-il-6-marzo-vertice-ue-straordinario-sullucraina_3304599b-4358-405e-bb4f-75d89ef0cdaf.html",
        "subtitle": "Anche la difesa europea sul tavolo dei leader dei 27",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente del Consiglio\neuropeo Antonio Costa, a quanto si apprende da fonti europee,\nnelle prossime ore convocherà un vertice Ue straordinario\nsull'Ucraina e sulla Difesa europea. Il vertice si terrà a\nBruxelles il 6 marzo. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 54,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.502159,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "Sources, 'on March 6th Extraordinary EU summit on Ukraine'",
        "en_content": "The President of the Council\nEuropean Antonio Costa, to learn from European sources,\nin the next few hours will convene an extraordinary EU summit\non Ukraine and European Defence. The summit will be held\nBrussels on 6 March.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "European defence on the table of 27 leaders",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "March 6th",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "27",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Costa",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the next few hours",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European Defence",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "6 March",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Vince la Cdu di Merz in Germania, l'Afd seconda al 19,5%",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:09:47 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/vince-la-cdu-di-merz-in-germania-lafd-seconda-al-195_33f2aeff-0c52-4509-8457-426b8dc317f5.html",
        "subtitle": "Spd solo terza al 16%. Liberali e Bsw rischiano di non entrare",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Unione Cdu/Csu di Friedrich Merz\nvince le elezioni in Germania con il 29%, secondo il primo exit\npoll della tv pubblica Ard. Seconda l'ultradestra di Afd con il\n19,5%, la prima volta nella storia della Repubblica federale.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tSeguono l'Spd al 16%, i Verdi al 13,5%, la Linke all'8,5%.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tRischiano di non entrare al Bundestag i liberali di Fdp con il\n4,9% e Bsw con il 4,7%. La soglia di sbarramento è del 5%.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 53,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740402021.525204,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-24 14:00:21",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-24T13.00.21",
        "en_title": "He wins the Merz Cdu in Germany, the Afd second to 19,5%",
        "en_content": "The Cdu/Csu Union of Friedrich Merz\nwins elections in Germany with 29%, according to the first exit\nPublic TV Ard. Second the highway of Afd with the\n19.5%, the first time in the history of the Federal Republic.\n\n\nThey follow the Spd to 16%, the Greens to 13.5%, the Link to 8.5%.\n\n\nThey refuse to enter the Bundestag the Fdp liberals with the\n4.9% and Bsw with 4.7%. The landing threshold is 5%.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Spd only third to 16%. Liberals and Bsw risk not entering",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Merz Cdu",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "19,5%",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Spd",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "only third",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "16%",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Bsw",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Cdu/Csu Union",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Friedrich Merz",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "29%",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Second",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Afd",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "19.5%",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Federal Republic",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spd",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "16%",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Greens",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "13.5%",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "8.5%",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Bundestag",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fdp",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "4.9%",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Bsw",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 356,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4.7%",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "5%",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Seggi aperti in Germania, alle 14.00 l'affluenza è stata del 52% ",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:04:14 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-23",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/23/seggi-aperti-in-germania-alle-14.00-laffluenza-e-del-52-_bf2fde48-e8de-42f4-af7a-0ae76d8ce208.html",
        "subtitle": "Il dato non contempla il voto postale. Oltre 59 milioni di tedeschi chiamati alle urne. Il Paese alla prova del voto fra attentati e ultradestra",
