[
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, 'molta strada da fare per la fine della guerra'",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 3 Mar 2025 08:08:17 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-03",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/03/zelensky-molta-strada-da-fare-per-la-fine-della-guerra_da712dee-cdf6-4cbd-a04a-185c5a4ae835.html",
        "subtitle": "'Sarebbe sbagliato parlare di concessioni territoriali'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            C'è \"molta strada da fare\" per\ngiungere alla fine della guerra con la Russia: lo ha detto il\npresidente ucraino Volodymyr Zelensky parlando ai giornalisti\nall'aeroporto di Stansted, riporta Sky News. Il capo di Stato ha\nribadito che un accordo dovrà essere \"onesto\", \"equo\" e\n\"stabile\", con \"garanzie di sicurezza molto specifiche\". Oggi\nl'Ucraina \"non sta parlando\" di alcuna concessione, ha aggiunto,\nperché sarebbe \"sbagliato\" e sta \"ascoltando segnali da vari\npartner\". Kiev, ha sottolineato, \"non riconoscerà mai i\nterritori occupati dalla Russia come territorio russo. Per noi,\nqueste saranno occupazioni temporanee\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988817.560158,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.17",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, 'many way to go for the end of the war'",
        "en_content": "There is \"many way to go\" to\narrive at the end of the war with Russia: He said that\nUkrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky speaking to journalists\nat Stansted airport, reports Sky News. The Head of State has\nreiterated that an agreement must be \"honest\", \" fair\" and\n\"stable\", with \"very specific security agencies\". Today\nUkraine \"is not talking\" of any concession, added,\nbecause it would be \"wrong\" and is \"hearing signals from various\npartner.\" Kiev, he emphasized, \"will never recognize the\nterritories occupied by Russia as Russian territory. For us,\nthese will be temporary occupations.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'It would be wrong to talk about territorial concessions'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stansted",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sky News",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 198,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 530,
                "end_char": 537,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas, Israele vuole far morire di fame residenti di Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 08:41:12 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/02/hamas-israele-vuole-far-morire-di-fame-residenti-di-gaza_1100d956-a90f-49eb-8e31-119f42a10deb.html",
        "subtitle": "'Conferma il suo disprezzo per le leggi internazionali'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'ufficio comunicazioni di Hamas\nha risposto alla decisione di Israele di sospendere gli aiuti\numanitari alla Striscia di Gaza, dichiarando al canale\ntelevisivo qatariota al-Arabi che \"la decisione di Netanyahu di\ninterrompere gli aiuti sta ancora una volta confermando il suo\ndisprezzo per le leggi internazionali e impedendo la\ndistribuzione di medicine e cibo\". Ha aggiunto che \"fermare\nl'ingresso degli aiuti significa la decisione di Israele di far\nmorire di fame i residenti della Striscia di Gaza. Deve essere\npresa una posizione internazionale dura per fare pressione su\nIsraele affinché fermi tutto questo\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988817.578589,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.17",
        "en_title": "Hamas, Israel wants to starve Gaza residents",
        "en_content": "Hamas communications office\nhas responded to Israel's decision to suspend aid\nhumanitarian at the Gaza Strip, declaring to the canal\nTV qatariota al-Arabi that \"the decision of Netanyahu of\ninterrupting the aid is once again confirming its\ndisdain for international laws and preventing\ndistribution of medicines and food\". He added that \"stop\nthe entry of aid means the decision of Israel to make\nto starve the residents of the Gaza Strip. It must be\ntaken a tough international position to pressure on\nIsrael to stop this.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Confirm your contempt for international laws'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "al-Arabi",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 382,
                "end_char": 388,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 424,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Cremlino, 'cambio politica estera Usa coincide con la nostra'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 10:32:50 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/02/cremlino-cambio-politica-estera-usa-coincide-con-la-nostra_9624a1df-160e-4153-aef7-49a28ac4160d.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo afferma Peskov in intervista alla Tv",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Cremlino ha affermato che il\ndrastico cambiamento nella politica estera degli Stati Uniti nei\nconfronti della Russia è in gran parte in linea con la visione\ndi Mosca.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"La nuova amministrazione sta rapidamente cambiando tutte le\nsue configurazioni in politica estera. Ciò coincide in gran\nparte con la nostra visione\", ha detto il portavoce del\nCremlino, Dmitri Peskov, in un'intervista alla televisione di\nStato russa registrata mercoledì scorso e trasmessa oggi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988817.6589618,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.17",
        "en_title": "Kremlin, US foreign policy change coincides with our",
        "en_content": "The Kremlin said that\ndrastic change in US foreign policy in\nRussia is largely in line with vision\nMoscow.\n\n\n\"The new administration is rapidly changing all\nits configurations in foreign policy. This coincides with great\npart with our vision,\" said the spokesman for\nKremlin, Dmitri Peskov, in an interview on television\nRussian state recorded last Wednesday and broadcast today.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Peskov says in interview with TV",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Peskov",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dmitri Peskov",
                "start_char": 276,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "last Wednesday",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele sospende l'ingresso di aiuti umanitari a Gaza",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 08:23:13 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/02/israele-sospende-lingresso-di-aiuti-umanitari-a-gaza_02ee0370-bf84-4638-bee9-af586ee527ed.html",
        "subtitle": "'Le ostilità non cesseranno senza il rilascio degli ostaggi'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Israele ha sospeso l'ingresso di\naiuti umanitari nella Striscia di Gaza e ha chiuso i valichi di\naccesso, lo riferisce in un comunicatp stampa l'ufficio del\nprimo ministro Benyamin Netanyahu.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La decisione è stata presa durante una riunione notturna tra\nsabato e domenica, in coordinamento con gli Stati Uniti, dopo la\nconclusione della prima fase dell'accordo sugli ostaggi. Il\nprovvedimento è legato al rifiuto di Hamas di accettare il\ncosiddetto 'piano Witkoff'.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La nota aggiunge che \"Israele non permetterà una cessazione\ndelle ostilità senza il rilascio dei nostri ostaggi. Se Hamas\ncontinuerà nel suo rifiuto, ci saranno ulteriori conseguenze\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988817.679302,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.17",
        "en_title": "Israel suspends the entry of humanitarian aid to Gaza",
        "en_content": "Israel has suspended the entrance of\nhumanitarian aid in the Gaza Strip and closed the vessels\naccess, reports it in a press release the office of the\nPrime Minister Benyamin Netanyahu.\n\n\nThe decision was taken during a night meeting between\nSaturday and Sunday, in coordination with the United States, after\nconclusion of the first phase of the hostage agreement. The\nmeasure is related to the refusal of Hamas to accept\nso-called 'Witkoff plan'.\n\n\nThe note adds that \"Israel will not allow a cessation\nof hostilities without the release of our hostages. If Hamas\nwill continue in its refusal, there will be further consequences.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'The hostilities will not cease without the release of hostages'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benyamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "night",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saturday",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 332,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Witkoff",
                "start_char": 433,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 476,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 564,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas, Israele viola accordo, mette in pericolo vite ostaggi",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 10:43:49 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/02/hamas-israele-viola-accordo-mette-in-pericolo-vite-ostaggi_d3752557-9f9d-4d80-9f8e-6b24da2f62cc.html",
        "subtitle": "'Elude l'adempimento dei suoi impegni sul cessate il fuoco'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Hamas ha dichiarato questa\nmattina che \"Israele si sottrae ripetutamente agli accordi\nfirmati e continua a eludere l'adempimento dei suoi impegni sul\ncessate il fuoco. Questa manipolazione in corso non restituirà i\nrapiti alle loro famiglie, ma al contrario, porterà a continue\nsofferenze e metterà in pericolo le loro vite, se non si\nesercita pressione su Israele affinché rispetti i suoi\nobblighi\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   E ha aggiunto: \"L'unico modo per raggiungere la stabilità\nnella regione e liberare i rapiti è completare l'accordo,\niniziando con l'attuazione della seconda fase\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988817.7570279,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.17",
        "en_title": "Hamas, Israel violates agreement, threatens lives hostages",
        "en_content": "Hamas declared this\nmorning that \"Israel repeatedly subtracts from agreements\nsigned and continues to fulfil its commitments on\ncease fire. This manipulation will not return\nabducted to their families, but on the contrary, will lead to continuous\nand put their lives in danger, if you do not\nexerts pressure on Israel to respect its\nobligations.\"\n\n\nAnd he added: \"The only way to achieve stability\nin the region and free the kidnapped is complete the agreement,\nbeginning with the implementation of the second phase\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Held the fulfillment of his commitments on ceasefire'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Starmer, Francia e Gb lavorano a un loro piano di pace",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 10:29:09 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/02/starmer-francia-e-gb-lavorano-a-un-loro-piano-di-pace_16b3db2b-66f3-49e1-ab2f-7b57d5560355.html",
        "subtitle": "Insieme con l'Ucraina",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Regno Unito e la Francia stanno\nlavorando, \"insieme con l'Ucraina\", a un loro piano per \"far\ncessare le ostilità\" con la Russia. Lo ha detto oggi il premier\nbritannico Keir Starmer, dopo aver incontrato ieri a Downing\nStreet il presidente Volodymyr Zelensky reduce dal fallimentare\nvertice di Washington con Donald Trump, e a poche ore\ndall'inizio alla Lancaster House di Londra di una riunione sulla\nsicurezza ucraina ed europea. Riunione a cui partecipano una\nquindicina di leader di Paesi Nato (Ue ed extra Ue), fra cui,\nper l'Italia, la premier Giorgia Meloni, nonché dei vertici\ndell'Unione e dell'Alleanza Atlantica. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988817.7631142,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:17",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.17",
        "en_title": "Starmer, France and Gb work on their peace plan",
        "en_content": "The UK and France are\nworking, \"together with Ukraine\", to their plan to \"make it\ncease hostilities\" with Russia. The premier said today\nBritish Keir Starmer, after meeting yesterday at Downing\nStreet President Volodymyr Zelensky veteran from failing\nWashington summit with Donald Trump, and a few hours\nfrom the beginning to the London Lancaster House of a meeting on\nUkrainian and European security. Meeting in which a\n15 leaders of NATO countries (EU and extra EU), including,\nfor Italy, the premier Giorgia Meloni, as well as the top\nof the Union and the Atlantic Alliance.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Together with Ukraine",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 106,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Keir Starmer",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Downing\nStreet",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few hours",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 330,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 369,
                "end_char": 378,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 439,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 517,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Union",
                "start_char": 545,
                "end_char": 550,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Atlantic Alliance",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 576,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Von der Leyen, 'la forza è la via per la pace, l'Ue è con Kiev'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 11:10:37 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/02/von-der-leyen-la-forza-e-la-via-per-la-pace-lue-e-con-kiev_bf55e603-d5ae-45c5-8592-ccf46e4bf156.html",
        "subtitle": "'Pronti a impegnarci per rafforzare la difesa europea'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"La via per la pace è la forza.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLa debolezza genera più guerra. Sosterremo l'Ucraina,\nimpegnandoci nel contempo in un rafforzamento della difesa\neuropea\". Lo scrive su X la presidente della Commissione\neuropea, Ursula von der Leyen, in viaggio verso Londra per il\nsummit convocato dal premier britannico Keir Starmer.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Il continuo sostegno dell'Europa all'Ucraina può portare a una\npace giusta e duratura nel Paese\", ha ribadito. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 57,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988819.9653823,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.19",
        "en_title": "Von der Leyen, 'force is the way for peace, the EU is with Kiev'",
        "en_content": "\"The way to peace is strength.\n\n\nThe weakness generates more war. We will support Ukraine,\nat the same time committing us to a strengthening of defence\nEuropean.\" The President of the Commission writes on X\nEuropean, Ursula von der Leyen, traveling to London for\nsummit convened by British Prime Minister Keir Starmer.\n\n\n\"Europe's continued support for Ukraine can lead to a\nright and lasting peace in the country,\" he said.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Ready to engage in strengthening European defence'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Von der",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 232,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 289,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Keir Starmer",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Panama verso l'Europa per uscire da liste paradisi fiscali",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 11:43:24 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/02/panama-verso-leuropa-per-uscire-da-liste-paradisi-fiscali_ebe7e96e-643d-4bb6-b4e3-0a60b2243285.html",
        "subtitle": "Mulino incontra Steinmeier e il re di Spagna a Montevideo",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente di Panama, José Raúl\nMulino, ha espresso l'intenzione di rafforzare i rapporti con i\nPaesi europei per promuovere una strategia volta a rimuovere il\nPaese dalle \"liste discriminatorie\" dei paradisi fiscali stilate\ndall'Ue e dall'Organizzazione per la cooperazione e lo sviluppo\neconomico (Ocse). Lo riportano i media internazionali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Mulino ha parlato oggi della sua strategia con il presidente\ntedesco Frank-Walter Steinmeier e il re Felipe di Spagna a\nmargine dell'insediamento del presidente dell'Uruguay Yamandú\nOrsi a Montevideo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il capo dello Stato aveva giustificato nei giorni scorsi il\nrafforzamento delle ambasciate di Madrid e Parigi sostenendo\nl'importanza degli sforzi diplomatici per raggiungere un accordo\ncon l'Ue. Il governo panamense ha aggiunto che anche le missioni\na Roma e Bruxelles sono incluse in questa strategia. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 51,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988820.0852275,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.20",
        "en_title": "Panama to Europe to exit tax havens",
        "en_content": "President of Panama, José Raúl\nMulino, has expressed its intention to strengthen relations with the\nEuropean countries to promote a strategy to remove\nCountry from the \"discriminatory lists\" of tax havens\nby the EU and the Organization for Cooperation and Development\neconomic (Ocse). International media reports it.\n\n\nMulino spoke today about his strategy with the President\nGerman Frank-Walter Steinmeier and King Felipe of Spain in\nmargin of the settlement of the president of Uruguay Yamandú\nBears in Montevideo.\n\n\nThe Head of State had justified in recent days the\nstrengthening the embassies of Madrid and Paris by supporting\nthe importance of diplomatic efforts to reach an agreement\nwith the EU. The Panamanian government added that even the missions\nin Rome and Brussels are included in this strategy.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Mill meets Steinmeier and the King of Spain in Montevideo",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Panama",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mill",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Steinmeier",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the King of Spain",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Montevideo",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Panama",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "José Raúl",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mulino",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Organization for Cooperation and Development\neconomic",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ocse",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mulino",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "German",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Frank-Walter Steinmeier",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 406,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Felipe",
                "start_char": 416,
                "end_char": 422,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Uruguay Yamandú",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Montevideo",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 531,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "recent days",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Madrid",
                "start_char": 601,
                "end_char": 607,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 612,
                "end_char": 617,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 700,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Panamanian",
                "start_char": 708,
                "end_char": 718,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rome",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 766,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 771,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas,'fuoco d'artiglieria israeliano vicino a Khan Yunis'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 17:46:28 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/03/02/hamasfuoco-dartiglieria-israeliano-vicino-a-khan-yunis_15066094-07d8-4f78-9a66-c52ae278e544.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo riferisce la Protezione Civile della Striscia di Gaza",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Protezione Civile della Striscia\ndi Gaza, gestita da Hamas, ha riferito di colpi di artiglieria e\nattacchi di carri armati nella zona di Khan Yunis, nel sud del\nterritorio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Bombardamento di artiglieria e fuoco di carri armati\nisraeliani contro aree ai margini della città di Abassan\nal-Kabira, a est di Khan Yunis\", si legge in un breve comunicato\nstampa. Interrogato dall'Afp l'esercito israeliano ha affermato\nche sta verificando queste informazioni. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 55,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988820.0972228,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.20",
        "en_title": "Hamas, Israeli artillery fire near Khan Yunis'",
        "en_content": "The Civil Protection of the Strip\nof Gaza, managed by Hamas, reported artillery blows and\ntank attacks in the Khan Yunis area, in the south of\nterritory.\n\n\n\"Bombarding of artillery and fire of tanks\nIsraelis against areas on the edge of Abassan city\nal-Kabira, east of Khan Yunis,\" reads in a brief statement\nprint. In response to the Afp question, the Israeli army said\nwhich is checking this information.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Civil Protection of the Gaza Strip",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khan Yunis'",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Civil Protection of the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Civil Protection of the Strip",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Khan Yunis",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 120,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israelis",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Abassan city",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "al-Kabira",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khan Yunis",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Afp",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Re Carlo attende Zelensky, tutto pronto per il vertice di Londra",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 11:26:57 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/02/re-carlo-attende-zelensky-tutto-pronto-per-il-vertice-di-londra_b6d46b0a-b614-4d3c-add9-23caf8afc571.html",
        "subtitle": "In mattinata pure il bilaterale Starmer-Meloni,poi riunione a 16",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            E' tutto pronto a Londra per\nl'inedito vertice a 16 sulle garanzie di sicurezza per l'Ucraina\ne sulla difesa europea promosso dal premier britannico Keir\nStarmer e che si svolge dopo il plateale fallimento\ndell'incontro di venerdì alla Casa Bianca fra il presidente\nucraino Volodymyr Zelensky  e quello americano Donald Trump.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    I leader stanno arrivando in queste ore e si raduneranno\nalla Lancaster House, non lontano da Buckingham Palace, dalle\n14. Nella mattinata Zelensky è atteso nella residenza reale di\ncampagna di Sandringham, nel Norfolk inglese, da re Carlo III\nper un colloquio fuori programma destinato a confermare il\n\"pieno sostegno\" britannico all'Ucraina, già enfaticamente\nsottolineato ieri da Starmer a Downing Street in un faccia a\nfaccia con il leader ucraino anticipato di un giorno.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    Stamattina il primo ministro laburista ha in agenda a Number\n10 un solo altro bilaterale, a margine del vertice collettivo:\ncon la presidente del Consiglio italiana Giorgia Meloni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    L'elenco aggiornato dei partecipanti al meeting di Lancaster\nHouse comprende i leader di Regno Unito, Ucraina, Francia,\nGermania, Italia, Danimarca, Olanda, Norvegia, Polonia, Spagna,\nFinlandia, Svezia, Repubblica Ceca, Romania e Canada; oltre al\nministro degli Esteri della Turchia, al segretario generale\ndella Nato, Mark Rutte, e ai presidenti della Commissione e del\nConsiglio europeo, Ursula von der Leyen e Antonio Costa. Si\ntratta di 15 Paesi della Nato, Ucraina a parte, 11 dei quali\nmembri anche dell'Ue e quattro esterni: Gran Bretagna, Norvegia\ne Turchia, assieme all'extraeuropeo Canada. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 53,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988820.10822,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.20",
        "en_title": "King Charles awaits Zelensky, all ready for the London summit",
        "en_content": "Everything is ready in London for\nthe unprecedented 16-point summit on security guarantees for Ukraine\nand European defence promoted by British Prime Minister Keir\nStarmer and that takes place after the square failure\nof the Friday meeting at the White House between the President\nUkrainian Volodymyr Zelensky and the American Donald Trump.\n\n\nLeaders are coming in these hours and will gather\nat Lancaster House, not far from Buckingham Palace, from\n14. In the morning Zelensky is expected in the royal residence of\nSandringham campaign, in the English Norfolk, by King Charles III\nfor a non-programme interview intended to confirm\nBritish \"full support\" to Ukraine, already emphatically\nunderlined yesterday by Starmer at Downing Street in a face to\nface with the early Ukrainian leader of a day.\n\n\nThis morning the Labour Prime Minister has on the agenda at Number\n10 another bilateral, at the margin of the collective summit:\nwith the President of the Italian Council Giorgia Meloni.\n\n\nThe updated list of participants at the Lancaster meeting\nHouse includes leaders of United Kingdom, Ukraine, France,\nGermany, Italy, Denmark, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Spain,\nFinland, Sweden, Czech Republic, Romania and Canada;\nMinister for Foreign Affairs of Turkey, the Secretary-General\nby NATO, Mark Rutte, and the presidents of the Commission and the\nEuropean Council, Ursula von der Leyen and Antonio Costa. Yes\n15 countries of NATO, Ukraine apart, 11 of which\nmembers of the EU and four outsiders: United Kingdom, Norway\nand Turkey, together with the extra-European Canada.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In the morning also the bilateral Starmer-Meloni, then meeting at 16",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Charles",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the morning",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "16",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "16",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Keir\nStarmer",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 281,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "these hours",
                "start_char": 365,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lancaster House",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Buckingham Palace",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "14",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 477,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sandringham",
                "start_char": 516,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "English",
                "start_char": 545,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norfolk",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 560,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Charles III",
                "start_char": 570,
                "end_char": 581,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 632,
                "end_char": 639,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 658,
                "end_char": 665,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 699,
                "end_char": 708,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Starmer",
                "start_char": 712,
                "end_char": 719,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Downing Street",
                "start_char": 723,
                "end_char": 737,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 771,
                "end_char": 780,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "This morning",
                "start_char": 800,
                "end_char": 812,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Labour",
                "start_char": 817,
                "end_char": 823,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 867,
                "end_char": 869,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 955,
                "end_char": 962,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 971,
                "end_char": 985,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lancaster",
                "start_char": 1029,
                "end_char": 1038,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 1047,
                "end_char": 1052,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 1073,
                "end_char": 1087,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 1089,
                "end_char": 1096,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 1098,
                "end_char": 1104,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 1106,
                "end_char": 1113,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1115,
                "end_char": 1120,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Denmark",
                "start_char": 1122,
                "end_char": 1129,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 1131,
                "end_char": 1142,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 1144,
                "end_char": 1150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 1152,
                "end_char": 1158,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 1160,
                "end_char": 1165,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finland",
                "start_char": 1167,
                "end_char": 1174,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sweden",
                "start_char": 1176,
                "end_char": 1182,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Czech Republic",
                "start_char": 1184,
                "end_char": 1198,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Romania",
                "start_char": 1200,
                "end_char": 1207,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 1212,
                "end_char": 1218,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 1252,
                "end_char": 1258,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 1285,
                "end_char": 1289,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mark Rutte",
                "start_char": 1291,
                "end_char": 1301,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Commission",
                "start_char": 1329,
                "end_char": 1339,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the\nEuropean Council",
                "start_char": 1344,
                "end_char": 1364,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ursula von der",
                "start_char": 1366,
                "end_char": 1380,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Leyen",
                "start_char": 1381,
                "end_char": 1386,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Costa",
                "start_char": 1391,
                "end_char": 1404,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 1410,
                "end_char": 1412,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 1426,
                "end_char": 1430,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 1432,
                "end_char": 1439,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "11",
                "start_char": 1447,
                "end_char": 1449,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 1474,
                "end_char": 1476,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 1481,
                "end_char": 1485,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 1497,
                "end_char": 1511,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norway",
                "start_char": 1513,
                "end_char": 1519,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 1524,
                "end_char": 1530,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 1556,
                "end_char": 1564,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 1565,
                "end_char": 1571,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Presidente Argentina, ci avviciniamo a un accordo con l'Fmi",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 11:11:08 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/02/presidente-argentina-ci-avviciniamo-a-un-accordo-con-lfmi_2aa27563-232e-4490-8cab-4322a08045a5.html",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il governo argentino sta\nprocedendo con la firma dell'atteso accordo con il Fondo\nmonetario internazionale: lo ha detto il presidente Javier Milei\nnel suo discorso di apertura della 143ma sessione ordinaria del\nCongresso.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Milei non ha fornito alcuna data sulla firma, ma ha\nsottolineato che \"l'accordo ci consentirà di uscire\ndefinitivamente dai controlli valutari quest'anno\". Ed ha\naggiunto: \"Voglio essere chiaro su una cosa: risolveremo il\nproblema che tutti i governi precedenti hanno causato con il\ndeficit fiscale e il suo finanziamento. Ci auguriamo pertanto\nche questo Congresso adotti la stessa posizione che ha assunto\ncon gli altri, ovvero quella di sostenere il Governo dai suoi\nbanchi in questo nuovo accordo\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 56,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988820.1160254,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.20",
        "en_title": "President Argentina, we approach an agreement with the IMF",
        "en_content": "The Argentine government is\nby signing the expected agreement with the Fund\nInternational money: President Javier Milei said\nin his opening speech of the 143th ordinary session of the\nCongress.\n\n\nMilei has not provided any date on the signature, but has\nunderlined that \"the agreement will allow us to leave\ndefinitively from the currency controls this year.\" Ed.\nadded: \"I want to be clear on one thing: we will solve\nproblem that all previous governments have caused with\ntax deficit and its financing. We hope so\nthat this Congress adopts the same position as it assumed\nwith others, that is to support the government from its\ncounters in this new agreement.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "IMF",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Javier Milei",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "143th",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Milei",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "this year",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ed",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 526,
                "end_char": 534,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tusk, 'appoggio la proposta di Meloni di un vertice Ue-Usa'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 11:32:37 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/02/tusk-appoggio-la-proposta-di-meloni-di-un-vertice-ue-usa_26946c0c-7865-47cb-93e4-50c625a54e07.html",
        "subtitle": "'Pieno sostegno a Kiev, l'alleanza con Washington resti salda'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Polonia appoggia la proposta\ndella premier Giorgia Meloni di organizzare un vertice tra Stati\nUniti ed Europa. Lo ha detto il primo ministro polacco e\npresidente di turno dell'Ue, Donald Tusk, prima di partire per\nil summit di Londra, secondo quanto riportato dai media\npolacchi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  \"Siamo dalla parte dell'Ucraina senza alcun dubbio: dev'essere\nfornito un sostegno inequivocabile e duraturo a Kiev nella sua\ndifesa contro l'aggressione russa\", ha ribadito Tusk. Allo\nstesso tempo, ha evidenziato, Varsavia \"sostiene la più stretta\nalleanza possibile tra l'intero Occidente e gli Stati Uniti\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 52,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988820.1316738,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.20",
        "en_title": "Tusk, 'support the proposal of Meloni of a Ue-Usa summit'",
        "en_content": "Poland supports the proposal\nby Premier Giorgia Meloni to organize a summit between States\nUnited States and Europe. The Polish Prime Minister said so.\nPresident of the EU, Donald Tusk, before leaving for\nthe London summit, according to the media\nPoles.\n\n\n\"We are on the side of Ukraine without any doubt: it must be\nprovided unequivocal and lasting support in Kiev in its\ndefense against Russian aggression,\" said Tusk. To the\nsame time, he highlighted, Warsaw \"supports the closest\npossible alliance between the entire West and the United States.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Pieno support in Kiev, the alliance with Washington remains firm'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tusk",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Pieno",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Tusk",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 184,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poles",
                "start_char": 247,
                "end_char": 252,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 389,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tusk",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 419,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Warsaw",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 530,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev, prima tranche prestito Londra arriva la prossima settimana",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 2 Mar 2025 11:20:41 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-02",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/02/kiev-prima-tranche-prestito-londra-arriva-la-prossima-settimana_c0bc29db-7f2f-437c-b6b4-4b8d062095d0.html",
        "subtitle": "Ukrinform cita il sito del governo britannico",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La prima tranche del prestito di 2,26\nmiliardi di sterline (circa 2,74 miliardi di euro) in tre rate\nannuali di 752 milioni di sterline (912 milioni di euro circa),\nper il quale ieri è stato firmato un accordo intergovernativo\ntra Regno Unito e Ucraina, sarà pagata all'Ucraina la prossima\nsettimana, come riporta il sito web del governo britannico\ncitato da Ukrinform.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il prestito sarà interamente destinato agli appalti militari\nper rafforzare le capacità di difesa dell'Ucraina e si prevede\nche la prima tranche verrà erogata all'Ucraina la prossima\nsettimana\" e sarà gestito e rimborsato tramite i profitti futuri\ngenerati dagli asset sovrani russi immobilizzati, scrive\nl'agenzia ucraina citando il sito britannico.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Si sottolinea inoltre che l'annuncio dell'accordo di prestito\nsi aggiunge all'impegno del Regno Unito di fornire assistenza\nmilitare all'Ucraina per un importo di 3 miliardi di sterline\nall'anno. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 54,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1740988820.1427689,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-03 09:00:20",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-03T08.00.20",
        "en_title": "Kiev, first tranche loan London arrives next week",
        "en_content": "The first tranche of the loan of 2.26\n£2.74 billion in three installments\nannual of 752 million pounds (912 million euros approximately),\nI would like to thank the rapporteur for his work.\nbetween United Kingdom and Ukraine, will be paid to Ukraine next\nweek, as reported by the British Government website\ncited by Ukrinform.\n\n\n\"The loan will be entirely intended for military procurement\nto strengthen the defence capabilities of Ukraine and is expected\nthat the first tranche will be delivered to Ukraine next\nweek\" and will be managed and refunded through future profits\ngenerated by immobilized Russian sovereign assets, writes\nthe Ukrainian agency citing the British site.\n\n\nIt also underlines that the announcement of the loan agreement\nis added to the UK's commitment to provide assistance\nmilitary to Ukraine for an amount of 3 billion pounds\na year.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Ukrinform cites the site of the British government",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next week",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukrinform",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2.26",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "£2.74 billion",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "annual",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "752 million pounds",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "912 million euros",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 197,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next\nweek",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 258,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the British Government",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrinform",
                "start_char": 315,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 469,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next\nweek",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 599,
                "end_char": 606,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 636,
                "end_char": 645,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 664,
                "end_char": 671,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "start_char": 759,
                "end_char": 761,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 809,
                "end_char": 816,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "3 billion pounds",
                "start_char": 834,
                "end_char": 850,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Meloni atterrata a Londra per il vertice, bilaterale con Starmer",
