[
    {
        "title": "Mosca, il gruppo \"Nord\" continua ad avanzare in Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 1 Jun 2024 04:16:03 +0200",
        "date": "2024-06-01",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/06/01/mosca-il-gruppo-nord-continua-ad-avanzare-in-ucraina_701e9257-6e27-4ecb-af8a-c31735fb82ff.html",
        "subtitle": "'Respinti i contrattacchi, morti circa 225 soldati ucraini'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nel corso di un'operazione militare\nspeciale in Ucraina, unità del gruppo di truppe Nord hanno\ncontinuato ad avanzare più in profondità nelle difese nemiche\ndurante il giorno. Lo ha riferito alla Tass il capo del centro\nstampa del gruppo, Sergei Zybinsky.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Le unità del gruppo di truppe Nord continuano ad avanzare\nnelle profondità della difesa nemica. Respinti quattro\ncontrattacchi a Liptsy e Volchansk. Le forze armate ucraine -\nconclude Zybinsky - hanno perso fino a 225 militari, un carro\narmato, 6 veicoli e un deposito di munizioni\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218022.7892215,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.22",
        "en_title": "Moscow, the group \"North\" continues to advance in Ukraine",
        "en_content": "During a military operation\nspecial in Ukraine, unit of the group of North troops have\ncontinued to advance deeper into enemy defenses\nduring the day. He told Tass the head of the center\nGroup press, Sergei Zybinsky.\n\n\n\"The units of the North Troop Group continue to advance\nin the depths of the enemy defense. Respire four\ncounterattacks in Liptsy and Volchansk. The Ukrainian armed forces -\nconcludes Zybinsky - they lost up to 225 military, a wagon\narmed, 6 vehicles and a munitions warehouse.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Respying counterattacks, dead about 225 Ukrainian soldiers'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "about 225",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "North",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the day",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 149,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sergei Zybinsky",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the North Troop Group",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Liptsy",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 348,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volchansk",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zybinsky",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "225",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 433,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "6",
                "start_char": 459,
                "end_char": 460,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Stoltenberg, Kiev sia responsabile con gli strike in Russia",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:33:26 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/stoltenberg-kiev-sia-responsabile-con-gli-strike-in-russia_aac0a920-9e66-4aa8-81a7-a80248399e2c.html",
        "subtitle": "'Uso armi avvenga in linea con il diritto internazionale'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli alleati si aspettano che l'uso\ndelle armi fornite all'Ucraina contro la Russia, ovvero colpendo\nobiettivi militari al di là del confine, avvenga \"in linea con\nil diritto internazionale e in modo responsabile\". Lo ha detto\nil segretario generale della Nato Jens Stoltenberg all'informale\nesteri di Praga. Quanto al rischio di una escalation, il sec gen\nha precisato: \"Ogni volta che abbiamo dato mezzi all'Ucraina\nVladimir Putin ci ha minacciato, è stato così per i pezzi di\nartiglieria, i tank, i missili, gli F-16\". \"È la Russia che ha\ndato il via all'escalation, prima invadendo un altro Paese e ora\naprendo il nuovo fronte a Kharkiv\" \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 68,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218022.9947927,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:22",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.22",
        "en_title": "Stoltenberg, Kiev is responsible for strikes in Russia",
        "en_content": "Allies expect use\nof the weapons supplied to Ukraine against Russia, i.e. hitting\nmilitary objectives beyond the border, take place \"in line with\ninternational law and responsibly.\" He said that.\nthe secretary general of NATO Jens Stoltenberg to the informal\nPrague. As for the risk of an escalation, the sec gen\nhas specified: \"Every time we have given means to Ukraine\nVladimir Putin threatened us, it was so for the pieces of\nartillery, tanks, missiles, F-16s.\" \"It is Russia that has\ngiven the start to escalation, first invading another country and now\nopening the new front to Kharkiv\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Use weapons happen in line with international law'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jens Stoltenberg",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prague",
                "start_char": 259,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "sec",
                "start_char": 305,
                "end_char": 308,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 370,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 371,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "F-16s",
                "start_char": 457,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 519,
                "end_char": 524,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 630,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Medvedev, 'errore pensare che Mosca non usi armi nucleari'",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:49:52 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/medvedev-errore-pensare-che-mosca-non-usi-armi-nucleari_8108de46-5314-4fd3-be61-74ed47a0cfe1.html",
        "subtitle": "'Paesi occidentali hanno sbagliato i calcoli'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            I Paesi occidentali \"qualche anno fa\ndicevano che la Russia non sarebbe arrivata a un conflitto\nmilitare aperto con il regime Banderiano (ucraino, ndr) per non\nlitigare con l'Occidente. Hanno sbagliato i calcoli. La guerra\nc'è. Potrebbero anche sbagliare i calcoli sull'uso delle armi\nTnw (armi nucleari tattiche, ndr). Anche se sarebbe un errore\nfatale\": lo scrive su Telegram il vicepresidente del Consiglio\ndi sicurezza russo, Dmitry Medvedev.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\"Dopo tutto, come ha giustamente sottolineato il presidente\nrusso (Vladimir Putin, ndr), i Paesi europei hanno una densità\ndi popolazione molto elevata. E per quei Paesi nemici le cui\nterre sono al di là della zona di copertura delle Tnw c'è,\ninfine, un potenziale strategico\", ha proseguito l'ex presidente\nrusso.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"E questa, ahimè, non è né intimidazione né bluff nucleare.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'attuale conflitto militare con l'Occidente si sta sviluppando\nsecondo il peggior scenario possibile. Si assiste a una costante\nescalation della potenza delle armi Nato applicabili. Pertanto,\nnessuno può escludere che il conflitto passi oggi alla sua fase\nfinale\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel suo lungo intervento, Medvedev sottolinea: \"I Paesi\noccidentali che hanno presumibilmente 'approvato l'uso' delle\nloro armi a lungo raggio sul territorio russo (indipendentemente\ndal fatto che si tratti di zone vecchie o nuove del nostro\nPaese) dovrebbero comprendere chiaramente quanto segue: 1) Tutti\ni loro equipaggiamenti militari e i loro specialisti che\ncombattono contro di noi saranno distrutti sia sul territorio\ndell'Ucraina b. (banderiana, ndr) sia sul territorio di altri\nPaesi, se da questi vengono lanciati attacchi contro il\nterritorio della Russia. 2) La Russia presume che tutti i mezzi\ndi sconfitta a lungo raggio utilizzati dall'Ucraina b. siano già\noggi direttamente controllati dal personale militare della Nato.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tQuesta non è 'assistenza militare', ma partecipazione alla\nguerra contro di noi. E le loro azioni potrebbero diventare\ncasus belli. 3) La Nato dovrà decidere come qualificare le\nconseguenze di eventuali attacchi di rappresaglia contro\nattrezzature/oggetti/personale militare di singoli Paesi del\nblocco nel contesto degli articoli 4 e 5 del Trattato di\nWashington. Con ogni probabilità, i vertici della Nato vogliono\nfar credere che stiamo parlando di decisioni sovrane di singoli\nPaesi dell'Alleanza Nord Atlantica di sostenere il regime di\nKiev e che non c'è motivo di applicare le regole del Trattato di\nautodifesa collettiva del 1949.  Si tratta di idee sbagliate\npericolose e dannose\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218023.0037334,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:23",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.23",
        "en_title": "Medvedev, 'warm thinking Moscow doesn't use nuclear weapons'",
        "en_content": "Western countries \"some year ago\nthey said that Russia would not come to a conflict\nmilitary open with the Banderiano regime (Ukrainian, ndr) for not\nFight with the West. They made the calculations wrong. The war\nThere is. They may also miss the calculations on the use of weapons\nTnw ( tactical nuclear weapons, ndr). Although it would be a mistake\nfatal\": on Telegram the Vice-President of the Council\nof Russian security, Dmitry Medvedev.\n\n\n\"After all, as the President rightly pointed out\nRussian (Vladimir Putin, ndr), European countries have a density\nof very high population. And for those enemies countries whose\nlands are beyond the cover area of the Tnw there,\nFinally, a strategic potential\", the former president continued\nRussian.\n\n\n\"And this, alas, is neither intimidation nor nuclear bluff.\n\n\nThe current military conflict with the West is developing\naccording to the worst possible scenario. We witness a constant\nescalation of NATO weapons power applicable. Therefore,\nno one can exclude that the conflict passes today to its stage\nFinal.\"\n\n\nIn his long speech, Medvedev emphasizes: \"The countries\nWesterners who have supposedly 'approved the use' of\ntheir long-range weapons on Russian territory (regardless\nthe fact that it is old or new areas of our\nCountry) should clearly understand the following: 1) All\ntheir military equipment and their specialists\nfight against us will be destroyed both in the territory\nof Ukraine b. (banderiana, ndr) both on the territory of others\nCountries, if attacks against them are launched\nRussia. 2) Russia assumes that all means\nof long-range defeat used by Ukraine b. already\ntoday directly controlled by NATO military personnel.\n\n\nThis is not 'military assistance', but participation in\nwar against us. And their actions could become\nBeautiful casus. 3) NATO must decide how to qualify\nconsequences of any retaliation attacks against\nmilitary equipment/objects/persons\nArticle 4 and 5 of the Treaty\nWashington. In all probability, NATO leaders want\nto make believe that we are talking about sovereign decisions of individuals\nNorth Atlantic Alliance countries to support the regime\nKiev and that there is no reason to apply the rules of the Treaty of Kiev\ncollective self-defense of 1949. These are wrong ideas\ndangerous and harmful.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Western countries have wronged the calculations'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Medvedev",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "some year ago",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Banderiano",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "ndr",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 407,
                "end_char": 414,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dmitry Medvedev",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 493,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ndr",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 532,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 735,
                "end_char": 742,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 847,
                "end_char": 851,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 944,
                "end_char": 948,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 1030,
                "end_char": 1035,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Medvedev",
                "start_char": 1079,
                "end_char": 1087,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westerners",
                "start_char": 1115,
                "end_char": 1125,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 1196,
                "end_char": 1203,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "1",
                "start_char": 1320,
                "end_char": 1321,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 1434,
                "end_char": 1441,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "banderiana",
                "start_char": 1446,
                "end_char": 1456,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ndr",
                "start_char": 1458,
                "end_char": 1461,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1543,
                "end_char": 1549,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2",
                "start_char": 1551,
                "end_char": 1552,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1554,
                "end_char": 1560,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 1613,
                "end_char": 1620,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 1632,
                "end_char": 1637,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 1661,
                "end_char": 1665,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 1808,
                "end_char": 1809,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 1811,
                "end_char": 1815,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Article 4 and 5",
                "start_char": 1926,
                "end_char": 1941,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Treaty",
                "start_char": 1949,
                "end_char": 1955,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 1956,
                "end_char": 1966,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 1988,
                "end_char": 1992,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "North Atlantic Alliance",
                "start_char": 2083,
                "end_char": 2106,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 2139,
                "end_char": 2143,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Treaty",
                "start_char": 2198,
                "end_char": 2204,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 2208,
                "end_char": 2212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1949",
                "start_char": 2240,
                "end_char": 2244,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 2297,
                "end_char": 2330,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Esercitazione congiunta di Russia e Bielorussia per armi aeree",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 05:07:06 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/esercitazione-congiunta-di-russia-e-bielorussia-per-armi-aeree_9bc46371-f4f8-4149-adcd-3826c954d4c6.html",
        "subtitle": "Addestramento contro obiettivi specifici",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli equipaggi dei caccia Su-30SM, dei\nbombardieri Su-24 e degli elicotteri Mi-24, Mi-8 delle Forze\naerospaziali russe hanno preso parte ad esercitazioni con\nl'Aeronautica Militare e la Difesa Aerea delle Forze Armate\ndella Bielorussia. Lo ha riferito il Ministero della Difesa\nrusso.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Gli equipaggi dei caccia multiruolo Su-30SM, dei bombardieri\ndi prima linea Su-24 e degli elicotteri dell'aviazione militare\nMi-24, Mi-8 delle Forze Aerospaziali della Federazione Russa\nhanno preso parte ad un'esercitazione volo-tattica congiunta con\nle forze e i mezzi dell'Aeronautica Militare e delle Forze di\nDifesa Aerea delle Forze Armate della Repubblica di Bielorussia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tNell'ambito delle attività nei campi di addestramento\naeronautico, gli equipaggi hanno sperimentato l'uso pratico\ndelle armi dell'aviazione contro obiettivi specifici\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Le esercitazioni si sono svolte dal 27 al 31 maggio in volo\ntattico sul territorio della Bielorussia. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 81,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218026.910628,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.26",
        "en_title": "Joint exercise of Russia and Belarus for aerial weapons",
        "en_content": "Su-30SM hunting crews,\nSu-24 bombers and Mi-24 helicopters, Mi-8 of the Forces\nRussian aerospaces took part in exercises with\nAir Force and Air Force Defense\nof Belarus. The Ministry of Defense reported it\nRussian.\n\n\n\"Su-30SM multi-role fighter crews, bombers\nSu-24 front line and military aviation helicopters\nMi-24, Mi-8 of the Russian Federation Aerospace Forces\ntook part in a joint flight-tactic exercise with\nthe forces and means of the Air Force and the Forces of\nAir Force Defense of the Republic of Belarus.\n\n\nAs part of training activities\naircraft, crews have experienced practical use\nof aviation weapons against specific objectives.\"\n\n\nExercises took place from 27 to 31 May in flight\ntactical on the territory of Belarus.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Training against specific objectives",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Su-24",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mi-24",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forces",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Air Force",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Air Force Defense",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of Defense",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Su-24",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mi-8",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Federation Aerospace Forces",
                "start_char": 326,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Air Force",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Air Force Defense of the Republic of Belarus",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "27 to 31 May",
                "start_char": 675,
                "end_char": 687,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 727,
                "end_char": 734,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Morta a Buenos Aires la Madre di Plaza de Mayo, Nora Cortiñas",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 09:33:22 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/31/morta-a-buenos-aires-la-madre-di-plaza-de-mayo-nora-cortinas_ac344161-c140-4cb0-98c5-8ab8825fa2d1.html",
        "subtitle": "Impegnata contro la dittatura e nella ricerca dei desaparecidos",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nora Cortiñas, storica\nmilitante argentina per i diritti umani impegnata nella ricerca\ndei desaparecidos vittime della dittatura (1976-1983), nonché\ncofondatrice e presidente del movimento delle Madri di Plaza de\nMayo-Linea Fundadora, è morta ieri a Buenos Aires all'età di 94\nanni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Operata il 17 maggio per un'ernia, Cortiñas era stata posta\nin un reparto di rianimazione alcuni giorni dopo per\nl'improvviso peggioramento delle sue condizioni di salute\ngenerali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La sua ultima presenza pubblica è stata il 24 marzo scorso,\nquando ha partecipato su una sedia a rotelle alla marcia di\ncommemorazione, per la memoria, la verità e la giustizia, di un\nnuovo anniversario dell'inizio della dittatura civico-militare\nnel 1976.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   'Norita', come tutti la chiamavano amabilmente, ha militato\nfin dal 1977 nella ricerca delle molte migliaia di desaparecidos\ncausati dall'azione dei militari argentini durante la dittatura,\nfra cui si trovava suo figlio Carlos Gustavo, scomparso il 15\naprile 1977.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel corso della sua intensa vita, aveva ricevuto quattro\nlauree honoris causa, fra cui una dell'Università libera di\nBruxelles, e giorni fa il Parlamento della città di Buenos Aires\nle aveva consegnato il premio Jorge Morresi \"per la carriera,\nl'impegno e la difesa della democrazia e dei diritti umani\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 79,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218026.9276268,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.26",
        "en_title": "The Mother of Plaza de Mayo died in Buenos Aires, Nora Cortiñas",
        "en_content": "Nora Cortiñas, historical\nArgentine human rights activist engaged in research\ndesaparecidos victims of the dictatorship (1976-1983) and\nco-founder and president of the movement of the Mothers of Plaza de\nMayo-Linea Fundadora, died yesterday in Buenos Aires at the age of 94\nYears.\n\n\nOperating on 17 May for a hernia, Cortiñas had been posted\nin a reanimation department a few days later for\nthe sudden worsening of his health conditions\nGeneral.\n\n\nHis last public presence was on 24 March last,\nwhen he participated in a wheelchair at the march\ncommemoration, for memory, truth and justice, of a\nnew anniversary of the beginning of the civic-military dictatorship\nin 1976.\n\n\n'Norita', as everyone called her lovingly, miligated\nsince 1977 in the search for the many thousands of desaparecidos\ncaused by the action of the Argentine military during the dictatorship,\nincluding his son Carlos Gustavo, who died 15\nApril 1977.\n\n\nDuring his intense life, he had received four\nHonorary degrees cause, including one of the Free University of\nBrussels, and days ago Parliament of the city of Buenos Aires\nhe gave her the Jorge Morresi award \"for career,\nthe commitment and defence of democracy and human rights.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Committed against dictatorship and the search for desaparecidos",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Mother of Plaza de Mayo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nora Cortiñas",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nora Cortiñas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "1976-1983",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mayo-Linea Fundadora",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the age of 94\nYears",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "17 May",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cortiñas",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days later",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 March last",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 493,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1976",
                "start_char": 667,
                "end_char": 671,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norita",
                "start_char": 676,
                "end_char": 682,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1977",
                "start_char": 734,
                "end_char": 738,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the many thousands",
                "start_char": 757,
                "end_char": 775,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 821,
                "end_char": 830,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carlos Gustavo",
                "start_char": 883,
                "end_char": 897,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 908,
                "end_char": 910,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "April 1977",
                "start_char": 911,
                "end_char": 921,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 966,
                "end_char": 970,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 1005,
                "end_char": 1008,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Free University",
                "start_char": 1012,
                "end_char": 1031,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "start_char": 1035,
                "end_char": 1043,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 1058,
                "end_char": 1068,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 1084,
                "end_char": 1096,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jorge Morresi",
                "start_char": 1113,
                "end_char": 1126,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tunisi: ministro Interno incontra presidente Ordine avvocati",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 09:28:14 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/05/31/tunisi-ministro-interno-incontra-presidente-ordine-avvocati_8ca90d43-1740-42bd-9f73-dfd720467883.html",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro tunisino dell'Interno\nKhaled Nouri ha ricevuto il presidente dell'Ordine degli\navvocati tunisini, Hatem Meziou, insieme al segretario di Stato\nincaricato della Sicurezza, Sofiane Ben Sadok, in un incontro\nche è stato \"un'occasione per esaminare le relazioni esistenti\ntra il ministro dell' Interno e l'Ordine nazionale degli\navvocati e le modalità per promuovere la cooperazione e la\ncomplementarità tra gli avvocati e l'istituzione di sicurezza\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Lo ha affermato il ministero dell'Interno in una nota,\nsottolineando che \"un campo d'azione comune unisce il ministero\ne l'Ordine degli avvocati\", che \"mira a preservare lo stato di\ndiritto e garantire tutti gli aspetti dei diritti dei cittadini\nottenendo giustizia e la corretta applicazione e rispetto delle\nnorme legge, preservando le libertà pubbliche e rispettando i\ndiritti umani\". Nel comunicato, il ministro Khaled Nouri,\nnominato pochi giorni fa, ha affermato che \"la professione\nlegale è una professione nobile con la nobile missione di\nottenere giustizia\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'incontro avviene dopo le polemiche seguite ai recenti\narresti di alcuni avvocati avvenuti presso la sede dell'Ordine,\nche hanno scatenato un'ondata di critiche da parte della\ncategoria e solidarietà da parte dei colleghi di tutto il mondo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t(ANSA)\n          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 80,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218026.9398732,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.26",
        "en_title": "Tunis: Minister Interior meets President Order lawyers",
        "en_content": "The Tunisian Interior Minister\nKhaled Nouri received the President of the Order\nTunisian lawyers, Hatem Meziou, together with the Secretary of State\nin charge of Security, Sofiane Ben Sadok, in a meeting\nthat it was \"an opportunity to examine existing relations\nbetween the Minister of the Interior and the National Order of the\nlawyers and ways to promote cooperation and\ncomplementarity between lawyers and the security institution\".\n\n\nThe Ministry of the Interior said this in a note,\nstressing that \"a common field of action unites the ministry\nand the Order of Lawyers, which \"was to preserve the state of\nright and ensure all aspects of citizens' rights\nobtaining justice and the correct application and respect of\nlaw rules, preserving public freedoms and respecting\nhuman rights.\" In the statement, Minister Khaled Nouri,\nappointed a few days ago, said that \"the profession\nlegal is a noble profession with the noble mission of\nobtain justice.\"\n\n\nThe meeting takes place after the controversy followed by the recent\narrests of some lawyers at the seat of the Order,\nthat triggered a wave of criticism from the\ncategory and solidarity from colleagues around the world.\n\n\n(ANSA)\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tunis",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tunisian",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khaled Nouri",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Order\nTunisian lawyers",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hatem Meziou",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Security",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sofiane Ben Sadok",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Order",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of the Interior",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Order of Lawyers",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Khaled Nouri",
                "start_char": 816,
                "end_char": 828,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days ago",
                "start_char": 840,
                "end_char": 854,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Order",
                "start_char": 1067,
                "end_char": 1072,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "solidarity",
                "start_char": 1131,
                "end_char": 1141,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA",
                "start_char": 1179,
                "end_char": 1183,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, 'Trump condannato? Americani scelgano il loro leader'",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 09:50:01 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/31/tajani-trump-condannato-americani-scelgano-il-loro-leader_2f26c24d-41f6-4bd2-bfa8-922b82aa4e54.html",
        "subtitle": "'L'Italia non è alleata di questo o di quel presidente'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Mi pare che sia una partita aperta\nquella negli Stati Uniti , ma l'Italia è alleata degli Stati\nUniti, non è alleata di questo o di quel presidente, sono gli\namericani che devono decidere chi vogliono che li guidi\npoliticamente\": lo ha detto a Mattino Cinque il ministro degli\nEsteri e vicepremier Antonio Tajani commentando la condanna\nall'ex presidente americano Donald Trump nel caso pornostar.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Per noi è indifferente, noi abbiamo un rapporto privilegiato\ncon gli Stati Uniti: sono l'altra faccia dell'Occidente, da una\nparte c'é l'Europa, e quindi l'Italia, dall'altra ci sono gli\nStati Uniti - ha aggiunto -. Siamo per democrazie liberali e\noccidentali e per il libero mercato, per lo stato di diritto,\nper la centralità della persona, ma non spetta a noi italiani\ndire chi deve fare il presidente degli Stati Uniti\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 78,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218026.9557745,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.26",
        "en_title": "Tajani, 'Trump convicted? Americans choose their leader",
        "en_content": "\"I think it's an open game.\nthat in the United States, but Italy is allied by the States\nU.S. is not ally of this or that president, it is the\nAmericans who have to decide who want them to drive\npolitically: told Mattino Cinque the minister of\nEsteri and vicepremier Antonio Tajani commenting on the condemnation\nto former American president Donald Trump in the pornstar case.\n\n\n\"For us it is indifferent, we have a privileged relationship\nwith the United States: I am the other face of the West, from one\nEurope, and therefore Italy, on the other hand there are the\nUnited States - he added -. We are for liberal democracies and\nWestern and free market, for the rule of law,\nfor the centrality of the person, but it is not up to us Italians\nsay who must be president of the United States.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Italy is not allied with this or that president'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Americans",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Americans",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mattino Cinque",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 227,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Esteri",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 445,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 491,
                "end_char": 495,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 505,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 506,
                "end_char": 512,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 533,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 567,
                "end_char": 580,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 733,
                "end_char": 741,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 771,
                "end_char": 788,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 796,
                "end_char": 829,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, possibile inviare altri Samp-T in Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:34:18 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/tajani-possibile-inviare-altri-samp-t-in-ucraina_80be9ed5-40ce-491c-820f-1c46be4ec39b.html",
        "subtitle": "'Ma importante usare queste armi per la difesa dentro il Paese'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Per noi è impossibile usare le\nnostre armi fuori dall'Ucraina. Siamo pronti a inviare altre\narmi ma è importante usare queste armi dentro l'Ucraina per la\ndifesa, come ad esempio la difesa aerea. Abbiamo inviato i\nSamp-T ed è possibile inviare altri Samp-T in difesa, ma è\nimportante utilizzare queste armi dentro l'Ucraina per la\ndifesa\". Lo ha detto il ministro degli Esteri Antonio Tajani\nalla ministeriale informale Esteri a Praga. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 77,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218026.9754972,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.26",
        "en_title": "Tajani, can send other Samp-T to Ukraine",
        "en_content": "\"It is impossible for us to use\nour weapons outside Ukraine. We are ready to send more\nweapons but it is important to use these weapons within Ukraine for\ndefence, such as air defense. We sent the\nSamp-T and you can send other Samp-T in defense, but it is\nimportant to use these weapons inside Ukraine for the\ndefense.\" The Foreign Minister Antonio Tajani said this\nto the informal Foreign Minister in Prague.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'But it's important to use these weapons for defense within the country'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 33,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prague",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mosca, conquistati 880 chilometri quadrati nel 2024",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:42:16 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/mosca-conquistati-880-chilometri-quadrati-nel-2024_a1f49c29-a028-49a8-b682-b2af247e0141.html",
        "subtitle": "Belousov: 'Kiev perde potenziale offensivo'",
        "content": " L'esercito russo sostiene di aver conquistato 880 km2 in Ucraina dall'inizio dell'anno. Lo afferma il ministro della Difesa Andrej Belousov, come riporta la Tass.     \"Kiev perde il potenziale offensivo ma continua a dire all'occidente che è pronta a combattere fino alla fine\", sostiene il ministro russo.     \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 76,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218027.0009944,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:27",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.27",
        "en_title": "Moscow, conquered 880 square kilometers in 2024",
        "en_content": "The Russian army claims to have conquered 880 km2 in Ukraine since the beginning of the year. Defense Minister Andrej Belousov says so, as the Tass reports. \"Kiev loses the offensive potential but continues to tell the West that he is ready to fight to the end,\" says the Russian minister.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Belousov: 'Kiev loses offensive potential'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "880 square kilometers",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "880 km2",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the beginning of the year",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Andrej Belousov",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 158,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 219,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 272,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Blinken, al vertice Nato ci sarà forte pacchetto per Kiev",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:34:03 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/31/blinken-al-vertice-nato-ci-sara-forte-pacchetto-per-kiev_984c306d-5fa9-48dd-b2c9-5756925e6b5a.html",
        "subtitle": "L'Alleanza si adatti per sfide future, come nell'Indo-Pacifico",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Oggi portiamo avanti le decisioni\nche verranno poi finalizzate al summit di Washington e si vedrà\nun pacchetto forte per l'Ucraina\". Lo ha detto il segretario di\nStato Usa Antony Blinken a Praga. \"Abbiamo un'alleanza più\nforte, più grande e con più risorse e prenderemo decisioni per\nportare la Nato nei prossimi 75 anni, adatta a fronteggiare le\nsfide del nostro tempo, e questo prevede anche il rafforzamento\ndella collaborazione con i nostri partner nell'Indo-Pacifico\",\nha aggiunto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 74,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218027.034138,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:27",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.27",
        "en_title": "Blinken, at the NATO summit there will be strong package for Kiev",
        "en_content": "\"Today we take decisions\nthat will then be finalized at the Washington summit and you will see\na strong package for Ukraine.\" The Secretary said so.\nState Use Antony Blinken in Prague. \"We have an alliance more\nstrong, bigger and with more resources and we will make decisions for\nbringing NATO to the next 75 years, suitable to face the\nchallenges of our time, and this also provides for strengthening\ncollaboration with our partners in the Indo-Pacific,\"\nadded.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Alliance adapts itself to future challenges, as in the Indo-Pacific",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Alliance",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Indo-Pacific",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antony Blinken",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 173,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prague",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the next 75 years",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Indo-Pacific",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Pechino, azioni Usa su Taiwan violano principio Unica Cina",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:33:51 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/05/31/pechino-azioni-usa-su-taiwan-violano-principio-unica-cina_64ddd1b0-edd0-4ebd-8804-25bb40f9de08.html",
        "subtitle": "Ministro della Difesa Dong durante incontro con capo Pentagono",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            I capi della Difesa di Cina e Usa\nhanno avuto un incontro \"positivo, pratico e costruttivo\" a\nmargine dei lavori dello Shangri-La Dialogue di Singapore.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tSecondo i media di Pechino, il ministro della Difesa Dong Jun si\nè lamentato con l'omologo americano Lloyd Austin per le azioni\ndegli Stati Uniti nei confronti di Taiwan ritenute \"in grave\nviolazione del principio della 'Unica Cina'\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 72,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218027.0435233,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:27",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.27",
        "en_title": "Beijing, US actions on Taiwan violate Single Principle China",
        "en_content": "The Heads of Defense of China and USA\nthey had a \"positive, practical and constructive\" meeting\nShangri-La Dialogue in Singapore.\n\n\nAccording to the Beijing media, Defense Minister Dong Jun\nis complained with American homologue Lloyd Austin for actions\nof the United States against Taiwan considered \"in grave\nviolation of the principle of 'China'.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Defense Minister Dong during meeting with Chief Pentagon",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Single Principle China",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Dong",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pentagon",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Heads of Defense of China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shangri-La Dialogue",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Singapore",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Defense",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dong Jun",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lloyd Austin",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Orban, l'Ue è a pochi centimetri dalla distruzione",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:43:57 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/orban-lue-e-a-pochi-centimetri-dalla-distruzione_2038cf91-6344-4e9a-bca0-d8c57875ea1e.html",
        "subtitle": "'Sta passando da discussione alla preparazione della guerra'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Europa è entrata in una fase\nintermedia dei preparativi per la guerra con la Russia: lo ha\ndichiarato il premier ungherese Viktor Orban alla radio Kossuth,\ncome riporta la Tass.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t  Il primo ministro ha sottolineato che \"l'entrata in guerra non\navviene in una sola fase\". \"Ci sono tre fasi: discussione,\npreparazione e distruzione. Ora stiamo terminando la discussione\ne siamo nella fase di preparazione. Siamo a pochi centimetri\ndalla distruzione\", ha detto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 75,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218027.052975,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:27",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.27",
        "en_title": "Orban, the EU is a few centimetres from destruction",
        "en_content": "Europe has entered a phase\nIntermediate preparations for war with Russia: He did.\nHungarian premier Viktor Orban on the Kossuth radio,\nas the Tass reports.\n\n\nThe Prime Minister underlined that \"war entry not\nit takes place in one phase.\" \"There are three stages: discussion,\npreparation and destruction. Now we're ending the discussion\nand we are in the preparation phase. We're a few inches.\nfrom destruction,\" he said.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'It is going from discussion to the preparation of war'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Orban",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a few centimetres",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hungarian",
                "start_char": 82,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Viktor Orban",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kossuth",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 226,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 254,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few inches",
                "start_char": 379,
                "end_char": 391,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa, ribadito il rispetto della politica di una sola Cina",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 10:33:58 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/31/usa-ribadito-il-rispetto-della-politica-di-una-sola-cina_6dcf9b3b-9115-4082-9dd7-8085aa0f277c.html",
        "subtitle": "'Non usi la transizione politica a Taiwan per misure coercitive'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nel primo incontro tra i\nresponsabili della Difesa Usa e Cina a Singapore gli  Stati\nUniti hanno ribadito il loro impegno a rispettare la politica di\nuna sola Cina. Il Pentagono ha reso noto anche che gli Usa hanno\nribadito che la Cina non deve usare la transizione politica di\nTaiwan \"come pretesto per misure coercitive\". I due Paesi, ha\nfatto sapere il Pentagono riprenderanno le comunicazioni\ntelefoniche militari \"nei prossimi mesi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 73,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717218027.0726328,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-06-01 07:00:27",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-06-01T07.00.27",
        "en_title": "U.S., reiterated the respect for a single China policy",
        "en_content": "In the first meeting between\nUS and China Defense Managers in Singapore States\nThe United States has reiterated their commitment to respect the policy of\none China. The Pentagon also announced that the US had\nreiterated that China should not use the political transition\nTaiwan \"as a pretext for coercive measures\". The two countries, has\nthat the Pentagon will report\nmilitary telephones \"in the coming months\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Do not use the political transition to Taiwan for coercive measures'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
