[
    {
        "title": "Navalnaya, 'Putin potrebbe usare le armi nucleari'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 21 Apr 2024 12:09:58 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-21",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/21/navalnaya-putin-potrebbe-usare-le-armi-nucleari_55982c78-50b7-48bb-a16b-cc5cfda9dd4b.html",
        "subtitle": "Vedova del dissidente russo:'Non sappiamo cosa aspettarci da lui",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La vedova in esilio del defunto\nleader dell'opposizione russa Aleksei Navalny, Yulia Navalnaya\nha detto in un'intervista alla Dpa, ripresa da Radio Free\nEurope, che \"nessuno sa\" cosa aspettarsi dal presidente russo\nVladimir Putin e ha avvertito che il leader del Cremlino\npotrebbe usare armi nucleari. \"Non  sappiamo cosa aspettarci da\nlui.Probabilmente lo farebbe\", ha affermato Navalnaya alla\ndomanda se pensava che Putin si sarebbe rifiutato di usare le\narmi nucleari. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.1910548,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Navalnaya, 'Putin could use nuclear weapons'",
        "en_content": "The widow of the deceased\nRussian opposition leader Aleksei Navalny, Yulia Navalnaya\nsaid in an interview with Dpa, taken from Radio Free\nEurope, which \"no one knows\" what to expect from Russian President\nVladimir Putin and warned that the leader of the Kremlin\ncould use nuclear weapons. \"We don't know what to expect from\nHe. He probably would,\" said Navalnaya at the\nquestion if he thought Putin would refuse to use the\nnuclear weapons.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Russian dissident widow:'We don't know what to expect from him",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Navalnaya",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aleksei Navalny",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yulia Navalnaya",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 84,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dpa",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Radio Free\nEurope",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Navalnaya",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 398,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Governo Ortega cancella Miss Nicaragua e lancia il suo concorso",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:19:31 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/04/20/governo-ortega-cancella-miss-nicaragua-e-lancia-il-suo-concorso_1b52c27f-671b-4f4b-afec-98f535c829f4.html",
        "subtitle": "Snobbato il trionfo di una connazionale all'ultimo Miss Universo",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il governo di Daniel Ortega ha\nlanciato il proprio concorso di bellezza femminile, in polemica\ncon l'organizzazione di Miss Nicaragua, la cui direttrice, Karen\nCelebertti, è stata bandita e accusata di tradimento della\npatria, riciclaggio di denaro e diffusione di notizie false.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il 26 aprile lanceremo, a Dio piacendo, una nuova attività\nper riconoscere il talento, la creatività e la bellezza del\nNicaragua\", ha annunciato la vicepresidente e moglie di Ortega,\nRosario Murillo, precisando che le nuove regine di bellezza\nelette saranno \"ambasciatrici dell'amore per il Nicaragua\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il nuovo concorso di bellezza, chiamato 'Regine del\nNicaragua', sarà gestito, tra gli altri enti, dal ministero\ndella Gioventù e dall'Istituto del Turismo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il trionfo della nicaraguense Sheynnis Palacios come Miss\nUniverso, il 18 novembre a San Salvador, è stato accolto con\nfreddezza dall'esecutivo, che ha impedito l'ingresso nel Paese\ndella direttrice di Miss Nicaragua, rimpatriata in Messico\ndall'aeroporto di Managua. Il 21 novembre, inoltre, la polizia\nha impedito a due artisti locali di realizzare un murale in\nomaggio alla loro connazionale vincitrice del concorso. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 46,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.2260244,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Ortega Government cancels Miss Nicaragua and launches its competition",
        "en_content": "The government of Daniel Ortega has\nlaunched its own female beauty contest, in polemic\nwith the organization of Miss Nicaragua, whose director, Karen\nCelebertti, has been banned and accused of treason\nHomeland, money laundering and dissemination of false news.\n\n\n\"On April 26th, we will launch a new activity to God.\nto recognize the talent, creativity and beauty of\nNicaragua\", announced the vice president and wife of Ortega,\nRosario Murillo, specifying that the new queens of beauty\nelette will be \"embassies of love for Nicaragua\".\n\n\nThe new beauty contest, called 'Queen of the\nNicaragua will be managed, among other bodies, by the Ministry\nYouth and Tourism Institute.\n\n\nThe triumph of Nicaraguan Sheynnis Palacios as Miss\nUniverso, on 18 November in San Salvador, was welcomed with\ncoldness from the executive, which prevented entry into the country\nof the director of Miss Nicaragua, repatriated in Mexico\nfrom Managua airport. On 21 November the police\nprevented two local artists from building a mural in\nhomage to their winning compatriot of the competition.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The triumph of a compatriot at the last Miss Universe",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ortega Government",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicaragua",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Universe",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Daniel Ortega",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicaragua",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karen\nCelebertti",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Homeland",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "April 26th",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicaragua",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 376,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ortega",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rosario Murillo",
                "start_char": 428,
                "end_char": 443,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicaragua",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 533,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicaragua",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 592,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry\nYouth and Tourism Institute",
                "start_char": 633,
                "end_char": 673,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicaraguan",
                "start_char": 692,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Miss\nUniverso",
                "start_char": 724,
                "end_char": 737,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "18 November",
                "start_char": 742,
                "end_char": 753,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "San Salvador",
                "start_char": 757,
                "end_char": 769,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicaragua",
                "start_char": 881,
                "end_char": 890,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 907,
                "end_char": 913,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Managua",
                "start_char": 919,
                "end_char": 926,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "21 November",
                "start_char": 939,
                "end_char": 950,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 972,
                "end_char": 975,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ministro Israele a Erdogan, vergognati a incontrare Hamas",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:42:02 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/20/ministro-israele-a-erdogan-vergognati-a-incontrare-hamas_c99bf32a-fd8c-4f29-ad3c-a509b2bc415d.html",
        "subtitle": "Dopo colloquio presidente turco con Haniyeh",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"I Fratelli Musulmani: stupri,\nomicidi, profanazione di cadaveri e bambini bruciati. Erdogan,\nvergognati!\". Così, in risposta all'incontro tra il presidente\nturco Erdogan e il capo di Hamas Ismail Haniyeh, reagisce su X\nil ministro degli Esteri israeliano Israel Katz. Il tweet è\nstato pubblicato anche sul suo account in turco. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 40,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.3315845,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Minister Israel in Erdogan, ashamed to meet Hamas",
        "en_content": "\"The Muslim Brothers: rape,\nmurders, dead bodies and burned children. Erdogan,\nshamed!\" Thus, in response to the meeting between the President\nTurkish Erdogan and the head of Hamas Ismail Haniyeh, reacts on X\nIsraeli Foreign Minister Israel Katz. The tweet is\nwas also posted on your Turkish account.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "After interview Turkish president with Haniyeh",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Muslim Brothers",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish Erdogan",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 158,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ismail Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel Katz",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Conservatori in vantaggio nella Macedonia del Nord",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:21:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/20/conservatori-in-vantaggio-nella-macedonia-del-nord_d65481da-d505-489b-90b9-e9f9d8f5ce2b.html",
        "subtitle": "Al culmine la campagna per presidenziali e legislative",
        "content": "La Macedonia del Nord è in piena campagna elettorale in vista delle due consultazioni di primavera - le presidenziali del 24 aprile e le parlamentari dell'8 maggio. E stando a un ultimo sondaggio condotto dal Centro per la ricerca politica e la comunicazione (Crpc), il fronte conservatore all'opposizione è dato in vantaggio sui socialdemocratici al potere in entrambe le elezioni. Per le presidenziali Gordana Siljanovska Davkova, candidata del Vmro-Dpmne, il principale partito dell'opposizione conservatrice, è accreditata di un 20,4% di consensi rispetto al 16,8% attribuito al presidente uscente Stevo Pendarovski, sostenuto dal Partito socialdemocratico (Sdsm) al governo, e che corre per un secondo mandato quinquennale. Tra i candidati della minoranza albanese, Arben Taravari della coalizione 'Vredi' (all'opposizione) può contare sul 7,9% di preferenze, mentre Bujar Osmani, attuale ministro degli esteri e rappresentante del Fronte europeo guidato dalla formazione 'Dui' (al governo), è accreditato del 6,9%. Su percentuali minori possono contare gli altri tre candidati alla carica di presidente - Maksim Dimitrievski ('Znam') al 2,7%, Biljana Vankovska ('Levica', Sinistra) data al 2,6%, Stevco Jakimovski ('Grom') all'1,2%. Il 18,2% ha affermato che non voterà per nessuno dei candidati.     Stando allo stesso sondaggio, il Vmro-Dpmne è dato in vantaggio anche per le elezioni legislative, con il 22,8% rispetto al 16,3% di cui è accreditato l'Sdsm. Seguono distanziate le due coalizioni della minoranza albanese - 'Vredi' (opposizione) al 7,7% e 'Dui'(al governo) al 6,9%, mentre 'Levica' (Sinistra) è data al 3,9%, seguito dal partito 'Znam' con il 3,2%. Il 17,6% ha risposto che non voterà per nessuna forza politica.     L'inchiesta del Crpc è stata condotta telefonicamente dall'8 al 13 aprile su un campione indicativo di 1.210 elettori. Con tutta probabilità alle presidenziali nessuno dei candidati otterrà il 50% più uno dei consensi al primo turno e sarà necessario un ballottaggio fra i primi due, in programma l'8 maggio, unitamente alle elezioni parlamentari. Le previsioni sono per una riedizione del duello fra Pendarovski e Siljanovska Davkova, che si erano sfidati anche alle precedenti presidenziali del 2019, quando Pendarovski si affermò al ballottaggio. La Macedonia del Nord, uno dei Paesi emersi dalla disgregazione della ex Jugoslavia, ha aderito alla Nato quattro anni fa, e nel luglio 2022 ha avviato il negoziato di adesione alla Ue. \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 39,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.3656774,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Conservators in advantage in North Macedonia",
        "en_content": "North Macedonia is in full electoral campaign in view of the two spring consultations - the presidential elections of 24 April and the MPs of 8 May. And according to a last survey conducted by the Centre for Political Research and Communication (Crpc), the Conservative Front for the Opposition is given in advantage on the Social-Democrats to power in both elections. For President Gordana Siljanovska Davkova, Vmro-Dpmne's candidate, the main party of the conservative opposition, is accredited by a 20.4% consensus over 16.8% attributed to the outgoing president Stevo Pendarovski, supported by the Social Democratic Party (Sdsm) to the government, and running for a second five-year term. Among the candidates of the Albanian minority, Arben Taravari of the 'Vredi' coalition (at the opposition) can count on 7.9% of preferences, while Bujar Osmani, current foreign minister and representative of the European Front led by the formation 'Dui' (to the government), is accredited 6.9%. On lower percentages can count the other three candidates to the office of president - Maksim Dimitrievski ('Znam') to 2.7%, Biljana Vankovska ('Levica', Left) given to 2.6%, Stevco Jakimovski ('Grom') to 1.2%. 18.2% said it would not vote for any of the candidates. According to the same survey, the Vmro-Dpmne is also given in the lead for legislative elections, with 22.8% compared to 16.3% of which the Sdsm is accredited. The two coalitions of the Albanian minority - 'Vredi' (opposition) to 7.7% and 'Dui' (government) to 6.9%, while 'Levica' (Sinistra) is 3.9%, followed by the 'Znam' party with 3.2%. 17.6% said it would not vote for any political force. The Crpc investigation was conducted by telephone from 8 to 13 April on an indicative sample of 1,210 voters. In all probability, none of the candidates will receive 50% more than one of the first round consents and a ballot will be required between the first two, scheduled on May 8, together with the parliamentary elections. The forecasts are for a re-edition of the duel between Pendarovski and Siljanovska Davkova, which also challenged the presidential precedents of 2019, when Pendarovski agreed to the ballot. North Macedonia, one of the countries that emerged from the disintegration of the former Yugoslavia, joined NATO four years ago, and in July 2022 initiated the EU accession negotiations.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "At the height of the presidential and legislative campaign",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "North Macedonia",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "North Macedonia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 April",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 May",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Centre for Political Research and Communication (Crpc",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Conservative Front for the Opposition",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 294,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Social-Democrats",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gordana Siljanovska",
                "start_char": 383,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vmro-Dpmne's",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "20.4%",
                "start_char": 502,
                "end_char": 507,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "16.8%",
                "start_char": 523,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Stevo Pendarovski",
                "start_char": 566,
                "end_char": 583,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Social Democratic Party",
                "start_char": 598,
                "end_char": 625,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 670,
                "end_char": 676,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "five-year",
                "start_char": 677,
                "end_char": 686,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Albanian",
                "start_char": 721,
                "end_char": 729,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arben Taravari",
                "start_char": 740,
                "end_char": 754,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vredi",
                "start_char": 763,
                "end_char": 768,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "7.9%",
                "start_char": 813,
                "end_char": 817,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Bujar Osmani",
                "start_char": 840,
                "end_char": 852,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Front",
                "start_char": 901,
                "end_char": 919,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "6.9%",
                "start_char": 982,
                "end_char": 986,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 1029,
                "end_char": 1034,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2.7%",
                "start_char": 1107,
                "end_char": 1111,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Biljana",
                "start_char": 1113,
                "end_char": 1120,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Levica",
                "start_char": 1133,
                "end_char": 1139,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Left",
                "start_char": 1142,
                "end_char": 1146,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2.6%",
                "start_char": 1157,
                "end_char": 1161,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Stevco Jakimovski",
                "start_char": 1163,
                "end_char": 1180,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1.2%",
                "start_char": 1193,
                "end_char": 1197,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "18.2%",
                "start_char": 1199,
                "end_char": 1204,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Vmro-Dpmne",
                "start_char": 1289,
                "end_char": 1299,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "22.8%",
                "start_char": 1358,
                "end_char": 1363,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "16.3%",
                "start_char": 1376,
                "end_char": 1381,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Sdsm",
                "start_char": 1395,
                "end_char": 1399,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1419,
                "end_char": 1422,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Albanian",
                "start_char": 1441,
                "end_char": 1449,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vredi",
                "start_char": 1462,
                "end_char": 1467,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "7.7%",
                "start_char": 1485,
                "end_char": 1489,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "6.9%",
                "start_char": 1516,
                "end_char": 1520,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Levica",
                "start_char": 1529,
                "end_char": 1535,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sinistra",
                "start_char": 1538,
                "end_char": 1546,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "3.9%",
                "start_char": 1551,
                "end_char": 1555,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "3.2%",
                "start_char": 1591,
                "end_char": 1595,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "17.6%",
                "start_char": 1597,
                "end_char": 1602,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Crpc",
                "start_char": 1655,
                "end_char": 1659,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 to 13 April",
                "start_char": 1706,
                "end_char": 1719,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1,210",
                "start_char": 1747,
                "end_char": 1752,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "50%",
                "start_char": 1817,
                "end_char": 1820,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "more than one",
                "start_char": 1821,
                "end_char": 1834,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1842,
                "end_char": 1847,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1905,
                "end_char": 1910,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 1911,
                "end_char": 1914,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 8",
                "start_char": 1929,
                "end_char": 1934,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pendarovski",
                "start_char": 2034,
                "end_char": 2045,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Siljanovska Davkova",
                "start_char": 2050,
                "end_char": 2069,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2019",
                "start_char": 2124,
                "end_char": 2128,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "North Macedonia",
                "start_char": 2169,
                "end_char": 2184,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 2186,
                "end_char": 2189,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yugoslavia",
                "start_char": 2258,
                "end_char": 2268,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 2277,
                "end_char": 2281,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four years ago",
                "start_char": 2282,
                "end_char": 2296,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "July 2022",
                "start_char": 2305,
                "end_char": 2314,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 2329,
                "end_char": 2331,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Erdogan ad Haniyeh, 'i palestinesi siano uniti contro Israele'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:40:01 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/20/erdogan-ad-haniyeh-i-palestinesi-siano-uniti-contro-israele_b95de941-ef57-428e-8990-71a132031ae1.html",
        "subtitle": "Nell'incontro discussi anche gli sforzi per cessate fuoco a Gaza",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Un appello all' \"unità\" dei\npalestinesi contro Israele è stato lanciato oggi dal presidente\nturco Recep Tayyip Erdogan al termine del suo incontro con il\nleader di Hamas Ismaïl Haniyeh a Istanbul nel quale, secondo\nl'emittente statale Trt i due hanno discusso degli sforzi per\nraggiungere un cessate il fuoco a Gaza e degli aiuti umanitari a\nGaza. \"È fondamentale che i palestinesi agiscano uniti in questo\nprocesso; la risposta più forte a Israele e il percorso verso la\nvittoria passano attraverso l'unità e l'integrità\", ha affermato\nErdogan secondo un comunicato della presidenza turca.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Dopo le recenti tensioni tra Israele e Iran, il presidente\nturco ha sottolineato che \"ciò che è accaduto non dovrebbe far\nguadagnare terreno a Israele e che è importante agire in modo da\nmantenere l'attenzione su Gaza\". Erdogan ha anche assicurato che\nla Turchia \"continuerà il suo aiuto umanitario alla Palestina\nper alleviare il più possibile le sofferenze\" della popolazione\ndi Gaza e ha ricordato che il suo Paese ha adottato \"una serie\ndi sanzioni contro Israele, comprese restrizioni commerciali\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 41,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.3797565,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Erdogan to Haniyeh, 'The Palestinians are united against Israel'",
        "en_content": "An appeal to the \"unity\" of\nPalestinians against Israel was launched today by the President\nTurkish Recep Tayyip Erdogan at the end of his meeting with the\nleader of Hamas Ismaïl Haniyeh in Istanbul in which, second\nthe state broadcaster Trt the two discussed efforts to\nto reach a ceasefire in Gaza and humanitarian aid\nGaza. \"It is essential that the Palestinians act together in this\nprocess; the strongest response to Israel and the path to\nvictory passes through unity and integrity,\" he said.\nErdogan according to a statement from the Turkish presidency.\n\n\nAfter the recent tensions between Israel and Iran, the President\nTurkish underlined that \"what happened should not make\nearn land in Israel and that it is important to act so as to\nkeep the attention on Gaza.\" Erdogan also assured that\nTurkey \"will continue its humanitarian aid to Palestine\nto relieve the suffering as much as possible\" of the population\nof Gaza and remembered that his country adopted \"a series\nof sanctions against Israel, including trade restrictions.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The meeting also discussed the efforts to ceasefire in Gaza",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 166,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ismaïl Haniyeh",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Istanbul",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 198,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 209,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trt the",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 422,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 548,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 597,
                "end_char": 603,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 608,
                "end_char": 612,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 628,
                "end_char": 635,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 696,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 766,
                "end_char": 770,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 773,
                "end_char": 780,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkey",
                "start_char": 799,
                "end_char": 805,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 845,
                "end_char": 854,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 922,
                "end_char": 926,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 998,
                "end_char": 1004,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Somalia rifiuta dialogo con l'Etiopia su accordo col Somaliland",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:28:23 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/04/20/somalia-rifiuta-dialogo-con-letiopia-su-accordo-col-somaliland_1f6f7565-3613-4fe9-8866-81b03b2a055c.html",
        "subtitle": "Risposta alla preoccupazione da parte del G7",
        "content": "Il Governo federale somalo ha dichiarato con fermezza che non avvierà alcun dialogo con l'Etiopia in merito agli accordi tra Addis Abeba e l'autoproclamata regione del Somaliland. La decisione, come riporta il sito Shabelle Media, è stata annunciata in risposta a un comunicato del G7 che esprimeva preoccupazione per l'accordo tra Etiopia e Somaliland, che la Somalia considera una violazione della propria sovranità e integrità territoriale.     La Somalia ha manifestato un forte impegno a mantenere la pace e la stabilità regionale e ha espresso la volontà di collaborare con il G7 e altri partner internazionali. Il Somaliland non è riconosciuto a livello internazionale come Paese indipendente, sebbene gestisca le proprie forze armate e la propria banca centrale e tenga regolari elezioni dal 1991, anno in cui ha rivendicato l'indipendenza dalla Somalia, pochi mesi dopo la caduta del Paese nella guerra civile.    \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 43,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.3980985,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Somalia refuses dialogue with Ethiopia on agreement with Somaliland",
        "en_content": "The Somali Federal Government has firmly stated that it will not start any dialogue with Ethiopia on the agreements between Addis Ababa and the self-proclaimed Somaliland region. The decision, as the Shabelle Media site reports, was announced in response to a G7 communiqué expressing concern for the agreement between Ethiopia and Somaliland, which Somalia considers a violation of its sovereignty and territorial integrity. Somalia has expressed a strong commitment to maintain regional peace and stability and expressed its willingness to cooperate with the G7 and other international partners. Somaliland is not internationally recognized as an independent country, although it manages its armed forces and its central bank and holds regular elections since 1991, when it claimed independence from Somalia, a few months after the country's fall in civil war.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Response to G7 concern",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Somalia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ethiopia",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Somaliland",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Response",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Somali Federal Government",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ethiopia",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Addis Ababa",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Somaliland",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Shabelle Media",
                "start_char": 200,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ethiopia",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Somaliland",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Somalia",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Somalia",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 433,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "G7",
                "start_char": 561,
                "end_char": 563,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Somaliland",
                "start_char": 598,
                "end_char": 608,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "1991",
                "start_char": 762,
                "end_char": 766,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Somalia",
                "start_char": 802,
                "end_char": 809,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few months",
                "start_char": 811,
                "end_char": 823,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Media, almeno tre morti in un raid israeliano nel sud Libano",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:26:09 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/20/media-almeno-tre-morti-in-un-raid-israeliano-nel-sud-libano_0850d87d-d0cc-417d-8e25-2817910d3e63.html",
        "subtitle": "Attacco contro postazioni di Hezbollah",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Almeno tre morti e un numero\nimprecisato di feriti sono il bilancio di un raid israeliano\ncontro postazioni di Hezbollah ad al-Jabin, nel sud del Libano.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo scrive Ynet citando media libanesi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 45,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.4598725,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Average, at least three deaths in an Israeli raid in southern Lebanon",
        "en_content": "At least three dead and a number\nthe budget of an Israeli raid\nagainst positions of Hezbollah to al-Jabin, in southern Lebanon.\n\n\nYnet writes about Lebanese media.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Attack against posts by Hezbollah",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "at least three",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "At least three",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 93,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "al-Jabin",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 119,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ynet",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanese",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "In Birmania riparte la guerriglia fra milizie entiche e giunta",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:29:21 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/20/in-birmania-riparte-la-guerriglia-fra-milizie-entiche-e-giunta_88278641-17b8-4447-9247-d08eb7b92808.html",
        "subtitle": "Scontri fra i militari e miliziani Karen sul confine thailandese",
        "content": "Dopo giorni di calma relativa, sono ripresi gli scontri armati in Birmania fra gruppi etnici e i militari che rispondono alla giunta che ha preso il potere con un golpe militare nel febbraio del 2021: scontri si sono verificati a ridosso del confine con la Thailandia, nel sud-est del Paese, dove i miliziani dell'Unione nazionale Karen (Knu), espressione dell'omonima etnia, un mese fa aveva costretto l'esercito a ritirarsi dalla città di Myawaddy, nello stato di Kayin (o Karen). I militari, nei giorni scorsi si erano ritirati sotto a un ponte che collega Myawaddy con la città thailandese di Mae Sot, secondo quanto dichiarato dal Knu. Fonti thailandesi dalla vicina Mae Sot confermano nelle ultime ore una \"intensificazione\" dei combattimenti, mentre circa 2.000 civili avrebbero attraversato il confine e sarebbero entrati in territorio thailandese, accolti da profughi.     Latente durante il decennio di democrazia, la ribellione armata delle etnie contro il potere centrale in Birmania è ripreso con forza dopo il colpo di stato dei militari. Questi ultimi, pur avendo represso nel sangue il dissenso nelle città, non riescono ad avere ragione delle insurrezioni periferiche e la minaccia per la giunta sta crescendo di mese in mese, infliggendo loro gravi perdite. Particolarmente duro è stata per i militari il colpo della perdita del controllo su Myawaddy e di conseguenza sul commercio di merci per un valore di oltre un miliardo di dollari che vi è transitato solo negli ultimi 12 mesi. \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 37,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.4747612,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "In Burma the guerrilla warfare between ancillary militias and the junta",
        "en_content": "After days of relative calm, armed clashes in Burma between ethnic groups and military responding to the junta that took power with a military coup in February 2021: clashes occurred near the border with Thailand, in the south-east of the country, where the militiamen of the National Union Karen (Knu), expression of the homonymous ethnicity, a month ago forced the army to withdraw from the city of Myawaddy, in the state of Kayin (or Karen). The military had recently retired under a bridge connecting Myawaddy to the Thai city of Mae Sot, according to Knu. Thai sources from nearby Mae Sot confirm in recent hours a \"intensification\" of the fighting, while about 2,000 civilians would cross the border and enter the Thai territory, welcomed by refugees. Latente during the decade of democracy, the armed rebellion of ethnic groups against central power in Burma is strongly resumed after the military coup. The latter, while having repressed the dissent in the cities, fail to have reason for peripheral insurrections and the threat to the junta is growing from month to month, inflicting serious losses on them. Particularly hard was for the military the blow of the loss of control on Myawaddy and consequently on the trade of goods for a value of more than a billion dollars that has passed there only in the last 12 months.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Meet the military and militia Karen on the Thai border",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Burma",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Karen",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thai",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "days",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Burma",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "February 2021",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thailand",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Union Karen (Knu",
                "start_char": 272,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a month ago",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Myawaddy",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 409,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kayin",
                "start_char": 427,
                "end_char": 432,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Karen",
                "start_char": 437,
                "end_char": 442,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Myawaddy",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 513,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thai",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mae Sot",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 541,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thai",
                "start_char": 561,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mae Sot",
                "start_char": 586,
                "end_char": 593,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent hours",
                "start_char": 605,
                "end_char": 617,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "about 2,000",
                "start_char": 661,
                "end_char": 672,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thai",
                "start_char": 720,
                "end_char": 724,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the decade",
                "start_char": 773,
                "end_char": 783,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Burma",
                "start_char": 860,
                "end_char": 865,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "month",
                "start_char": 1066,
                "end_char": 1071,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Myawaddy",
                "start_char": 1191,
                "end_char": 1199,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than a billion dollars",
                "start_char": 1254,
                "end_char": 1281,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last 12 months",
                "start_char": 1312,
                "end_char": 1330,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "La Camera Usa vota oggi gli aiuti per Ucraina e Israele",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:14:20 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/20/la-camera-usa-vota-oggi-gli-aiuti-per-ucraina-e-israele_a7b0b0ad-3efe-4ccf-a982-629e579e765e.html",
        "subtitle": "Nel mirino anche TikTok, asset Mosca e sanzioni a Russia-Iran",
        "content": "La Camera Usa vota quattro distinti disegni di legge per gli aiuti per l'Ucraina (60 miliardi di dollari), Israele (26, di cui 9 per aiuti umanitari) e Taiwan (8 miliardi), mentre uno mira a bandire TikTok (se l'app cinese non verrà venduta), a utilizzare gli asset russi congelati e imporre nuove sanzioni a Mosca, Teheran e Pechino.     In caso di approvazione, il Senato seguirà a ruota nel weekend, quindi la firma di Joe Biden. In tal caso i primi aiuti a Kiev potrebbero arrivare gia' la prossima settimana. Lo speaker della Camera Mike Johnson mettera' ai voti anche un provvedimento per una stretta sui migranti al confine col Messico.\n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 34,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.4913216,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "The Room USA today votes for Ukraine and Israel",
        "en_content": "The Room USA votes four distinct bills for aid for Ukraine (60 billion dollars), Israel (26, of which 9 for humanitarian aid) and Taiwan (8 billion), while one aims to ban TikTok (if the Chinese app is not sold), to use the frozen Russian assets and impose new sanctions in Moscow, Tehran and Beijing. In the event of approval, the Senate will be revolving on the weekend, so the signature of Joe Biden. In that case, the first aid in Kiev could be coming next week. House Speaker Mike Johnson will also vote for a ban on migrants bordering Mexico.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In the view also TikTok, Moscow asset and sanctions to Russia-Iran",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "TikTok",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 55,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Room USA",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "60 billion dollars",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "26",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "9",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "8 billion",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "TikTok",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 178,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 187,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 293,
                "end_char": 300,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the weekend",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 422,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 439,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next week",
                "start_char": 456,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mike Johnson",
                "start_char": 481,
                "end_char": 493,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 541,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ribadito il no alla Russia per cerimonia anniversario Hiroshima",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:20:53 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-20",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/20/ribadito-il-no-alla-russia-per-cerimonia-anniversario-hiroshima_7e7bc35c-7f6f-4d48-b4f4-1ff312f6c048.html",
        "subtitle": "E' terzo anno consecutivo, anche a Bielorussia. Invito a Israele",
        "content": "Per il terzo anno consecutivo, la Russia e la Bielorussia non saranno invitate alla commemorazione dell'anniversario della bomba atomica che si terrà il 6 agosto nella città di Hiroshima, mentre l'invito sarà esteso a Israele.     Lo anticipa il giornale online Asahi Shimbun, che cita fonti a conoscenza del dossier, spiegando che i rappresentanti di Russia e Bielorussia saranno considerate \"persone non grate\" alla cerimonia annuale al Memoriale della Pace, a causa del conflitto in corso in Ucraina .     \"La situazione non è cambiata rispetto all'anno scorso, e per questo motivo attueremo le stesse decisioni , ha dichiarato all'Asahi un funzionario dell'amministrazione cittadina, con il governo centrale che è stato già informato della decisione.     Hiroshima ha tuttavia intenzione di invitare un rappresentante di Israele - che da ottobre è impegnato in una guerra contro il gruppo militante islamico Hamas da ottobre, riferisce l'Asahi.     \"Non c'è in questo momento un'opinione condivisa nei Paesi del mondo sul conflitto in corso in Medio Oriente. Per questo motivo vogliamo trasmettere un messaggio di pace invitando Israele\", affermano le fonti.     Nel 2023, per il 78/esimo anniversario del bombardamento atomico, Hiroshima aveva richiesto la presenza dei leader e degli ambasciatori di 167 Paesi. La mattina del 6 agosto del 1945 un ordigno atomico venne sganciato dal bombardiere B29 statunitense 'Enola Gay', causando la morte di circa 140.000 residenti. Una seconda bomba venne utilizzata su Nagasaki il 9 agosto, con un bilancio di 74.000 vittima, decretando di fatto la fine della Seconda guerra mondiale pochi giorni dopo, con la resa incondizionata del Giappone.   \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 44,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713697226.5188925,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-04-21 13:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-21T13.00.26",
        "en_title": "Redeemed no to Russia for anniversary ceremony Hiroshima",
        "en_content": "For the third consecutive year, Russia and Belarus will not be invited to commemorate the anniversary of the atomic bomb that will be held on August 6 in the city of Hiroshima, while the invitation will be extended to Israel. The online newspaper Asahi Shimbun, which mentions sources to the dossier, explaining that representatives of Russia and Belarus will be considered \"non-grateful people\" at the annual ceremony at the Peace Memorial, because of the ongoing conflict in Ukraine . \"The situation has not changed since last year, and for this reason we will implement the same decisions,\" said Asahi, an official of the city administration, with the central government who has already been informed of the decision. Hiroshima, however, intends to invite an Israeli representative - who has been engaged in a war against the Islamic militant group Hamas since October, reports Asahi. \"There is currently no shared opinion in the countries of the world on the ongoing conflict in the Middle East. For this reason we want to convey a message of peace by inviting Israel,\" the sources say. In 2023, for the 78th anniversary of the atomic bombing, Hiroshima requested the presence of leaders and ambassadors from 167 countries. On the morning of August 6, 1945, an atomic device was released by the US bomber B29 'Enola Gay', causing the death of about 140.000 residents. A second bomb was used on Nagasaki on 9 August, with a budget of 74,000 casualties, effectively decreed the end of World War II a few days later, with the unconditional surrender of Japan.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "It's third consecutive year, even in Belarus. Send to Israel",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hiroshima",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "third consecutive year",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the third consecutive year",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "August 6",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 150,
