[
    {
        "title": "Netanyahu, la guerra non finirà fino a eliminazione Hamas",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 20:56:31 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/31/netanyahu-la-guerra-non-finira-fino-a-eliminazione-hamas_0af9c20a-8c96-4f7d-b8fa-8beca0b30a29.html",
        "subtitle": "'La road map proposta ci consente di raggiungere gli obiettivi'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il premier israeliano Benyamin\nNetanyahu ha autorizzato la squadra negoziale a \"presentare uno\nschema per raggiungere la liberazione degli ostaggi\". Lo ha\nannunciato l'ufficio del primo ministro precisando tuttavia che\n\"la guerra non finirà finché non saranno raggiunti tutti gli\nobiettivi prefissati, compreso il ritorno degli ostaggi e\nl'eliminazione dei miliziani e del governo di Hamas\". \"Lo schema\nproposto da Israele, inclusa la transizione condizionata da una\nfase all'altra - si aggiunge -, consente a Israele di mantenere\nquesti obiettivi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182032.7336166,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:32",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.32",
        "en_title": "Netanyahu, the war will not end until the elimination of Hamas",
        "en_content": "Israeli Prime Minister Benyamin\nNetanyahu authorized the negotiating team to \"present a\nplan to achieve the liberation of the hostages\". He did.\nannounced the office of the Prime Minister, however, specifying that\n\"The war will not end until all\nset targets, including the return of hostages and\nthe elimination of militiamen and the government of Hamas\". \"The scheme\nproposed by Israel, including the transition conditioned by a\nphase to the other - it adds -, allows Israel to maintain\nthese goals.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'The proposed road map allows us to achieve the objectives'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benyamin",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 348,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 380,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 469,
                "end_char": 475,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 540,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "In Ecuador denunciate 'ripetute morti violente in carcere'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 21:10:45 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/30/in-ecuador-denunciate-ripetute-morti-violente-in-carcere_4ad5e88e-296a-41f3-a924-158bb0874f9f.html",
        "subtitle": "Il Difensore civico sollecita lo Stato a prendere provvedimenti",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Ufficio del Difensore civico\ndell'Ecuador ha denunciato ripetuti casi di morte violenta di\ndetenuti \"con segni di presunte torture\" nelle carceri\necuadoriane, oltre ad avvertire di detenuti morti con evidenti\nsegni di denutrizione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    La denuncia arriva dopo l'ordine di un giudice di indagare\nsulle accuse di violazione dei diritti umani mosse dalle\norganizzazioni non governative, in allerta per la\nmilitarizzazione delle prigioni ordinata dal governo del\npresidente Daniel Noboa, per combattere la criminalità.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    Il Difensore civico ha sollecitato lo Stato a prendere\nprovvedimenti urgenti per garantire i diritti delle persone\nprivate della libertà. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 72,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.7336495,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "In Ecuador, you denounce violent deaths in prison",
        "en_content": "The Office of the Ombudsman\nof Ecuador has denounced repeated cases of violent death of\nprisoners \"with signs of alleged torture\" in prisons\nEcuadorian, as well as warn of dead prisoners with obvious\nsigns of malnutrition.\n\n\nThe complaint arrives after the order of a judge to investigate\non allegations of human rights violation\nnon-governmental organizations, in alert for\nmilitarization of prisons ordered by the government of\nPresident Daniel Noboa, to fight crime.\n\n\nThe Ombudsman urged the State to take\nurgent measures to ensure the rights of persons\nprivate freedom.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Ombudsman urges the State to take measures",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ombudsman",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Office of the Ombudsman",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuador",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ecuadorian",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Daniel Noboa",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ombudsman",
                "start_char": 476,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 496,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "La Colombia non invia i suoi osservatori elettorali in Venezuela",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 21:53:55 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/30/la-colombia-non-invia-i-suoi-osservatori-elettorali-in-venezuela_ac7ca579-fa4a-40e8-bce8-40923f1409aa.html",
        "subtitle": "La richiesta di Caracas declinata 'per motivi di tempo'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il governo colombiano non invierà i\nsuoi osservatori alle elezioni del 28 luglio in Venezuela. Lo ha\ndichiarato il ministro degli Esteri Luis Gilberto Murillo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'esponente del governo di Gustavo Petro ha detto che in\nqueste settimane è stata valutata la possibilità di inviare un\nteam della Missione di osservazione tecnica  elettorale, ma\nl'idea è stata scartata perché non c'è abbastanza tempo per\npreparare la trasferta.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La richiesta di una missione di osservatori dalla Colombia\nera stata avanzata dallo stesso governo di Nicolas Maduro,\nattraverso il ministro degli Esteri Yvan Gil.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Anche il Tribunale superiore elettorale del Brasile ha fatto\nsapere che non parteciperà al monitoraggio delle urne in\nVenezuela. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 71,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.7994766,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Colombia does not send its electoral observers to Venezuela",
        "en_content": "The Colombian government will not send\nhis observers at the July 28 elections in Venezuela. He did.\ndeclared Foreign Minister Luis Gilberto Murillo.\n\n\nGustavo Petro's government representative said that in\nthese weeks the possibility of sending a\nteam of the Election Technical Observation Mission, but\nthe idea was rejected because there is not enough time for\nprepare the transfer.\n\n\nThe request for a mission of observers from Colombia\nhad been advanced by the same government as Nicolas Maduro,\nthrough the Foreign Minister Yvan Gil.\n\n\nBrazil's Higher Election Tribunal also made\nknow that it will not participate in the monitoring of urns in\nVenezuela.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Caracas' request declined 'for reasons of time'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Colombian",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "July 28",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luis Gilberto Murillo",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gustavo Petro's",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "these weeks",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Election Technical Observation Mission",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicolas Maduro",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 497,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yvan Gil",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 536,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 540,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Higher Election Tribunal",
                "start_char": 549,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 647,
                "end_char": 656,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump, 'un processo farsa, è una vergogna'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 23:27:52 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/30/trump-un-processo-farsa-e-una-vergogna_aa732f4a-d1f7-4ede-b9eb-a22105dc34dd.html",
        "subtitle": "'Continuerò a combattere, il vero verdetto il 5 novembre'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"E' stato un processo farsa, è\nuna vergogna. Sono un uomo innocente\". Lo ha detto Donald Trump\nfuori dall'aula annunciando che \"continuerà a combattere\". \"Il\nvero verdetto sarà il 5 novembre\", ha aggiunto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 69,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.8104215,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Trump, 'a farce process, is a shame'",
        "en_content": "\"It was a farce process, it is\na shame. I'm an innocent man.\" Donald Trump said\noutside the court, announcing that \"will continue to fight\". \"\nTrue verdict will be on November 5,\" he added.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'I will continue to fight, the true verdict on November 5'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "November 5'",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "November 5",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump condannato nel caso pornostar",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 23:26:44 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/30/trump-condannato-nel-caso-pornostar_d825cf6f-6314-4cfb-a584-fd25f8b0ef5b.html",
        "subtitle": "'Colpevole' per tutti i 34 capi di imputazione",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Con lo storico verdetto di\ncolpevolezza raggiunto all'unanimità dalla giuria dopo due\ngiorni di camera di consiglio nel caso pornostar, Donald Trump\ndiventa il primo ex presidente americano condannato in un\nprocesso penale e anche il primo candidato presidenziale a\ncorrere come pregiudicato, uno status che comunque non gli\nimpedisce di essere eletto e fare il commander in chief. La\ncondanna, che sara' stabilita in un'udienza successiva, può\nvariare da un massimo di 4 anni di carcere alla messa in prova\nsino ad una multa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tTrump è stato ritenuto colpevole per tutti i 34 capi di\nimputazione. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 70,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.8349345,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Trump convicted in the pornstar case",
        "en_content": "With the historic verdict of\nguilty unanimously reached by the jury after two\nadvice room days in the pornstar case, Donald Trump\nbecomes the first former American president convicted in a\ncriminal trial and also the first presidential candidate to\nrun as prejudiced, a status that still does not\nprevents being elected and making the commander in chief. The\ncondemnation, which will be established in a subsequent hearing, may\nvary from a maximum of 4 years in prison to trial\nuntil a fine.\n\n\nTrump was found guilty for all 34 heads of\ndefendant.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Aware' for all 34 counts",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "34",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "days",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 147,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 222,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "4 years",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 494,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "34",
                "start_char": 525,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Campagna Biden, Trump? Nessuno è al di sopra della legge",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 23:41:17 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/30/campagna-biden-trump-nessuno-e-al-di-sopra-della-legge_65183f8a-6157-45a8-9c7f-d99c1fe22026.html",
        "subtitle": "Prima reazione ufficiale dei democratici sul verdetto",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Il verdetto di colpevolezzo\ncontro Donald Trump dimostra che nessuno è al di sopra della\nlegge\". Lo fa sapere la campagna del presidene Joe Biden nella\nprima reazione ufficiale dei democratici sul verdetto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 68,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.8446474,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Biden campaign, Trump? No one is above the law",
        "en_content": "\"The verdict of guilt\nagainst Donald Trump shows that no one is above the\nread.\" That's how Dean Joe Biden's campaign in\nFirst official reaction of the Democrats on the verdict.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "First official reaction of the Democrats on the verdict",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "First",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Democrats",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dean Joe Biden's",
                "start_char": 92,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "First",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Democrats",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Attacchi aerei in Yemen. Gb: operazione congiunta con Usa",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 01:16:27 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/attacchi-aerei-in-yemen.-gb-operazione-congiunta-con-usa_e8138c0e-f948-4dcf-bab5-86861ecd4134.html",
        "subtitle": "Colpite la capitale Sanaa e la città portuale di Hodeida",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nella notte attacchi aerei hanno\ncolpito diverse aree dello Yemen, tra cui la capitale Sanaa e la\ncittà portuale di Hodeida. Si tratta, ha precisato il ministero\ndella Difesa britannico, di una operazione congiunta tra Londra\ne Washington.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Si sono udite forti esplosioni nelle due città. Secondo il\ncanale al-Masira, controllato dai ribelli yemeniti Houthi, gli\nattacchi hanno preso di mira anche le infrastrutture di\ntelecomunicazioni nella città di Taiz. Al-Masira ha riferito di\n\"diversi\" morti e feriti. Il canale Houthi ha da subito\nattribuito tutti questi attacchi aerei alle forze americane e\nbritanniche nella regione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Gli attacchi notturni nello Yemen sono una \"operazione\ncongiunta\" di Stati Uniti e Regno Unito volta a \"minare\" le\ncapacità militari dei ribelli Houthi, ha affermato il Ministero\ndella Difesa britannico. \"Gli Houthi - si legge in una nota del\nministero - continuano a effettuare attacchi alle navi\ninternazionali nel Mar Rosso e nel Golfo di Aden\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.8757427,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Air strikes in Yemen. Gb: joint operation with Usa",
        "en_content": "In the night air attacks\nhit several areas of Yemen, including the capital Sanaa and the\nport city of Hodeida. This is the matter, it has specified the ministry\nBritish Defense, a joint operation between London\nand Washington.\n\n\nStrong explosions have been heard in the two cities. According to\nal-Masira channel, controlled by the Yemeni rebels Houthi, the\nattacks also targeted infrastructure\ntelecommunications in the city of Taiz. Al-Masira reported about\n\"different\" dead and wounded. The Houthi channel immediately\nattributed all these air attacks to American forces and\nBritish in the region.\n\n\nNight attacks in Yemen are a \"operation\nUnited States and United Kingdom to \"mine\" the\nmilitary capacity of the Houthi rebels, said the Ministry\nBritish Defense. \"The Houthi - read in a note of\nministry - continue to carry out attacks on the ships\ninternational in the Red Sea and the Gulf of Aden\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Hit the capital Sanaa and the port city of Hodeida",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sanaa",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hodeida",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "night",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanaa",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hodeida",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British Defense",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "al-Masira",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemeni",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiz",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 433,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Masira",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 494,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 557,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 577,
                "end_char": 584,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 619,
                "end_char": 624,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 642,
                "end_char": 655,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 660,
                "end_char": 674,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 714,
                "end_char": 720,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ministry",
                "start_char": 738,
                "end_char": 746,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "British Defense",
                "start_char": 747,
                "end_char": 762,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 769,
                "end_char": 775,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 867,
                "end_char": 878,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Aden",
                "start_char": 883,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Biden, 'Trump si può eliminare solo con il voto'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 23:54:39 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/30/biden-trump-si-puo-eliminare-solo-con-il-voto_7053dfc1-8b3b-4023-a3e9-470babf35545.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo ha scritto su X la sentenza di colpevolezza per il tycoon",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"C'è un solo modo per tenere\nDonald Trump fuori dallo Studio Ovale: andare alle urne\". Lo ha\nscritto su X Joe Biden dopo la sentenza di colpevolezza per il\ntycoon. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.8821778,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Biden, 'Trump can only be eliminated with the vote'",
        "en_content": "\"There is only one way to keep\nDonald Trump out of the Oval Studio: go to the urns.\" He did.\nwritten on X Joe Biden after the sentence of guilt for\ntycoon.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "He wrote on X the guilty sentence for tycoon",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "only one",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Oval Studio",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "X Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump saluta i suoi sostenitori sotto la sua residenza, 'grazie'",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 01:12:28 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/31/trump-saluta-i-suoi-sostenitori-sotto-la-sua-residenza-grazie_441b6b11-4e58-412c-8c44-6fcf848dc6b5.html",
        "subtitle": "Il tycoon accolto dai fan alla Trump Tower a Ny",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Donald Trump è stato accolto da\nuna piccola folla di suoi sostenitori sotto alla Trump Tower, la\nresidenza dell'ex presidente a Manhattan, dopo la sentenza di\ncolpevolezza. \"Grazie\", ha detto il tycoon con il pugno alzato\nalle persone che lo aspettavano. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 66,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.9339802,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Trump salutes his supporters under his residence, 'thank you'",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump was welcomed by\na small crowd of his supporters under the Trump Tower, the\nresidence of the former president in Manhattan, after the sentence of\nguilty. \"Thank you,\" said the tycoon with his fist raised\nto the people who waited for him.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The tycoon welcomed by fans at Trump Tower in Ny",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump Tower",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ny",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Trump Tower",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manhattan",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Attacchi aerei in Yemen. Gb: operazione congiunta con Usa",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 01:16:29 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/05/31/attacchi-aerei-in-yemen.-gb-operazione-congiunta-con-usa_641b083f-c30c-4c96-b4ae-c942bfb53ad3.html",
        "subtitle": "Colpite la capitale Sanaa e la città portuale di Hodeida",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nella notte attacchi aerei hanno\ncolpito diverse aree dello Yemen, tra cui la capitale Sanaa e la\ncittà portuale di Hodeida. Si tratta, ha precisato il ministero\ndella Difesa britannico, di una operazione congiunta tra Londra\ne Washington.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Si sono udite forti esplosioni nelle due città. Secondo il\ncanale al-Masira, controllato dai ribelli yemeniti Houthi, gli\nattacchi hanno preso di mira anche le infrastrutture di\ntelecomunicazioni nella città di Taiz. Al-Masira ha riferito di\n\"diversi\" morti e feriti. Il canale Houthi ha da subito\nattribuito tutti questi attacchi aerei alle forze americane e\nbritanniche nella regione.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Gli attacchi notturni nello Yemen sono una \"operazione\ncongiunta\" di Stati Uniti e Regno Unito volta a \"minare\" le\ncapacità militari dei ribelli Houthi, ha affermato il Ministero\ndella Difesa britannico. \"Gli Houthi - si legge in una nota del\nministero - continuano a effettuare attacchi alle navi\ninternazionali nel Mar Rosso e nel Golfo di Aden\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 65,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.9558022,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Air strikes in Yemen. Gb: joint operation with Usa",
        "en_content": "In the night air attacks\nhit several areas of Yemen, including the capital Sanaa and the\nport city of Hodeida. This is the matter, it has specified the ministry\nBritish Defense, a joint operation between London\nand Washington.\n\n\nStrong explosions have been heard in the two cities. According to\nal-Masira channel, controlled by the Yemeni rebels Houthi, the\nattacks also targeted infrastructure\ntelecommunications in the city of Taiz. Al-Masira reported about\n\"different\" dead and wounded. The Houthi channel immediately\nattributed all these air attacks to American forces and\nBritish in the region.\n\n\nNight attacks in Yemen are a \"operation\nUnited States and United Kingdom to \"mine\" the\nmilitary capacity of the Houthi rebels, said the Ministry\nBritish Defense. \"The Houthi - read in a note of\nministry - continue to carry out attacks on the ships\ninternational in the Red Sea and the Gulf of Aden\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Hit the capital Sanaa and the port city of Hodeida",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sanaa",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hodeida",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "night",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sanaa",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hodeida",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British Defense",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 215,
                "end_char": 225,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "al-Masira",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemeni",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 352,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiz",
                "start_char": 429,
                "end_char": 433,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Masira",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 494,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 557,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 577,
                "end_char": 584,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 619,
                "end_char": 624,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 642,
                "end_char": 655,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 660,
                "end_char": 674,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 714,
                "end_char": 720,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ministry",
                "start_char": 738,
                "end_char": 746,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "British Defense",
                "start_char": 747,
                "end_char": 762,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 769,
                "end_char": 775,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 867,
                "end_char": 878,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gulf of Aden",
                "start_char": 883,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Avvocato Trump, 'ricorreremo in appello appena possibile'",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 03:24:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/31/avvocato-trump-ricorreremo-in-appello-appena-possibile_55f8f754-1b7b-43e4-add1-cfb4ef0f2a4e.html",
        "subtitle": "'Eravamo preparati anche a un verdetto di colpevolezza'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Ricorreremo in appello appena\npossibile\". Lo ha detto in un'intervista alla Cnn l'avvocato di\nDonald Trump Todd Blanche, che ha guidato il team difensivo del\ntycoon nel caso a New York. \"Eravamo preparati anche ad un\nverdetto di colpevolezza\", ha detto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.9708617,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Attorney Trump, 'we will appeal as soon as possible'",
        "en_content": "\"We will appeal as soon as\npossible.\" He said in an interview with Cnn the lawyer of\nDonald Trump Todd Blanche, who led the defensive team of\ntycoon in case in New York. \"We were also prepared for a\nguilty verdict,\" he said.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'We were also prepared for a verdict of guilt'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Todd Blanche",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Consigliere di Biden incontra a Washington vice ministro cinese",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 02:01:38 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/05/31/consigliere-di-biden-incontra-a-washington-vice-ministro-cinese_d7cfb494-3ac6-4fe1-97eb-9b51d8446370.html",
        "subtitle": "'Conversazione franca e costruttiva'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il vice consigliere per la\nsicurezza nazionale Jon Finer ha incontrato oggi il vice\nministro degli eseri cinese Ma Zhaoxu a Washington. Lo riferisce\nla Casa Bianca in una nota sottolineando che i due hanno avuto\n\"una conversazione france e costruttiva, sulla base del vertice\ntra il presidente Biden e il presidente Xi a Woodside,\nCalifornia, nel novembre 2023. Fine e la contro parte cinese\nhanno hanno concordato di \"proseguire gli sforzi per mantenere\naperto il dialogo e gestire in modo responsabile la\nconcorrenza\".  Tra gli altri temi al centro del colloquio la\ncomunicazione tra le forze armate di Cina e Stati Uniri e  la\ncooperazione nella lotta al narcotraffico.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t      Finer ha affermato, inoltre, l'importanza di mantenere la\npace e la stabilità nello Stretto di Taiwan e ha sottoloineato\nil sostegno degli Stati Uniti al diritto internazionale e alla\nlibertà di navigazione nel Mar Cinese Meridionale.  Le due parti\nhanno discusso anche della guerra della Russia contro l'Ucraina,\ndelle sfide in Medio Oriente e degli sforzi per portare avanti\nla denuclearizzazione della penisola coreana. All'incontro è\nintervenuto anche il consigliere per la sicurezza nazionale Jake\nSullivan. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182040.9919453,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:40",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.40",
        "en_title": "Biden meeting in Washington Deputy Chinese Minister",
        "en_content": "Deputy Counsellor for\nNational Security Jon Finer met today the deputy\nChinese Foreign Minister Ma Zhaoxu in Washington. It refers\nthe White House in a note pointing out that the two had\n\"a frank and constructive conversation, based on the summit\nbetween President Biden and President Xi in Woodside,\nCalifornia, November 2023. End and the Chinese side\nhave agreed to \"prosecute efforts to maintain\nopen dialogue and manage responsibly\ncompetition\". Other topics at the centre of the interview\ncommunication between the armed forces of China and the United States and the\ncooperation in the fight against drug trafficking.\n\n\nFiner also stated the importance of maintaining the\npeace and stability in the Taiwan Strait and underlined\nUS support for international law and\nfreedom of navigation in the South China Sea. The two parts\nthey also discussed Russia's war against Ukraine,\nof the challenges in the Middle East and efforts to move forward\nthe denuclearization of the Korean peninsula. At the meeting is\nintervened also the national security adviser Jake\nSullivan.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Conversation frank and constructive'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Jon Finer",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 71,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ma Zhaoxu",
                "start_char": 96,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the White House",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 287,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Woodside",
                "start_char": 291,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "California",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "November 2023",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 541,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 563,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Finer",
                "start_char": 625,
                "end_char": 630,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Taiwan Strait",
                "start_char": 700,
                "end_char": 717,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 733,
                "end_char": 735,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the South China Sea",
                "start_char": 795,
                "end_char": 814,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 820,
                "end_char": 823,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 850,
                "end_char": 856,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 871,
                "end_char": 878,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 901,
                "end_char": 916,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Korean",
                "start_char": 973,
                "end_char": 979,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jake\nSullivan",
                "start_char": 1055,
                "end_char": 1068,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Donald Trump terrà un discorso a New York alle 17",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 03:06:29 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/31/donald-trump-terra-un-discorso-a-new-york-alle-17_96796b02-2fea-43e6-87cf-032f148ba718.html",
        "subtitle": "Alla Trump Tower",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Donald Trump terrà un discorso\nalle 11 di venerdì ora locale, le 17 di oggi in Italia. Lo\nannuncia la campagna precisando che l'ex presidente parlerà alla\nTrump Tower all'indomani della sentenza di colpevolezza a\nManhattan. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182041.0206711,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:41",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.41",
        "en_title": "Donald Trump will hold a speech in New York at 17:00",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump will hold a speech\nat 11 am on Friday local time, the 17th of today in Italy. I do.\nannounces the campaign stating that the former president will speak to\nTrump Tower in the aftermath of the sentence of guilt\nManhattan.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Trump Tower",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "17:00",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Trump Tower",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "11 am",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump Tower",
                "start_char": 168,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Manhattan",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Esercitazione congiunta di Russia e Bielorussia per armi aeree",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 05:07:06 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/esercitazione-congiunta-di-russia-e-bielorussia-per-armi-aeree_9bc46371-f4f8-4149-adcd-3826c954d4c6.html",
        "subtitle": "Addestramento contro obiettivi specifici",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli equipaggi dei caccia Su-30SM, dei\nbombardieri Su-24 e degli elicotteri Mi-24, Mi-8 delle Forze\naerospaziali russe hanno preso parte ad esercitazioni con\nl'Aeronautica Militare e la Difesa Aerea delle Forze Armate\ndella Bielorussia. Lo ha riferito il Ministero della Difesa\nrusso.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Gli equipaggi dei caccia multiruolo Su-30SM, dei bombardieri\ndi prima linea Su-24 e degli elicotteri dell'aviazione militare\nMi-24, Mi-8 delle Forze Aerospaziali della Federazione Russa\nhanno preso parte ad un'esercitazione volo-tattica congiunta con\nle forze e i mezzi dell'Aeronautica Militare e delle Forze di\nDifesa Aerea delle Forze Armate della Repubblica di Bielorussia.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tNell'ambito delle attività nei campi di addestramento\naeronautico, gli equipaggi hanno sperimentato l'uso pratico\ndelle armi dell'aviazione contro obiettivi specifici\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Le esercitazioni si sono svolte dal 27 al 31 maggio in volo\ntattico sul territorio della Bielorussia. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 59,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182041.0658913,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:41",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.41",
        "en_title": "Joint exercise of Russia and Belarus for aerial weapons",
        "en_content": "Su-30SM hunting crews,\nSu-24 bombers and Mi-24 helicopters, Mi-8 of the Forces\nRussian aerospaces took part in exercises with\nAir Force and Air Force Defense\nof Belarus. The Ministry of Defense reported it\nRussian.\n\n\n\"Su-30SM multi-role fighter crews, bombers\nSu-24 front line and military aviation helicopters\nMi-24, Mi-8 of the Russian Federation Aerospace Forces\ntook part in a joint flight-tactic exercise with\nthe forces and means of the Air Force and the Forces of\nAir Force Defense of the Republic of Belarus.\n\n\nAs part of training activities\naircraft, crews have experienced practical use\nof aviation weapons against specific objectives.\"\n\n\nExercises took place from 27 to 31 May in flight\ntactical on the territory of Belarus.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Training against specific objectives",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Su-24",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mi-24",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forces",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Air Force",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Air Force Defense",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of Defense",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Su-24",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mi-8",
                "start_char": 318,
                "end_char": 322,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Russian Federation Aerospace Forces",
                "start_char": 326,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Air Force",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 452,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Air Force Defense of the Republic of Belarus",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 515,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "27 to 31 May",
                "start_char": 675,
                "end_char": 687,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belarus",
                "start_char": 727,
                "end_char": 734,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tunisi: ministro Interno incontra presidente Ordine avvocati",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 09:28:14 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/05/31/tunisi-ministro-interno-incontra-presidente-ordine-avvocati_8ca90d43-1740-42bd-9f73-dfd720467883.html",
        "subtitle": "",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro tunisino dell'Interno\nKhaled Nouri ha ricevuto il presidente dell'Ordine degli\navvocati tunisini, Hatem Meziou, insieme al segretario di Stato\nincaricato della Sicurezza, Sofiane Ben Sadok, in un incontro\nche è stato \"un'occasione per esaminare le relazioni esistenti\ntra il ministro dell' Interno e l'Ordine nazionale degli\navvocati e le modalità per promuovere la cooperazione e la\ncomplementarità tra gli avvocati e l'istituzione di sicurezza\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Lo ha affermato il ministero dell'Interno in una nota,\nsottolineando che \"un campo d'azione comune unisce il ministero\ne l'Ordine degli avvocati\", che \"mira a preservare lo stato di\ndiritto e garantire tutti gli aspetti dei diritti dei cittadini\nottenendo giustizia e la corretta applicazione e rispetto delle\nnorme legge, preservando le libertà pubbliche e rispettando i\ndiritti umani\". Nel comunicato, il ministro Khaled Nouri,\nnominato pochi giorni fa, ha affermato che \"la professione\nlegale è una professione nobile con la nobile missione di\nottenere giustizia\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'incontro avviene dopo le polemiche seguite ai recenti\narresti di alcuni avvocati avvenuti presso la sede dell'Ordine,\nche hanno scatenato un'ondata di critiche da parte della\ncategoria e solidarietà da parte dei colleghi di tutto il mondo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t(ANSA)\n          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182041.0721338,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:41",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.41",
        "en_title": "Tunis: Minister Interior meets President Order lawyers",
        "en_content": "The Tunisian Interior Minister\nKhaled Nouri received the President of the Order\nTunisian lawyers, Hatem Meziou, together with the Secretary of State\nin charge of Security, Sofiane Ben Sadok, in a meeting\nthat it was \"an opportunity to examine existing relations\nbetween the Minister of the Interior and the National Order of the\nlawyers and ways to promote cooperation and\ncomplementarity between lawyers and the security institution\".\n\n\nThe Ministry of the Interior said this in a note,\nstressing that \"a common field of action unites the ministry\nand the Order of Lawyers, which \"was to preserve the state of\nright and ensure all aspects of citizens' rights\nobtaining justice and the correct application and respect of\nlaw rules, preserving public freedoms and respecting\nhuman rights.\" In the statement, Minister Khaled Nouri,\nappointed a few days ago, said that \"the profession\nlegal is a noble profession with the noble mission of\nobtain justice.\"\n\n\nThe meeting takes place after the controversy followed by the recent\narrests of some lawyers at the seat of the Order,\nthat triggered a wave of criticism from the\ncategory and solidarity from colleagues around the world.\n\n\n(ANSA)\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tunis",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tunisian",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khaled Nouri",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Order\nTunisian lawyers",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hatem Meziou",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 143,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Security",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sofiane Ben Sadok",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Order",
                "start_char": 303,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of the Interior",
                "start_char": 438,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Order of Lawyers",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Khaled Nouri",
                "start_char": 816,
                "end_char": 828,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days ago",
                "start_char": 840,
                "end_char": 854,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Order",
                "start_char": 1067,
                "end_char": 1072,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "solidarity",
                "start_char": 1131,
                "end_char": 1141,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA",
                "start_char": 1179,
                "end_char": 1183,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Attacco con droni in Russia, a fuoco deposito petrolifero",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 03:19:34 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/31/attacco-con-droni-in-russia-a-fuoco-deposito-petrolifero_969f9ade-d8e8-4e9c-9b33-fe5b185dec7e.html",
        "subtitle": "Nel territorio di Krasnodar, ci sono vittime",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Tre serbatoi di combustibile sono\nandati a fuoco a causa di un attacco sferrato dai droni a un\ndeposito petrolifero in Russia, nel distretto di Temryuk nel\nterritorio di Krasnodar. Tre carri armati hanno preso fuoco,\ncausando vittime tra i dipendenti dell'impianto. A darne notizia\nsu un canale Telegram il capo della regione, Veniamin\nKondratyev.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Un massiccio attacco di droni - scrive - è stato respinto in\ndiversi comuni della regione. La situazione è più grave nella\nregione di Temryuk. Danneggiata e incendiata l'infrastruttura di\nun deposito petrolifero. L'incendio è in fase di spegnimento. I\ndipendenti verranno evacuati\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182041.0854743,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:41",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.41",
        "en_title": "Attack with drones in Russia, on fire oil deposit",
        "en_content": "Three fuel tanks are\nFired due to an attack by drones to a\noil deposit in Russia, in the Temryuk district in\nKrasnodar territory. Three tanks fired,\ncausing victims among the employees of the plant. To give news\non a channel Telegram the head of the region, Veniamin\nKondratyev.\n\n\n\"A massive drone attack - writes - was rejected in\ndifferent municipalities of the region. The situation is more serious in\nTemryuk region. Damaged and burned the infrastructure of\nAn oil warehouse. The fire is in the shutdown phase. I\nemployees will be evacuated.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "In Krasnodar, there are victims",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Krasnodar",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Three",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Krasnodar",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Three",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Veniamin",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kondratyev",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 552,
                "end_char": 585,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Morta a Buenos Aires la Madre di Plaza de Mayo, Nora Cortiñas",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 09:33:22 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/31/morta-a-buenos-aires-la-madre-di-plaza-de-mayo-nora-cortinas_ac344161-c140-4cb0-98c5-8ab8825fa2d1.html",
        "subtitle": "Impegnata contro la dittatura e nella ricerca dei desaparecidos",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nora Cortiñas, storica\nmilitante argentina per i diritti umani impegnata nella ricerca\ndei desaparecidos vittime della dittatura (1976-1983), nonché\ncofondatrice e presidente del movimento delle Madri di Plaza de\nMayo-Linea Fundadora, è morta ieri a Buenos Aires all'età di 94\nanni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Operata il 17 maggio per un'ernia, Cortiñas era stata posta\nin un reparto di rianimazione alcuni giorni dopo per\nl'improvviso peggioramento delle sue condizioni di salute\ngenerali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La sua ultima presenza pubblica è stata il 24 marzo scorso,\nquando ha partecipato su una sedia a rotelle alla marcia di\ncommemorazione, per la memoria, la verità e la giustizia, di un\nnuovo anniversario dell'inizio della dittatura civico-militare\nnel 1976.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   'Norita', come tutti la chiamavano amabilmente, ha militato\nfin dal 1977 nella ricerca delle molte migliaia di desaparecidos\ncausati dall'azione dei militari argentini durante la dittatura,\nfra cui si trovava suo figlio Carlos Gustavo, scomparso il 15\naprile 1977.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel corso della sua intensa vita, aveva ricevuto quattro\nlauree honoris causa, fra cui una dell'Università libera di\nBruxelles, e giorni fa il Parlamento della città di Buenos Aires\nle aveva consegnato il premio Jorge Morresi \"per la carriera,\nl'impegno e la difesa della democrazia e dei diritti umani\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 57,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717182041.1077304,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 21:00:41",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T21.00.41",
        "en_title": "The Mother of Plaza de Mayo died in Buenos Aires, Nora Cortiñas",
        "en_content": "Nora Cortiñas, historical\nArgentine human rights activist engaged in research\ndesaparecidos victims of the dictatorship (1976-1983) and\nco-founder and president of the movement of the Mothers of Plaza de\nMayo-Linea Fundadora, died yesterday in Buenos Aires at the age of 94\nYears.\n\n\nOperating on 17 May for a hernia, Cortiñas had been posted\nin a reanimation department a few days later for\nthe sudden worsening of his health conditions\nGeneral.\n\n\nHis last public presence was on 24 March last,\nwhen he participated in a wheelchair at the march\ncommemoration, for memory, truth and justice, of a\nnew anniversary of the beginning of the civic-military dictatorship\nin 1976.\n\n\n'Norita', as everyone called her lovingly, miligated\nsince 1977 in the search for the many thousands of desaparecidos\ncaused by the action of the Argentine military during the dictatorship,\nincluding his son Carlos Gustavo, who died 15\nApril 1977.\n\n\nDuring his intense life, he had received four\nHonorary degrees cause, including one of the Free University of\nBrussels, and days ago Parliament of the city of Buenos Aires\nhe gave her the Jorge Morresi award \"for career,\nthe commitment and defence of democracy and human rights.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Committed against dictatorship and the search for desaparecidos",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Mother of Plaza de Mayo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nora Cortiñas",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Nora Cortiñas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "1976-1983",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mayo-Linea Fundadora",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 244,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the age of 94\nYears",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 279,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "17 May",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cortiñas",
                "start_char": 317,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days later",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 March last",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 493,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "1976",
                "start_char": 667,
                "end_char": 671,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Norita",
                "start_char": 676,
                "end_char": 682,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1977",
                "start_char": 734,
                "end_char": 738,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the many thousands",
                "start_char": 757,
                "end_char": 775,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 821,
                "end_char": 830,
