[
    {
        "title": "Eliseo conferma i paesi partecipanti al summit di Parigi",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 16 Feb 2025 16:43:55 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-16",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/16/eliseo-conferma-i-paesi-partecipanti-al-summit-di-parigi_06388919-bb78-4f98-8c01-25fce2b23bb1.html",
        "subtitle": "'Germania, Gb, Italia, Polonia, Spagna, Olanda e Danimarca e Ue'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente della Repubblica\nfrancese, Emmanuel Macron, \"terrà una riunione informale domani\npomeriggio con i capi di governo di Germania, Gb, Italia,\nPolonia, Spagna, Olanda e Danimarca\" oltre ai vertici dell'Ue e\nal segretario Nato Mark Rutte. Lo confermano fonti dell'Eliseo,\nsottolineando l'intenzione di Macron di \"avviare consultazioni\nfra dirigenti europei sulla situazione in Ucraina e i nodi della\nsicurezza in Europa\". La riunione si svolgerà \"nel pomeriggio\",\nsaranno presenti anche \"la presidente della Commissione Ue e il\nsegretario generale Nato\". \"I lavori potranno prolungarsi in\naltri formati per riunire tutti i partner interessati alla pace\ne alla sicurezza in Europa\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.2747028,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Eliseo confirms the participating countries at the Paris summit",
        "en_content": "The President of the Republic\nFrench, Emmanuel Macron, \"will be an informal meeting tomorrow\nafternoon with the heads of government of Germany, Gb, Italy,\nPoland, Spain, the Netherlands and Denmark\" in addition to EU leaders\nSecretary Born Mark Rutte. They confirm it as sources of the Elysée,\nstressing Macron's intention to \"start consultations\namong European leaders on the situation in Ukraine and the knots of\nsafety in Europe\". The meeting will take place \"in the afternoon\",\nwill also be present \"the President of the EU Commission and the\nSecretary General NATO\". \"The work can be extended in\nother formats to bring together all partners interested in peace\nand security in Europe.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Germany, Gb, Italy, Poland, Spain, Netherlands and Denmark and the EU'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Eliseo",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Denmark",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Republic\nFrench",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emmanuel Macron",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow\nafternoon",
                "start_char": 84,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gb",
                "start_char": 144,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Denmark",
                "start_char": 190,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Born Mark Rutte",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Elysée",
                "start_char": 286,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 353,
                "end_char": 361,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 397,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "afternoon",
                "start_char": 470,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the EU Commission",
                "start_char": 521,
                "end_char": 538,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 565,
                "end_char": 569,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 682,
                "end_char": 688,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky, 100.000 al freddo a Mykolaiv per raid russo",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 16 Feb 2025 16:44:56 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-16",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/16/zelensky-100.000-al-freddo-a-mykolaiv-per-raid-russo_2d2175c7-2a10-4d00-86d8-3e1524612258.html",
        "subtitle": "'Chi si prepara a negoziati di pace non fa così\"",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            (V. 'Kiev, 'abbattuti 95 droni russi, un ferito...' delle 10.42)\n   \"Oggi più di centomila persone a\nMykolaiv sono rimaste senza riscaldamento a causa di un attacco\nrusso con droni alle infrastrutture critiche della città. Una\nnormale città ucraina, normali infrastrutture civili. Questo non\nha nulla a che vedere con i combattimenti e la situazione al\nfronte, dimostra ancora una volta che i russi stanno combattendo\ncontro il nostro popolo, contro la vita in Ucraina. E combattono\ncon cattiveria, senza allentare la pressione. Non è questo che\nfanno coloro che vogliono davvero che la pace venga ristabilita\ne si preparano ai negoziati\". Così su Telegram il presidente\nucraino Volodymyr Zelensky. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.3670201,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, 100,000 cold in Mykolaiv for Russian raid",
        "en_content": "(V. 'Kiev,' lowered 95 Russian drones, one wounded...' by 10.42)\n\"Today more than one hundred thousand people to\nMykolaiv remained without heating due to an attack\nRussian with drones to the critical infrastructure of the city. One\nnormal Ukrainian city, normal civil infrastructure. This is not\nhas nothing to do with fighting and the situation at\nfront, it shows once again that the Russians are fighting\nagainst our people, against life in Ukraine. And fight\nwith evil, without loosening the pressure. That's not what\nmake those who really want peace to be restored\nand prepare for the negotiations.\" So on Telegram the President\nUkrainian Volodymyr Zelensky.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Who prepares for peace negotiations does not do so'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "100,000",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mykolaiv",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "95",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "10.42",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 66,
                "end_char": 71,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than one hundred thousand",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mykolaiv",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 164,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 385,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 443,
                "end_char": 450,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 610,
                "end_char": 618,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 633,
                "end_char": 642,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 643,
                "end_char": 661,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas, 'raid israeliano su Gaza è grave violazione tregua'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 16 Feb 2025 16:46:55 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-16",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/02/16/hamas-raid-israeliano-su-gaza-e-grave-violazione-tregua_10e5292b-2458-4ce7-b381-5deced9c8bb1.html",
        "subtitle": "'Uccisi 3 agenti a garanzia dell'ingresso degli aiuti umanitari'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Hamas ha accusato Israele di aver\ncommesso una \"grave violazione\" del cessate il fuoco dopo che un\nattacco aereo avvenuto questa mattina ha ucciso tre agenti di\npolizia vicino a Rafah, nel sud della Striscia di Gaza.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il vile bombardamento compiuto questa mattina da un drone\nsionista a est della città di Rafah contro gli agenti di polizia\nincaricati di garantire l'ingresso degli aiuti (umanitari), è\nconsiderato una grave violazione dell'accordo di cessate il\nfuoco\" in vigore dal 19 gennaio dopo 15 mesi di guerra, ha\ndichiarato in una nota Hamas. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.3841095,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Hamas, Israeli raid on Gaza is grave tregua violation",
        "en_content": "Hamas accused Israel of having\ncommitted a \"grave violation\" of ceasefire after a\nair strike occurred this morning killed three agents\nPolice near Rafah, south of the Gaza Strip.\n\n\n\"The vile bombing made this morning by a drone\nZionist to the east of the city of Rafah against police officers\nto ensure the entry of aid (humanitarian), is\nconsidered a serious violation of the cease-fire agreement\nfire\" in force from 19 January after 15 months of war, has\nstated in a note Hamas.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Used 3 agents guaranteeing the entry of humanitarian aid'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "3",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this morning",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this morning",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 216,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zionist",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "19 January after",
                "start_char": 418,
                "end_char": 434,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "15 months",
                "start_char": 435,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 479,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Sikorski, in Francia summit europeo su Ucraina lunedì",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:39:47 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/15/sikorski-in-francia-summit-europeo-su-ucraina-lunedi_adf08ad0-59a7-434e-a063-c426b6af04fe.html",
        "subtitle": "Ma l'Eliseo non conferma l'incontro",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"La Francia ospiterà un summit\neuropeo sull'Ucraina lunedì prossimo\". Lo ha annunciato\nintervenendo alla Conferenza di Monaco sulla sicurezza il\nministro degli Esteri polacco Radoslaw Sikorski.  Il primo\nministro polacco Donald Tusk \"parteciperà a un incontro dei\nleader europei lunedì su invito del presidente Emmanuel Macron.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tDobbiamo mostrare la nostra forza e unità\", ha detto il ministro\npolacco su X.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Fonti dell'Eliseo però \"non confermano\" il vertice dei leader\nUe. Le fonti parlando di \"discussioni in corso fra leader\neuropei per un possibile incontro informale\", ma precisano che\n\"nulla è fissato per il momento\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 34,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.3962247,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Sikorski, in France European summit on Ukraine Monday",
        "en_content": "\"France will host a summit\nEuropean on Ukraine next Monday.\" It has announced\nIntervening at the Munich Conference on Security\nPolish Foreign Minister Radoslaw Sikorski. The first\nPolish Minister Donald Tusk \"will participate in a meeting of\nEuropean leaders on Monday at the invitation of President Emmanuel Macron.\n\n\nWe must show our strength and unity,\" said the minister\nPolish on X.\n\n\nEliseo sources, however, \"do not confirm\" the summit of leaders\nUe. Sources talking about \"current debates between leaders\nEuropeans for a possible informal meeting\", but point out that\n\"Nothing is fixed for the moment.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "But the Elysée does not confirm the meeting",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sikorski",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Elysée",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next Monday",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 58,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Munich Conference on Security",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 126,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Radoslaw Sikorski",
                "start_char": 151,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 186,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Tusk",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 262,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emmanuel Macron",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 381,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "X.\n\n\nEliseo",
                "start_char": 385,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Scoppiano le proteste in un ateneo in Iran, numerosi arresti",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:31:19 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2025/02/15/scoppiano-le-proteste-in-un-ateneo-in-iran-numerosi-arresti_7943823e-07c0-462d-bd25-0ce7129eac47.html",
        "subtitle": "Dopo uccisione studente da due ladri, giovani chiedono sicurezza",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Nuovo pugno di ferro delle\nautorità iraniane contro i giovani. Le autorità hanno annunciato\noggi di avere effettuato numerosi arresti dopo che l'uccisione\ndi uno studente da parte di due ladri dentro il campus ha\nscatenato una notte di protesta all'Università di Teheran. Amir\nMohammad Khaleghi, uno studente di economia di 19 anni, è stato\nucciso mercoledì scorso. L'omicidio ha suscitato indignazione\ncon gli studenti che hanno chiesto maggiore sicurezza nel\ncampus, al grido di 'abbasso il dittatore'. Nel corso della\nprotesta una studentessa è stata picchiata dagli agenti in\nborghese e ad un'altra studentessa è stato rotto il naso.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 36,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.4489338,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Expand protests in an Athenaeum in Iran, numerous arrests",
        "en_content": "New iron fist\nIranian authorities against young people. The authorities have announced\ntoday to have made numerous arrests after the killing\nof a student by two thieves inside the campus has\na night of protest at the University of Tehran. Amir\nMohammad Khaleghi, a 19-year-old economic student, was\nkilled last Wednesday. The murder aroused indignation\nwith students who asked for greater security in\ncampus, at the cry of 'low dictator'. In the course of\nprotest a student was beaten by agents in\nbourgeois and another student was broken.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "After killing student from two thieves, young people ask for security",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Athenaeum",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iranian",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 87,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the University of Tehran",
                "start_char": 213,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Amir\nMohammad Khaleghi",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "19-year-old",
                "start_char": 265,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "last Wednesday",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 320,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky,ho rifiutato accordo con gli Usa sulle terre rare",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:39:27 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/15/zelenskyho-rifiutato-accordo-con-gli-usa-sulle-terre-rare_37344b81-04b1-4635-bddd-bc74750a3b8c.html",
        "subtitle": "'Non è pronto, va collegato alle garanzie di sicurezza'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            (ANSA-AFP) - MONACO, 15 FEB - Il presidente ucraino Volodymyr\nZelensky annuncia di aver rifiutato l'accordo con Washington\nsulle terre rare.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tZelensky dice che l'accordo \"deve essere collegato con le\ngaranzie di sicurezza\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"L'accordo - ha detto il leader ucraino, come rriporta Rbc\nUkraina - era pronto a livello ministeriale. Ma io sono il\npresidente e avrò un'influenza sulla qualità di questo\ndocumento. Ed è per questo che non ho lasciato che i ministri\nfirmassero l'accordo, perché non è pronto, secondo me. Non è\nancora pronto a proteggere i nostri interessi\", ha detto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t(ANSA-AFP).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 33,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.4653378,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Zelensky, I refused agreement with the U.S. on rare lands",
        "en_content": "(ANSA-AFP) - MONACO, 15 FEB - Ukrainian President Volodymyr\nZelensky announces he refused the deal with Washington\non rare lands.\n\n\nZelensky says the deal \"must be connected with the\nsecurity guarantees.\"\n\n\n\"The agreement - the Ukrainian leader said, as Rbc\nUkraine - was ready at ministerial level. But I am the\nPresident and I will have an influence on the quality of this\ndocument. And that's why I didn't let the ministers\nthey signed the agreement, because it is not ready, in my opinion. It's not\nstill ready to protect our interests,\" he said.\n\n\n(ANSA-AFP).\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'It is not ready, it must be linked to security guarantees'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "MONACO",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "15",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rbc",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA-AFP",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Usa inviano a Ue richiesta per garanzie sicurezza a Kiev'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:33:51 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/15/usa-inviano-a-ue-richiesta-per-garanzie-sicurezza-a-kiev_6a4291b9-6569-4a38-8696-6a54f6812116.html",
        "subtitle": "Ft, informazioni su armi, truppe che paesi europei possono dare'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il dipartimento di Stato americano ha\nchiesto ai governi europei di fornire informazioni dettagliate\nsulle armi, sulle truppe di mantenimento della pace e sulle\nmisure di sicurezza che potrebbero fornire all'Ucraina come\nparte di eventuali garanzie di sicurezza per porre fine alla\nguerra con la Russia. Lo scrive il Financial Times che ha\nvisionato il documento. La richiesta sarebbe stata inviata\nquesta settimana. Secondo il piano di Washington, il documento\nmira a determinare la volontà dell'Europa di difendere l'Ucraina\ndopo un accordo di pace nonché il prezzo che l'Europa è disposta\na pagare per partecipare ai negoziati. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 35,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.5638504,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "'Usa send to EU request for security in Kiev'",
        "en_content": "The US State Department has\nasked European governments to provide detailed information\non arms, peacekeeping troops and\nsecurity measures that could provide Ukraine as\npart of any security guarantees to end the\nwar with Russia. The Financial Times writes\nread the document. The request would be sent\nThis week. According to Washington plan, the document\naims to determine the will of Europe to defend Ukraine\nAfter a peace agreement and the price that Europe is willing\nto pay to participate in the negotiations.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Ft, information on weapons, troops that European countries can give",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Usa",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The US State Department",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 164,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 220,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Financial Times",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "This week",
                "start_char": 300,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 390,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 401,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Attacco islamista a Monaco, morte mamma e figlia rimaste ferite",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:48:22 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/15/attacco-islamista-a-monaco-morte-mamma-e-figlia-rimaste-ferite_0322cb66-9b52-4db1-ac9e-6cce3b0dee45.html",
        "subtitle": "La bimba di due anni e la mamma erano rimaste ferite ed erano in condizioni molto gravi. Lo ha riferito l'anticrimine del Land bavarese",
        "content": "dove un afgano di 24 anni è piombato con un'auto sulla folla durante una manifestazione del sindacato Verdi. Lo ha reso noto l'Anticrimine regionale, secondo quanto riporta la Dpa.    \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 32,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.5746818,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Islamist attack in Monaco, dead mother and daughter injured",
        "en_content": "where a 24-year-old afghan landed with a car on the crowd during a rally of the Verdi union. It has made known the Regional Anticrime, according to the Dpa.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The two-year-old girl and mom were injured and were in very serious condition. The anti-crime of the Bavarian Land reported it",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Islamist",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monaco",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "two-year-old",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Bavarian Land",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 114,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "24-year-old",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 19,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "afghan",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Regional Anticrime",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Dpa",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 155,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Attacco islamista a Monaco, morta anche la mamma della piccola",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:34:41 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/15/attacco-islamista-a-monaco-morta-anche-la-mamma-della-piccola_a7b49db4-ff97-4f30-be6e-075955ccd3eb.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo ha riferito l'anticrimine del Land bavarese",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Anche la donna di 37 anni\nricoverata i gravissime condizioni è deceduta a Monaco di\nBaviera dopo l'attentato di due giorni fa: lo ha riferito la\nDpa, citando l'anticrimine del Land bavarese, dopo aver dato\nnotizia della morte della figlia di due anni. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 31,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.5808775,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Islamist attack in Monaco, also dead the mother of the little",
        "en_content": "Also the 37 year old woman\nadmitted the very serious conditions died in Munich\nBavaria after the attack two days ago: it reported\nDpa, citing the anti-crime of the Bavarian Land, after giving\nnews of the death of the daughter of two years.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The anti-crime of the Bavarian Land reported it",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Islamist",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monaco",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 25,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Bavarian Land",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "37 year old",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Munich",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bavaria",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two days ago",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dpa",
                "start_char": 130,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Bavarian Land",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two years",
                "start_char": 229,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Lula, 'vincerò le bugie e dimostrerò che sono io il migliore'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 19:05:03 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/15/lula-vincero-le-bugie-e-dimostrero-che-sono-io-il-migliore_30db2a7f-123a-43d4-8e4a-6c28c4f2f8e1.html",
        "subtitle": "'Basta fake news, il 2025 sarà l'anno della verità'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente del Brasile,\nLuiz Inácio Lula da Silva, la cui popolarità è scesa ai minimi\nstorici in base ai sondaggi, ha dichiarato, in riferimento alle\nfake news in politica, che il 2025 sarà l'anno volto a\n\"sconfiggere la menzogna\" e che dimostrerà di essere la persona\npiù adatta a governare il Paese.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Dobbiamo sconfiggere l'era delle bugie in cui viviamo, dove\nl'importante è mentire sempre. Tizio si chiude in camera con il\ncellulare e continua a inventare bugie, provocando gli altri.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tBasta guardare cosa succede negli Stati Uniti\", ha detto il\nleader progressista, cogliendo l'occasione per criticare il\ngoverno del presidente americano Donald Trump.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Dedicherò il 2025 a sconfiggere le bugie. Il 2025 sarà\nl'anno della verità. Voglio dimostrare che siamo migliori di\naltri per governare questo Paese\", ha aggiunto Lula durante un\ndiscorso ai dipendenti della compagnia mineraria Vale a Belém do\nPará. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 28,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.5882096,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Lula, I'll win the lies and prove I'm the best.",
        "en_content": "The President of Brazil,\nLuiz Inácio Lula da Silva, whose popularity fell to the lowest\naccording to the polls, he declared, in reference to\nfake news in politics, that the 2025 will be the year aimed at\n\"disconfiguring lies\" and that will prove to be the person\nmore suitable for governing the country.\n\n\n\"We must defeat the age of lies we live in, where\nThe important thing is to lie always. Tizio closes in the room with the\ncellular and continues to invent lies, causing others.\n\n\nJust look what happens in the United States,\" he said.\nprogressive leader, taking the opportunity to criticize\nAmerican President Donald Trump.\n\n\n\"I'm going to dedicate 2025 to defeating lies. 2025 will be\nthe year of truth. I want to prove we're better than\nothers to govern this country,\" added Lula during a\nspeech to the employees of the mining company Vale in Belém do\nPará.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "\"Just fake news, 2025 will be the year of truth\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the year",
                "start_char": 30,
                "end_char": 38,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Inácio",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula da Silva",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the year",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tizio",
                "start_char": 394,
                "end_char": 399,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 596,
                "end_char": 604,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 615,
                "end_char": 627,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 654,
                "end_char": 658,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2025",
                "start_char": 678,
                "end_char": 682,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the year",
                "start_char": 691,
                "end_char": 699,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 782,
                "end_char": 786,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vale",
                "start_char": 842,
                "end_char": 846,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belém",
                "start_char": 850,
                "end_char": 855,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pará",
                "start_char": 859,
                "end_char": 863,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Vertice dei Brics il 6 e 7 luglio a Rio de Janeiro",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:43:57 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/02/15/vertice-dei-brics-il-6-e-7-luglio-a-rio-de-janeiro_45a85f6a-6898-445e-a061-498fbaa66a00.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo ha confermato il ministro degli Esteri brasiliano",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro degli Esteri\nbrasiliano, Mauro Vieira, ha confermato che il vertice dei\nleader dei Brics, previsto per l'inizio di luglio, sarà\norganizzato a Rio de Janeiro. La notizia è stata pubblicata sui\nsocial dal sindaco carioca, Eduardo Paes, dopo un incontro a Rio\ncon il ministro e altri rappresentanti del governo federale.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il presidente (Lula) mi ha autorizzato ad annunciare che\nl'incontro dei capi di Stato dei Brics si terrà a Rio de Janeiro\na luglio di quest'anno, il 6 e il 7, quando daremo il benvenuto\nnella città ai capi di Stato dei 20 Paesi che compongono i\nBrics, come membri a pieno titolo e partner\", ha dichiarato\nVieira.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il capo della diplomazia brasiliano ha aggiunto che il\nvertice di Rio de Janeiro sarà essenziale per \"prendere\ndecisioni molto importanti per lo sviluppo di tutti questi Paesi\ne per la cooperazione\". \"Ancora una volta Rio de Janeiro\nospiterà un incontro internazionale di grande importanza\", ha\nconcluso Vieira.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il 1 gennaio il Brasile ha assunto la presidenza di turno dei\nBrics, un gruppo formato da Brasile, Russia, India, Cina,\nSudafrica, Arabia Saudita, Egitto, Etiopia, Emirati Arabi Uniti\ne Iran. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 29,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.603932,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Brics Summit on 6 and 7 July in Rio de Janeiro",
        "en_content": "Foreign Minister\nBrazilian, Mauro Vieira, has confirmed that the summit of\nleader of the Brics, planned for the beginning of July, will be\norganized in Rio de Janeiro. The news was published on\nsocial by the mayor carioca, Eduardo Paes, after a meeting in Rio\nwith the minister and other representatives of the federal government.\n\n\n\"The President (Lula) has authorized me to announce that\nthe meeting of the Heads of State of the Brics will be held in Rio de Janeiro\nin July this year, 6 and 7, when we welcome\nin the city to the Heads of State of the 20 Countries that make up the\nBrics, as full members and partners,\" he said.\nVieira.\n\n\nThe head of Brazilian diplomacy added that the\nRio de Janeiro summit will be essential to \"take\nvery important decisions for the development of all these countries\nand for cooperation.\" \"Once again Rio de Janeiro\nwill host an international meeting of great importance,\" he\nconcluded Vieira.\n\n\nOn 1 January Brazil took over the presidency of the\nBrics, a group formed by Brazil, Russia, India, China,\nSouth Africa, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Ethiopia, United Arab Emirates\nand Iran.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The Brazilian Foreign Minister confirmed this",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brics Summit",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "6 and 7 July",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio de Janeiro",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mauro Vieira",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brics",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the beginning of July",
                "start_char": 108,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio de Janeiro",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "carioca",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eduardo Paes",
                "start_char": 223,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 349,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Heads of State of the Brics",
                "start_char": 405,
                "end_char": 436,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio de Janeiro",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 467,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "July this year",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "6",
                "start_char": 487,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 493,
                "end_char": 494,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Heads of State",
                "start_char": 527,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 555,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brics",
                "start_char": 583,
                "end_char": 588,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vieira",
                "start_char": 630,
                "end_char": 636,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 652,
                "end_char": 661,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio de Janeiro",
                "start_char": 687,
                "end_char": 701,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rio de Janeiro",
                "start_char": 838,
                "end_char": 852,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vieira",
                "start_char": 923,
                "end_char": 929,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1 January",
                "start_char": 936,
                "end_char": 945,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 946,
                "end_char": 952,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brics",
                "start_char": 985,
                "end_char": 990,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazil",
                "start_char": 1010,
                "end_char": 1016,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1018,
                "end_char": 1024,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "India",
                "start_char": 1026,
                "end_char": 1031,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 1033,
                "end_char": 1038,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Africa",
                "start_char": 1040,
                "end_char": 1052,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Saudi Arabia",
                "start_char": 1054,
                "end_char": 1066,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 1068,
                "end_char": 1073,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ethiopia",
                "start_char": 1075,
                "end_char": 1083,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United Arab Emirates",
                "start_char": 1085,
                "end_char": 1105,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 1110,
                "end_char": 1114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": " Austria, attacco con coltello a Villach, un morto e 4 feriti",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 16 Feb 2025 12:36:02 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-16",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/15/austria-attacco-con-coltello-a-villach-un-morto-e-4-feriti_cbd1083e-0152-4b93-b256-2ef387263647.html",
        "subtitle": "Il killer sarebbe un cittadino siriano poi arrestato. Fermato da un passante in auto che lo avrebbe investito",
        "content": "  \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 27,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.6210587,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Austria, knife attack in Villach, dead and 4 wounded",
        "en_content": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The killer would be a Syrian citizen then arrested. Stopped by a car passer who would invest him",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Austria",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Villach",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Syrian",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Le Isole Cook firmano una partnership strategica con la Cina",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 16 Feb 2025 06:18:06 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-16",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/oceania/2025/02/16/le-isole-cook-firmano-una-partnership-strategica-con-la-cina_ea1a4cd0-ced8-4eef-b776-48e65d871ab8.html",
        "subtitle": "Premier Brown, 'non sostituirà intese con i vicini del Pacifico'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Le Isole Cook hanno annunciato\nla firma di una \"partnership strategica\" con la Cina,\naffermando, tuttavia, che questa \"non sostituisce\" le relazioni\ncon i vicini del Pacifico, una regione in cui Pechino sta\nespandendo la propria influenza.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il primo ministro del piccolo arcipelago di 17.000 abitanti,\nMark Brown, sta concludendo una visita di cinque giorni in Cina,\ndove ha incontrato il suo omologo Li Qiang. L'accordo copre\n\"aree in linea con i nostri interessi nazionali e gli obiettivi\ndi sviluppo a lungo termine\", ha affermato Brown in una\ndichiarazione, rivelando il \"Piano d'azione per un partenariato\nstrategico globale\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Le Isole Salomone e Kiribati sono altri importanti\nbeneficiari degli aiuti cinesi nella regione. Brown ha affermato\nche la partnership delle Isole Cook con Pechino riguarda\ncommercio, investimenti, oceanografia, infrastrutture e\ntrasporti, aggiungendo che i dettagli saranno annunciati \"nei\nprossimi giorni\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"I nostri rapporti e il nostro impegno con la Cina\ncompletano, e non sostituiscono, i nostri rapporti di lunga data\ncon la Nuova Zelanda e molti altri partner bilaterali, regionali\ne multilaterali\", ha affermato.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'arcipelago ha un accordo di \"libera associazione\" con\nWellington, che fornisce sostegno finanziario e assistenza negli\naffari esteri e nella difesa. Anche la diplomazia neozelandese\naveva espresso la propria \"preoccupazione\" prima della visita di\nBrown in Cina. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 25,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.6983294,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Cook Islands sign a strategic partnership with China",
        "en_content": "Cook Islands have announced\nsigning a \"strategic partnership\" with China,\nstating, however, that this \"does not replace\" relations\nwith Pacific neighbors, a region where Beijing is\nexpanding its influence.\n\n\nThe prime minister of the small archipelago of 17,000 inhabitants,\nMark Brown, he's closing a five-day visit to China,\nwhere he met his counterpart Li Qiang. The agreement covers\n\"in line with our national interests and objectives\nlong-term development,\" said Brown in a\ndeclaration, revealing the \"Action Plan for a Partnership\nglobal strategic\".\n\n\nSolomon Islands and Kiribati are other important\nbeneficiaries of Chinese aid in the region. Brown said\nthat the partnership of the Cook Islands with Beijing concerns\ntrade, investment, oceanography, infrastructure and\ntransport, adding that the details will be announced \"in\nnext days.\"\n\n\n\"Our relations and our commitment to China\ncomplete, and do not replace, our long-standing relationships\nwith New Zealand and many other bilateral, regional partners\nand multilateral,\" he said.\n\n\nThe archipelago has an agreement of \"free association\" with\nWellington, which provides financial support and assistance in\nforeign affairs and defence. Also New Zealand diplomacy\nhad expressed its \"preoccupation\" before the visit\nBrown in China.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Premier Brown, 'will not replace intended with Pacific neighbors'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cook Islands",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brown",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pacific",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cook Islands",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 72,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pacific",
                "start_char": 136,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "17,000",
                "start_char": 255,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mark Brown",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 285,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "five-day",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Li Qiang",
                "start_char": 356,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brown",
                "start_char": 468,
                "end_char": 473,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Action Plan",
                "start_char": 507,
                "end_char": 518,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Solomon Islands",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiribati",
                "start_char": 578,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 624,
                "end_char": 631,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brown",
                "start_char": 651,
                "end_char": 656,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Cook Islands",
                "start_char": 686,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 708,
                "end_char": 715,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "next days",
                "start_char": 834,
                "end_char": 843,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 885,
                "end_char": 890,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New Zealand",
                "start_char": 958,
                "end_char": 969,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wellington",
                "start_char": 1104,
                "end_char": 1114,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "New Zealand",
                "start_char": 1201,
                "end_char": 1212,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brown",
                "start_char": 1274,
                "end_char": 1279,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 1283,
                "end_char": 1288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kellogg, 'l'Europa non siederà al tavolo dei negoziati'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:37:45 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-15",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/15/kellogg-leuropa-non-siedera-al-tavolo-dei-negoziati_e9da13cd-8b7a-4a56-bf37-560fc192505b.html",
        "subtitle": "'Appartengo alla scuola del realismo e ciò non accadrà'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Europa sarà consultata ma non\nsiederà al tavolo dei colloqui di pace sull'Ucraina: lo ha\nrivelato l'inviato speciale di Donald Trump per l'Ucraina Keith\nKellogg. Alla domanda se l'Europa sarebbe stata presente ai\ncolloqui programmati Kellogg ha risposto di appartenere alla\n\"scuola del realismo e che ciò non accadrà\", come riporta il\nGuardian.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Potrebbe essere come il gesso sulla lavagna, potrebbe\nirritare un po', ma sono molto onesto\", ha detto alla conferenza\ndi Monaco. \"Ai miei amici europei, dico: entrate nel dibattito,\nnon lamentandovi del fatto che potreste, sì o no, essere al\ntavolo, ma proponendo idee, aumentando la spesa\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 30,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.7142816,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Kellogg, 'Europe will not sit at the negotiating table'",
        "en_content": "Europe will be consulted but not\nwill sit at the table of peace talks on Ukraine: He did.\nrevealed Donald Trump's special envoy for Ukraine Keith\nKellogg. The question whether Europe would be present at\nscheduled interviews Kellogg responded to belong to\n\"school of realism and that this will not happen\", as the\nGuardian.\n\n\n\"It could be like chalk on the board, it could\nirritate a little, but I'm very honest,\" he said at the conference\nMunich. \"To my European friends, I say: enter the debate,\nnot complaining that you might, yes or no, be at\ntable, but proposing ideas, increasing expenditure\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'I approach the school of realism and this will not happen'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kellogg",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 10,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump's",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine Keith",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 145,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kellogg",
                "start_char": 146,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 176,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kellogg",
                "start_char": 224,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guardian",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 321,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Munich",
                "start_char": 439,
                "end_char": 445,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 454,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "I sostenitori di Navalny sfidano Mosca a un anno dalla sua morte",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 16 Feb 2025 08:37:05 +0100",
        "date": "2025-02-16",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/02/16/i-sostenitori-di-navalny-sfidano-mosca-a-un-anno-dalla-sua-morte_87c3d16e-ab41-41e1-a864-24ff3b850a82.html",
        "subtitle": "Si temono ritorsioni per coloro che visiteranno la sua tomba",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Un anno dopo la morte dietro le\nsbarre del leader dell'opposizione russa Alexei Navalny, i suoi\nsostenitori si preparano a ricordarlo oggi con eventi\ncommemorativi nonostante i rischi di ritorsioni per coloro che\nvisiteranno la sua tomba a Mosca.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Intanto, il movimento di opposizione russo - costretto\nall'esilio da una repressione senza precedenti - è afflitto da\nlotte intestine e gravemente indebolito dalla perdita del suo\nleader. Esiliati in vari Paesi, i suoi esponenti di spicco hanno\ncercato di rilanciare la lotta contro il lungo regno del\npresidente Vladimir Putin anche in Russia, dove le critiche alle\nautorità sono severamente punite. Navalny, il principale\noppositore di Putin, è stato dichiarato \"estremista\" dalle\nautorità di Mosca, una sentenza che rimane in vigore nonostante\nla sua morte in una colonia penale artica il 16 febbraio 2024.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In Russia, chiunque menzioni Navalny o la sua Fondazione\nanticorruzione senza dichiarare che entrambi sono stati\ndichiarati \"estremisti\" è soggetto a multe o fino a quattro anni\ndi carcere. \"I sostenitori di Alexei terranno eventi\ncommemorativi in ;;tutto il mondo\", ha scritto su Telegram l'ex\ncollaboratore di Navalny, Leonid Volkov,. \"In alcuni luoghi ci\nsaranno manifestazioni o marce, in altri verrà proiettato il\ndocumentario 'Navalny', in altri ci saranno cerimonie\ncommemorative\", ha aggiunto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La vedova di Navalny, Yulia Navalnaya, condividerà i ricordi\ndel marito durante un evento a Berlino, dove si sono stabiliti\nmolti sostenitori dell'opposizione russa. \"Ovunque voi siate, in\nRussia o all'estero, speriamo davvero che il 16 febbraio\nincontrerete persone che la pensano allo stesso modo\", ha\nscritto Volkov, fornendo gli orari di apertura del cimitero\nBorisovskoye di Mosca dove è sepolto Navalny.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Ma i canali russi Telegram pro-Cremlino hanno messo in\nguardia i sostenitori dall'andare al cimitero. \"Diamo un breve\nconsiglio a coloro che intendono andarci ma non sono ancora\nsicuri: non andate!\", si legge in un post condiviso dal\ngiornalista filo-Cremlino Dmitry Smirnov e da altri canali. Il\nmessaggio avverte del \"Grande Fratello e del suo occhio sempre\nvigile\", con la foto del cartello della telecamera di sicurezza\nai cancelli del cimitero. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 23,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1739721618.720459,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-02-16 17:00:18",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-02-16T16.00.18",
        "en_title": "Navalny's supporters challenge Moscow a year after his death",
