[
    {
        "title": "Avvocato Trump, 'ricorreremo in appello appena possibile'",
        "date_raw": "Fri, 31 May 2024 03:24:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-31",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/31/avvocato-trump-ricorreremo-in-appello-appena-possibile_55f8f754-1b7b-43e4-add1-cfb4ef0f2a4e.html",
        "subtitle": "'Eravamo preparati anche a un verdetto di colpevolezza'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Ricorreremo in appello appena\npossibile\". Lo ha detto in un'intervista alla Cnn l'avvocato di\nDonald Trump Todd Blanche, che ha guidato il team difensivo del\ntycoon nel caso a New York. \"Eravamo preparati anche ad un\nverdetto di colpevolezza\", ha detto. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120834.6624603,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:34",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.34",
        "en_title": "Attorney Trump, 'we will appeal as soon as possible'",
        "en_content": "\"We will appeal as soon as\npossible.\" He said in an interview with Cnn the lawyer of\nDonald Trump Todd Blanche, who led the defensive team of\ntycoon in case in New York. \"We were also prepared for a\nguilty verdict,\" he said.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'We were also prepared for a verdict of guilt'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 97,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Todd Blanche",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 160,
                "end_char": 168,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Taiwan, 38 jet e 7 navi militari cinesi intorno all'isola",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 06:03:52 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/05/30/taiwan-38-jet-e-7-navi-militari-cinesi-intorno-allisola_79b09746-d8ba-4d85-8cfa-f6886c76de04.html",
        "subtitle": "Taipei, 'monitorata la situazione e risposto di conseguenza'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministero della Difesa\ntaiwanese ha riferito di aver rilevato nelle 24 ore alle 6.00\nlocali (mezzanotte in Italia) 38 aerei e 7 navi da guerra cinesi\nintorno all'isola, nonché 4 unità della guardia costiera, sempre\npiù integrate nelle attività di pressione di Pechino su quella\nche è ritenuta una provincia ribelle.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In totale, si legge in una nota, 28 jet hanno attraversato la\nlinea mediana finendo \"nella zona di riconoscimento di difesa\naerea (Adiz) settentrionale e sudoccidentale\". Le forze armate\ndi Taipei, di fronte all'impennata delle operazioni militari\ncinesi, hanno \"monitorato la situazione e risposto di\nconseguenza\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 51,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120835.87199,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:35",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.35",
        "en_title": "Taiwan, 38 jets and 7 Chinese military ships around the island",
        "en_content": "The Ministry of Defense\nTaiwanese reported having detected in 24 hours at 6.00\npremises (mezzanotte in Italy) 38 aircraft and 7 Chinese warships\naround the island, as well as 4 units of the Coast Guard, always\nmore integrated into the pressure activities of Beijing on that\nthat is considered a rebel province.\n\n\nIn total, you read in a note, 28 jets crossed\nmedian line ending \"in the area of defense recognition\nAerial (Adiz) north and southwestern. The armed forces\nin Taipei, facing the surge of military operations\nChinese, have \"set the situation and responded to\nconsequence.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Taipei, 'discussed the situation and responded accordingly'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taiwan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "38",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Taipei",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Ministry of Defense",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Taiwanese",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "24 hours",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "6.00",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "mezzanotte",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 103,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "38",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 128,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "4",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 176,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Coast Guard",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 265,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "28",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aerial (Adiz",
                "start_char": 414,
                "end_char": 426,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Taipei",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 520,
                "end_char": 527,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 589,
                "end_char": 622,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Schmit: 'Draghi ai vertici Ue? non rispetteremmo il sistema' ",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 09:30:23 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/30/schmit-draghi-ai-vertici-ue-non-rispetteremmo-il-sistema-_0ef8a8f9-9cab-4a2b-8920-a773ce39d149.html",
        "subtitle": "Candidato di punta dei socialisti europei: 'Meloni uguale a Le Pen, un lupo travestito da agnello'",
        "content": "Un'eventuale nomina dell'ex governatore della Bce, Mario Draghi, alla presidenza della Commissione europea o del Consiglio europeo \"significherebbe che non rispettiamo il sistema\". E' quanto afferma il candidato di punta dei socialisti europei, Nicolas Schmit, in un'intervista alle agenzie di stampa, tra cui ANSA, riunite nell'European Newsroom.Il lussemburghese, tuttavia, ha indicato che potrebbe esserci, nel caso del presidente della Commissione europea, \"il problema che nessuno riesca a ottenere la maggioranza in Parlamento perché alla fine è il Parlamento che decide\". Lo spitzenkandidat dei socialisti europei afferma quindi che la premier italiana Giorgia Meloni \"ha giocato una partita moderata in Consiglio\", ma \"ciò che fa in Italia dimostra che è sempre la stessa: non è diventata una grande democratica e non ha davvero rotto con il passato fascista suo e del suo partito. Il suo obiettivo è trasformare l'Italia in una società stile Orban\". E' \"un lupo travestito da agnello\".  \"Il flirt tra Meloni e Le Pen - aggiunge - dimostra che non c'è differenza tra estrema destra dignitosa e non dignitosa, è solo una questione di potere\".Il commissario Ue al lavoro torna poi ad attaccare il memorandum Ue-Tunisia sulla migrazione per il modo in cui \"è stato fatto\" e perché dà al presidente tunisino Kais Saied \"carta bianca\" sui rifugiati. L'intesa a suo parere rappresenta \"un aspetto essenziale delle relazioni esterne sulla migrazione: si tratta di denaro, di una scelta politica, di un Paese che ora è dominato da un regime autoritario, mi sarei aspettato uno scambio reale\" ha spiegato, lamentando \"l'assenza di discussione all'interno del collegio\" dei Commissari: \"in un'ora dovevamo dire sì o no\": se non dicevi niente, era sì, quindi bisognava dire no in un'ora di venerdì pomeriggio\".\"Sono un politico, ma sono anche un commissario e membro del collegio, quindi voglio essere informato sulle decisioni importanti e questa credo lo sia. Meloni era più informata di me\", ha aggiunto. Nel merito, Schmit ha criticato il fatto che con l'intesa l'Ue abbia di fatto \"dato carta bianca\" a Saied, dicendogli \"beh, cerca di fare qualcosa con questi rifugiati e proteggici dai contrabbandieri che portano i rifugiati in Europa\", senza disporre dei controlli sul trattamento dei migranti. \"Ora - ha concluso - sappiamo che i rifugiati vengono picchiati, portati nel deserto, violentati, derubati: questo non è, a mio avviso, un vero accordo\". \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 49,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120846.7608285,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:46",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.46",
        "en_title": "Schmit: 'Do you owe the Ue leadership? We wouldn't respect the system.",
        "en_content": "A possible appointment of the former governor of the ECB, Mario Draghi, to the Presidency of the European Commission or of the European Council \"would mean that we do not respect the system\". This is what the leading candidate of European Socialists says, Nicolas Schmit, in an interview with press agencies, including ANSA, gathered in the European Newsroom. The Luxembourg presidency, however, indicated that there might be, in the case of the President of the European Commission, \"the problem that no one can obtain a majority in Parliament because it is ultimately the Parliament who decides\". The spitzenkandidat of the European Socialists therefore states that the Italian premier Giorgia Meloni \"played a moderate game in the Council\", but \"what he does in Italy shows that it is always the same: It has not become a great democratic and has not really broken with its fascist past and its party. Its goal is to transform Italy into an Orban-style society.\" It's a lamb wolf. \"The flirtation between Meloni and Le Pen - he adds - shows that there is no difference between extreme right dignified and not dignified, is only a question of power\". Commissioner Ue at work then returns to attack the EU-Tunisia memorandum on migration for the way \"it was done\" and why he gives Tunisian President Kais Saied \"white paper\" on refugees. The agreement in its opinion represents \"an essential aspect of external relations on migration: This is money, a political choice, a country which is now dominated by an authoritarian regime, I would have expected a real exchange,\" he explained, complaining \"the absence of discussion within the boarding school\" of the Commissioners: \"In an hour we had to say yes or no\": If you didn't say anything, it was yes, so you had to say no in an hour on Friday afternoon.\" \"I'm a politician, but I'm also a commissioner and board member, so I want to be informed about the important decisions and I think it is. Meloni was more aware of me,\" he added. On the merits, Schmit criticized the fact that with the understanding the EU has in fact \"gifted white paper\" to Saied, saying \"Well, try to do something with these refugees and protect us from smugglers who bring refugees to Europe\", without having the controls on the treatment of migrants. \"Now - he has concluded - we know that refugees are beaten, brought into the desert, raped, robbed: This is not, in my opinion, a real deal.\"\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Top candidate for European Socialists: \"Meloni equal to Le Pen, a wolf disguised as lamb\"",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schmit",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ue",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "European Socialists",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Le Pen",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "ECB",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Mario Draghi",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Council",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 143,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European Socialists",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 249,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicolas Schmit",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 270,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "ANSA",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Newsroom",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Luxembourg",
                "start_char": 364,
                "end_char": 374,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Commission",
                "start_char": 459,
                "end_char": 482,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 544,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 574,
                "end_char": 584,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Socialists",
                "start_char": 622,
                "end_char": 645,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 672,
                "end_char": 679,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 734,
                "end_char": 741,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 765,
                "end_char": 770,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 930,
                "end_char": 935,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orban",
                "start_char": 944,
                "end_char": 949,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 1008,
                "end_char": 1014,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Le Pen",
                "start_char": 1019,
                "end_char": 1025,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 1204,
                "end_char": 1206,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tunisia",
                "start_char": 1207,
                "end_char": 1214,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tunisian",
                "start_char": 1282,
                "end_char": 1290,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kais Saied",
                "start_char": 1301,
                "end_char": 1311,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "an hour",
                "start_char": 1679,
                "end_char": 1686,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "an hour",
                "start_char": 1777,
                "end_char": 1784,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 1788,
                "end_char": 1794,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "afternoon",
                "start_char": 1795,
                "end_char": 1804,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meloni",
                "start_char": 1946,
                "end_char": 1952,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schmit",
                "start_char": 2001,
                "end_char": 2007,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 2060,
                "end_char": 2062,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Saied",
                "start_char": 2099,
                "end_char": 2104,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 2212,
                "end_char": 2218,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Xi, 'profondo senso di affinità con gli Stati arabi'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 07:25:44 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/05/30/xi-profondo-senso-di-affinita-con-gli-stati-arabi_62911df7-5c3f-477e-bf8b-41d0fd948ca6.html",
        "subtitle": "Presidente cinese all'apertura del Forum cooperazione a Pechino",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente cinese Xi Jinping ha\nelogiato il \"profondo senso di affinità\" condiviso con gli Stati\narabi, parlando durante la cerimonia di apertura del decimo\nincontro ministeriale del Forum di cooperazione tra Cina e Stati\narabi di Pechino. Xi, che ha sollecitato \"una maggiore\ncooperazione finanziaria e tecnologica\", ha affermato che \"ogni\nvolta che incontro i nostri amici arabi, provo un profondo senso\ndi affinità. L'amicizia tra la Cina e il suo popolo e i Paesi e\ni popoli arabi ha origine da scambi amichevoli lungo l'antica\nVia della Seta\". La Cina ospiterà il secondo vertice sino-arabo\nnel 2026, ha poi annunciato Xi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 50,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.0497637,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Xi, 'profound sense of affinity with Arab States'",
        "en_content": "Chinese President Xi Jinping has\npraised the \"profound sense of affinity\" shared with states\nArabic, speaking during the opening ceremony of the tenth\nMinisterial meeting of the Cooperation Forum between China and States\nArabs of Beijing. Xi, who urged \"a greater\nfinancial and technological cooperation,\" he said, \"everything\nwhen I meet our Arab friends, I feel a deep sense\nof affinity. The friendship between China and its people and countries and\nArab peoples originate from friendly exchanges along the ancient\nSilk Road. China will host the second syno-Arab summit\nin 2026, announced Xi.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Chinese President at the opening of the Cooperation Forum in Beijing",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab States'",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Cooperation Forum",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "LAW",
                "info": "Named documents made into laws."
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chinese",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi Jinping",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arabic",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "tenth",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Cooperation Forum between China",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 209,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arabs",
                "start_char": 221,
                "end_char": 226,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 343,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Arab",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Silk Road",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 526,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 533,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the second syno-Arab",
                "start_char": 544,
                "end_char": 564,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2026",
                "start_char": 575,
                "end_char": 579,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi",
                "start_char": 591,
                "end_char": 593,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Le Pen, 'Macron vuole semplicemente entrare in guerra'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 10:53:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/30/le-pen-macron-vuole-semplicemente-entrare-in-guerra_8312618c-8781-4b2d-b9d8-6735302d9d0e.html",
        "subtitle": "E denuncia 'meccanismi di ingresso in un conflitto mondiale'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La leader del Rassemblement\nNational, Marine Le Pen, ha accusato oggi Emmanuel Macron di\nvoler \"entrare semplicemente in guerra con la Russia\", dopo le\nparole del presidente francese che vuole consentire l'uso di\narmi occidentali per \"neutralizzare\" basi militari russe. Una\nmossa - ha detto ai microfoni di France Info - che \"sarebbe un\nulteriore passo di coinvolgimento in questo conflitto\" che\n\"creerebbe un pericolo assolutamente catastrofico per la\nsicurezza dei nostri connazionali e per l'integrità del nostro\nterritorio\". La leader di estrema destra ha denunciato\n\"meccanismi di ingresso in una guerra mondiale\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 47,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.0574498,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Le Pen, 'Macron just wants to go into war'",
        "en_content": "Rassemblement leader\nNational, Marine Le Pen, today accused Emmanuel Macron of\nwant to \"just go into war with Russia\", after\nPresident of the European Parliament\nWestern weapons to \"neutralize\" Russian military bases. One\nmove - told the microphones of France Info - that \"would be a\nfurther step of involvement in this conflict\"\n\"would create an absolutely catastrophic danger for\nsafety of our compatriots and the integrity of our\nterritory.\" The right extreme leader denounced\n\"Mechanisms of entry into a world war\".\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "It denounces 'mechanisms of entry into a world conflict'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Le Pen",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Macron",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "National",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Marine Le Pen",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emmanuel Macron",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Parliament",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 194,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "One",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 221,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 259,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Khamenei agli studenti Usa, 'voi state dalla parte giusta'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 10:52:33 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/30/khamenei-agli-studenti-usa-voi-state-dalla-parte-giusta_d6f64de9-bc58-417d-9e48-2b3725f51d9e.html",
        "subtitle": "'Proteste pro Palestina sono un ramo del Fronte di Resistenza'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Cari studenti universitari negli\nStati Uniti d'America, questo messaggio è un'espressione della\nnostra empatia e solidarietà con voi. Mentre la storia sta\nvoltando pagina, voi state dalla parte giusta\". Lo ha affermato\nla Guida suprema dell'Iran, Ali Khamenei, in una lettera agli\nstudenti delle università americane che hanno partecipato alle\ndimostrazioni per la Palestina. \"Il mio consiglio per voi è di\nacquisire familiarità con il Corano\" si legge nel testo,\npubblicato sul sito di Khamenei, dove la Guida suprema della\nRepubblica islamica afferma che, manifestando nelle università,\ngli studenti hanno \"formato un ramo del Fronte di Resistenza\",\n\"nonostante la spietata pressione del vostro governo, un governo\nche sostiene apertamente l'usurpatore e brutale regime\nsionista\". Nella lettera, Khamenei accusa il governo degli Usa\ndi \"ipocrisia\" per il suo sostegno a Israele, menziona una\n\"élite sionista globale\" che controllerebbe i media negli Stati\nUniti e in Europa, e dichiara che \"l'odierno genocidio del\nregime sionista dell'apartheid è la continuazione di un\ncomportamento estremamente oppressivo che va avanti da decenni\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tSecondo la Guida suprema della Repubblica islamica, in questo\nmomento \"la coscienza delle persone si è risvegliata su scala\nglobale e la verità sta venendo alla luce. Inoltre, il Fronte\ndella Resistenza si è rafforzato e diventerà ancora più forte\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 45,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.0660746,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Khamenei to US students, 'you're on the right side'",
        "en_content": "\"Dear university students in\nUSA, this message is an expression of\nour empathy and solidarity with you. While history is\nturn the page, you are on the right side.\" He said\nthe Supreme Guide of Iran, Ali Khamenei, in a letter to\nstudents of American universities who attended\ndemonstrations for Palestine. \"My advice for you is of\nto become familiar with the Koran\" reads in the text,\npublished on the site of Khamenei, where the supreme guide of\nIslamic Republic states that, manifesting in universities,\nstudents have \"formed a branch of the Resistance Front\",\n\"despite the ruthless pressure of your government, a government\nwho openly supports the usurper and brutal regime\nZionist.\" In the letter, Khamenei accuses the U.S. government\nof \"hypocrisy\" for its support to Israel, mentions a\n\"global Zionist elite\" that would control media in states\nUnited States and Europe, and declares that \"the present genocide of the\nZionist regime of apartheid is the continuation of a\nextremely oppressive behaviour that has been going on for decades.\"\n\n\nAccording to the Supreme Guide of the Islamic Republic, in this\nmoment \"the conscience of people has awakened on scale\nglobal and truth is coming to light. In addition, the Front\nof the Resistance has strengthened and will become even stronger\".\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Protex pro Palestine are a branch of the Resistance Front'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Protex pro Palestine",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Resistance Front'",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Guide of Iran",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ali Khamenei",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestine",
                "start_char": 294,
                "end_char": 303,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Koran",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 409,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamic Republic",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Resistance Front",
                "start_char": 539,
                "end_char": 559,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zionist",
                "start_char": 676,
                "end_char": 683,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Khamenei",
                "start_char": 701,
                "end_char": 709,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 722,
                "end_char": 726,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 772,
                "end_char": 778,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zionist",
                "start_char": 799,
                "end_char": 806,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 849,
                "end_char": 862,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 867,
                "end_char": 873,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zionist",
                "start_char": 922,
                "end_char": 929,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "decades",
                "start_char": 1033,
                "end_char": 1040,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Guide of the Islamic Republic",
                "start_char": 1058,
                "end_char": 1099,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Front",
                "start_char": 1218,
                "end_char": 1223,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Resistance",
                "start_char": 1231,
                "end_char": 1241,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il ministro delle Finanze brasiliano Haddad da papa Francesco",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 11:02:34 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/30/il-ministro-delle-finanze-brasiliano-haddad-da-papa-francesco_b9740960-3875-466d-a418-e8b700743634.html",
        "subtitle": "Con un progetto di tasse ai super-ricchi per combattere la fame",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro delle Finanze\nbrasiliano, Fernando Haddad, si recherà la settimana prossima in\nVaticano dove sarà ricevuto da papa Francesco a cui presenterà\nil progetto in elaborazione di tassazione dei super-ricchi per\ncontribuire a combattere la fame nel mondo, uno dei temi\ncentrali della presidenza di turno brasiliana del G20 nel 2024.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'annuncio del viaggio di Haddad è stato fatto ieri dal\npresidente Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva durante una cerimonia\nufficiale a Brasilia a cui partecipavano anche il vicepresidente\nGeraldo Alckmin, ministri e parlamentari.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In occasione della sua permanenza in Italia, il ministro\ndelle Finanze brasiliano parteciperà a un seminario ('Addressing\nthe Debt Crisis in the Global South') organizzato dalla\nPontificia Accademia delle Scienze Sociali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   A quanto si è appreso Haddad dovrebbe presentare durante la\nsua visita alla Santa Sede il progetto di tassazione dei\nsuper-ricchi del mondo che Lula ha illustrato il 23 maggio nel\ncorso di un incontro con il presidente del Benin, Patrice Talon.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Se i 3.000 miliardari del pianeta pagassero il 2% di tasse\nsui redditi derivanti dalle loro fortune - ha sottolineato in\npresenza del capo dello stato africano - potremmo generare\nrisorse sufficienti per nutrire 340 milioni di persone\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Da parte sua Haddad, inaugurando il 27 febbraio scorso a San\nPaolo l'incontro dei ministri dell'Economia e delle Finanze del\nG20 aveva già indicato che \"dobbiamo far si'  che i miliardari\ndel mondo paghino la loro giusta quota di tasse\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 48,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.0738583,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Brazilian Finance Minister Haddad by Pope Francis",
        "en_content": "Minister for Finance\nBrazilian, Fernando Haddad, will go next week in\nVatican where it will be received by Pope Francis\nthe project in processing of super-rich taxation for\nhelp fight hunger in the world, one of the themes\nCentral of the Brazilian presidency of the G20 in 2024.\n\n\nThe announcement of Haddad's trip was made yesterday by\nPresident Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva during a ceremony\nofficial in Brasilia who also participated in the vice-president\nGeraldo Alckmin, ministers and parliamentarians.\n\n\nOn the occasion of his stay in Italy, the Minister\nof Brazilian Finance will participate in a seminar ('Addressing\nthe Debt Crisis in the Global South'\nPontifical Academy of Social Sciences.\n\n\nTo what was learned Haddad should present during the\nhis visit to the Holy See the plan of taxation of\nsuper-rich of the world that Lula illustrated on 23 May in\nA meeting with Benin's president, Patrice Talon.\n\n\n\"If the 3,000 billionaires of the planet paid 2% of taxes\non incomes deriving from their fortunes - it has emphasized in\npresence of the head of the African state - we could generate\nsufficient resources to feed 340 million people.\"\n\n\nFor his part Haddad, opening on 27 February last in San\nPaul the meeting of the Ministers of Economy and Finance of\nG20 had already indicated that \"we must make billionaires\nof the world pay their right share of taxes.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "With a super-rich tax project to fight hunger",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haddad",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Francis",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fernando Haddad",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "next week",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vatican",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pope Francis",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 119,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "2024",
                "start_char": 273,
                "end_char": 277,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haddad",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 307,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 324,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 372,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brasilia",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Geraldo Alckmin",
                "start_char": 456,
                "end_char": 471,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 543,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian Finance",
                "start_char": 561,
                "end_char": 578,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Global South'",
                "start_char": 641,
                "end_char": 658,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pontifical Academy of Social Sciences",
                "start_char": 659,
                "end_char": 696,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Haddad",
                "start_char": 720,
                "end_char": 726,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lula",
                "start_char": 832,
                "end_char": 836,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "23 May",
                "start_char": 852,
                "end_char": 858,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benin",
                "start_char": 877,
                "end_char": 882,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Patrice Talon",
                "start_char": 896,
                "end_char": 909,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "3,000",
                "start_char": 921,
                "end_char": 926,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2%",
                "start_char": 959,
                "end_char": 961,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "African",
                "start_char": 1062,
                "end_char": 1069,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "340 million",
                "start_char": 1125,
                "end_char": 1136,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Haddad",
                "start_char": 1161,
                "end_char": 1167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "27 February last",
                "start_char": 1180,
                "end_char": 1196,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "San\nPaul",
                "start_char": 1200,
                "end_char": 1208,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministers of Economy and Finance",
                "start_char": 1224,
                "end_char": 1260,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 1373,
                "end_char": 1406,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Massima allerta Europa per roghi dolosi,zampino di Mosca'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 10:53:03 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/30/massima-allerta-europa-per-roghi-dolosizampino-di-mosca_e8ef1667-a580-42fe-a30d-ba716d1968d2.html",
        "subtitle": "Guardian: 'Nei Paesi Baltici, in Germania, nel Regno Unito'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            I servizi di sicurezza di tutta\nEuropa sono in massima allerta per quella che viene considerata\nuna nuova arma di guerra della Russia: incendi dolosi e\nsabotaggi nei Paesi Baltici, in Germania, nel Regno Unito. Lo\nriporta il Guardian. Per il rogo all'Ikea di Vilnius, il premier\npolacco Donald Tusk ha suggerito che potrebbe essere opera di un\nsabotatore straniero. Gli investigatori europei hanno già\nipotizzato un potenziale coinvolgimento russo in un incendio\ndoloso nella zona est di Londra, in un altro che ha distrutto il\npiù grande centro commerciale della Polonia, in Baviera e per i\ngraffiti antisemiti a Parigi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 46,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.0826175,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "'Maximum alert Europe for Dolose Rogues, Moscow Pudding'",
        "en_content": "Security services of all\nEurope is in maximum alert for what is considered\na new weapon of war of Russia: fires and\nsabotage in the Baltic countries, Germany, the United Kingdom. I do.\nReport the Guardian. For the rogue at the Ikea in Vilnius, the premier\nPolish Donald Tusk suggested that it could be the work of a\nforeign saboteur. European investigators already have\nhypothesized a potential Russian involvement in a fire\nDoloso in the east of London, in another who destroyed the\nPoland's largest shopping mall, Bavaria and\nanti-Semitic graffiti in Paris.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Guardian: In the Baltic States, Germany, the United Kingdom",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dolose Rogues",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow Pudding'",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Baltic States",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Baltic",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Germany",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United Kingdom",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guardian",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 204,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ikea",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vilnius",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 262,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Tusk",
                "start_char": 263,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 342,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 402,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Doloso",
                "start_char": 425,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "start_char": 447,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "start_char": 484,
                "end_char": 490,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bavaria",
                "start_char": 516,
                "end_char": 523,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "anti-Semitic",
                "start_char": 528,
                "end_char": 540,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Paris",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 558,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Avanza in Senato la Legge Base chiave del governo argentino",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 11:27:25 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2024/05/30/avanza-in-senato-la-legge-base-chiave-del-governo-argentino_d895d2c8-9dce-4a1e-8ace-6a15a8aba4d5.html",
        "subtitle": "Grazie all'intervento del capo di gabinetto, Guillermo Francos",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Dopo intensi negoziati il\ngoverno argentino è riuscito ad ottenere la notte scorsa le\nfirme necessarie per far avanzare in Senato il suo ambizioso\npacchetto composto dalla 'Legge Base' e dalle riforme fiscali.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    Lo sblocco dei provvedimenti  è avvenuto dopo una giornata\ndi incertezza e di intenso lavoro di persuasione realizzato\ndagli operatori governativi del partito La Libertad Avanza nei\nconfronti dei senatori federali e radicali incerti, appartenenti\nad un settore politico di opposizione moderata propenso al\ndialogo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In questo processo di convincimento, che ha riguardato in\npratica quattro senatori il cui voto era essenziale per il\nraggiungimento della maggioranza, sottolineano i media\nargentini, ha svolto un ruolo fondamentale il nuovo capo di\ngabinetto Guillermo Francos, che ha sostituito due giorni fa il\ndimissionario Nicolás Posse.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel corso di dichiarazioni al termine delle complesse\ntrattative, Francos ha ammesso che per rendere possibile\nl'avanzamento dei provvedimenti al Senato, dove verranno\nesaminati probabilmente la settimana prossima, è stato\nnecessario fare concessioni riguardanti la Legge sulle miniere e\nla base minima di pagamento dell'imposta sul reddito. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 43,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.0904827,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "The key basic law of the Argentine government",
        "en_content": "After intense negotiations\nArgentine government managed to get last night the\nnecessary signatures to advance in the Senate his ambitious\npackage consisting of 'Basic Law' and tax reforms.\n\n\nUnlocking measures took place after a day\nof uncertainty and intense work of persuasion realized\nby the government operators of the party La Libertad Advanced in\ncomparisons of uncertain federal and radical senators, belonging\nto a moderate opposition political sector\ndialogue.\n\n\nIn this process of conviction, which he dealt with in\npractice four senators whose vote was essential for\nAchievement of the majority, emphasize the media\nArgentinians, the new head of the\ncabinet Guillermo Francos, which replaced two days ago\ndimissionario Nicolás Posse.\n\n\nIn the course of statements at the end of complex\nnegotiations, Francos admitted that to make possible\nthe advancement of the measures to the Senate, where they will come\nprobably examined next week, it was\nnecessary to make concessions regarding the Law on Mines and\nthe minimum payment basis of income tax.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Thanks to the intervention of the chief of cabinet, Guillermo Francos",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Guillermo Francos",
                "start_char": 52,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "last night",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 73,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 117,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "La Libertad Advanced",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "four",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 539,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentinians",
                "start_char": 627,
                "end_char": 639,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Guillermo Francos",
                "start_char": 669,
                "end_char": 686,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two days ago",
                "start_char": 703,
                "end_char": 715,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "dimissionario Nicolás Posse",
                "start_char": 716,
                "end_char": 743,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Francos",
                "start_char": 811,
                "end_char": 818,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 889,
                "end_char": 895,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "next week",
                "start_char": 936,
                "end_char": 945,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Law on Mines",
                "start_char": 994,
                "end_char": 1010,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Wck sospende le sue attività a Rafah per attacchi Israele",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 10:51:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/30/wck-sospende-le-sue-attivita-a-rafah-per-attacchi-israele_71121609-9bd9-402b-ba9f-f460ae08c04b.html",
        "subtitle": "'Trasferite molte cucine a nord'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La World Centrale Kitchen (Wck)\nha annunciato di aver sospeso le sue attività a Rafah, nel sud\ndella Striscia, a causa \"delle operazioni israeliane in città\ndove innumerevoli famiglie sono costrette a fuggire ancora una\nvolta\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Gli attacchi in corso - ha detto su X l'ong, di cui sette\noperatori umanitari sono stati uccisi dal fuoco dell'Idf lo\nscorso aprile a Gaza a seguito di un'errata identificazione - ci\nhanno costretto a sospendere il lavoro nella nostra cucina\nprincipale a Rafah e a trasferire molte delle nostre cucine\ncomunitarie più a nord\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 44,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.098371,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Wck suspends his activities in Rafah for Israel attacks",
        "en_content": "The World Central Kitchen (Wck)\nhas announced that it has suspended its activities in Rafah, in the south\nof the Strip, because of \" Israeli operations in the city\nwhere countless families are forced to flee again\ntime.\"\n\n\n\"The ongoing attacks - said about X l'ong, of which seven\nhumanitarian workers were killed by the fire of Idf lo\nlast April in Gaza following an incorrect identification - we\nforced to suspend work in our kitchen\nmain to Rafah and to transfer many of our kitchens\nCommunity further north.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Transfer many kitchens to the north'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The World Central Kitchen (Wck",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 91,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 118,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 275,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf lo",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "last April",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 346,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 350,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 444,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 551,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "La Spagna approva in via definitiva la legge sull'amnistia",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 11:45:56 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/30/la-spagna-approva-in-via-definitiva-la-legge-sullamnistia_52438006-3062-4248-976d-db538ee14929.html",
        "subtitle": "Con 178 voti a favore e 172 contrari del Pp e di Vox",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La legge di amnistia per gli\nimplicati nel processo secessionista in Catalogna, dal novembre\n2011 al novembre 2023, è stata approvata oggi in via definitiva\ndal Congresso spagnolo. Il provvedimento che revoca il veto\napposto dal Senato, ha ricevuto 178 voti a favore della\nmaggioranza progressista Psoe-Sumar, sostenuta dai partiti \nnazionalisti baschi e catalani e regionalisti,  e 172 contrari \ndei partiti di opposizione, il Partito Popolare, quello di\nestrema destra Vox e il deputato di Upn. La controversa\nnormativa apre la strada al ritorno in Spagna dell'ex presidente\nCharles Puigdemont, riparato all'estero nell'ottobre 2017.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 42,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.113397,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Spain definitively approves the amnesty law",
        "en_content": "Amnesty law for\ninvolved in the secessionist process in Catalonia, since November\n2011 to November 2023, was approved today in a definitive way\nfrom the Spanish Congress. The measure revoking the veto\nappointed by the Senate, received 178 votes in favor of\nProgressive majority Psoe-Sumar, supported by parties\nBasque and Catalan and regionalist nationalists, and 172 against\nof opposition parties, the People's Party, that of\nextreme right Vox and Upn MP. The Converse\nlegislation opens the way back to Spain of the former president\nCharles Puigdemont, repaired abroad in October 2017.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "With 178 votes in favour and 172 against Pp and Vox",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "178",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "172",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pp",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vox",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Amnesty",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Catalonia",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "November\n2011",
                "start_char": 73,
                "end_char": 86,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "November 2023",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 103,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Spanish",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 169,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Senate",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "178",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 238,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Progressive",
                "start_char": 257,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Psoe-Sumar",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Basque",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Catalan",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 329,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "172",
                "start_char": 364,
                "end_char": 367,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the People's Party",
                "start_char": 399,
                "end_char": 417,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vox",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Spain",
                "start_char": 504,
                "end_char": 509,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Charles Puigdemont",
                "start_char": 534,
                "end_char": 552,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "October 2017",
                "start_char": 573,
                "end_char": 585,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Gallant, 'informazioni concrete su ostaggi a Rafah'",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 11:59:20 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/30/gallant-informazioni-concrete-su-ostaggi-a-rafah_a40f2eb4-8b8f-4720-a5a5-b91544b15c66.html",
        "subtitle": "Ministro parla con suo omologo Usa Austin",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Ci sono \"informazioni concrete\nriguardo gli ostaggi detenuti a Rafah\". Lo ha detto il ministro\ndella difesa Yoav Gallant in una conversazione telefonica con il\nsuo omologo Usa Lloyd Austin al quale ha ribadito \"l'importanza\ndi continuare ad operare nell'area\" della città più a sud della\nStriscia. Gallant - secondo il suo ufficio - ha poi aggiornato\nAustin \"sugli sviluppi della guerra ad Hamas\" nella zona e sui\n\"20 tunnel scoperti dall'esercito sul posto\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Gallant ha anche parlato con  Austin della situazione nel\nnord di Israele e dei \"continui lanci quotidiani da parte degli\nHezbollah di decine di missili verso le comunità israeliane\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tIsraele - ha spiegato Gallant -è determinato a difendere i suoi\ncittadini e a riportare in sicurezza gli sfollati nelle loro\ncase a nord. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 39,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.492404,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Gallant, 'concrete information on hostages in Rafah'",
        "en_content": "There are \"concrete information\nabout the hostages held in Rafah.\" The Minister said so.\ndefense Yoav Gallant in a telephone conversation with the\nhis omologist Usa Lloyd Austin to whom he reiterated \"the importance\nto continue to operate in the area\" of the city more south of\nStrip. Gallant - according to his office - he then updated\nAustin \"on developments in the war in Hamas\" in the area and on\n\"20 tunnels discovered by the army on the spot.\"\n\n\nGallant also talked to Austin about the situation in\nNorthern Israel and the \"continuous daily launches by the\nHezbollah of dozens of missiles to the Israeli communities.\"\n\n\nIsrael - Gallant has explained - is determined to defend its\ncitizens and to safely report the displaced in their\nhouses north.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Minister speaks to his counterpart Usa Austin",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Usa Austin",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 64,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yoav Gallant",
                "start_char": 97,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Usa Lloyd Austin",
                "start_char": 161,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 292,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Austin",
                "start_char": 337,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gallant",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Austin",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 481,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Northern Israel",
                "start_char": 505,
                "end_char": 520,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the \"continuous daily",
                "start_char": 525,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hezbollah",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 572,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 576,
                "end_char": 582,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 602,
                "end_char": 609,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 626,
                "end_char": 632,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Via libera Ue ai dazi maggiorati sul grano russo",
        "date_raw": "Thu, 30 May 2024 12:27:50 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-30",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/30/via-libera-ue-ai-dazi-maggiorati-sul-grano-russo_8857b86b-2f89-495a-96c3-06b7b56e386a.html",
        "subtitle": "Dal 1° luglio misure anche sui prodotti agricoli da Bielorussia",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Via libera dei ministri Ue ai\ndazi maggiorati sulle importazioni di prodotti agricoli - finora\nin gran parte esentati - dalla Russia e dalla Bielorussia, a\npartire dal primo luglio. Lo annuncia il commissario Ue per il\nCommercio, Valdis Dombrovskis.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La misura punta a \"impedire che il grano russo destabilizzi\nil settore agricolo europeo, limitare le entrate della Russia\nper finanziare la sua guerra contro l'Ucraina e contrastare le\nesportazioni illegali russe di grano rubato dall'Ucraina nei\nmercati dell'Ue\", sottolinea Dombrovskis. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 40,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1717120847.4995527,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-31 04:00:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-31T04.00.47",
        "en_title": "Free EU to increased duties on Russian wheat",
        "en_content": "Free movement of EU ministers\nIncreased duties on imports of agricultural products - so far\nlargely exempted - from Russia and Belarus, to\nfrom July 1st. It is announced by Commissioner Ue for\nTrade, Valdis Dombrovskis.\n\n\nThe measure aims to \"prevent Russian wheat from destabilizing\nthe European agricultural sector, restrict Russia's revenue\nto finance his war against Ukraine and counteract the\nRussian illegal grain exports stolen from Ukraine in\nEU markets,\" says Dombrovskis.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "From 1 July measures also on agricultural products from Belarus",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 31,
