[
    {
        "title": "Ucraina, Trump: l'Europa contribuisca di più agli aiuti",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:46:11 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/13/ucraina-trump-leuropa-contribuisca-di-piu-agli-aiuti_0f549be4-a596-42a7-986c-faec29d1283d.html",
        "subtitle": "L'ex presidente Usa: stiamo esaminando forme di prestito",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Donald Trump ha dichiarato che\nsta esaminando con i repubblicani al Congresso americano la\npossibilità di fornire aiuti all'Ucraina \"sotto forma di\nprestito e non donazioni di miliardi e miliardi di dollari\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Durante una conferenza stampa in Florida con lo speaker Mike\nJohnson, il tycoon ha anche detto che \"l'Europa deve contribuire\ndi più perché è più toccata dalla guerra\" in Ucraina. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 57,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.611964,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Ukraine, Trump: Europe contributes more to aid",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump said that\nis examining with Republicans at the American Congress\npossibility of providing aid to Ukraine \"in the form of\nloan and donations of billions and billions of dollars\".\n\n\nDuring a press conference in Florida with speaker Mike\nJohnson, tycoon also said that \"Europe must contribute\nmore because it is more touched by war\" in Ukraine.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Republicans",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "billions and billions of dollars",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mike\nJohnson",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, 'sirene d'allarme al confine nord con il Libano'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 23:42:54 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/13/israele-sirene-dallarme-al-confine-nord-con-il-libano_ad29c59d-c62b-49f6-a888-043b3aeaa0f7.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo ha detto il portavoce militare",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Le sirene di allarme anti razzi\nstanno risuonando nel nord di Israele, al confine con il Libano.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo ha detto il portavoce militare. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.6183245,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Israel, 'warning sirens on the north border with Lebanon'",
        "en_content": "Anti rocket alarm sirens\nare resounding in the north of Israel, at the border with Lebanon.\n\n\nThe military spokesman said that.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ucraina, Trump: l'Europa contribuisca di più agli aiuti",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:46:13 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/13/ucraina-trump-leuropa-contribuisca-di-piu-agli-aiuti_28a09813-1bc0-47dd-93fb-a4e48bb8762d.html",
        "subtitle": "L'ex presidente Usa: stiamo esaminando forme di prestito",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Donald Trump ha dichiarato che\nsta esaminando con i repubblicani al Congresso americano la\npossibilità di fornire aiuti all'Ucraina \"sotto forma di\nprestito e non donazioni di miliardi e miliardi di dollari\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Durante una conferenza stampa in Florida con lo speaker Mike\nJohnson, il tycoon ha anche detto che \"l'Europa deve contribuire\ndi più perché è più toccata dalla guerra\" in Ucraina. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.6396399,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Ukraine, Trump: Europe contributes more to aid",
        "en_content": "Donald Trump said that\nis examining with Republicans at the American Congress\npossibility of providing aid to Ukraine \"in the form of\nloan and donations of billions and billions of dollars\".\n\n\nDuring a press conference in Florida with speaker Mike\nJohnson, tycoon also said that \"Europe must contribute\nmore because it is more touched by war\" in Ukraine.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Republicans",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 69,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "billions and billions of dollars",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Florida",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 229,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mike\nJohnson",
                "start_char": 243,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, Wsj: Usa posizionano navi guerra per difesa da Iran",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 07:00:29 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/13/israele-wsj-usa-posizionano-navi-guerra-per-difesa-da-iran_62c0df44-7511-471b-8fbb-c3695f44bd8b.html",
        "subtitle": "Cnn: Teheran attaccherà obiettivo dentro lo Stato ebraico",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Wall Street Journal riporta\nche gli Stati Uniti hanno spostato le navi da guerra in\nposizione per proteggere non solo Israele ma le proprie forze in\nMedio Oriente, in mezzo alla crescente preoccupazione che l'Iran\npossa lanciare un attacco diretto contro lo Stato ebraico.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tGli Stati Uniti si aspettano che l'Iran effettuerà \"attacchi\ncontro molteplici obiettivi all'interno di Israele\" e che\nnell'operazione \"potrebbero essere coinvolti alleati di\nTeheran\". Lo riferiscono alla Cnn un alto funzionario\ndell'amministrazione Biden e una fonte vicina all'intelligence\nUsa. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 50,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.7669668,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Israel, Wsj: Use place war ships for defense from Iran",
        "en_content": "The Wall Street Journal reports\nthat the United States has moved the warships to\nposition to protect not only Israel but their forces in\nMiddle East, in the midst of the growing concern that Iran\ncan launch a direct attack against the Jewish state.\n\n\nThe United States expects Iran to carry out \"attacks\nagainst multiple objectives within Israel\" and\nin the operation \"they could be involved allies of\nTehran.\" The Cnn report a high official\nof the Biden administration and a source close to the intelligence\nUse.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wsj",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Wall Street Journal",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Middle East",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, Wsj: Usa posizionano navi guerra per difesa da Iran",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 07:00:32 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/13/israele-wsj-usa-posizionano-navi-guerra-per-difesa-da-iran_ec42ea7d-9c75-4f1e-a772-30a21d4f9b4f.html",
        "subtitle": "Cnn: Teheran attaccherà obiettivo dentro lo Stato ebraico",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il Wall Street Journal riporta\nche gli Stati Uniti hanno spostato le navi da guerra in\nposizione per proteggere non solo Israele ma le proprie forze in\nMedio Oriente, in mezzo alla crescente preoccupazione che l'Iran\npossa lanciare un attacco diretto contro lo Stato ebraico.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tGli Stati Uniti si aspettano che l'Iran effettuerà \"attacchi\ncontro molteplici obiettivi all'interno di Israele\" e che\nnell'operazione \"potrebbero essere coinvolti alleati di\nTeheran\". Lo riferiscono alla Cnn un alto funzionario\ndell'amministrazione Biden e una fonte vicina all'intelligence\nUsa. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 51,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.784658,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Israel, Wsj: Use place war ships for defense from Iran",
        "en_content": "The Wall Street Journal reports\nthat the United States has moved the warships to\nposition to protect not only Israel but their forces in\nMiddle East, in the midst of the growing concern that Iran\ncan launch a direct attack against the Jewish state.\n\n\nThe United States expects Iran to carry out \"attacks\nagainst multiple objectives within Israel\" and\nin the operation \"they could be involved allies of\nTehran.\" The Cnn report a high official\nof the Biden administration and a source close to the intelligence\nUse.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wsj",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The Wall Street Journal",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Middle East",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jewish",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 268,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 277,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tehran",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 415,
                "end_char": 418,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 449,
                "end_char": 454,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Attacco in centro commerciale a Sydney, diversi morti",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 10:22:00 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/13/attacco-in-centro-commerciale-a-sydney-diversi-morti_bbb1452d-a720-42ff-8772-99085f2b7722.html",
        "subtitle": "La polizia uccide un uomo che ha accoltellato molte persone",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Diverse persone sono state\naccoltellate, fra le quali vi sarebbero \"alcuni morti\", fino a\nsei secondo alcune fonti, in un'aggressione avvenuta in un\ncentro commerciale della città australiana di Sydney, secondo\nquanto riferisce la polizia locale e testimoni citati dalla\nstampa. La polizia ha sparato e ucciso un uomo ed è alla ricerca\ndi un possibile secondo aggressore.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il centro commerciale, durante l'attacco, è stato posto in\nlockdown mentre si spargeva il panico. La polizia è riuscita a\nevacuare molta gente mentre l'attacco era in corso. Non è ancora\nstato dichiarato se si sia trattato di terrorismo.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Immagini catturate dalle telecamere di sicurezza del centro\ncommerciale Westfield di Bondi Junction, alle porte di Sydney,\nmostrano un uomo in maglietta e calzoncini che si aggira nei\ncorridori con un coltello in mano. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 49,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.9606526,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Attack in the mall in Sydney, several dead",
        "en_content": "Several people have been\nstabbed, among which there would be \"some dead\", until\nsix according to some sources, in an attack in a\nSydney City Shopping Mall, Second\nwhat the local police report and witnesses cited by\nprint. The police shot and killed a man and is looking\nof a possible second attacker.\n\n\nThe mall, during the attack, was placed in\nLockdown while she panicked. The police managed to\nevacuate many people while the attack was on. Not yet.\nIt was stated that it was terrorism.\n\n\nImages captured by the center security cameras\nBondi Junction Westfield, at the gates of Sydney,\nshow a man in shirt and shorts wandering around\nrunners with a knife in hand.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "six",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 83,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Second",
                "start_char": 156,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "second",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lockdown",
                "start_char": 346,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bondi Junction Westfield",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 562,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 580,
                "end_char": 586,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "In Russia già 14.000 evacuati per inondazioni a Orenburg",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:42:49 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/13/in-russia-gia-14.000-evacuati-per-inondazioni-a-orenburg_f48f3254-5c4e-43f6-a83f-b66228973c0e.html",
        "subtitle": "La regione degli Urali sommersa con punte di 11,7 metri",
        "content": "In Russia, oltre 14.000 sono già state evacuate, e altre se ne aggiungono ogni ora, dalla città di Orenburg e dintorni, nella regione russa degli Urali, non lontano dal confine con il Kazakhistan, investita da nubifragi e conseguenti inondazioni. In alcuni punti il livello dell'acqua esondata dal fiume Ural ha toccato gli 11,7 metri, oltre 40 centimetri in più rispetto a ieri. Lo rendono noto le autorità locali, fra cui il sindaco di Orenburg, capoluogo dell'omonima regione russa.     L'inondazione ha investito quartieri residenziali della città, originata dalle piogge torrenziali innescate da un anomalo incremento delle temperature. Diverse le strade allagate, con il conseguente isolamento di alcune aree.   \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 47,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.9876306,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "In Russia already 14,000 floods in Orenburg",
        "en_content": "In Russia, more than 14,000 have already been evacuated, and others are added every hour, from the city of Orenburg and its surroundings, in the Russian region of the Urals, not far from the border with Kazakhstan, invested by clouds and consequent floods. In some places the water level exonerated from the Ural River touched 11.7 meters, over 40 centimeters more than yesterday. The local authorities make it known, including the mayor of Orenburg, the capital of the homonymous Russian region. The flood has invested residential districts of the city, originating from the torrential rains triggered by an abnormal increase in temperatures. Different flooded roads, with the consequent isolation of some areas.\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "14,000",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orenburg",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than 14,000",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "every hour",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orenburg",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 115,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Urals",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 172,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kazakhstan",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 213,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ural River",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "11.7 meters",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 338,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "40 centimeters",
                "start_char": 345,
                "end_char": 359,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "more than yesterday",
                "start_char": 360,
                "end_char": 379,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orenburg",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 481,
                "end_char": 488,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ucraina, media: Putin vuole riavviare centrale Zaporizhzhia",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:02:14 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/04/13/ucraina-media-putin-vuole-riavviare-centrale-zaporizhzhia_082535d9-a3a6-4fa3-8def-834b7ed132d4.html",
        "subtitle": "Wsj: il presidente russo lo avrebbe già comunicato all'Aiea",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il presidente russo Vladimir Putin ha\ncomunicato all'Agenzia internazionale per l'energia atomica\n(Aiea) che il Cremlino intende riavviare la centrale nucleare di\nZaporizhzhia, attualmente sotto occupazione russa. Lo scrive il\nWall Street Journal, sottolineando l'ulteriore aumento dei\nrischi di un incidente nella più grande centrale nucleare\nd'Europa.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'obiettivo della Russia sarebbe di riportare in servizio\nalmeno un reattore per il 40mo anniversario della connessione\ndell'impianto alla rete elettrica dell'Unione sovietica a\ndicembre. L'intenzione di riavviare la centrale sarebbe stata\nannunciata da Putin in un incontro con il capo dell'Aiea, Rafael\nGrossi \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 56,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045625.998432,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:25",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.25",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Ukraine, average: Putin wants to restart central Zaporizhzhia",
        "en_content": "Russian President Vladimir Putin\ncommunicated to the International Atomic Energy Agency\n(Ayea) that the Kremlin intends to restart the nuclear power plant\nZaporizhzhia, currently under Russian occupation. He writes it\nWall Street Journal, underlining the further increase in\nrisk of an accident in the largest nuclear power plant\nin Europe.\n\n\nThe aim of Russia would be to return to service\nat least one reactor for the 40th anniversary of the connection\nof the plant to the electricity network of the Soviet Union\nDecember. The intention to restart the power station would have been\nannounced by Putin in a meeting with the head of the Aiea, Rafael\nGross\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zaporizhzhia",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Atomic Energy Agency",
                "start_char": 49,
                "end_char": 87,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zaporizhzhia",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 167,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 192,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wall Street Journal",
                "start_char": 218,
                "end_char": 237,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 333,
                "end_char": 339,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "at least one",
                "start_char": 391,
                "end_char": 403,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "40th",
                "start_char": 420,
                "end_char": 424,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Soviet Union",
                "start_char": 498,
                "end_char": 514,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "December",
                "start_char": 515,
                "end_char": 523,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 597,
                "end_char": 602,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aiea",
                "start_char": 637,
                "end_char": 641,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafael\nGross",
                "start_char": 643,
                "end_char": 655,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, Jihad islamica lancia 8 razzi da Gaza su Sderot",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:22:55 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/13/israele-jihad-islamica-lancia-8-razzi-da-gaza-su-sderot_90572fc7-76b6-4c64-a4d6-2375895520d6.html",
        "subtitle": "Al momento nessuna vittima o danno segnalati",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Almeno otto razzi sono stati lanciati\nieri sera dalla Striscia di Gaza contro la città meridionale\nisraeliana di Sderot: l'attacco è stato rivendicato dalle\nBrigate al-Quds, braccio armato della Jihad islamica\npalestinese.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Lo riportano i media locali, specificando che al momento non\nsi hanno notizie di danni a persone o cose e che alcuni dei\nrazzi sono stati intercettati dal sistema di difesa israeliano\nIron dome. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 55,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.0039432,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Israel, Islamic Jihad launches 8 rockets from Gaza on Sderot",
        "en_content": "At least eight rockets were launched\nlast night from the Gaza Strip against the southern city\nIsraeli of Sderot: the attack was claimed by\nAl-Quds brigades, armed arm of Islamic Jihad\nPalestinian.\n\n\nLocal media reports it, specifying that at the moment\nyou have news of damage to people or things and that some of\nrockets have been intercepted by the Israeli defence system\nIron dome.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamic Jihad",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "8",
                "start_char": 31,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sderot",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "At least eight",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "last night",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Quds",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamic Jihad",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 184,
                "end_char": 195,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, Cnn: gli Usa hanno visto l'Iran spostare asset militari",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:29:31 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/13/israele-cnn-gli-usa-hanno-visto-liran-spostare-asset-militari_7856323d-9500-4edf-a109-95a866183f05.html",
        "subtitle": "Washington tenterà di intercettare qualsiasi arma verrà lanciata",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Osservatori americani hanno\nnotato che l'Iran sta spostando \"asset militari\" in vista di un\nattacco contro Israele. Lo riferiscono fonti informate alla Cnn.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Gli Stati Uniti \"tenteranno di intercettare qualsiasi arma\nlanciata contro Israele se sarà possibile farlo\", hanno riferito\ninoltre due funzionari.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Le forze della Marina americana nel Mar Rosso hanno nei mesi\nscorsi intercettato diversi missili a lungo raggio lanciati\ndagli Houthi nello Yemen verso Israele e le forze statunitensi\nin Iraq e Siria sono potenzialmente in grado di bloccare droni e\nrazzi indirizzati contro il nord di Israele, a seconda della\nposizione da cui vengono lanciati. Proprio ieri, il generale\nErik Kurilla, comandante del Comando centrale degli Stati Uniti,\nha avuto un incontro con il capo di stato maggiore delle forze\nisraeliane, il tenente generale Herzi Halevi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 54,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.009074,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Israel, Cnn: the U.S. have seen Iran move military assets",
        "en_content": "American observers have\nnoted that Iran is moving \"military assemblies\" in view of a\nattack against Israel. Sources reported to the Cnn.\n\n\nThe United States \"will attempt to intercept any weapon\nlaunched against Israel if it will be possible to do so,\" they reported\nIn addition, two officials.\n\n\nThe forces of the American Navy in the Red Sea have in the months\nintercepted several long-range missiles launched\nfrom the Houthi in Yemen to Israel and US forces\nin Iraq and Syria are potentially able to block drones and\nrockets directed against the north of Israel, depending on the\nlocation from which they are launched. Just yesterday, the general\nErik Kurilla, commander of the United States Central Command,\nhas had a meeting with the chief of staff\nIsraeli, Lieutenant General Herzi Halevi.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the American Navy",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the months",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 436,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 564,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Just yesterday",
                "start_char": 622,
                "end_char": 636,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erik Kurilla",
                "start_char": 650,
                "end_char": 662,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States Central Command",
                "start_char": 677,
                "end_char": 710,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 754,
                "end_char": 761,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Herzi Halevi",
                "start_char": 782,
                "end_char": 794,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Polizia, 'aggressore a Sydney era solo, non è chiaro il movente'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:13:23 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/13/polizia-aggressore-a-sydney-era-solo-non-e-chiaro-il-movente_9d838fd9-dcdd-4348-adc6-b18a78aa4372.html",
        "subtitle": "'Nessuna pista esclusa, nemmeno il terrorismo'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Dalle indagini preliminari\nsembrerebbe che questa persona abbia agito da sola\": lo ha\naffermato in conferenza stampa la polizia locale riguardo\nall'attacco di oggi nel centro commerciale di Sydney da parte di\nun uomo che ha accoltellato diverse persone, uccidendone almeno\n5 prima di essere a sua volta ucciso da una agente. Le autorità\nhanno inoltre affermato che al momento non vi è chiarezza sul\nmovente: \"Non c'è nulla di cui siamo a conoscenza sulla scena\nche possa indicare un movente o un'ideologia\" ha affermato in\nconferenza stampa il vice commissario Anthony Cooked, il quale,\nalla domanda di un giornalista se la polizia escludesse il\nterrorismo, ha detto: \"Non escludiamo nulla\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 48,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.0147238,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Police, the attacker in Sydney was alone, it's not clear the motive",
        "en_content": "\"From preliminary investigations\nIt would seem that this person acted alone: He did.\nstated at the press conference local police regarding\ntoday's attack in Sydney's shopping centre\na man who stabbed several people, killing at least\n5 before he was killed by an agent. The authorities\nhave also stated that at the moment there is no clarity on the\nmotive: \"There's nothing we know about on the scene\nthat may indicate motive or ideology\" he said in\npress conference Deputy Commissioner Anthony Cooked,\nto the question of a journalist if the police excluded the\nterrorism, he said: \"Let's not exclude anything.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 157,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Anthony Cooked",
                "start_char": 486,
                "end_char": 500,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Polizia, salito a 7 il bilancio dei morti a Sydney",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 12:25:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/13/polizia-salito-a-7-il-bilancio-dei-morti-a-sydney_7281e9ab-6212-4b5e-a070-4ed97d4e5787.html",
        "subtitle": "Incluso l'aggressore ucciso dagli agenti",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La polizia del New South Wales ha\naffermato che è morta una sesta persona attaccata a coltellate\nnel centro commerciale Westfield di Bondi Junction, a Sydney,\nportando il totale di morti a 7, incluso l'aggressore ucciso\ndagli agenti. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 45,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.0814247,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Police, seven of the dead in Sydney",
        "en_content": "The NYPD has\nclaimed that a sixth person was killed\nin the Westfield shopping center of Bondi Junction, Sydney,\nbringing the total death to 7, including the offender killed\nthe agents.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "seven",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 13,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "NYPD",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "sixth",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Westfield",
                "start_char": 59,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bondi Junction",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 104,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "7",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, Cnn: gli Usa hanno visto l'Iran spostare asset militari",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 02:14:02 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/13/israele-cnn-gli-usa-hanno-visto-liran-spostare-asset-militari_0534679a-f9d6-49f0-ad85-2571ff519392.html",
        "subtitle": "Washington tenterà di intercettare qualsiasi arma verrà lanciata",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Osservatori americani hanno\nnotato che l'Iran sta spostando \"asset militari\" in vista di un\nattacco contro Israele. Lo riferiscono fonti informate alla Cnn.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Gli Stati Uniti \"tenteranno di intercettare qualsiasi arma\nlanciata contro Israele se sarà possibile farlo\", hanno riferito\ninoltre due funzionari.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Le forze della Marina americana nel Mar Rosso hanno nei mesi\nscorsi intercettato diversi missili a lungo raggio lanciati\ndagli Houthi nello Yemen verso Israele e le forze statunitensi\nin Iraq e Siria sono potenzialmente in grado di bloccare droni e\nrazzi indirizzati contro il nord di Israele, a seconda della\nposizione da cui vengono lanciati. Proprio ieri, il generale\nErik Kurilla, comandante del Comando centrale degli Stati Uniti,\nha avuto un incontro con il capo di stato maggiore delle forze\nisraeliane, il tenente generale Herzi Halevi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 53,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.1021068,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Israel, Cnn: the U.S. have seen Iran move military assets",
        "en_content": "American observers have\nnoted that Iran is moving \"military assemblies\" in view of a\nattack against Israel. Sources reported to the Cnn.\n\n\nThe United States \"will attempt to intercept any weapon\nlaunched against Israel if it will be possible to do so,\" they reported\nIn addition, two officials.\n\n\nThe forces of the American Navy in the Red Sea have in the months\nintercepted several long-range missiles launched\nfrom the Houthi in Yemen to Israel and US forces\nin Iraq and Syria are potentially able to block drones and\nrockets directed against the north of Israel, depending on the\nlocation from which they are launched. Just yesterday, the general\nErik Kurilla, commander of the United States Central Command,\nhas had a meeting with the chief of staff\nIsraeli, Lieutenant General Herzi Halevi.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 8,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 36,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cnn",
                "start_char": 132,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 280,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the American Navy",
                "start_char": 311,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 332,
                "end_char": 343,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the months",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 362,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 421,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yemen",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 436,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 446,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 453,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iraq",
                "start_char": 464,
                "end_char": 468,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Syria",
                "start_char": 473,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 564,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Just yesterday",
                "start_char": 622,
                "end_char": 636,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Erik Kurilla",
                "start_char": 650,
                "end_char": 662,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States Central Command",
                "start_char": 677,
                "end_char": 710,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 754,
                "end_char": 761,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Herzi Halevi",
                "start_char": 782,
                "end_char": 794,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Usa: faceva la spia per Cuba', 15 anni a un ex ambasciatore",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 03:48:52 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/04/13/usa-faceva-la-spia-per-cuba-15-anni-a-un-ex-ambasciatore_54effe57-8882-489e-bf6f-b7d96c8367c1.html",
        "subtitle": "Aveva iniziato nel 1981, era stato consigliere di Bill Clinton",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Un ex ambasciatore degli Stati\nUniti che si è dichiarato colpevole di spionaggio a favore di\nCuba per oltre 40 anni è stato condannato da un tribunale\nfederale a 15 anni di prigione. Lo riportano i media americani.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Victor Manuel Rocha, 73 anni, è stato arrestato a dicembre\nper quella che i funzionari statunitensi hanno definito \"una\ndelle infiltrazioni di più vasta portata e di più lunga durata\nda parte di un agente straniero\" nel governo degli Stati Uniti.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tRocha si è dichiarato non colpevole a febbraio delle accuse di\ncospirazione ma in seguito ha accettato un patteggiamento. Dopo\nun'udienza di tre ore e mezza a Miami venerdì la giudice Beth\nBloom ha inflitto all'ex ambasciatore \"la pena massima\nconsentita dalla legge\". Oltre alla condanna a 15 anni, gli è\nstata comminata una multa di 500.000 dollari. Rocha, originario\ndella Colombia e naturalizzato americano, avrebbe iniziato ad\naiutare L'Avana come agente sotto copertura della Direzione\nGenerale dell'Intelligence (Dgi) di Cuba nel 1981, quando era\nentrato nel Dipartimento di Stato. Ha scalato i ranghi come\ndiplomatico di carriera, ricoprendo incarichi all'Avana, Buenos\nAires, Città del Messico e Washington. Rocha ha prestato\nservizio nel Consiglio di sicurezza nazionale dal 1994 al 1995\nsotto l'amministrazione del presidente Bill Clinton, ed è stato\nambasciatore in Bolivia dal 2000 al 2002 sotto Clinton e George\nW. Bush. Ha servito anche come consigliere del comando militare\nstatunitense responsabile di Cuba. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 52,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.208184,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "He was spying on Cuba, 15 years old at a former ambassador.",
        "en_content": "A former ambassador of the States\nUnited who pleaded guilty of espionage in favor of\nCuba for over 40 years has been convicted by a court\nFederal at 15 years in prison. The American media report it.\n\n\nVictor Manuel Rocha, 73, was arrested in December\nfor what U.S. officials called \"one\nof the most extensive and long-lasting infiltrations\nby a foreign agent\" in the US government.\n\n\nRocha pleaded not guilty in February of charges\nconspiracy but later accepted a plea deal. After\na three and a half hour hearing in Miami Friday Judge Beth\nBloom inflicted on former ambassador \"the maximum penalty\npermitted by law.\" In addition to the 15-year sentence, he is\nA fine of $500,000 was set. Rocha, comes from\nof Colombia and naturalized American, would begin\nHelp Havana as an undercover agent of the Direction\nGeneral of the Intelligence (Dgi) of Cuba in 1981, when he was\nentered the State Department. He climbed the ranks as\ncareer diplomat, holding positions in Havana, Buenos Aires\nBuenos Aires, Mexico City and Washington. Rocha lent\nservice in the National Security Council from 1994 to 1995\nunder the administration of President Bill Clinton, and was\nAmbassador to Bolivia from 2000 to 2002 under Clinton and George\nW. Bush. He also served as a military advisor\nAmerican responsible for Cuba.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cuba",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "15 years old",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the States\nUnited",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cuba",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 40 years",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "15 years",
                "start_char": 149,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Victor Manuel Rocha",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 220,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "73",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 224,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "December",
                "start_char": 242,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "U.S.",
                "start_char": 260,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 286,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rocha",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 389,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "February",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 420,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "three and a half hour",
                "start_char": 483,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Miami",
                "start_char": 516,
                "end_char": 521,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 522,
                "end_char": 528,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beth\nBloom",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 545,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "15-year",
                "start_char": 636,
                "end_char": 643,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "500,000",
                "start_char": 671,
                "end_char": 678,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rocha",
                "start_char": 688,
                "end_char": 693,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Colombia",
                "start_char": 709,
                "end_char": 717,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 734,
                "end_char": 742,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Help Havana",
                "start_char": 756,
                "end_char": 767,
                "label": "FAC",
                "info": "Buildings, airports, highways, bridges, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Direction\nGeneral of the Intelligence (Dgi",
                "start_char": 794,
                "end_char": 840,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Cuba",
                "start_char": 845,
                "end_char": 849,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "1981",
                "start_char": 853,
                "end_char": 857,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State Department",
                "start_char": 879,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Havana",
                "start_char": 963,
                "end_char": 969,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 971,
                "end_char": 983,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos Aires",
                "start_char": 984,
                "end_char": 996,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico City",
                "start_char": 998,
                "end_char": 1009,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 1014,
                "end_char": 1024,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rocha",
                "start_char": 1026,
                "end_char": 1031,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the National Security Council",
                "start_char": 1048,
                "end_char": 1077,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "1994 to 1995",
                "start_char": 1083,
                "end_char": 1095,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bill Clinton",
                "start_char": 1134,
                "end_char": 1146,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bolivia",
                "start_char": 1170,
                "end_char": 1177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2000",
                "start_char": 1183,
                "end_char": 1187,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "2002",
                "start_char": 1191,
                "end_char": 1195,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Clinton",
                "start_char": 1202,
                "end_char": 1209,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "George\nW. Bush",
                "start_char": 1214,
                "end_char": 1228,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 1267,
                "end_char": 1275,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cuba",
                "start_char": 1292,
                "end_char": 1296,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, rischio escalation, ho invitato Iran a prudenza",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 12:20:56 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/13/tajani-rischio-escalation-ho-invitato-iran-a-prudenza_86207fcb-5052-4b6c-ade2-52b202653999.html",
        "subtitle": "'Purtroppo la situazione è molto tesa'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            In Medio Oriente \"purtroppo la\nsituazione è molto tesa, i rischi di una escalation ci sono\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tCosì il ministro degli Esteri, Antonio Tajani, a margine di un\nevento di Forza Italia a Milano.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Ieri ho parlato per un'ora con il ministro degli Esteri\ndell'Iran e ho invitato alla prudenza. Mi sono preoccupato di\ntutelare i militari italiani che sono al confine tra Libano e\nIsraele - ha aggiunto - e ho insistito sulla necessità di\ngarantire il traffico mercantile attraverso Suez e il mar Rosso.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tMi è stato detto che gli Houthi non attaccheranno mercantili che\nnon portano armi a Israele\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 46,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.2306054,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Tajani, risk escalation, I invited Iran to prudence",
        "en_content": "In the Middle East \"unfortunately\nsituation is very tense, the risks of an escalation are there\".\n\n\nSo the Foreign Minister, Antonio Tajani, on the edge of a\nevent of Forza Italia in Milan.\n\n\n\"I spoke to the Foreign Minister yesterday\nof Iran and I invited to caution. I'm worried about you.\nprotect the Italian soldiers who are at the border between Lebanon and\nIsrael - he added - and I insisted on the need for\nensure merchant traffic through Suez and the Red Sea.\n\n\nI was told that the Houthi will not attack merchants who\ndo not bring weapons to Israel.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the Middle East",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Forza Italia",
                "start_char": 167,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 183,
                "end_char": 188,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "yesterday",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 234,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iran",
                "start_char": 238,
                "end_char": 242,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 304,
                "end_char": 311,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lebanon",
                "start_char": 351,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 363,
                "end_char": 369,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Suez",
                "start_char": 446,
                "end_char": 450,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Red Sea",
                "start_char": 455,
                "end_char": 466,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Houthi",
                "start_char": 490,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 551,
                "end_char": 557,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, 'non ci risultano italiani coinvolti a Sydney'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 12:57:57 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2024/04/13/tajani-non-ci-risultano-italiani-coinvolti-a-sydney_5cb296ed-0fdc-4a6e-9aee-cd9a333eea69.html",
        "subtitle": "'La polizia non esclude nessuna pista, aspettiamo le indagini'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Stiamo seguendo la situazione in\nAustralia attraverso la nostra ambasciata a Sydney e la nostra\nUnità di crisi. Non ci sono notizie certe\" ma \"al momento non ci\nrisultano italiani coinvolti\". Così il ministro degli Esteri\nAntonio Tajani parlando a margine di un evento di FI a Milano in\nmerito all'attacco in un centro commerciale a Sydney. \"La\npolizia australiana non esclude nessuna pista ma bisogna\nattendere le loro indagini. La nostra Unità di crisi ha inviato\ncome facciamo sempre dei messaggi a tutti gli italiani che sono\nnell'area per far sì che ogni italiano possa essere aggiornato\nsu ciò che sta accadendo\", ha aggiunto Tajani. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 44,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1713045626.238964,
        "language": "it",
        "source": "ANSA_Esteri",
        "local_time": "2024-04-14 00:00:26",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-04-14T00.00.26",
        "filename": "ner_en_2024-04-14T00.00.24E1713052824.666033.json",
        "en_title": "Tajani, 'there are no Italians involved in Sydney'",
        "en_content": "\"We are following the situation in\nAustralia through our embassy in Sydney and our\nCrisis unit. There is no certain news, but \"at the moment there is no\nItalians are involved.\" So the Foreign Minister\nAntonio Tajani speaking in the margin of a FI event in Milan in\ndue to the attack in a mall in Sydney. \"\nAustralian police do not exclude any track but must\nWait for their investigation. Our Crisis Unit has sent\nas we always make messages to all Italians who are\nin the area to ensure that every Italian can be updated\non what is happening,\" added Tajani.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 22,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Australia",
                "start_char": 35,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Crisis",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 215,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Milan",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sydney",
                "start_char": 296,
                "end_char": 302,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Australian",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 316,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italians",
                "start_char": 447,
                "end_char": 455,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 497,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 549,
                "end_char": 555,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Israele, 'l'Iran subirà conseguenze se aggrava la situazione'",
        "date_raw": "Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:31:10 +0200",
        "date": "2024-04-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/04/13/israele-liran-subira-conseguenze-se-aggrava-la-situazione_4540639d-842d-4366-8dcb-40936cb67300.html",
