[
    {
        "title": "Caracas attiva il 'Piano di indipendenza produttiva assoluta'",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 23:35:33 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/04/caracas-attiva-il-piano-di-indipendenza-produttiva-assoluta_69791e7b-7253-47e3-b076-bf6d575a9db4.html",
        "subtitle": "Dopo il ritiro della licenza a Chevron da parte degli Usa",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La vicepresidente venezuelana,\nDelcy Rodríguez, che è anche la ministra degli Idrocarburi, ha\nreso noto tramite un comunicato che \"il Venezuela attiva il\nPiano Indipendenza Produttiva Assoluta, di fronte alle sanzioni\ncontro Chevron\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel comunicato, diffuso stasera sui social network del\ngoverno di Nicolás Maduro, Rodríguez sottolinea che \"il nuovo\ngoverno degli Stati Uniti, pretendendo di danneggiare il popolo\nvenezuelano, sta autoinfliggendo un danno causando un aumento\ndel prezzo dei combustibili e influenzando la sicurezza\ngiuridica degli investimenti delle sue aziende all'estero,\nmettendo in discussione la presunta e ingannevole libertà\neconomica\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel comunicato Rodríguez afferma che \"il nuovo governo degli\nStati Uniti ha ceduto alla pressione di settori oppositori,\nfalliti e sconfitti, del Venezuela, imponendo sanzioni\ndefinitive alla compagnia statunitense Chevron\", annunciando che\n\"il presidente Nicolás Maduro ha ordinato l'attivazione del\nPiano Indipendenza Produttiva Assoluta, affinché la nostra\nindustria degli idrocarburi e l'economia del Paese continuino la\nloro ripresa stabile e diversificata\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129216.2402792,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:16",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.16",
        "en_title": "Caracas activates the 'absolute production independence plan'",
        "en_content": "Venezuelan vice president,\nDelcy Rodríguez, who is also the hydrocarbon minister, has\nannounced by a statement that \" Venezuela activates the\nAbsolute Production Independence Plan, in front of sanctions\nagainst Chevron.\n\n\nIn the statement, released tonight on social networks\nGovernment of Nicolás Maduro, Rodríguez emphasizes that \"the new\nUnited States government, claiming to harm the people\nVenezuelan, is self-imposing damage causing an increase\nthe price of fuels and affecting safety\nlegal investment of its companies abroad,\nquestioning the alleged and misleading freedom\neconomic.\"\n\n\nIn the statement Rodríguez states that \"the new government of\nUnited States has yielded pressure of opposing sectors,\nfailed and defeated, of Venezuela, imposing sanctions\ndefinitive to the American company Chevron\", announcing that\n\"President Nicolás Maduro ordered the activation of\nAbsolute Production Independence Plan, so that our\nhydrocarbon industry and the country's economy continue\ntheir stable and diversified recovery.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "After the withdrawal of the license to Chevron by the US",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Caracas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Chevron",
                "start_char": 39,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Delcy Rodríguez",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 118,
                "end_char": 127,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chevron",
                "start_char": 211,
                "end_char": 218,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "tonight",
                "start_char": 249,
                "end_char": 256,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicolás Maduro",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 304,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Rodríguez",
                "start_char": 306,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 354,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuelan",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 405,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rodríguez",
                "start_char": 610,
                "end_char": 619,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 655,
                "end_char": 668,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Venezuela",
                "start_char": 735,
                "end_char": 744,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 783,
                "end_char": 791,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Chevron",
                "start_char": 800,
                "end_char": 807,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicolás Maduro",
                "start_char": 837,
                "end_char": 851,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Trump sospende tutti gli aiuti militari all'Ucraina'",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 00:58:17 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/04/trump-sospende-tutti-gli-aiuti-militari-allucraina_fad8674c-39bc-425f-bb13-fcbff04772a8.html",
        "subtitle": "Bloomberg,fino a quando Trump determinerà buona fede Kiev a pace",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli Stati Uniti hanno sospeso\ntutti gli attuali aiuti militari all'Ucraina. Lo riporta\nl'agenzia Bloomberg citando alcune fonti, secondo le quali la\npausa durerà fino a quando il presidente Donald Trump non avrà\ndeterminato la buona fede dell'impegno di Kiev verso la pace.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 67,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.0902076,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "'Trump suspends all military aid to Ukraine'",
        "en_content": "The United States has suspended\nall current military aid to Ukraine. He's got it.\nthe agency Bloomberg citing some sources, according to which the\nbreak will last until President Donald Trump will have\ndetermined the good faith of Kiev's commitment to peace.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Bloomberg,until Trump will determine good faith Kiev to peace",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bloomberg",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bloomberg",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "'Trump sospende tutti gli aiuti militari all'Ucraina'",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 00:58:17 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/04/trump-sospende-tutti-gli-aiuti-militari-allucraina_a05a033e-bbb6-41ed-b320-cbdb548185d6.html",
        "subtitle": "Bloomberg,fino a quando Trump determinerà buona fede Kiev a pace",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Gli Stati Uniti hanno sospeso\ntutti gli attuali aiuti militari all'Ucraina. Lo riporta\nl'agenzia Bloomberg citando alcune fonti, secondo le quali la\npausa durerà fino a quando il presidente Donald Trump non avrà\ndeterminato la buona fede dell'impegno di Kiev verso la pace.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 66,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.1028385,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "'Trump suspends all military aid to Ukraine'",
        "en_content": "The United States has suspended\nall current military aid to Ukraine. He's got it.\nthe agency Bloomberg citing some sources, according to which the\nbreak will last until President Donald Trump will have\ndetermined the good faith of Kiev's commitment to peace.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Bloomberg,until Trump will determine good faith Kiev to peace",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bloomberg",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "The United States",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bloomberg",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 102,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 235,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Argentina, multa di 16 miliardi per la nazionalizzazione di Ypf",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 02:34:31 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/04/argentina-multa-di-16-miliardi-per-la-nazionalizzazione-di-ypf_b894889a-7a89-4ad9-a674-800992b16d78.html",
        "subtitle": "Respinto in Usa ricorso per indagare su quanto avvenne nel 2012",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La giudice Loretta Preska,\nche guida la corte del distretto meridionale di New York, ha\nrespinto il ricorso che aveva presentato qualche giorno fa l'ong\nstatunitense Republican Action for Argentina, la Rafa, per\nindagare sulla nazionalizzazione della compagnia petrolifera\nYpf.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Obiettivo del ricorso era rivedere e revocare la decisione di\nprimo grado che lo scorso anno ha condannato lo stato argentino\na pagare un risarcimento di 16,1 miliardi di dollari più un\nmiliardo di interessi ai fondi Burford ed Eton Park per\nl'esproprio, avvenuto nel 2012 durante governo dell'allora\npresidente Cristina Fernández de Kirchner (2007-2015).\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Lo riporta il sito del quotidiano argentino La Nación. \"Sono\ntarati ('tarados' in spagnolo) quelli che pensano che lo stato\ndebba essere stupido e comprare tutto secondo la legge della\nstessa Ypf, rispettando il suo statuto\", aveva detto Axel\nKicillof quando era ministro dell'Economia nel governo Kirchner,\ndifendendo quella decisione davanti al parlamento. Tale\ndichiarazione dell'oggi governatore della provincia di Buenos\nAires è stata presa dalla giudice Preska come prova\ndell'irregolarità dell'esproprio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Ora la causa continuerà il suo corso naturale. La sentenza\ndella Corte d'appello di New York non dovrebbe arrivare prima\ndel marzo 2026 ma, nel frattempo, altre richieste del fondo\nBurford saranno giudicate da Preska tra cui quella di rimanere\nle azioni che lo stato in Ypg, pari al 51%. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 62,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.1281593,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "Argentina, fine of 16 billion for the nationalization of Ypf",
        "en_content": "Judge Loretta Preska,\nwho leads the court of the southern district of New York, has\ndismissed the appeal which he had filed a few days ago\nAmerican Republican Action for Argentina, the Rafa, for\ninvestigate the nationalization of the oil company\nYpf.\n\n\nThe purpose of the action was to review and revoke the decision to\nfirst degree that last year condemned the Argentine state\nto pay a compensation of 16,1 billion dollars plus a\nbillion interest in Burford and Eton Park funds for\nthe expropriation, occurred in 2012 during government of the then\nPresident Cristina Fernández de Kirchner (2007-2015).\n\n\nThis is the site of the Argentine newspaper La Nación. \"\ntarati ('tarados' in Spanish) those who think the state\nmust be stupid and buy everything according to the law of\nYpf himself, respecting his statute,\" Axel said.\nKicillof when he was Minister of Economy in the Kirchner government,\ndefending that decision before Parliament. Article\nstatement of today governor of the province of Buenos\nBuenos Aires was taken by Judge Preska as proof\nof the irregularity of the expropriation.\n\n\nNow the cause will continue its natural course. The judgment\nof the New York Court of Appeal should not arrive before\nof March 2026 but, meanwhile, other requests of the fund\nBurford will be judged by Preska including staying\nthe actions that the state in Ypg, pairs to 51%.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Rejected to the US appeal to investigate what happened in 2012",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "16 billion",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2012",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 62,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Loretta Preska",
                "start_char": 6,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "New York",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "a few days ago",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 138,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "American Republican Action",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 165,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentina",
                "start_char": 170,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafa",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ypf.",
                "start_char": 246,
                "end_char": 250,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last year",
                "start_char": 338,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 362,
                "end_char": 371,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "16,1 billion dollars",
                "start_char": 403,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "Burford",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 458,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Eton Park",
                "start_char": 463,
                "end_char": 472,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "2012",
                "start_char": 514,
                "end_char": 518,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cristina Fernández de Kirchner",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 589,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "2007-2015",
                "start_char": 591,
                "end_char": 600,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Argentine",
                "start_char": 629,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "La Nación",
                "start_char": 649,
                "end_char": 658,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tarati",
                "start_char": 662,
                "end_char": 668,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Spanish",
                "start_char": 683,
                "end_char": 690,
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "info": "Any named language"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ypf",
                "start_char": 776,
                "end_char": 779,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Axel",
                "start_char": 814,
                "end_char": 818,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kicillof",
                "start_char": 825,
                "end_char": 833,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kirchner",
                "start_char": 873,
                "end_char": 881,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 925,
                "end_char": 935,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 958,
                "end_char": 963,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buenos\nBuenos",
                "start_char": 992,
                "end_char": 1005,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aires",
                "start_char": 1006,
                "end_char": 1011,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Preska",
                "start_char": 1031,
                "end_char": 1037,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the New York Court",
                "start_char": 1155,
                "end_char": 1173,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "March 2026",
                "start_char": 1212,
                "end_char": 1222,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Burford",
                "start_char": 1266,
                "end_char": 1273,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Preska",
                "start_char": 1292,
                "end_char": 1298,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ypg",
                "start_char": 1347,
                "end_char": 1350,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "51%",
                "start_char": 1361,
                "end_char": 1364,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Boluarte contro il 'raid' nella casa del ministro dell'Interno",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 01:40:56 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/americalatina/2025/03/04/boluarte-contro-il-raid-nella-casa-del-ministro-dellinterno_86c15b53-d4e9-4a1f-8b4d-f383d0ffcc9a.html",
        "subtitle": "Per la presidente 'oggi i golpe in Perù li fa la procura'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La presidente del Perù, Dina\nBoluarte, ha condannato la perquisizione effettuata dalla\nProcura generale del paese sudamericano nella casa del ministro\ndell'Interno, Juan José Santiváñez, nell'ambito di un'indagine\nche lo vede accusato per il presunto reato di abuso di autorità.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo riporta il sito del quotidiano El Comercio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Durante una riunione multisettoriale nel Centro operativo\ndelle Emergenze di Lima per coordinare le azioni contro le\npiogge e le inondazioni di quest'anno, Boluarte, con al suo\nfianco  Santiváñez, ha detto che \"possono perquisire la casa di\ntutti i ministri se vogliono, possono perquisire l'ufficio di\ntutti i ministri se così dispone la procura che sta giocando con\nquesta cattiva stampa per dare un golpe bianco\", ha detto la\npresidente aggiungendo che \"oggi i colpi di Stato non li fa più\nl'Esercito, ma la Procura generale.\"\n   \"A chi protegge La procura? Odebrecht (multinazionale\nbrasiliana coinvolta nella Lava Jato peruviana), il Club delle\ncostruzioni, l'OAS (altra multinazionale verde-oro)? A chi\nprotegge la procura che attenta contro ministri attenti e\nonesti?\", ha aggiunto Boluarte.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   In serata, dopo le dichiarazioni della presidente, la Procura\ndel Perù ha chiesto alla Corte suprema di proibire l'uscita dal\npaese andino al ministro degli interni, Juan José Santiváñez,\nnel quadro delle indagini per il presunto crimine di abuso di\nautorità che aveva portato alla perquisizione della sua\nabitazione questa mattina. Dal canto suo, l'ong Istituto Stampa\ne Società, l'Ypis, ha esortato Boluarte a rispettare\nl'indipendenza della stampa e della procura. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 65,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.133677,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "Boluarte against the 'raid' in the home of the Interior Minister",
        "en_content": "President of Peru, Dina\nBoluarte, has condemned the search carried out by\nAttorney General of the South American country in the Minister's house\nof the Interior, Juan José Santiváñez, under an investigation\nwho sees him accused for the alleged offence of authority.\n\n\nThis is the site of the daily El Comercio.\n\n\nDuring a multisectoral meeting in the Operating Center\nof the emergency of Lima to coordinate actions against\nrains and floods this year, Boluarte, with its\nside Santiváñez, said that \"they can search the house of\nall ministers if they want, they can search the office of\nall the ministers if so has the proxy that is playing with\nthis bad press to give a white coup,\" he said.\nPresident adding that \"today the strikes of state do not make them anymore\nThe Army, but the Attorney General. \"\n\"Who protects the prosecutor? Odebrecht (multinational)\nBrazilian involved in the Peruvian Lava Jato), the Club delle\nconstructions, the OAS (other green-gold multinational)? To whom\nprotects the prosecuting against attentive ministers and\nhonest?\", added Boluarte.\n\n\nIn the evening, after the statements of the President, the Prosecutor\nof Peru asked the Supreme Court to prohibit the exit from\nAndean country to the Interior Minister, Juan José Santiváñez,\nin the framework of investigations for alleged crime of abuse\nauthority which led to the search for his\nHouse this morning. For its part, the Institute of Press\nand Society, the Ypis, urged Boluarte to respect\nthe independence of the press and the prosecutor.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "For the president 'today the goals in Peru makes them prosecute'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peru",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Peru",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 17,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Dina\nBoluarte",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 32,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "South American",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 152,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Juan José Santiváñez",
                "start_char": 162,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "El Comercio",
                "start_char": 298,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lima",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 392,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this year",
                "start_char": 440,
                "end_char": 449,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Boluarte",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 459,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Santiváñez",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 714,
                "end_char": 719,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Army",
                "start_char": 770,
                "end_char": 774,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Odebrecht",
                "start_char": 834,
                "end_char": 843,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brazilian",
                "start_char": 860,
                "end_char": 869,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peruvian",
                "start_char": 886,
                "end_char": 894,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "OAS",
                "start_char": 941,
                "end_char": 944,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boluarte",
                "start_char": 1060,
                "end_char": 1068,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the evening",
                "start_char": 1075,
                "end_char": 1086,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Peru",
                "start_char": 1145,
                "end_char": 1149,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Supreme Court",
                "start_char": 1156,
                "end_char": 1173,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Andean",
                "start_char": 1200,
                "end_char": 1206,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interior",
                "start_char": 1222,
                "end_char": 1230,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Juan José Santiváñez",
                "start_char": 1241,
                "end_char": 1261,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 1367,
                "end_char": 1372,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "this morning",
                "start_char": 1373,
                "end_char": 1385,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Institute of Press",
                "start_char": 1401,
                "end_char": 1423,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Society",
                "start_char": 1428,
                "end_char": 1435,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ypis",
                "start_char": 1441,
                "end_char": 1445,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Boluarte",
                "start_char": 1453,
                "end_char": 1461,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Cina a Usa, adotteremo contromisure verso dazi aggiuntivi",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 02:32:46 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2025/03/04/cina-a-usa-adotteremo-contromisure-verso-dazi-aggiuntivi_c03acecd-0060-4976-934e-f80d06b403ac.html",
        "subtitle": "A poche ore dall'entrata in vigore di ulteriori tariffe del 10%",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Cina mette in guardia gli Stati\nUniti assicurando che adotterà tutte le necessarie contromisure\nse Washington deciderà di procedere con i nuovi dazi Usa\naggiuntivi del 10% sulle importazioni di tutti i beni made in\nChina.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   A poche ore dalla loro entrata in vigore, Pechino, ha\nriferito un portavoce del ministero del Commercio in una nota,\nha espresso \"il suo forte disappunto nei confronti di tutto\nquesto e in modo deciso vi si oppone. Allo stesso tempo,\nprenderemo le contromisure per tutelare in modo risoluto i\nnostri diritti e interessi e legittimi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 64,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.1467073,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "China to US, we will adopt countermeasures towards additional duties",
        "en_content": "China warns States\nUnited ensuring that it will take all necessary countermeasures\nif Washington decides to proceed with the new US duties\n10% additional on imports of all goods made in\nChina.\n\n\nA few hours after their entry into force, Beijing, has\nreported a spokesman of the Ministry of Commerce in a note,\nexpressed \"his strong disappointment towards everything\nthis and decisively opposes you. At the same time,\nWe will take countermeasures to protect in a resolute manner the\nour rights and legitimate interests.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "A few hours after the entry into force of additional charges of 10%",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "A few hours",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "10%",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10%",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "A few hours",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Commerce",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Cina a Usa, adotteremo contromisure verso dazi aggiuntivi",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 02:32:44 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/04/cina-a-usa-adotteremo-contromisure-verso-dazi-aggiuntivi_a16bf10c-67f5-42e2-94cb-133e76f54d5b.html",
        "subtitle": "A poche ore dall'entrata in vigore di ulteriori tariffe del 10%",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La Cina mette in guardia gli Stati\nUniti assicurando che adotterà tutte le necessarie contromisure\nse Washington deciderà di procedere con i nuovi dazi Usa\naggiuntivi del 10% sulle importazioni di tutti i beni made in\nChina.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   A poche ore dalla loro entrata in vigore, Pechino, ha\nriferito un portavoce del ministero del Commercio in una nota,\nha espresso \"il suo forte disappunto nei confronti di tutto\nquesto e in modo deciso vi si oppone. Allo stesso tempo,\nprenderemo le contromisure per tutelare in modo risoluto i\nnostri diritti e interessi e legittimi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 63,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.157108,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "China to US, we will adopt countermeasures towards additional duties",
        "en_content": "China warns States\nUnited ensuring that it will take all necessary countermeasures\nif Washington decides to proceed with the new US duties\n10% additional on imports of all goods made in\nChina.\n\n\nA few hours after their entry into force, Beijing, has\nreported a spokesman of the Ministry of Commerce in a note,\nexpressed \"his strong disappointment towards everything\nthis and decisively opposes you. At the same time,\nWe will take countermeasures to protect in a resolute manner the\nour rights and legitimate interests.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "A few hours after the entry into force of additional charges of 10%",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "A few hours",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "10%",
                "start_char": 64,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 86,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "10%",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "start_char": 186,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "A few hours",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Commerce",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Russia, noi contrari a peacekeeper europei in Ucraina",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 05:18:21 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/04/russia-noi-contrari-a-peacekeeper-europei-in-ucraina_407e9b71-3358-4184-a1a1-8755f4f1a980.html",
        "subtitle": "'Devono essere imparziali, l'UE è di parte'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Mikhail Ulyanov, rappresentante\npermanente della Russia presso le organizzazioni internazionali\na Vienna, ha affermato che La Russia è categoricamente contraria\nallo schieramento di peacekeeper europei in Ucraina. Lo riporta\nla Tass.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"L'idea di stazionare ipoteticamente peacekeeper europei in\nUcraina è, per usare un eufemismo, altamente discutibile almeno\nper due motivi. Innanzitutto l'UE è di parte mentre i\npeacekeeper devono essere imparziali. In secondo luogo, la\nRussia si oppone categoricamente\". Ulyanov ha anche sottolineato\nche \"i funzionari europei stanno mettendo il carro davanti ai\nbuoi\", quando discutono della questione \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 58,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.1740005,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "Russia, we against European peacekeepers in Ukraine",
        "en_content": "Mikhail Ulyanov, representative\npermanent Russia at international organizations\nin Vienna, said that Russia is categorically contrary\nEuropean peacekeepers in Ukraine. He's got it.\nTass.\n\n\n\"The idea of stating hypothetically European peacekeepers in\nUkraine is, to use an euphemism, highly questionable at least\nfor two reasons. First of all, the EU is part of the\npeacekeeper must be impartial. Secondly, the\nRussia opposes categorically.\" Ulyanov has also emphasized\nthat \"European officials are putting the wagon in front of the\nwhen they discuss the matter\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'They must be impartial, the EU is part'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 44,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 29,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Mikhail Ulyanov",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vienna",
                "start_char": 83,
                "end_char": 89,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 107,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 142,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 166,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 181,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 250,
                "end_char": 257,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "First",
                "start_char": 329,
                "end_char": 334,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Secondly",
                "start_char": 396,
                "end_char": 404,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 410,
                "end_char": 416,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ulyanov",
                "start_char": 441,
                "end_char": 448,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 475,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Vance, Zelensky accetterà colloqui di pace con la Russia",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 05:18:43 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2025/03/04/vance-zelensky-accettera-colloqui-di-pace-con-la-russia_81aec84b-64c3-40d1-83c3-b85891c088b7.html",
        "subtitle": "Vicepresidente Usa: 'Con Trump ha dimostrato un chiaro rifiuto'",
        "content": " Il vicepresidente degli Stati Uniti JD Vance si è detto fiducioso che il leader ucraino Volodymyr Zelensky accetterà alla fine i colloqui di pace con la Russia dopo il fallito incontro con Donald Trump di venerdì.     In un'intervista rilasciata a Fox News, Vance ha affermato che il presidente ucraino ha \"mostrato un chiaro rifiuto di impegnarsi nel processo di pace\" auspicato dal presidente americano. \"Penso che Zelensky non fosse ancora pronto - ha detto - e penso, francamente, che non lo sia ancora, ma penso che prima o poi ci arriveremo. Dobbiamo farlo.\" (ANSA-   \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 60,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.2235065,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "Vance, Zelensky will accept peace talks with Russia",
        "en_content": "US Vice President JD Vance was confident that Ukrainian leader Volodymyr Zelensky will eventually accept peace talks with Russia after the failed meeting with Donald Trump on Friday. In an interview with Fox News, Vance said that the Ukrainian president \"showed a clear refusal to engage in the peace process\" hoped by the American president. \"I think Zelensky wasn't ready yet - he said - and I think, frankly, he's not yet, but I think we'll eventually get there. We have to do this.\"\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "US Vice President: 'With Trump has shown a clear rejection'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Vance",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "JD Vance",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 81,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 128,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 159,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 175,
                "end_char": 181,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Fox News",
                "start_char": 204,
                "end_char": 212,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Vance",
                "start_char": 214,
                "end_char": 219,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 323,
                "end_char": 331,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zelensky",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 360,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Entrano in vigore dazi Usa su prodotti di Canada e Messico",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 06:21:23 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/04/entrano-in-vigore-dazi-usa-su-prodotti-di-canada-e-messico_0dd4e1e9-f4b2-4b1a-91fc-775025001d46.html",
        "subtitle": "Scaduto il termine stabilito da Trump senza un accordo",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Sono entrati in vigore i dazi degli\nUsa su prodotti canadesi e messicani: il termine imposto da\nDonald Trump è infatti scaduto senza trovare un accordo con il\nPaese nordamericano. Le merci canadesi saranno soggette a dazi\ndel 25%, con le risorse energetiche colpite da un tasso\ninferiore del 10 percento, mentre i prodotti messicani saranno\nsoggetti a un'imposta generale del 25 percento, in base agli\nordini esecutivi firmati da Trump. Il presidente Usa ha\ngiustificato l'aumento delle tariffe citando la mancanza di\nprogressi nella lotta al traffico di droga. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 57,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.2323742,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "Tariffs entered into force Use on Canada and Mexico products",
        "en_content": "The duties of the\nUse on Canadian and Mexican products: the term imposed by\nDonald Trump has expired without finding an agreement with the\nNorth American country. Canadian goods will be subject to duties\nof 25%, with energy resources affected by a rate\nless than 10%, while Mexican products will be\nsubject to a general tax of 25%, based on\nexecutive orders signed by Trump. US President has\nthe increase in rates by citing the lack of\nprogress in the fight against drug trafficking.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Expired the term established by Trump without an agreement",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexico",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 51,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 25,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 76,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "North American",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 171,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 207,
                "end_char": 210,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "less than 10%",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 266,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Mexican",
                "start_char": 274,
                "end_char": 281,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "25%",
                "start_char": 327,
                "end_char": 330,
                "label": "PERCENT",
                "info": "Percentage, including \"%\""
            },
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 375,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Portaerei Usa in Corea del Sud, sorella di Kim promette 'azioni'",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 03:13:15 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/asia/2025/03/04/portaerei-usa-in-corea-del-sud-sorella-di-kim-promette-azioni_80602562-0f4a-4467-9989-ec763501b7bb.html",
        "subtitle": "'Giustifica il rafforzamento delle forze nucleari del Nord.",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Kim Yo-jong, la potente sorella\ndel leader nordcoreano Kim Jong-un, ha avvertito di una\nimprecisata \"'azione intensificata\" contro l'arrivo in Corea del\nSud di domenica al porto di Busan della portaerei americana Uss\nCarl Vinson, sostenendo che la mossa degli Stati Uniti\ngiustifica il rafforzamento delle forze nucleari del Nord.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Kim, in un dispaccio dell'agenzia statale Kcna, ha affermato\nche gli Usa hanno schierato le loro risorse strategiche nella\npenisola coreana a un livello \"costante\", denunciando l'arrivo\ndella portaerei statunitense come espressione di Washington\ndella sua \"volontà più ostile e conflittuale\" contro il Nord.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"La politica ostile accompagnata da azioni nei confronti\ndella Corea del Nord perseguita dagli Stati Uniti al momento\noffre una giustificazione sufficiente per rafforzare\nindefinitamente la deterrenza di guerra nucleare\", ha aggiunto\nKim nel dispaccio.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Pyongyang sta anche \"pianificando di esaminare attentamente\nl'opzione di aumentare le azioni che minacciano la sicurezza del\nnemico a livello strategico\", ha avvertito Kim, sottolineando\nche se gli Stati Uniti continueranno a rinnovare i propri record\nnella conduzione di dimostrazioni militari contro la Corea del\nNord, il suo Paese sarà \"naturalmente costretto a rinnovare i\npropri record nell'esercizio della deterrenza strategica\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tL'ultimo arrivo della Uss Carl Vinson è il primo del suo genere\nin Corea del Sud dall'insediamento del presidente Donald Trump \ndallo scorso giugno, in una manifestazione di supporto a Seul\ncontro le intemperanze del Nord. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 61,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1741129219.2388904,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2025-03-05 00:00:19",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2025-03-04T23.00.19",
        "en_title": "USA carrier in South Korea, Kim's sister promises 'actions'",
        "en_content": "Kim Yo-jong, the powerful sister\nof North Korean leader Kim Jong-un, warned of a\nimprecisated \"enlarged action\" against the arrival in Korea\nSouth of Sunday at the port of Busan of the American carrier Uss\nCarl Vinson, claiming that the US move\njustify the strengthening of the North nuclear forces.\n\n\nKim, in a dispatch of the state agency Kcna, said\nthat the US has deployed their strategic resources in\nKorean peninsula at a \"constant\" level, denouncing arrival\nof the American carrier as an expression of Washington\nof his \"most hostile and conflicting will\" against the North.\n\n\n\"The hostile policy accompanied by actions against\nNorth Korea persecuted by the United States at the moment\noffers sufficient justification to strengthen\nindefinitely the deterrence of nuclear war\", he added\nKim in the dispatch.\n\n\nPyongyang is also \"planning to carefully examine\noption to increase actions that threaten safety of\nenemy at strategic level\", Kim warned, underlining\nthat if the United States will continue to renew its records\nconducting military demonstrations against Korea\nNorth, his country will be \"naturally forced to renew the\nown records in the exercise of strategic deterrence\".\n\n\nThe last arrival of Uss Carl Vinson is the first of his kind\nin South Korea from the settlement of President Donald Trump\nfrom last June, in a demonstration of support to Seoul\nagainst the North.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'It legitimizes the strengthening of the North nuclear forces.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "USA",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Korea",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kim",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 31,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "North",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kim Yo-jong",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "North Korean",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kim Jong-un",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Korea",
                "start_char": 135,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 146,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sunday",
                "start_char": 150,
                "end_char": 156,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Busan",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Uss",
                "start_char": 202,
                "end_char": 205,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "Carl Vinson",
                "start_char": 206,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 239,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "North",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kim",
                "start_char": 302,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kcna",
                "start_char": 341,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 361,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Korean",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 412,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 472,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Washington",
                "start_char": 509,
                "end_char": 519,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "North",
                "start_char": 575,
                "end_char": 580,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "North Korea",
                "start_char": 635,
                "end_char": 646,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 661,
                "end_char": 678,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kim",
                "start_char": 793,
                "end_char": 796,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pyongyang",
                "start_char": 816,
                "end_char": 825,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kim",
                "start_char": 943,
                "end_char": 946,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 975,
                "end_char": 992,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Korea",
                "start_char": 1071,
                "end_char": 1076,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Uss Carl Vinson",
                "start_char": 1211,
                "end_char": 1226,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 1234,
                "end_char": 1239,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "South Korea",
                "start_char": 1255,
                "end_char": 1266,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Trump",
                "start_char": 1300,
                "end_char": 1312,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "last June",
                "start_char": 1318,
                "end_char": 1327,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Seoul",
                "start_char": 1362,
                "end_char": 1367,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "North",
                "start_char": 1380,
                "end_char": 1385,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Rubio, 'Trump vuole portare Mosca a tavolo trattative'",
        "date_raw": "Tue, 4 Mar 2025 07:35:30 +0100",
        "date": "2025-03-04",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2025/03/04/rubio-trump-vuole-portare-mosca-a-tavolo-trattative_ac6417d9-4251-4f25-81e6-55d1b571270b.html",
        "subtitle": "Segretario di Stato: 'Vogliamo esplorare se la pace è possibile'",
