[
    {
        "title": "Ministra Bernini in Algeria per la cooperazione scientifica",
        "date_raw": "Mon, 13 May 2024 14:51:15 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-13",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/05/13/ministra-bernini-in-algeria-per-la-cooperazione-scientifica_0476f384-4140-48d7-956a-96376f0601e5.html",
        "subtitle": "Sono già 30 le collaborazioni attive con le università algerine",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il ministro dell'Università e della\nRicerca, Anna Maria Bernini, sarà domani -  14 maggio - in\nAlgeria dove incontrerà l'omologo, Kamel Baddari. Per il\nministro Bernini, è la terza missione in Africa nell'ambito del\nPiano Mattei, dopo Tunisia e Libia dove si è recata con il\npresidente del Consiglio, Giorgia Meloni.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La cooperazione scientifica fra Italia e Algeria ha radici\nprofonde. Il primo accordo intergovernativo di cooperazione nel\nsettore scientifico e tecnologico fra i due Paesi risale,\ninfatti, al 1975.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Tra il 2017  e il 2023 sono stati sottoscritte 30\ncollaborazioni, che interessano 18 Università, e 79 accordi\ninteruniversitari.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La presenza di studenti algerini nel nostro Paese è\ncostantemente aumentata nel tempo: dai 142 del 2017-18 ai 351\ndel 2022-23. Dati che qualificano l'Algeria - fa sapere il\nministero dell'Università - come il 10mo Paese africano per\nstudenti iscritti a corsi di laurea in Italia e il quarto  (dopo\nEgitto, Etiopia e Tunisia) per studenti iscritti ad un percorso\ndi dottorato.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Sono 18, invece, i progetti finanziati in Algeria dalle\nuniversità italiane sono 18, tra cui prevalgono quelli di\nricerca locale in agricoltura e gestione delle risorse idriche.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tUn altro focus prevalente è quello delle energie rinnovabili.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605249.3858478,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:49",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.49",
        "en_title": "Bernini Minister for Scientific Cooperation in Algeria",
        "en_content": "The Minister of the University and the\nSearch, Anna Maria Bernini, will be tomorrow - 14 May - in\nAlgeria where he will meet the homologue, Kamel Baddari. For the\nMinister Bernini, is the third mission in Africa within the framework of\nPiano Mattei, after Tunisia and Libya where he went with\nPresident of the Council, Giorgia Meloni.\n\n\nScientific cooperation between Italy and Algeria has roots\ndeep. The first intergovernmental cooperation agreement in\nscientific and technological sector between the two countries dates back,\nIn fact, 1975.\n\n\nBetween 2017 and 2023 30 were signed\ncollaborations, affecting 18 universities, and 79 agreements\nInteruniversity.\n\n\nThe presence of Algerian students in our country is\nconstantly increased over time: from 142 of 2017-18 to 351\n2022-23. Data qualifying for Algeria - lets you know\nUniversity Ministry - as the 10th African Country for\nstudents enrolled in undergraduate courses in Italy and the fourth (after\nEgypt, Ethiopia and Tunisia) for students enrolled in a course\nPhD.\n\n\nThere are 18 projects financed by Algeria\nItalian universities are 18, including those of\nlocal research in agriculture and water resources management.\n\n\nAnother prevalent focus is that of renewable energies.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "There are already 30 active collaborations with Algerian universities",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Bernini Minister",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Scientific Cooperation",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "30",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algerian",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 56,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "University",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Anna Maria Bernini",
                "start_char": 47,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "tomorrow - 14",
                "start_char": 75,
                "end_char": 88,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 98,
                "end_char": 105,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kamel Baddari",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bernini",
                "start_char": 172,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "third",
                "start_char": 188,
                "end_char": 193,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Africa",
                "start_char": 205,
                "end_char": 211,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Piano Mattei",
                "start_char": 236,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tunisia",
                "start_char": 256,
                "end_char": 263,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libya",
                "start_char": 268,
                "end_char": 273,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Council",
                "start_char": 310,
                "end_char": 317,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Giorgia Meloni",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 368,
                "end_char": 373,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 385,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 406,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 503,
                "end_char": 506,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "1975",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 542,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Between 2017 and 2023 30",
                "start_char": 546,
                "end_char": 570,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 609,
                "end_char": 611,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "79",
                "start_char": 630,
                "end_char": 632,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Interuniversity",
                "start_char": 644,
                "end_char": 659,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Algerian",
                "start_char": 679,
                "end_char": 687,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "142",
                "start_char": 752,
                "end_char": 755,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2017-18",
                "start_char": 759,
                "end_char": 766,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "351",
                "start_char": 770,
                "end_char": 773,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "2022-23",
                "start_char": 774,
                "end_char": 781,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 803,
                "end_char": 810,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "University Ministry",
                "start_char": 827,
                "end_char": 846,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "10th",
                "start_char": 856,
                "end_char": 860,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "African Country",
                "start_char": 861,
                "end_char": 876,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 927,
                "end_char": 932,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "fourth",
                "start_char": 941,
                "end_char": 947,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 955,
                "end_char": 960,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ethiopia",
                "start_char": 962,
                "end_char": 970,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tunisia",
                "start_char": 975,
                "end_char": 982,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 1035,
                "end_char": 1037,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Algeria",
                "start_char": 1059,
                "end_char": 1066,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italian",
                "start_char": 1067,
                "end_char": 1074,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "18",
                "start_char": 1092,
                "end_char": 1094,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Blinken, a Gaza uccisi più civili che terroristi",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 15:38:57 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/nordamerica/2024/05/12/blinken-a-gaza-uccisi-piu-civili-che-terroristi_7f936f02-2340-49d9-90f0-71499157855a.html",
        "subtitle": "'C'è un divario tra le intenzioni di Israele e i risultati'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            A Gaza sono stati uccisi più\ncivili che terroristi e c'è un divario fra le intenzioni di\nIsraele e i risultati in termini di protezione dei civili. Lo ha\ndetto il segretario di Stato Usa Antony Blinken in un'intervista\na Cbs. Nel rapporto del Dipartimento di Stato presentato al\nCongresso nei giorni scorsi si afferma che Israele ha \"la\nconoscenza e gli strumenti per attuare le pratiche migliori per\nridurre i danni civili nelle sue operazioni militari\". Tuttavia,\ni \"risultati sul terreno, incluso l'elevato numero di vittime\ncivili, sollevano sostanziali dubbi sul fatto che l'Idf li abbia\nusati in modo efficace in tutti i casi\". \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 51,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.3293862,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Blinken, in Gaza killed more civilian than terrorists",
        "en_content": "More were killed in Gaza\nand there is a gap between the intentions of\nIsrael and civilian protection results. He did.\nsaid US Secretary of State Antony Blinken in an interview\nto Cbs. In the State Department report submitted to\nCongress recently states that Israel has \"the\nknowledge and tools to implement best practices for\nreduce civilian damage in its military operations.\" However,\nthe \"results on the ground, including the high number of victims\nCivilians, raise substantial doubts about the fact that Idf has them\nused effectively in all cases.\"\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'There is a gap between the intentions of Israel and the results'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Blinken",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 16,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 70,
                "end_char": 76,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 125,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "State",
                "start_char": 139,
                "end_char": 144,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Antony Blinken",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cbs",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 182,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "State Department",
                "start_char": 191,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Congress",
                "start_char": 228,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 258,
                "end_char": 264,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Civilians",
                "start_char": 452,
                "end_char": 461,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 508,
                "end_char": 511,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Reproduction reserved © Copyright",
                "start_char": 558,
                "end_char": 591,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Erdogan, 'metodi genocidi Netanyahu farebbero invidia a Hitler'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 15:38:50 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/12/erdogan-metodi-genocidi-netanyahu-farebbero-invidia-a-hitler_6d432710-da68-45c5-bff4-6d01479de3af.html",
        "subtitle": "Leader turco torna a paragonare il premier israeliano al Furher",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Il premier israeliano, Benyamin\nNetanyahu, \"con i suoi metodi genocidi ha raggiunto un livello\ntale da fare ingelosire Hitler\": lo ha dichiarato il presidente\nturco, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, in un'intervista al quotidiano\ngreco \"Kathimerini\" ripresa dalla stampa turca. Intervista\nconcessa, alla vigilia della visita ad Ankara del primo ministro\ngreco, Kyriakos Mitsotakis.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Dall'inizio della guerra a Gaza, il leader turco ha più volte\nparagonato il premier israeliano a Hitler. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 50,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.34009,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Erdogan, Netanyahu genocidal methods would envy Hitler.",
        "en_content": "Israeli premier, Benyamin\nNetanyahu, \"with its genocidal methods has reached a level\nto make Hitler jealous\": the President\nTurkish, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, in an interview with the daily newspaper\nGreek \"Kathimerini\" resumed from the Turkish press. Interview\non the eve of the visit to Ankara of the Prime Minister\nGreek, Kyriakos Mitsotakis.\n\n\nSince the beginning of the war in Gaza, the Turkish leader has repeatedly\ncompared the Israeli premier to Hitler.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Turkish leader returns to compare Israeli premier to the Furher",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Erdogan",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hitler",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 54,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Furher",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benyamin\nNetanyahu",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 35,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hitler",
                "start_char": 93,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 124,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Recep Tayyip Erdogan",
                "start_char": 133,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 180,
                "end_char": 185,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greek",
                "start_char": 196,
                "end_char": 201,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kathimerini",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 233,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ankara",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 291,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greek",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kyriakos Mitsotakis",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 378,
                "end_char": 382,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Turkish",
                "start_char": 388,
                "end_char": 395,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 438,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hitler",
                "start_char": 450,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Idf, 'operazioni in corso a Jabalya, Rafah e Zeitun'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 15:21:55 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/12/idf-operazioni-in-corso-a-jabalya-rafah-e-zeitun_c1287198-c11c-4a4e-9620-0b1985fda0ad.html",
        "subtitle": "'In tutto colpiti e distrutti oltre 150 obiettivi terroristici'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Idf ha confermato sia l'avvio\ndell'operazione contro Hamas a Jabalya nel nord della Striscia\nsia la prosecuzione di quella già corso nela parte orientale di\nRafah, nel sud a confine con l'Egitto. Lo ha detto il portavoce\nmilitare spiegando che a Jabalya - dopo gli appelli\nall'evacuazione \"temporanea\" della popolazione della zona -\nl'azione è stata avviata la scorsa notte sulla base di\ninformazioni di intelligence, \"un'operazione\" volta a\ncontrastare i tentativi di Hamas di \"rimettere in piedi la sua\nstruttura terroristica e operativa\". Prima dell'azione, raid\naerei \"hanno colpito circa 30 obiettivi terroristici nell'area\neliminando numerosi operativi della fazione armata\". Lo stesso a\nRafah dove -secondo la stessa fonte -  sono stati localizzati e\nsmantellati \"una serie di imbocchi di tunnel\". \"In uno di questi\n- ha proseguito - sono stati uccisi 10 uomini armati di Hamas\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Prosegue l'azione anche a Zeitun, sempre nel nord di Gaza.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tComplessivamente nelle ultime 24 ore - ha detto il portavoce -\nsono \"stati colpiti e distrutti oltre 150 obiettivi\" delle\nfazioni armate in tutta la Striscia. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 53,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.3879633,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Idf, 'operations in progress in Jabalya, Rafah and Zeitun'",
        "en_content": "Idf confirmed both the start\nof the operation against Hamas in Jabalya in the north of the Strip\nboth the continuation of that already course in the eastern part of\nRafah, in the south bordering Egypt. The spokesman said that\nmilitary explaining that in Jabalya - after the appeals\nthe \"temporaneous\" evacuation of the population of the area -\nthe action was started last night on the basis of\nintelligence information, \"an operation\" time to\ncounter Hamas' attempts to \"remit his\nterrorist and operational structure\". Before the action, raid\nplanes \"has hit about 30 terrorist targets in the area\neliminating numerous armed faction operatives.\" The same to\nRafah where -according to the same source - were located and\ndismantled a series of tunnels. \"In one of these\n- he continued - 10 armed men of Hamas were killed.\n\n\nThe action continues in Zeitun, also in the north of Gaza.\n\n\nOverall in the last 24 hours - the spokesperson said -\nover 150 goals have been hit and destroyed\narmed factions throughout the Strip.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'In all affected and destroyed over 150 terrorist objectives'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jabalya",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Zeitun",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "150",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Idf",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Jabalya",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 70,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 96,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 165,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 195,
                "end_char": 200,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Jabalya",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 261,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "last night",
                "start_char": 367,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 451,
                "end_char": 456,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "about 30",
                "start_char": 559,
                "end_char": 567,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 658,
                "end_char": 663,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 755,
                "end_char": 758,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "10",
                "start_char": 785,
                "end_char": 787,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 801,
                "end_char": 806,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Zeitun",
                "start_char": 846,
                "end_char": 852,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 875,
                "end_char": 879,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the last 24 hours",
                "start_char": 894,
                "end_char": 911,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "over 150",
                "start_char": 938,
                "end_char": 946,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Strip",
                "start_char": 1011,
                "end_char": 1016,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Macedonia Nord, si insedia la presidente Siljanovska Davkova",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 15:21:48 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/12/macedonia-nord-si-insedia-la-presidente-siljanovska-davkova_22df5e9f-91cb-4793-a993-937a643fa63b.html",
        "subtitle": "Prima donna capo di Stato nel Paese ex jugoslavo",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            La presidente eletta macedone, la\nconservatrice Gordana Siljanovska Davkova, prima donna capo di\nstato nel Paese ex jugoslavo, ha prestato oggi giuramento\nsolenne nel corso di una cerimonia in parlamento a Skopje.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLeggendo la formula di giuramento ha usato tuttavia il termine\n'Macedonia' e non 'Repubblica della Macedonia del Nord', quello\nnuovo inserito in costituzione dopo l'accordo degli anni scorsi\nche pose fine a una disputa quasi trentennale con la Grecia. E\nper questo è stata ripresa dal presidente del parlamento. \n   Sostenuta dal partito conservatore Vmro-Dpmne, principale\nforza di opposizione, Siljanovska Davkova ha battuto largamente\nil presidente uscente, il socialdemocratico Stevo Pendarovski,\nnel ballottaggio dell'8 maggio scorso. Critica degli accordi con\nGrecia e Bulgaria, che hanno sbloccato negli ultimi anni il\ncammino di integrazione euroatlantica del Paese balcanico, la\nneopresidente è ferma in particolare nella volontà di tornare al\nvecchio nome di 'Macedonia', non escludendo un referendum. Nel\nsuo intervento davanti ai deputati ha fatto riferimento\nall'importante ruolo delle donne nella vita politica. Dopo la\ncerimonia in parlamento, la nuova presidente si è recata alla\nresidenza del capo dello stato per il passaggio delle consegne\ncon Pendarovski. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 52,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.3934996,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "North Macedonia, President Siljanovska Davkova settled",
        "en_content": "The elected Macedonian President, the\nconservative Gordana Siljanovska Davkova, first woman head of\nstate in the former Yugoslavia, he lent oath today\nsolemn during a ceremony in parliament in Skopje.\n\n\nReading the oath formula however used the term\n'Macedonia' and not 'Republic of North Macedonia',\nnew entered into constitution after the agreement of recent years\nwhich put an end to an almost thirty-year dispute with Greece. E\nThat is why it was resumed by the President of Parliament.\nSupported by the Conservative Party Vmro-Dpmne, main\nopposition force, Siljanovska Davkova beaten widely\nthe outgoing president, the Social-Democrat Stevo Pendarovski,\non the 8th of May. Criticism of agreements with\nGreece and Bulgaria, which have unlocked in recent years the\nEuropean integration path of the Balkan Country, the\nnew president is firm in particular in the will to return to\nold name of 'Macedonia', not excluding a referendum. In\nMr President, ladies and gentlemen, I would like to congratulate the rapporteur on his report.\nthe important role of women in political life. After the\nceremony in parliament, the new president went to\nresidence of the head of state for the passage of deliveries\nwith Pendarovski.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "First woman head of state in the former Yugoslav country",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "North Macedonia",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Siljanovska Davkova",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 46,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "First",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yugoslav",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Macedonian",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gordana Siljanovska Davkova",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 80,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Yugoslavia",
                "start_char": 120,
                "end_char": 130,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 150,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Skopje",
                "start_char": 193,
                "end_char": 199,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Macedonia",
                "start_char": 251,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "'Republic of North Macedonia'",
                "start_char": 270,
                "end_char": 299,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent years",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 366,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "thirty-year",
                "start_char": 397,
                "end_char": 408,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greece",
                "start_char": 422,
                "end_char": 428,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 479,
                "end_char": 489,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the Conservative Party Vmro-Dpmne",
                "start_char": 504,
                "end_char": 537,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Siljanovska Davkova",
                "start_char": 562,
                "end_char": 581,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Democrat",
                "start_char": 631,
                "end_char": 639,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Stevo Pendarovski",
                "start_char": 640,
                "end_char": 657,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 8th of May",
                "start_char": 662,
                "end_char": 676,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Greece",
                "start_char": 707,
                "end_char": 713,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bulgaria",
                "start_char": 718,
                "end_char": 726,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "recent years",
                "start_char": 751,
                "end_char": 763,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 768,
                "end_char": 776,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Balkan Country",
                "start_char": 797,
                "end_char": 815,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Macedonia",
                "start_char": 895,
                "end_char": 904,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pendarovski",
                "start_char": 1206,
                "end_char": 1217,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Tajani, nessun pericolo di attacchi russi alla Nato",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 15:41:46 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/12/tajani-nessun-pericolo-di-attacchi-russi-alla-nato_0d56bba5-ee75-462e-9e6e-d232c35b78c0.html",
        "subtitle": "'Non sottovalutare ma neanche drammatizzare situazione Kharkiv'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Non sottovaluterei ma non\ndrammatizzerei la situazione, bisogna seguire con la massima\nattenzione le mosse di Mosca, non ci sono pericoli di attacchi\nalla Nato, lo escludo, né ci sono intenzioni da parte\ndell'Italia, e devo dire dell'Ue e della Nato di mandare truppe\na combattere in Ucraina, non se ne è mai parlato in una riunione\nUe o della Nato e l'Italia non invierà neanche un soldato a\ncombattere in Ucraina\". Lo ha detto il ministro degli Esteri\nAntonio Tajani a In Mezz'ora su Rai3, commentando la nuova\noffensiva russa nel Kharkiv. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 49,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.4418924,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Tajani, no danger of Russian attacks on NATO",
        "en_content": "\"I would not underestimate but not\nI should like to thank the rapporteur for his work.\nattention the moves of Moscow, there are no dangers of attacks\nto NATO, I exclude it, nor are there intentions\nof Italy, and I must say of the EU and NATO to send troops\nto fight in Ukraine, he never talked about it at a meeting\nEU or NATO and Italy will not send a soldier to\nfight in Ukraine\". The Foreign Minister said so.\nAntonio Tajani in Mezz'ora on Rai3, commenting on the new\nRussian offensive in Kharkiv.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "'Do not underestimate but not even dramatize Kharkiv situation'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tajani",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 116,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 157,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 206,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 230,
                "end_char": 232,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 237,
                "end_char": 241,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 269,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 316,
                "end_char": 318,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 322,
                "end_char": 326,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 336,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 373,
                "end_char": 380,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Antonio Tajani",
                "start_char": 413,
                "end_char": 427,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kharkiv",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 499,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Mosca, 'attacco a Belgorod con armi fornite dalla Nato'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 16:25:30 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/europa/2024/05/12/mosca-attacco-a-belgorod-con-armi-fornite-dalla-nato_7c3caca2-6936-4395-a23a-16b06a4fdffe.html",
        "subtitle": "Lo denuncia la missione russa all'Osce",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Il brutale attacco terroristico di\noggi da parte del regime di Kiev contro i quartieri pacifici di\nBelgorod ha causato decine di vittime. È stato effettuato con\nl'uso di armi fornite dai Paesi della Nato\". Lo denuncia la\nmissione della Russia presso l'Osce in un messaggio sul suo\ncanale Telegram rilanciato dalla Tass. \"Esortiamo la leadership\ndell'Osce, in primo luogo l'attuale Presidenza di Malta, a\ndenunciare l'atto criminale il più duramente possibile. È\ninaccettabile ignorare ostentatamente le vittime civili tra i\nrussi, sia a Belgorod, nel Donbass o altrove\", ha aggiunto.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 46,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.4524236,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Moscow, 'attack to Belgorod with weapons provided by NATO'",
        "en_content": "\"The brutal terrorist attack of\ntoday by the Kiev regime against peaceful neighborhoods of\nBelgorod has caused dozens of victims. It was carried out with\nthe use of weapons provided by NATO countries.\" The complaint\nmission of Russia to the Osce in a message on its\nTelegram channel relaunched by the Tass. \"We exhort leadership\nof the OSCE, first of all the current Presidency of Malta,\ndenounce the criminal act as hard as possible. It is\nunacceptable to disregard civilian casualties among\nRussians, both in Belgorod, in Donbass or elsewhere,\" he added.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "He denounces the Russian mission to the Osce",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 6,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Osce",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 44,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 32,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kiev",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 49,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 99,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "dozens",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "NATO",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 189,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 227,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Osce",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 245,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram",
                "start_char": 266,
                "end_char": 274,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tass",
                "start_char": 301,
                "end_char": 305,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "OSCE",
                "start_char": 336,
                "end_char": 340,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 347,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Malta",
                "start_char": 381,
                "end_char": 386,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russians",
                "start_char": 493,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgorod",
                "start_char": 511,
                "end_char": 519,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donbass",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 531,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Egitto con il Sud Africa in azione contro Israele all'Aia",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 16:08:02 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/12/egitto-con-il-sud-africa-in-azione-contro-israele-allaia_2fd841f8-5550-4ee2-8c21-fc6940a99116.html",
        "subtitle": "La stessa cosa ha fatto il Consiglio presidenziale libico",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'Egitto ha annunciato, in una\ndichiarazione del Ministero degli Esteri, la sua intenzione di\nintervenire ufficialmente a sostegno dell'azione del Sud Africa\ncontro Israele dinanzi alla Corte Internazionale di Giustizia\nper esaminare le sue presunte violazioni della Convenzione sulla\nprevenzione e la repressione del crimine di genocidio nella\nStriscia di Gaza.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t    Altrettanto ha fatto il Consiglio presidenziale libico,\nsecondo l'ambasciata libica nei Paesi Bassi. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 48,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.4583588,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Egypt with South Africa in action against Israel at the Hague",
        "en_content": "Egypt has announced, in one\ndeclaration by the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, its intention\nofficially intervene in support of South Africa's action\nagainst Israel before the International Court of Justice\nto examine its alleged violations of the Convention on\nprevention and repression of the crime of genocide in\nGaza Strip.\n\n\nHe also made the Libyan presidential council,\naccording to the Libyan embassy in the Netherlands.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The same thing did the Libyan presidential council",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Africa",
                "start_char": 11,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 42,
                "end_char": 48,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hague",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "one",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Ministry of Foreign Affairs",
                "start_char": 43,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "South Africa's",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 161,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the International Court of Justice",
                "start_char": 169,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Convention",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 255,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 313,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 344,
                "end_char": 350,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 396,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netherlands",
                "start_char": 412,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas, frasi di Biden su ostaggi sono ostacolo a negoziati",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 17:24:14 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mediooriente/2024/05/12/hamas-frasi-di-biden-su-ostaggi-sono-ostacolo-a-negoziati_6099bd93-cfc3-4e0b-b4b1-5062fccf8f0f.html",
        "subtitle": "Il presidente aveva detto: 'Cessate fuoco subito se li libera'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            Hamas ha affermato che le frasi\npresidente Usa Joe Biden sugli ostaggi sono una \"battuta di\narresto\" per i negoziati in corso. Ieri il capo della Casa\nBianca aveva affermato che un cessate il fuoco ci sarebbe\n\"domani\" se Hamas liberasse gli ostaggi.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Condanniamo questa posizione del presidente degli Stati\nUniti, la consideriamo una battuta d'arresto rispetto ai\nrisultati dell'ultimo round di negoziati, che avevano portato al\nconsenso del movimento sulla proposta avanzata dai mediatori\",\nha dichiarato Hamas in una nota.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Hamas ha inoltre accusato il premier israeliano Benyamin\nNetanyahu di avere rovinato le chance di un accordo con\nl'attacco a Rafah. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 45,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.4645696,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Hamas, Biden phrases on hostages are obstacle to negotiations",
        "en_content": "Hamas said that the phrases\nUS President Joe Biden on the hostages are a \"battle of\narrest\" for the ongoing negotiations. Yesterday the head of the House\nBianca said that a ceasefire would be there\n\"Tomorrow\" if Hamas freed the hostages.\n\n\n\"We condemn this position of the President of the States\nUnited States, we consider it a setback compared to\nresults of the last round of negotiations, which led to\nconsent of the movement on the proposal advanced by the mediators\",\nstated Hamas in a note.\n\n\nHamas also accused Israeli PM Benyamin\nNetanyahu to have ruined the chances of a deal with\nthe attack on Rafah.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "The president said: 'Cessate fire immediately if he frees them'",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Biden",
                "start_char": 7,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Cessate",
                "start_char": 21,
                "end_char": 28,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 30,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Joe Biden",
                "start_char": 41,
                "end_char": 50,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yesterday",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 131,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "House",
                "start_char": 148,
                "end_char": 153,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Bianca",
                "start_char": 154,
                "end_char": 160,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tomorrow",
                "start_char": 199,
                "end_char": 207,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 212,
                "end_char": 217,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "States",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 296,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "United States",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 310,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 480,
                "end_char": 485,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 499,
                "end_char": 504,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 525,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benyamin",
                "start_char": 529,
                "end_char": 537,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 538,
                "end_char": 547,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafah",
                "start_char": 604,
                "end_char": 609,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "A Tripoli conferenza sulla protezione dei beni culturali",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 17:25:36 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/05/12/a-tripoli-conferenza-sulla-protezione-dei-beni-culturali_4fa1cdf9-8838-4086-ae57-b10e2f6734b5.html",
        "subtitle": "Amb. Ue Orlando, rafforzerà unità nazionale e riconciliazione",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            L'ambasciatore dell'Ue in Libia\nNicola Orlando ha aperto oggi a Tripoli una conferenza sulla\nprotezione del patrimonio culturale libico, con la\npartecipazione di 20 esperti provenienti da 5 Paesi europei,\nmissioni archeologiche e rappresentanti delle forze dell'ordine.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tLo fa sapere lo stesso Orlando su X.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"Il patrimonio culturale libico è straordinario - ha detto\nl'ambasciatore -. Appartiene a tutti i libici e all'umanità.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\tRappresenta le nostre ricche e comuni radici mediterranee. Il\nsuo potenziale economico e occupazionale è notevole. Per questo\ndobbiamo tutelarlo insieme da saccheggi, traffici e atti\nvandalici\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   \"L'Unione europea e i suoi Stati membri sono orgogliosi della\nloro partnership per proteggere e preservare il patrimonio\nculturale libico, contribuendo a rafforzare l'unità nazionale e\nla riconciliazione\".\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   L'iniziativa è stata promossa con il Dipartimento delle\nAntichità, la polizia turistica e il ministero degli Esteri\nlibico. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 44,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.4701865,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "A Tripoli conference on the protection of cultural heritage",
        "en_content": "EU Ambassador to Libya\nNicola Orlando today opened a conference on Tripoli\nprotection of Libyan cultural heritage, with\nparticipation of 20 experts from 5 European countries,\nArchaeological missions and representatives of law enforcement.\n\n\nThat's what Orlando said about X.\n\n\n\"The Libyan cultural heritage is extraordinary - he said\nthe ambassador -. It belongs to all Libyans and to humanity.\n\n\nIt represents our rich and common Mediterranean roots. The\nits economic and employment potential is remarkable. That's why\nwe must protect it together from looting, traffic and acts\nvandalism.\"\n\n\n\"The European Union and its Member States are proud of the\ntheir partnership to protect and preserve the heritage\nLibyan culture, helping to strengthen national unity and\nreconciliation.\"\n\n\nThe initiative was promoted with the Department of the\nAntiquities, tourist police and foreign ministry\nLibyan.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Amb. Ue Orlando, will strengthen national unity and reconciliation",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Tripoli",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ue Orlando",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Libya",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nicola Orlando",
                "start_char": 23,
                "end_char": 37,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tripoli",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 74,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 89,
                "end_char": 95,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "20",
                "start_char": 137,
                "end_char": 139,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "5",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 155,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orlando",
                "start_char": 253,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyans",
                "start_char": 370,
                "end_char": 377,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Mediterranean",
                "start_char": 431,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "The European Union",
                "start_char": 594,
                "end_char": 612,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 707,
                "end_char": 713,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Department of the\nAntiquities",
                "start_char": 816,
                "end_char": 849,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Libyan",
                "start_char": 887,
                "end_char": 893,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Il principe Harry e Meghan in Nigeria, 'un tour quasi reale'",
        "date_raw": "Sun, 12 May 2024 18:05:15 +0200",
        "date": "2024-05-12",
        "url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/mondo_rss.xml",
        "news_url": "https://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/mondo/africa/2024/05/12/il-principe-harry-e-meghan-in-nigeria-un-tour-quasi-reale_7101f289-0c24-4512-b390-5fd70016cb5e.html",
        "subtitle": "Daily Mail, 'vestita di giallo onora sue radici africane'",
        "content": "\n                                                \n            \"Meghan porta il sole!\". E' il titolo\nscelto dal quotidiano britannico DailyMail commentando il tour\n\"quasi reale\" di tre giorni in Nigeria della duchessa di Sussex,\ninsieme al marito Harry. La moglie americana del principe\nribelle ha visitato oggi la casa del governatore dello stato di\nLagos \"vestita con un abito giallo, onorando le sue radici\nnigeriane e abbandonando i colori neutri per toni vivaci nel il\nterzo giorno del suo viaggio\", sottolinea il media britannico.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Il duca di Sussex è arrivato con la moglie venerdì nella\ncapitale della Nigeria, Abuja, dove ha assistito ad un evento\nscolastico sulla salute mentale. Il viaggio in Nigeria ha come\nobiettivo la promozione degli Invictus Games, le competizioni\nsportive per i veterani militari feriti. Harry ha quindi avuto\nmodo di incontrare alcuni soldati nigeriani feriti nel\nnord-ovest del Paese nel corso delle incursioni dei Boko Haram.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Nel terzo e ultimo giorno della visita, i due hanno preso\nparte a un evento di basket con la Giants of Africa Foundation\ndi Lagos, un'organizzazione che aiuta i giovani attraverso\nl'impegno nello sport. Il principe si è anche esercitato a\ndribblare un pallone da basket con i bambini durante l'evento\nespositivo della fondazione, gestita dall'ex giocatore della Nba\nMasai Ujiri. \"Il potere dello sport può cambiare la vita, unisce\nle persone e crea comunità e non ci sono barriere, questa è la\ncosa più importante\", ha affermato il principe.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   La visita si conclude con una partita di polo per raccogliere\nfondi per Nigeria Unconquered e con una cena di gala. Poi il\npassaggio a Londra e il rientro in California.\n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t   Harry, un ex capitano dell'esercito che ha pilotato\nelicotteri in Afghanistan, ha fondato gli Invictus Games dieci\nanni fa per aiutare a portare i veterani feriti agli eventi\nsportivi ed aiutarli nel loro recupero. \n                                    \n                                       \n\t\t\t\t          \n                                \n\nRiproduzione riservata © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "ranked": 42,
        "placed": "Esteri",
        "epoch": 1715605252.5262597,
        "language": "IT",
        "source": "ANSA",
        "local_time": "2024-05-13 15:00:52",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-13T15.00.52",
        "en_title": "Prince Harry and Meghan in Nigeria, 'an almost real tour'",
        "en_content": "\"Meghan brings the sun!\" It's the title\nchosen by the British daily DailyMail commenting on the tour\n\"almost\" of three days in Nigeria of the Duchess of Sussex,\nwith her husband Harry. The American wife of the prince\nrebel visited today the house of the governor of the state of\nLagos \"dressed with a yellow dress, honoring its roots\nnigeriane and abandoning neutral colors for bright tones in the\nThe third day of his journey,\" the British average emphasised.\n\n\nThe Duke of Sussex arrived with his wife Friday in\ncapital of Nigeria, Abuja, where he witnessed an event\nschool on mental health. Your trip to Nigeria has how\nthe promotion of Invictus Games, competitions\nsports for wounded military veterans. Harry then had\nway to meet some Nigerian soldiers injured in\nNorthwest of the country during the raids of the Boko Haram.\n\n\nIn the third and last day of the visit, the two took\npart of a basketball event with the Giants of Africa Foundation\nby Lagos, an organization that helps young people through\nthe commitment in sport. The prince also practiced\ndribblare a basketball with children during the event\nFoundation exhibition, managed by former Nba player\nMasai Ujiri. \"The power of sport can change life, unites\npeople and create communities and there are no barriers, this is\nmore importantly,\" the prince said.\n\n\nThe visit ends with a polo match to collect\nfunds for Nigeria Unconquered and with a gala dinner. Then the\nmoving to London and returning to California.\n\n\nHarry, a former army captain who flew\nhelicopters in Afghanistan, founded the Invictus Games ten\nyears ago to help bring injured veterans to events\nsportsmen and help them in their recovery.\n\n\n\n\n\nReproduction reserved © Copyright ANSA\n\n\n\n",
        "en_subtitle": "Daily Mail, yellow dress honors its African roots",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Prince Harry",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 12,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Meghan",
                "start_char": 17,
                "end_char": 23,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nigeria",
                "start_char": 27,
                "end_char": 34,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Daily Mail",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "African",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 43,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Meghan",
                "start_char": 1,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 54,
                "end_char": 61,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "daily",
                "start_char": 62,
                "end_char": 67,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "DailyMail",
                "start_char": 68,
                "end_char": 77,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three days",
                "start_char": 113,
                "end_char": 123,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nigeria",
                "start_char": 127,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sussex",
                "start_char": 153,
                "end_char": 159,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Harry",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "American",
                "start_char": 189,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 236,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lagos",
                "start_char": 279,
                "end_char": 284,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "The third day",
                "start_char": 398,
                "end_char": 411,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 433,
                "end_char": 440,
                "label": "NORP",
