[
    {
        "title": "A atualidade de Caspar David Friedrich",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.46",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/opiniao/2024-05-09-a-atualidade-de-caspar-david-friedrich-0ba17a37",
        "subtitle": "Em Portugal, perguntamos pouco, mal e, normalmente, fora de tempo",
        "content": "pintura pode ajudar-nos a pensar sobre a política internacional. Gosto de pensar que o homem no quadro “Caminhante sobre Um Manto de Nevoeiro” (c. 1818), de Caspar David Friedrich, contempla a paisagem do futuro com uma curiosidade determinada. A sua dificuldade é compreender as fronteiras do vale que se estende à sua frente debaixo do nevoeiro, o caminho até às montanhas e rochas e o que eventualmente estará para lá delas. Que caminho seguir?",
        "ranked": 1,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346166.7847166,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:46",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.46",
        "en_title": "The Currentity of Caspar David Friedrich",
        "en_content": "painting can help us think about international politics. I like to think that the man in the painting “Travel on a Fog Mantle” (c. 1818), by Caspar David Friedrich, contemplates the landscape of the future with a determined curiosity. Its difficulty is to understand the borders of the valley that extends ahead of you under the fog, the way to the mountains and rocks and what will eventually be beyond them. What way to go?",
        "en_subtitle": "In Portugal, we ask little, bad and normally out of time",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Caspar David Friedrich",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Portugal",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 11,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "1818",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 135,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Caspar David Friedrich",
                "start_char": 141,
                "end_char": 163,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Portugal atrasou-se e arrisca incumprir novas regras de controlo de fronteiras da UE",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.46",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/economia/2024-05-09-portugal-atrasou-se-e-arrisca-incumprir-novas-regras-de-controlo-de-fronteiras-da-ue-6ef73477",
        "subtitle": "Governo de Costa atrasou-se na compra do novo equipamento biométrico para controlo das fronteiras Schengen, e a 22 de fevereiro o Conselho de Ministro autorizou o recurso ao ajust direto e a libertação de €25 milhões para a sua aquisição, alegando “urgência imperiosa”. Sistema devia ser validado em julho para ficar ativo em outubro, mas em abril o equipamento ainda não tinha sido encomendado",
        "content": "oam os alarmes. Vai haver novas regras para a entrada de pessoas fora do Espaço Schengen na União Europeia (UE), o que implicará mudanças no controlo de fronteiras e obrigará à aquisição de novo equipamento para leitura de dados biométricos. Portugal está atrasado no processo e arrisca não estar preparado para começar a testar o equipamento no outono deste ano, nomeadamente nos aeroportos onde será um instrumento essencial na aplicação das novas regras de entrada no Espaço Schengen.",
        "ranked": 2,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346166.8207788,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:46",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.46",
        "en_title": "Portugal has been delayed and risks to set up new EU border control rules",
        "en_content": "oam alarms. There will be new rules for the entry of people outside the Schengen area into the European Union (EU), which will involve changes in border control and will require the acquisition of new equipment for reading biometric data. Portugal is late in the process and risks not being prepared to start testing the equipment in the fall of this year, particularly at airports where it will be an essential instrument in applying the new rules of entry into the Schengen area.",
        "en_subtitle": "Costa's government was delayed in the purchase of the new biometric equipment for the control of the Schengen borders, and on 22 February the Council of Ministers authorized the use of direct adjustment and the release of €25 million for its acquisition, claiming \"imperrious resurgence\". System should be validated in July to stay active in October, but in April the equipment had not yet been ordered",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Portugal",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Costa",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Schengen",
                "start_char": 101,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "22 February",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 137,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Council of Ministers",
                "start_char": 138,
                "end_char": 162,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "€25 million",
                "start_char": 222,
                "end_char": 233,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "July",
                "start_char": 319,
                "end_char": 323,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "October",
                "start_char": 342,
                "end_char": 349,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "April",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 363,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Schengen",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 80,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Union",
                "start_char": 91,
                "end_char": 109,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 111,
                "end_char": 113,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Portugal",
                "start_char": 239,
                "end_char": 247,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the fall of this year",
                "start_char": 334,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Schengen",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 475,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Iolanda: “A ambição é ganhar a Eurovisão. Para mim, faz sentido lutar pelo troféu”",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/blitz/2024-05-09-iolanda-a-ambicao-e-ganhar-a-eurovisao.-para-mim-faz-sentido-lutar-pelo-trofeu-f3691ba2",
        "subtitle": "A partir de Malmö, na Suécia, Iolanda revela no podcast Posto Emissor que o sonho ‘eurovisivo’ não se esgota na chegada à final de sábado. “Estamos a fazer isto há muitos meses, portanto para mim faz sentido lutar até ao fim”",
        "content": "Iolanda é a convidada desta semana do Posto Emissor. A partir de Malmö, a representante de Portugal no festival da Eurovisão falou à BLITZ sobre a experiência eurovisiva que está a viver na Suécia.  Após ter garantido o apuramento para a grande final, que se realiza este sábado, 11 de maio, Iolanda não esconde que o feito já constituiu “uma vitória”, mas ambiciona voos mais altos. “A ambição passa, sempre, por conquistar o troféu”, disse. “Nós estamos a fazer isto há muitos meses”, sublinha, lembrando a preparação para o Festival da Canção, que venceu em março. “Para mim, faz sempre sentido lutar até ao fim pelo troféu”, acrescenta, assumindo-se feliz por perceber que o público estrangeiro entende a mensagem de ‘Grito’, a canção que defende: “Perceberam que nós estamos aqui a fazer isto pela arte”. Ouça a resposta completa, a partir dos 28 minutos e 39 segundos:",
        "ranked": 3,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346167.0441692,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "en_title": "Iolanda: “The ambition is to win the Eurovision. For me, it makes sense to fight for the trophy”",
        "en_content": "Iolanda is the guest of this week at the Emissor Post. From Malmö, Portugal's representative at the Eurovision festival spoke to BLITZ about the eurovisive experience that is living in Sweden. After having secured the clearance for the grand final, which takes place this Saturday, May 11, Iolanda does not hide that the feat has already constituted “a victory”, but ambitions higher flights. “The ambition always goes by conquering the trophy,” he said. “We’ve been doing this for many months,” stresses, recalling the preparation for the Song Festival, which won in March. “For me, it always makes sense to fight to the end for the trophy”, he adds, assuming happy to realize that the foreign audience understands the message of ‘Grito’, the song that defends: “They realized that we are here doing this for art.” Listen to the full answer from 28 minutes and 39 seconds:",
        "en_subtitle": "From Malmö, Sweden, Iolanda reveals in the podcast Post Emissor that the ‘European’ dream is not exhausted on arrival at the end of Saturday. “We have been doing this for many months, so for me it makes sense to fight to the end”",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iolanda",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eurovision",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 47,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Malmö",
                "start_char": 5,
                "end_char": 10,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sweden",
                "start_char": 12,
                "end_char": 18,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iolanda",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Post Emissor",
                "start_char": 51,
                "end_char": 63,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 74,
                "end_char": 82,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the end of Saturday",
                "start_char": 121,
                "end_char": 140,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Iolanda",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "this week",
                "start_char": 24,
                "end_char": 33,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Emissor Post",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 53,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Malmö",
                "start_char": 60,
                "end_char": 65,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Portugal",
                "start_char": 67,
                "end_char": 75,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eurovision",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "BLITZ",
                "start_char": 129,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sweden",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this Saturday",
                "start_char": 267,
                "end_char": 280,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "May 11",
                "start_char": 282,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Iolanda",
                "start_char": 290,
                "end_char": 297,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Song Festival",
                "start_char": 536,
                "end_char": 553,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "March",
                "start_char": 568,
                "end_char": 573,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Grito’",
                "start_char": 732,
                "end_char": 738,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "28 minutes and 39 seconds",
                "start_char": 847,
                "end_char": 872,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Quase Famosos: Sérgio Onze, o jovem fadista do Seixal que encontrou a sua identidade num álbum chamado “Nós”",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/blitz/2024-05-09-quase-famosos-sergio-onze-o-jovem-fadista-do-seixal-que-encontrou-a-sua-identidade-num-album-chamado-nos-03db2a40",
        "subtitle": "Subiu pela primeira vez a um palco aos 5 anos, venceu a Grande Noite do Fado com apenas 9, passou pelas mais conceituadas casas de fado de Lisboa e acaba de se estrear com “Nós”, álbum coproduzido por Agir e Ricardo Ribeiro que inclui contribuições de Conan Osiris, Joana Espadinha ou Teresinha Landeiro. Sérgio Onze é o destaque desta semana da rubrica da BLITZ dedicada a talentos emergentes",
        "content": "Quase Famosos, rubrica da BLITZ dedicada a artistas emergentes, procura tirar o pulso à nova música portuguesa. Todas as semanas, o foco incide sobre um novo nome. O convidado da oitava edição é Sérgio Onze, fadista do Seixal que subiu pela primeira vez ao palco com apenas 5 anos e acabou de se estrear nos álbuns com “Nós”, produzido por Agir e Ricardo Ribeiro.",
        "ranked": 4,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346167.062319,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "en_title": "Almost Famous: Sérgio Onze, the young fado singer of Seixal who found his identity on an album called “We”",
        "en_content": "Almost Famous, BLITZ's line dedicated to emerging artists, seeks to take the pulse to the new Portuguese music. Every week, the focus focuses on a new name. The guest of the eighth edition is Sérgio Onze, the fado singer of Seixal who first climbed the stage with only 5 years and just debuted on the albums with “We”, produced by Agir and Ricardo Ribeiro.",
        "en_subtitle": "He first went on a stage at the age of 5, won the Fado Grand Night with only 9, passed the most renowned Lisbon fado houses and just debuted with “We”, album co-produced by Agir and Ricardo Ribeiro that includes contributions from Conan Osiris, Joana Espadinha or Teresinha Landeiro. Sérgio Onze is the highlight of this week's BLITZ line dedicated to emerging talent",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Sérgio Onze",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Seixal",
                "start_char": 53,
                "end_char": 59,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 8,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the age of 5",
                "start_char": 28,
                "end_char": 40,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Fado Grand Night",
                "start_char": 46,
                "end_char": 66,
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "info": "Titles of books, songs, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "only 9",
                "start_char": 72,
                "end_char": 78,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lisbon",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Agir",
                "start_char": 173,
                "end_char": 177,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ricardo Ribeiro",
                "start_char": 182,
                "end_char": 197,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Conan Osiris",
                "start_char": 231,
                "end_char": 243,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Joana Espadinha",
                "start_char": 245,
                "end_char": 260,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Teresinha Landeiro",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 282,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Sérgio Onze",
                "start_char": 284,
                "end_char": 295,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "week",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 325,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "BLITZ",
                "start_char": 328,
                "end_char": 333,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "BLITZ",
                "start_char": 15,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Portuguese",
                "start_char": 94,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Every week",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 122,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "eighth",
                "start_char": 174,
                "end_char": 180,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Sérgio Onze",
                "start_char": 192,
                "end_char": 203,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Seixal",
                "start_char": 224,
                "end_char": 230,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 235,
                "end_char": 240,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "only 5 years",
                "start_char": 264,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Agir",
                "start_char": 331,
                "end_char": 335,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ricardo Ribeiro",
                "start_char": 340,
                "end_char": 355,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "O verdadeiro Pedro Mafama que se levante: vem aí a maior noite da vida dele",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/blitz/2024-05-09-o-verdadeiro-pedro-mafama-que-se-levante-vem-ai-a-maior-noite-da-vida-dele-3867681d",
        "subtitle": "Cresceu na Lisboa bairrista, estudou artes plásticas e estreou-se nos álbuns com referências a Giacometti. Empurrado pelo sucesso de ‘Preço Certo’, Pedro Mafama sobe agora ao maior palco da sua vida: Sagres Campo Pequeno, Lisboa, sexta-feira",
        "content": "esde que o seu nome começou a andar de boca em boca, nunca foi uma figura consensual. Também não o será hoje. Pedro Simões, que o país conheceu como Pedro Mafama, assume que abraçou desde sempre as suas contradições e que, imerso no processo de autodescoberta, percebeu que queria agitar consciências e conceitos predefinidos do que é ser-se português (e não só). Cresceu em Lisboa, no bairro da Graça, é filho de artistas, estudou Belas-Artes, estagiou na Enchufada (editora de Branko e Buraka Som Sistema) e demorou algum tempo a atirar-se de cabeça a uma paixão que lhe vinha de criança. Na música, começou por dar os primeiros passos no hip-hop, enquanto Pedro Simmons, há uma década, partilhando temas que promete revisitar no concerto em modo “bailecore” que leva ao palco do Campo Pequeno, em Lisboa, esta sexta. Depois desses primeiros passos, encontrou no  , ferramenta de manipulação vocal, um bom instrumento para o ajudar a descobrir e criar melodias.",
        "ranked": 5,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346167.1284628,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "en_title": "The real Peter Mafama who stands up: the greatest night of his life is coming",
        "en_content": "Since his name began to walk in mouth, he was never a consensual figure. It won't be today either. Pedro Simões, who the country has known as Pedro Mafama, assumes that it has always embraced its contradictions and that, immersed in the process of self-discovery, realized that it wanted to stir predefined consciousness and concepts of what it is to be Portuguese (and not only). He grew up in Lisbon, in the neighborhood of Graça, he is the son of artists, studied Belas-Artes, aged in the Enchufada (editor of Branko and Buraka Som Sistema) and took some time to throw himself in the head of a passion that came to him as a child. In the song, he began by taking the first steps in hip-hop, while Pedro Simmons, a decade ago, sharing themes that promises to revisit in the concert in “bailecore” mode that leads to the Little Field stage in Lisbon this Friday. After these first steps, he found in the vocal manipulation tool, a good instrument to help him discover and create melodies.",
        "en_subtitle": "He grew up in Lisbon, studied plastic arts and debuted on the albums with references to Giacometti. Pushed by the success of ‘Right Price’, Pedro Mafama now rises to the biggest stage of his life: Sagres Campo Small, Lisbon, Friday",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Peter Mafama",
                "start_char": 9,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the greatest night",
                "start_char": 37,
                "end_char": 55,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Lisbon",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 20,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Giacometti",
                "start_char": 88,
                "end_char": 98,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Mafama",
                "start_char": 140,
                "end_char": 152,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lisbon",
                "start_char": 217,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Friday",
                "start_char": 225,
                "end_char": 231,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 85,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Simões",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Mafama",
                "start_char": 142,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Portuguese",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 364,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lisbon",
                "start_char": 395,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Graça",
                "start_char": 426,
                "end_char": 431,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belas-Artes",
                "start_char": 467,
                "end_char": 478,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Enchufada",
                "start_char": 492,
                "end_char": 501,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Branko",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 519,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Buraka Som Sistema",
                "start_char": 524,
                "end_char": 542,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 670,
                "end_char": 675,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Pedro Simmons",
                "start_char": 700,
                "end_char": 713,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "a decade ago",
                "start_char": 715,
                "end_char": 727,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lisbon",
                "start_char": 844,
                "end_char": 850,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this Friday",
                "start_char": 851,
                "end_char": 862,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "first",
                "start_char": 876,
                "end_char": 881,
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "info": "\"first\", \"second\", etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kendrick Lamar vs. Drake: a história do maior ‘beef’ do hip-hop desde Tupac Shakur e Notorious B.I.G., assassinados nos anos 90",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/blitz/2024-05-08-kendrick-lamar-vs.-drake-a-historia-do-maior-beef-do-hip-hop-desde-tupac-shakur-e-notorious-b.i.g.-assassinados-nos-anos-90-63697df0",
        "subtitle": "Kendrick Lamar e Drake, dois dos maiores nomes da cena rap atual, decidiram lançar-se à jugular um do outro, enchendo o ‘streaming’ de música, as redes sociais de teorias e os jornais de manchetes. O ‘beef’ já resultou em acusações gravíssimas – violência doméstica, pedofilia, abuso de poder – e fica desde já marcado pelo incidente que envolveu um guarda-costas de Drake, baleado à porta da mansão do músico canadiano. E impossível não recordar a ‘guerra’ entre Tupac Shakur e The Notorious B.I.G., na década de 90, da qual nenhum saiu vencedor: ambos morreram",
        "content": "Há muito que o hip-hop não tinha dias assim. Foram milhões e milhões de  , milhões e milhões de “gostos” e “não gostos” no YouTube, horas perdidas no Genius (repositório de letras e análise de letras de canções) a transcrever e a apontar o que fosse preciso, até mesmo noites sem dormir. A disputa entre Kendrick Lamar e Drake, dois dos nomes mais sonantes da cena hip-hop atual - se não os dois nomes mais sonantes, pelo menos a nível mediático - fez parar as máquinas, gerou manchetes e parangonas, deixou os fãs em polvorosa e divididos em dois campos. Dez canções, algumas mais aclamadas que outras, versos de ataque e defesa, revelações e acusações bombásticas e, entre quase todos, o sentimento de que o   está bem vivo.",
        "ranked": 6,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346167.1664863,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "en_title": "Kendrick Lamar vs. Drake: the history of the greatest ‘beef’ of hip-hop since Tupac Shakur and Notorious B.I.G., murdered in the 1990s",
        "en_content": "Long ago, hip-hop had no days like this. It was millions and millions, millions and millions of “likes” and “not like” on YouTube, hours lost in Genius (repository of lyrics and analysis of song lyrics) to transcribe and point out what was needed, even nights without sleep. The dispute between Kendrick Lamar and Drake, two of the drowsiest names of the current hip-hop scene - if not the two most drowsy names, at least at the media level - stopped the machines, generated headlines and parangonas, left the fans in octopus and divided into two fields. Ten songs, some more acclaimed than others, verses of attack and defense, revelations and bombing accusations and, among almost all, the feeling that he is well alive.",
        "en_subtitle": "Kendrick Lamar and Drake, two of the biggest names in the current rap scene, decided to pitch each other, filling the ‘streaming’ of music, the social networks of theories and headline newspapers. The ‘beef’ has already resulted in serious accusations – domestic violence, pedophilia, abuse of power – and is already marked by the incident involving a Drake bodyguard, shot at the door of the Canadian musician's mansion. It is impossible not to recall the ‘war’ between Tupac Shakur and The Notorious B.I.G., in the 1990s, of which none came out winner: both died",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kendrick Lamar",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Drake",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tupac Shakur",
                "start_char": 78,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Notorious B.I.G.",
                "start_char": 95,
                "end_char": 111,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 1990s",
                "start_char": 125,
                "end_char": 134,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Kendrick Lamar",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Drake",
                "start_char": 19,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 26,
                "end_char": 29,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Drake",
                "start_char": 352,
                "end_char": 357,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canadian",
                "start_char": 393,
                "end_char": 401,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the ‘war’",
                "start_char": 453,
                "end_char": 462,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Tupac Shakur",
                "start_char": 471,
                "end_char": 483,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "The Notorious B.I.G.",
                "start_char": 488,
                "end_char": 508,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the 1990s",
                "start_char": 513,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "millions and millions, millions and millions",
                "start_char": 48,
                "end_char": 92,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "info": "Monetary values, including unit"
            },
            {
                "word": "YouTube",
                "start_char": 122,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "info": "Objects, vehicles, foods, etc. (not services)"
            },
            {
                "word": "hours",
                "start_char": 131,
                "end_char": 136,
                "label": "TIME",
                "info": "Times smaller than a day"
            },
            {
                "word": "Genius",
                "start_char": 145,
                "end_char": 151,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kendrick Lamar",
                "start_char": 295,
                "end_char": 309,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Drake",
                "start_char": 314,
                "end_char": 319,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 321,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 390,
                "end_char": 393,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 543,
                "end_char": 546,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ten",
                "start_char": 555,
                "end_char": 558,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "No Dia da Vitória, Putin voltou a jogar o trunfo nuclear e a Ucrânia ficou mais perto de entrar na UE (o 806.º dia de guerra)",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/internacional/guerra-na-ucrania/2024-05-09-no-dia-da-vitoria-putin-voltou-a-jogar-o-trunfo-nuclear-e-a-ucrania-ficou-mais-perto-de-entrar-na-ue--o-806.-dia-de-guerra--4ad65b99",
        "subtitle": "Naquela que é uma das datas mais importantes do calendário russo, que assinala a capitulação da Alemanha nazi perante a União Soviética, Vladimir Putin frisou que as forças nucleares russas estão “sempre” prontas para o combate. Paralelamente, a presidente do Parlamento Europeu anunciou que as negociações para a adesão da Ucrânia à UE deverão arrancar em junho",
        "content": "⇒ A Ucrânia atingiu esta quinta-feira com um 'drone' uma refinaria russa na república de Bashkortostan, a uma distância de quase 1.200 quilómetros da sua fronteira. Incidente não causou vítimas ⇒ O Presidente da Ucrânia, Volodymyr Zelensky, demitiu o chefe do Departamento de Proteção do Estado (UDO), a que pertenciam até há dois dias dois coronéis detidos por alegado envolvimento numa conspiração russa para assassiná-lo. A destituição de Serhi Rudi decorreu no âmbito de um processo de remodelação das altas patentes das Forças Armadas. Hoje foi também nomeado o novo comandante das Forças de Operações Especiais, Oleksander Trepak. ⇒ A situação na frente de guerra está a deteriorar-se para a Ucrânia devido à pressão da Rússia, que continua a ganhar terreno perto da cidade de Avdivka, tomada pelas forças russas em fevereiro após meses de cerco. A conclusão consta em uma das últimas 'newsletters' do canal ucraniano Telegram DeepState, considerado um dos mais influentes e informados grupos de monitorização e análise de conflitos.",
        "ranked": 7,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346167.7239678,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "en_title": "On Victory Day, Putin returned to play the nuclear trump and Ukraine became closer to entering the EU (the 806th day of war)",
        "en_content": "⇒ Ukraine hit this Thursday with a 'drone' a Russian refinery in the Republic of Bashkortostan, a distance of nearly 1,200 kilometres from its border. Incident did not cause victims ⇒ The President of Ukraine, Volodymyr Zelensky, dismissed the head of the State Protection Department (UDO), which belonged until two days ago two colonels detained for alleged involvement in a Russian conspiracy to assassinate him. The destitution of Serhi Rudi took place in a process of reshaping the high ranks of the Armed Forces. Today he was also named the new commander of the Special Operations Forces, Oleksander Trepak. ⇒ The situation in front of war is deteriorating to Ukraine due to the pressure of Russia, which continues to gain ground near the city of Avdivka, taken by the Russian forces in February after months of siege. The conclusion is found in one of the latest 'newsletters' of the Ukrainian channel Telegram DeepState, considered one of the most influential and informed groups of conflict monitoring and analysis.",
        "en_subtitle": "In what is one of the most important dates of the Russian calendar, which marks the capitulation of Nazi Germany to the Soviet Union, Vladimir Putin stressed that Russian nuclear forces are “always” ready for combat. At the same time, the President of the European Parliament announced that negotiations for Ukraine's accession to the EU should start in June",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Victory Day",
                "start_char": 3,
                "end_char": 14,
                "label": "EVENT",
                "info": "Named hurricanes, battles, wars, sports events, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 21,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 61,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 101,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "806th",
                "start_char": 107,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 50,
                "end_char": 57,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nazi Germany",
                "start_char": 100,
                "end_char": 112,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Soviet Union",
                "start_char": 116,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 148,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 163,
                "end_char": 170,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Parliament",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 275,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 308,
                "end_char": 315,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "start_char": 335,
                "end_char": 337,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "June",
                "start_char": 354,
                "end_char": 358,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 2,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "this Thursday",
                "start_char": 14,
                "end_char": 27,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 45,
                "end_char": 52,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Republic of Bashkortostan",
                "start_char": 65,
                "end_char": 94,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "nearly 1,200 kilometres",
                "start_char": 110,
                "end_char": 133,
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "info": "Measurements, as of weight or distance"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 201,
                "end_char": 208,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
                "start_char": 210,
                "end_char": 228,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the State Protection Department",
                "start_char": 252,
                "end_char": 283,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "UDO",
                "start_char": 285,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "two days ago",
                "start_char": 312,
                "end_char": 324,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 325,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 376,
                "end_char": 383,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Serhi Rudi",
                "start_char": 434,
                "end_char": 444,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Armed Forces",
                "start_char": 500,
                "end_char": 516,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Today",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 523,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Special Operations Forces",
                "start_char": 563,
                "end_char": 592,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Oleksander Trepak",
                "start_char": 594,
                "end_char": 611,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 665,
                "end_char": 672,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 696,
                "end_char": 702,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Avdivka",
                "start_char": 752,
                "end_char": 759,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 774,
                "end_char": 781,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "February",
                "start_char": 792,
                "end_char": 800,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "months",
                "start_char": 807,
                "end_char": 813,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukrainian",
                "start_char": 890,
                "end_char": 899,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Telegram DeepState",
                "start_char": 908,
                "end_char": 926,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Trump prometeu levantar restrições a petrolíferas em troca de 1000 milhões para a sua campanha",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/internacional/eua/2024-05-09-trump-prometeu-levantar-restricoes-a-petroliferas-em-troca-de-1000-milhoes-para-a-sua-campanha-2b9db16d",
        "subtitle": "Os ambientalistas criticaram o antigo presidente pela franqueza gritante com que propôs o acordo, expondo a proximidade entre a sua política e a indústria petrolífera",
        "content": "",
        "ranked": 8,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346167.9675326,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:47",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.47",
        "en_title": "Trump promised to raise oil restrictions in exchange for 1000 million for his campaign",
        "en_content": "",
        "en_subtitle": "The environmentalists criticized the former president for the blatant frankness he proposed the agreement, exposing the proximity between his policy and the oil industry",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Trump",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "1000 million",
                "start_char": 57,
                "end_char": 69,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "As europeias na Lituânia: eleições irracionais e invisíveis",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.48",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/politica/eleicoes/europeias-2024/2024-05-09-as-europeias-na-lituania-eleicoes-irracionais-e-invisiveis-29f6d895",
        "subtitle": null,
        "content": "As eleições para o Parlamento Europeu (PE) realizar-se-ão a 9 de junho deste ano. A Lituânia elegerá onze deputados europeus. Entre os candidatos em funções, apenas se sabe com certeza que Aušra Seibutytė (antes Maldeikienė), eleita pela plataforma O comboio de Aušra Maldeikienė, e que mais tarde se juntou à conservadora União da Pátria, vai abandonar a vida política. Alguns candidatos, como Aurelijus Veryga (Agricultores e Verdes) e   (Partido da Liberdade, liberal), estão a concorrer tanto à presidência da República como ao Parlamento Europeu. Diversos candidatos ao PE são deputados proeminentes no Seimas [Parlamento] da Lituânia. Entre eles, contam-se Eugenijus Gentvilas, que irá liderar a lista do Movimento dos Liberais (conservador-liberal); Radvilė Morkūnaitė-Mikulėnienė, atual membro sénior da União da Pátria; e Paulius Saudargas, vice-presidente do Parlamento.",
        "ranked": 9,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346168.1062794,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:48",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.48",
        "en_title": "Europeans in Lithuania: irrational and invisible elections",
        "en_content": "The elections for the European Parliament (EP) will be held on 9 June this year. Lithuania will elect eleven European Members. Among the candidates in roles, it is only sure that Aušra Seibutytė (before Maldeikienė), elected by the platform The train of Aušra Maldeikienė, who later joined the conservative Union of the Homeland, will abandon political life. Some candidates, such as Aurelijus Veryga (Agricultores e Verdes) and (Partido da Liberdade, liberal), are running for both the presidency of the Republic and the European Parliament. A number of EP candidates are prominent MEPs in the Lithuanian Seimas. They include Eugenijus Gentvilas, who will lead the list of the Liberal Movement (conservative-liberal); Radvilė Morkūnaitė-Mikulėnienė, the current senior member of the Union of the Homeland; and Paulius Saudargas, Vice President of Parliament.",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Europeans",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuania",
                "start_char": 13,
                "end_char": 22,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "the European Parliament",
                "start_char": 18,
                "end_char": 41,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "9 June this year",
                "start_char": 63,
                "end_char": 79,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuania",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 90,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "eleven",
                "start_char": 102,
                "end_char": 108,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "start_char": 109,
                "end_char": 117,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Aušra Seibutytė",
                "start_char": 179,
                "end_char": 194,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maldeikienė",
                "start_char": 203,
                "end_char": 214,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aušra Maldeikienė",
                "start_char": 254,
                "end_char": 271,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Union of the Homeland",
                "start_char": 307,
                "end_char": 328,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Aurelijus Veryga",
                "start_char": 384,
                "end_char": 400,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Agricultores e Verdes",
                "start_char": 402,
                "end_char": 423,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Partido da Liberdade",
                "start_char": 430,
                "end_char": 450,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "the European Parliament",
                "start_char": 518,
                "end_char": 541,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Lithuanian",
                "start_char": 595,
                "end_char": 605,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Eugenijus Gentvilas",
                "start_char": 627,
                "end_char": 646,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Liberal Movement",
                "start_char": 674,
                "end_char": 694,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Radvilė Morkūnaitė-Mikulėnienė",
                "start_char": 719,
                "end_char": 749,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Union of the Homeland",
                "start_char": 780,
                "end_char": 805,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Paulius Saudargas",
                "start_char": 811,
                "end_char": 828,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Parliament",
                "start_char": 848,
                "end_char": 858,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Putin quer abrir o diálogo com o Ocidente? E o que quer Xi Jinping da Europa? E em que ponto ficam as relações entre Moscovo e Pequim?",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.48",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/internacional/guerra-na-ucrania/2024-05-09-putin-quer-abrir-o-dialogo-com-o-ocidente--e-o-que-quer-xi-jinping-da-europa--e-em-que-ponto-ficam-as-relacoes-entre-moscovo-e-pequim--5a49b721",
        "subtitle": "Putin tem uma estratégia de propaganda contra o Ocidente: criar uma barreira entre o Oeste e o Sul Global e afirmar que Moscovo é a verdadeira aliada de todas as capitais que lutam contra a hegemonia norte-americana. Mas, então, para quê vincar a sua disponibilidade para o diálogo? Pequim tem mantido uma postura semelhante, ora com aproximações, ora com hostilidades. No entanto, entre Moscovo e Pequim há grandes - e cada vez maiores - diferenças no balanço custo-benefício das tensões com o Ocidente",
        "content": "Churchill descreveu a Rússia como “um enigma, envolto num mistério, dentro de um enigma”. O mesmo pode ser dito de Putin. Dois anos após o início da guerra, o Presidente russo continua a oscilar entre a ameaça beligerante e a (menos frequente) defesa do diálogo com o Ocidente. Há dois dias, a Rússia ameaçou atacar instalações militares britânicas e ordenou que os seus militares realizassem exercícios de treino para manuseio de armas nucleares no campo de batalha. O Kremlin alegou, nessa altura, que se tratava de uma resposta aos comentários do Presidente francês, Emmanuel Macron, sobre as tropas ocidentais poderem lutar na Ucrânia, e do secretário dos Negócios Estrangeiros britânico, David Cameron, sobre o uso de armas fornecidas pelos britânicos contra o território russo. Um dia depois, quando tomou posse para um novo mandato de seis anos, Vladimir Putin disse que cabe ao Ocidente escolher entre a confrontação e a cooperação. O Presidente russo já deixou claro várias vezes que acredita que os países ocidentais usam a Ucrânia como um meio para um só fim: derrotar e desmembrar a Rússia. Mas, na cerimónia da tomada de posse, e depois de prestar juramento, Putin vincou perante a elite política da Rússia que não rejeitava o diálogo com o Ocidente, inclusive sobre armas nucleares. “A escolha é deles: pretendem continuar a tentar conter o desenvolvimento da Rússia, continuar a política de agressão, de pressão incessante sobre o nosso país durante anos, ou procurar um caminho para a cooperação e a paz?”, atirou. Mas porquê falar de diálogo quando as tensões entre Moscovo e as capitais ocidentais parecem não ter fim à vista?",
        "ranked": 10,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346168.120406,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:48",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.48",
        "en_title": "Putin wants to open dialogue with the West? And what does Xi Jinping want from Europe? And where are the relations between Moscow and Beijing?",
        "en_content": "Churchill described Russia as “a riddle, wrapped in a mystery, within a riddle.” The same can be said of Putin. Two years after the war began, the Russian President continues to oscillate between the belligerent threat and the (less frequent) defense of dialogue with the West. Two days ago, Russia threatened to attack British military facilities and ordered its military to carry out training exercises for nuclear weapons handling on the battlefield. The Kremlin claimed, at that time, that it was a response to the comments of the French President, Emmanuel Macron, about Western troops being able to fight in Ukraine, and the British Foreign Secretary, David Cameron, on the use of weapons provided by the British against the Russian territory. One day later, when he took office for a new six-year term, Vladimir Putin said it is up to the West to choose between confrontation and cooperation. The Russian President has made it clear several times that he believes Western countries use Ukraine as a means for a single end: defeat and dismember Russia. But at the inauguration ceremony, and after taking oath, Putin avenged the political elite of Russia that did not reject dialogue with the West, including nuclear weapons. “The choice is theirs: do they intend to continue to try to contain the development of Russia, to continue the policy of aggression, of unceasing pressure on our country for years, or to seek a path to cooperation and peace?”, he shot. But why talk about dialogue when the tensions between Moscow and the Western capitals seem to have no end to sight?",
        "en_subtitle": "Putin has a propaganda strategy against the West: creating a barrier between the West and the Global South and affirming that Moscow is the true ally of all capitals that fight US hegemony. But then, why avenge your willingness to dialogue? Beijing has maintained a similar posture, now with approaches, praying with hostilities. However, between Moscow and Beijing there are large - and increasing - differences in the cost-benefit balance of tensions with the West",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 38,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Xi Jinping",
                "start_char": 58,
                "end_char": 68,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "start_char": 79,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 123,
                "end_char": 129,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 134,
                "end_char": 141,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 81,
                "end_char": 85,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Global South",
                "start_char": 90,
                "end_char": 106,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 126,
                "end_char": 132,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "start_char": 177,
                "end_char": 179,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 241,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 347,
                "end_char": 353,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Beijing",
                "start_char": 358,
                "end_char": 365,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Churchill",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 9,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 20,
                "end_char": 26,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 105,
                "end_char": 110,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Two years",
                "start_char": 112,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 147,
                "end_char": 154,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 272,
                "end_char": 276,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Two days ago",
                "start_char": 278,
                "end_char": 290,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 292,
                "end_char": 298,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 320,
                "end_char": 327,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kremlin",
                "start_char": 458,
                "end_char": 465,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "French",
                "start_char": 535,
                "end_char": 541,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Emmanuel Macron",
                "start_char": 553,
                "end_char": 568,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western",
                "start_char": 576,
                "end_char": 583,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 614,
                "end_char": 621,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 631,
                "end_char": 638,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "David Cameron",
                "start_char": 658,
                "end_char": 671,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "British",
                "start_char": 711,
                "end_char": 718,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 731,
                "end_char": 738,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "One day later",
                "start_char": 750,
                "end_char": 763,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "six-year",
                "start_char": 795,
                "end_char": 803,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vladimir Putin",
                "start_char": 810,
                "end_char": 824,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 846,
                "end_char": 850,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russian",
                "start_char": 904,
                "end_char": 911,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ukraine",
                "start_char": 993,
                "end_char": 1000,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1051,
                "end_char": 1057,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Putin",
                "start_char": 1116,
                "end_char": 1121,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1153,
                "end_char": 1159,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "West",
                "start_char": 1198,
                "end_char": 1202,
                "label": "LOC",
                "info": "Non-GPE locations, mountain ranges, bodies of water"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "start_char": 1318,
                "end_char": 1324,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "years",
                "start_char": 1405,
                "end_char": 1410,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Moscow",
                "start_char": 1521,
                "end_char": 1527,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Western",
                "start_char": 1536,
                "end_char": 1543,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hamas diz que “bola está do lado” de Israel para trégua em Gaza",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.48",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/internacional/medio-oriente/guerra-israel-hamas/2024-05-10-hamas-diz-que-bola-esta-do-lado-de-israel-para-tregua-em-gaza-934c2cc9",
        "subtitle": "Hamas afirma que tinha concordado com a proposta apresentada pelos mediadores e que a decisão de tréguas cabe a Israel que rejeitou o acordo. A proposta previa uma trégua em três fases, que incluía a retirada israelita de Gaza e uma troca de reféns. O objetivo seria alcançar um cessar-fogo permanente, o que fez recuar Israel",
        "content": "O movimento islamita palestiniano Hamas declarou hoje, depois da partida da delegação do Egito, onde decorrem negociações, que \"a bola está inteiramente do lado de Israel\", com vista a um acordo de tréguas na Faixa de Gaza. \"A delegação negociadora deixou o Cairo em direção a Doha. A ocupação rejeitou a proposta apresentada pelos mediadores, que nós tínhamos aceite. Por conseguinte, a bola está agora inteiramente no campo da ocupação\", nome dado a Israel pelo movimento islamita, indicou o Hamas, numa carta enviada às outras fações palestinianas. Os representantes dos dois campos deixaram o Cairo \"depois de dois dias de negociações\" para uma trégua na guerra que dura há sete meses no enclave palestiniano, informou na quinta-feira o meio de comunicação Al-Qahera News, próximo dos serviços secretos egípcios. Os esforços do Egito e dos outros países mediadores, neste caso o Qatar e os Estados Unidos, \"prosseguem para aproximar os pontos de vista das duas partes\", acrescentou o Al-Qahera News, citando uma fonte egípcia. Na segunda-feira, o Hamas deu \"luz verde\" a uma proposta apresentada pelos mediadores que, de acordo com o movimento, prevê uma trégua em três fases, cada uma com a duração de 42 dias, incluindo uma retirada israelita do território, bem como uma troca de reféns detidos em Gaza e de palestinianos detidos por Israel, com o objetivo de um \"cessar-fogo permanente\". Israel respondeu que esta proposta estava \"longe das suas exigências\" e reiterou a oposição a um cessar-fogo definitivo, enquanto o Hamas, que está no poder em Gaza desde 2007 e é considerado uma organização terrorista, não for derrotado. O primeiro-ministro israelita, Benjamin Netanyahu, indicou ter dado instruções à delegação no Cairo para \"continuar a ser firme nas condições necessárias para a libertação [dos reféns e] essenciais\" para a segurança de Israel.",
        "ranked": 11,
        "placed": "Abroad",
        "epoch": 1715346168.166279,
        "language": "PT",
        "source": "ExpressoPt",
        "local_time": "2024-05-10 14:02:48",
        "timezone": "Europe/Lisbon",
        "scraping_time": "2024-05-10T15.02.48",
        "en_title": "Hamas says “ball is on the side” of Israel for truce in Gaza",
        "en_content": "The Palestinian Islamist movement Hamas today declared, after the departure of the delegation from Egypt, where negotiations are taking place, that \"the ball is entirely on the side of Israel\", with a view to an agreement of truce in the Gaza Strip. \"The negotiating delegation left Cairo towards Doha. The occupation rejected the proposal presented by the mediators, which we had accepted. Therefore, the ball is now entirely in the field of occupation\", the name given to Israel by the Islamist movement, indicated Hamas, in a letter sent to the other Palestinian factions. The representatives of the two camps left Cairo \"after two days of negotiations\" for a truce in the war that lasts seven months in the Palestinian enclave, reported on Thursday the media Al-Qahera News, near the Egyptian secret services. Egypt's efforts and other mediating countries, in this case, Qatar and the United States, \"continue to approach the views of the two parties\", added Al-Qahera News, citing an Egyptian source. On Monday, Hamas gave \"green light\" to a proposal presented by the mediators who, according to the movement, foresees a truce in three phases, each lasting 42 days, including an Israeli withdrawal from the territory, as well as an exchange of hostages held in Gaza and Palestinians held by Israel, with the aim of a \"permanent burning\". Israel responded that this proposal was \"out of its demands\" and reiterated opposition to a definitive ceasefire, while Hamas, who has been in power in Gaza since 2007 and is considered a terrorist organization, is not defeated. The Israeli Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, indicated that he had given instructions to the delegation in Cairo to \"continue to be firm in the conditions necessary for the liberation [of the essential hostages and]\" for the security of Israel.",
        "en_subtitle": "Hamas asserts that he had agreed with the proposal submitted by the mediators and that the truce decision is up to Israel who rejected the agreement. The proposal provided for a three-stage truce, which included the Israeli withdrawal from Gaza and an exchange of hostages. The goal would be to achieve a permanent ceasefire, which led to Israel backing",
        "title_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 36,
                "end_char": 42,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 56,
                "end_char": 60,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "subtitle_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 0,
                "end_char": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 115,
                "end_char": 121,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 178,
                "end_char": 183,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 216,
                "end_char": 223,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 240,
                "end_char": 244,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 339,
                "end_char": 345,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ],
        "content_NER": [
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 4,
                "end_char": 15,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamist",
                "start_char": 16,
                "end_char": 24,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 34,
                "end_char": 39,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "today",
                "start_char": 40,
                "end_char": 45,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 99,
                "end_char": 104,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 185,
                "end_char": 191,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the Gaza Strip",
                "start_char": 234,
                "end_char": 248,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cairo",
                "start_char": 283,
                "end_char": 288,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Doha",
                "start_char": 297,
                "end_char": 301,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 474,
                "end_char": 480,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Islamist",
                "start_char": 488,
                "end_char": 496,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 517,
                "end_char": 522,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 554,
                "end_char": 565,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 603,
                "end_char": 606,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cairo",
                "start_char": 618,
                "end_char": 623,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two days",
                "start_char": 631,
                "end_char": 639,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "seven months",
                "start_char": 691,
                "end_char": 703,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinian",
                "start_char": 711,
                "end_char": 722,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Thursday",
                "start_char": 744,
                "end_char": 752,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Qahera News",
                "start_char": 763,
                "end_char": 777,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Egyptian",
                "start_char": 788,
                "end_char": 796,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Egypt",
                "start_char": 814,
                "end_char": 819,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Qatar",
                "start_char": 875,
                "end_char": 880,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "the United States",
                "start_char": 885,
                "end_char": 902,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "two",
                "start_char": 943,
                "end_char": 946,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "Al-Qahera News",
                "start_char": 963,
                "end_char": 977,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Egyptian",
                "start_char": 989,
                "end_char": 997,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Monday",
                "start_char": 1009,
                "end_char": 1015,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1017,
                "end_char": 1022,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "three",
                "start_char": 1135,
                "end_char": 1140,
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "info": "Numerals that do not fall under another type"
            },
            {
                "word": "42 days",
                "start_char": 1162,
                "end_char": 1169,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1184,
                "end_char": 1191,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1266,
                "end_char": 1270,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Palestinians",
                "start_char": 1275,
                "end_char": 1287,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1296,
                "end_char": 1302,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1343,
                "end_char": 1349,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Hamas",
                "start_char": 1463,
                "end_char": 1468,
                "label": "ORG",
                "info": "Companies, agencies, institutions, etc."
            },
            {
                "word": "Gaza",
                "start_char": 1495,
                "end_char": 1499,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "2007",
                "start_char": 1506,
                "end_char": 1510,
                "label": "DATE",
                "info": "Absolute or relative dates or periods"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israeli",
                "start_char": 1576,
                "end_char": 1583,
                "label": "NORP",
                "info": "Nationalities or religious or political groups"
            },
            {
                "word": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
                "start_char": 1600,
                "end_char": 1618,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "info": "People, including fictional"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cairo",
                "start_char": 1682,
                "end_char": 1687,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            },
            {
                "word": "Israel",
                "start_char": 1812,
                "end_char": 1818,
                "label": "GPE",
                "info": "Countries, cities, states"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Netanyahu contra o mundo e a fuga de centenas de milhares de palestinianos de Rafah",
        "date_raw": "2024-05-10T15.02.48",
        "date": "2024-05-10",
        "url": "https://expresso.pt/",
        "news_url": "https://expresso.pt/internacional/medio-oriente/guerra-israel-hamas/2024-05-09-netanyahu-contra-o-mundo-e-a-fuga-de-centenas-de-milhares-de-palestinianos-de-rafah-f0a959d6",
        "subtitle": "O Governo israelita desencadeou uma ofensiva militar com a qual quer varrer o último reduto do Hamas na Faixa de Gaza. Crítica da operação e pressionada por protestos estudantis, a Casa Branca suspendeu a entrega de munições ao aliado",
        "content": "As Forças de Defesa de Israel instaram populações a leste de Rafah a abandonar a área, desde segunda-feira, dia 6. Fizeram-no através de panfletos, SMS, telefonemas e anúncios em órgãos de informação árabes. Horas depois, os tanques israelitas avançaram e tomaram o controlo do lado palestiniano do posto fronteiriço de Rafah, junto ao Egito, a passagem usada pelas organizações humanitárias para fazer entrar ajuda no território. A incursão mereceu a censura dos Estados Unidos, principal aliado do Estado judaico no mundo.",
        "ranked": 12,
